<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Name and Logo for Truist Championship</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/truist_championship_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Name and Logo for Truist Championship" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.pgatour.com/article/news/latest/2024/08/06/how-the-truist-championship-came-to-be-quail-hollow-club-new-tournament-sponsor-charlotte-north-carolina">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_and_logo_for_truist_championship.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_and_logo_for_truist_championship.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for San Francisco International Airport</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/sfo_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for San Francisco International Airport" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.flysfo.com/about/media/brand">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_san_francisco_international_airport.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_san_francisco_international_airport.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: The Powers that V</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/news_visalia_logo_selected.png" alt="The Powers that V" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.yourcentralvalley.com/news/local-news/visalia-announces-new-city-logo-formally/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>It&#8217;s a sad day at Brand New as <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/?s=visalia" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the Visalia logo saga</a> ends without any additional drama or surprising turns of events as the council voted to adopt entry number 59 as suggested by the logo redesign committee <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/v_almost_for_victory.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a few weeks ago</a>. The winning design by local, 69-year-old artist Lori Caccamo, displays “the iconic Fox Theatre towers over a smaller building and farmland in front of the Sierra Nevada and rising sun.” Caccamo received $1,500 and a bouquet of flowers. The original logo will still be used when its details can be displayed at the appropriate size. It was a good run for this story.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/the_powers_that_v.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/the_powers_that_v.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Hold Steel”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/fm_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1835) &#8220;<a href="https://www.fm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FM</a> is one of the world&#8217;s largest commercial property insurers. For nearly two centuries, businesses have trusted us to deliver comprehensive risk assessments, develop robust property insurance plans, and foster engineering-based solutions that help protect them against fire, natural disasters, and more. We provide over one-third of all Fortune 1000 companies with data-backed risk management solutions that allow them to prepare and prosper. Fortune Magazine ranks FM as the United State&#8217;s 534th most prominent company.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://prophet.com/" target="_blank">Prophet</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://newsroom.fmglobal.com/releases/releases-20240717" target="_blank">FM press release</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>Taking cues from engineering and heavy industry, a modern three-dimensional logo spells FM in angular, titanium beams that connote engineering and protection. In shades of stone against a dark, rich, yet calming steel background, the letters are accented by orange. Their faceted structure communicates the strength and premium nature of a diamond.<br /><br />The precise, faceted structure was designed to speak to FM’s innovative, engineering-led approach. The combined forms of the “F” and the “M” was designed to demonstrate the organization’s unity and partnership. This new logo effectively connects F and M. Instead of a step denoting the left side of the M, the top of the F transitions into the M shape – as if the M is embracing the F. Because this creates a precise 2:1 ratio, the logo can be scaled without any adjustments.<br /><br />Prophet worked with Commercial Type to customize their fonts Algebra Display, and Review. The new fonts are  FM Algebra and FM Review. FM’s new colors build off the steel of the logo with primary colors Orange, Steel (navy) and Stone (warmer lighter grays).  The orange is used to give depth and warmth to the steel of the logo and in video, animation and signage it backlights the FM. Prophet updated the entire look and feel of the FM brand with guidelines and systems that create ownable 3D Graphics, Iconography, Illustration, Data Visualization and Layouts - used by FM in its marketing, client communications, sales materials, signage and more. 
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-296745"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_logo_explanation.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Logo explanation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_typography.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_identity_elements.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Identity elements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_identity_overview.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Identity overview.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_business_card.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Business card.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_icon_set.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Icon set.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_conference_stage_ad.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Conference stage ad.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_building_sign.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Building sign.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fm_Hardhat_Jacket.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for FM by Prophet" />
<figcaption>Hardhat and jacket.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JONCal3r44s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Tiny brand video with logo animation at the end.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo was a vibe, with one mint or pink hue away from screaming 1980s but it was also pretty bad, with three completely unrelated elements, except, arguably, for the fact that they were all condensed. The new logo is a drastic change, making it look like old and new are two completely different companies servicing completely different industries. The new logo is hardcore and industrial, conveying a literal strong sense of solidity in what they do. Before adding the chiseled effect, the structure of the new “FM” monogram is actually pretty cool, clever, and unexpected. While I would normally advocate for a flat design, I do think the volume of the facets helps a lot with the readability of the two letters and without it, the “FM” could have been very lackluster and potentially very awkward. The final rendering is a bit odd though, with the very thin stroke around the letterforms and the white strokes in the apices of the chisels. Both things seem unnecessary.<span></span> For the identity, the typography goes in an unexpected and untrendy direction with the choice of Commercial Type's <a href="https://commercialtype.com/catalog/algebra" target="_blank">Algebra</a>, which is a really nice, editorial-esque slab serif that would probably compete with any other logo but since the titanium FM is so much its own “thing”, Algebra's peculiarities can also shine. It also provides a way of conveying corporate-ness in a more interesting way. Not much in application and what's there is kind of generic but it's arguably fine. In the hardhat and jacket we also get a glimpse at a flat, 2-color solution to the logo and it works mostly well but in the first stroke of the “M” I think the shadow should be on the upper part. Overall, this may lean a little too hard on an industrial, steel-producing aesthetic more so than insurance but it's still good to see a design approach that skirts the edge of the box to think just right outside of it with some unexpected design decisions.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_fm_by_prophet.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_fm_by_prophet.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Variety is the Spectrum of Life”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/spectrum_life_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 2018, <a href="https://www.spectrum.life/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spectrum.Life</a> is an online platform for customizable health services that provides clinical services and tech infrastructure for immediate, direct access to a full spectrum of personalized care covering digital health, mental health, and wellbeing. With over 260 employees, Spectrum.Life provides its services internationally to more than 7.5 million insurance members; 3,000 corporate clients; and to over 60 third-level institutions and 650,000 university students. Members can easily access services like wellbeing essentials through live programming and lifestyle content or mental health options like lifestyle coaching, short-term therapy, and guidance to long-term counseling and in-patient care — all in one app, one platform. Recently, Spectrum.Life introduced a new identity designed by Brighton, UK-based <a href="https://unitedus.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UnitedUs</a>.</p>

<span id="more-296740"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>Embracing a dynamic pace of change, anticipating future opportunities, and remaining firmly rooted in a core mission, we brought a full-spectrum brand to life. The strapline ‘full spectrum care, for a full spectrum life’ unlocked creative opportunity for the identity while directly communicating the offering and impact Spectrum.Life has on people’s lives.<br /><br />‘Full spectrum care’ captures the multitude services of care across digital health, mental health, and wellbeing. ‘Full spectrum life’ captures the ability to engage, empower, and transform lives across diverse experiences.<br /><br />Drawing inspiration from the analogy of the spectrum of light – and leaning into their evocative name – a ‘spectrum’ device was placed at the heart of the brand. This prompted a visual identity composed of different colours, frequencies and shapes, but all part of one unified system. Using this metaphor with multiple spectrums, we captured the many ways Spectrum.Life supports a myriad of lives and experiences.<br /><br />The Spectrum.Life logo is a modified wordmark, where a custom ‘m’ mimics the wave and wobble of the ‘spectrum’ device. Using Raptor V3 for the wordmark and main display type conveys professionalism, modernity, and approachability, while providing legibility and versatility across various media.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://unitedus.co.uk/work/spectrum-life/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UnitedUs project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_icon_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Shorthand logo with different icons.</figcaption>
</figure>



<p>The old logo wasn&#8217;t good but it wasn&#8217;t supper offensive either. By trying to minimize the real estate it needed, though, it ended up with a very awkward and unbalanced composition and the large period fought for attention with the small, textured heart. Having written this out, I guess it <em>was</em> sort of offensive. The new logo embraces the length of the name and renders everything in a single, tightly typeset line with a relatively wide icon to boot. The wordmark makes for a friendly and nice first impression but maybe it was customized a little too much. Using <a href="https://www.superiortype.com/fonts/raptor-v3" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Raptor V3</a> as a basis, some letters have been trimmed on their terminals, descenders and ascenders shortened, and the “t” given a little extra curve on its crossbar. All of these subtle changes take some attention away from the groovy “m”, which would have been enough of a customization.</p>

<p>The “m” could have also been exaggerated a little more to replace the need for an additional icon altogether and I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if, in an earlier exploration, the icon lived where the “m” is now. Nonetheless, I do like the addition of the icon as it provides a nice balance with the “m” and I really like the various spectrum icons they&#8217;ve come up with and how easily they can switch between them for the logo and for other messaging. Their animation could be just a tad smoother on the curves but it&#8217;s certainly energetic and its upward movement optimistic. The shorthand version is a fun rebus only if you know the name of the company and are familiar with its brand assets, which isn&#8217;t a bad thing, it just means it needs to be deployed &#8220;deeper” in the identity system and user experience vs. being used in first-contact uses like ads.</p>

<blockquote>‘Full spectrum colour’ personifies the vivid experiences, radiant outlook and impactful services that Spectrum.Life deliver. Colour also plays a pivotal role in flexing to specific audiences. Whether using neutral colours for insurer audiences to imagine their own brand being the hero, engaging workplace audiences with a bold purple, or ramping up vibrancy for diverse education audiences, the Spectrum.Life brand is always prepared to communicate across the full spectrum.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://unitedus.co.uk/work/spectrum-life/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UnitedUs project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_color_palette.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_spectrum_graphics.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_icon_set.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_icon_set_animated.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>The full spectrum of spectrum icons and graphics.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_typography.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_photography_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_photography_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Another interpretation of “spectrum” is an oversize, extra wavy circle that lives in the background, spinning and morphing its contour while a spectrum of colors also do their own dance within and are rendered in grainy, wavy gradients. In principle, I would say it&#8217;s too much but in the opposite of principle, I very much enjoy that treatment and I&#8217;m digging the way they use it with photography by placing it between a subject and a background. The typography uses Raptor V3 out of the box, so there is both synergy and dissonance with the logo given the customizations on the wordmark where they look related but don&#8217;t share the same details. It&#8217;s fine though… the type looks good. It&#8217;s a little serious, a little playful, and it&#8217;s inviting.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_editorial_spread.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Editorial spread.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_web_elements.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_web_elements_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>UI elements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_website_mobile.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Website on mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_app_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_app_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_app_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>App.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_lanyards.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Lanyards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_tshirt.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>T-shirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Spectrum.Life by UnitedUs" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The applications are all good. I particularly like the ad with the person swimming and interacting with the messaging and iconography… it literally looks full of life. There is also a good flexibility to the system in using the wobbly, spectrum-y contours as holding shapes in different ways and the grainy gradients do add some welcome texture across touchpoints, from advertising to the app.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/spectrum_life_identity_overview.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Identity overview.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/989633350?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Brand video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">If it wasn&#8217;t clear what Spectrum.Life is or does (as it was to me) the long-ish video above does do a good job in giving a better picture of what you actually get from it. Would have loved to see some of the system applied to it. Overall, an optimistic and lively identity that bridges the needs of the corporations and institutions that hire its services with a polished and slightly serious look and the experience and expectations of the end-users with an approachable and relatively fun attitude.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_spectrum_life_by_unitedus.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_spectrum_life_by_unitedus.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Name and Logo for OH!SOME</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/oh_some_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Name and Logo for OH!SOME" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/C-Hne6TuyJ0/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_and_logo_for_ohsome.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_and_logo_for_ohsome.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Sip &#038; Bark by See Saw</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/sip_and_bark_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sip &amp; Bark by See Saw" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://see-saw.studio/sip_and_bark/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_sip_bark_by_see_saw.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_sip_bark_by_see_saw.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Aged Brand Synergy</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/funny_parmesan_olympic_gymnast.jpg" alt="Aged Brand Synergy" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Sports/wireStory/cheese-giorgia-villa-viral-parmesan-sponsorship-deal-after-112534990">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>With the recent silver medal won by Italy in the women’s gymnastics team event, one of its members, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/giorgiavilla23/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Giorgia Villa</a>, has enjoyed some additional attention when the internet found out that she&#8217;s been the brand ambassador of parmesan cheese maker Parmigiano Reggiano, which entered a sponsorship deal with her in 2021, and <a href="https://gabrieleseghizzi.com/stories/giorgia-villa-parmigiano-reggiano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the promotional photos by Gabriele Seghizzi are epic</a>.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aged_brand_synergy.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aged_brand_synergy.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Ain’t No Cracker Crispy Enoughs”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/nufs_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2022) &#8220;<a href="https://www.getnufs.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NUFS</a> is a women-owned and led family business — founded by sisters Kristine and Jessica Tran — that&#8217;s bringing bold flavor experiences made from simple ingredients to the cracker aisle. We believe simple ingredients are enough to make great tasting food.”</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://theworkingassembly.com/" target="_blank">The Working Assembly</a> (New York, NY)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://theworkingassembly.com/case-studies/nufs" target="_blank">The Working Assembly project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>The agency's comprehensive brand system features graphic representations of the products, a bold yet legible wordmark, a personality-packed mascot, and an organic illustration style. These elements combine to reflect the brand's commitment to both fun and flavor while highlighting the clean ingredients of NUFS snacks.<br /><br />“Our primary challenge was to visually convey the purity of the product's ingredients while highlighting its playful and flavorful essence,” said Jolene Delisle, founder and head of creative at The Working Assembly. “We achieved this by integrating vibrant, bold colors and striking graphic elements, perfectly reflecting NUFS' core values.”
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-296699"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66%;background:black"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_illustration.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_illustration_02.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<figcaption>Mascot.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<figcaption>Packaging, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<figcaption>Packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_transparent.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<figcaption>Other type of packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_lifestyle.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_lifestyle_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nufs_packaging_lifestyle_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for NUFS by The Working Assembly" />
<figcaption>Hero shots.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo had its charm, with a thick marker-slash-brush wordmark that made it look earthy and organic. The smily face “u” was fun and it worked well with the lowercase “s” on the other side. The “F” was kind of bad, though, and started to go into <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_be_best_by_melania_trump.php" target="_blank">Be Best territory</a>. The new logo is quite a drastic departure, adopting a more serious personality. It's a solid bit of typography and I like the subtle notch in the “U” to give it some flair. Seeing the logo before and after on its own might feel like the brand sacrificed a lot of playfulness and vibrancy but the new packaging has a fun looseness to it that makes up for the more serious first impression of the new logo.<span></span> Peppered with abstract crackers in the background and paired with a great photo of a single, crispy, crunchy, salty cracker as well as a fancy but hip serif in <a href="https://pangrampangram.com/products/editorial-new" target="_blank">Editorial New</a>, the new boxes and wraps pack a vibrant, bold punch. The resulting primary color palette of red, blue, yellow, and black across the products makes for a very attractive family. The mascot on its own feels a little gratuitous and out of character with the rest of the look but, to its credit, it works really well on the side of the boxes as a lighthearted accent. Overall, a drastic change that elevates the brand to compete better in the cutthroat Direct-to-Consumer food brand market where all these non-mainstream products are so well designed as well as have a much better presence on the coveted shelf space of stores like Whole Foods.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_nufs_by_the_working_assembly.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_nufs_by_the_working_assembly.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Arch Nouveau”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/PICA_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 1989 and officially opened in 1991, the <a href="https://pica.org.au/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts (PICA)</a> is a prominent centre for contemporary arts located in Perth, Western Australia. Housed in the iconic Perth Boys School building in the heart of Perth’s Cultural Centre, PICA works with artists who are trail-blazers, exemplars, innovators, and change-makers and acts as a site for challenging and timely conversations. It&#8217;s also well known for its innovative and interdisciplinary approach, featuring a diverse programme that includes exhibitions, performances, and public events. The institute is committed to fostering creative risk-taking and experimentation, offering artists residencies and development opportunities. PICA enlisted the help of Perth&#8217;s very own <a href="https://www.blockbranding.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Block</a> to help revamp their identity and website.</p>

<span id="more-296665"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>
Since 1991, PICA has occupied the iconic Perth Boys School building in the heart of Perth’s Cultural Centre. From there, it has built a national and international reputation as a grassroots incubator and amplifier of contemporary artists and their practices. However, it lacked an identity that matched the boldness of its ambition and the idiosyncrasy of its location—an identity that would highlight this “Grit in the Oyster of Western Australia” and stand out among its more traditional cultural neighbours.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.blockbranding.com/work/perth-institute-of-contemporary-arts" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Block&#8217;s project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_logo_full.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Full logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_logo_stacked_a.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Stacked version.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_logo_initials.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Acronym version.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_logo_detail.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Logo details.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_logo_concept.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo concept.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_logo_pattern.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Logo with window shapes.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The old logo was as straight as they come, with a clean, sans-serif, typographic logo. Pretty ok for a modern art museum and definitely neutral enough to allow the exhibits be the hero, but totally devoid of any real sense of character. The new logo, well, it&#8217;s a departure and certainly not something we see every day. It does away with neutrality, with blandness, and, ultimately, with the rule-book. Set in all caps, in a custom monospaced font, it embraces the innovative and adventurous spirit of the museum. The genius for me is in its concept, and how each letter is derived from the iconic shapes found in the building. A simple idea that could have been iterated endlessly to a more conforming typeface, but I love the fact they just bluntly ran with it and still managed to create a set of letters that do feel harmonious. I&#8217;m sure this logo will divide opinion, and I don&#8217;t think I could even describe it as &#8220;beautiful&#8221; but thinking about what the museum represents — its edgy and trail-blazing attitude — it&#8217;s a logo that feels very fit for purpose and it&#8217;s rare you get opportunities to do something genuinely different in branding these days, so I commend Block fully on that!</p>


<blockquote>
A challenging and evocative Brand Platform was developed to encapsulate the intent of this dynamic destination and the provocative art that extends beyond its walls. This was articulated through the deceptively simple Brand Idea: “Cultivating the Provocative. Provoking the Culture.” This idea served as the guiding light for the rebrand.
<br><br>
The new identity proudly draws inspiration from the building itself, elevating it to its rightful place as the city’s “Agnostic Temple dedicated to The Now and its Stories.” The building’s arched entrance—through which people, ideas, and creativity flow in and out—became the perfect metaphor for the connection, support, and protection PICA offers to contemporary arts practitioners. The cornerstone of the identity is the wordmark, a distinctive piece of custom typography inspired by the old school’s architecture, with each glyph’s dimensions reflecting the unique entrance tower.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.blockbranding.com/work/perth-institute-of-contemporary-arts" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Block&#8217;s project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_graphic_system_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Graphic system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_graphic_system_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Graphic system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_colour.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Colour palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_typography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_guidelines_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Brand guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_guidelines_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Brand guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Oh, you thought the avant-garde approach ended in the logo? We&#8217;re just getting started. The identity takes what it started in the logo and injects a hefty chunk of David Carson inspired design into the rest of the identity. Craving a bit of graphic normality, we have blocks with three arches cut out along the base of blocks, another clever use of the device established in the logo. For colour, we have <em>all of the greens</em> (Block&#8217;s words not mine). Which I&#8217;m not entirely sure of the rationale for, but it&#8217;s giving off a slightly 1990s acid vibe which feels true to the system they&#8217;re creating. Typography appears to be <a href="https://type.tmpstate.net/preview/Panama/Proportional%20Regular/overview/">Panama by Temporary State</a> set in all caps and placed kinda wherever the designers feels like – changing size, going italic, bleeding slightly off the page, twisting and bending. I also see some arrows in the guidelines but I&#8217;m too afraid at this point to ask their purpose so let&#8217;s move on. Honestly, it&#8217;s actually kind of hard to tell where the system starts and where it ends. But again, I don&#8217;t mind it! I&#8217;m thinking they could have saved a lot of ink and just published a one page set of guidelines which say &#8220;fuck the rules&#8221; and it would work just the same.</p>

<p>I&#8217;m being slightly facetious, because whilst I wasn&#8217;t around for this era of design, I can certainly appreciate its place and how the seemingly chaotic approach is actually quite controlled; how each design conveys its own distinct message but overall feel united as one through colour, typography, and individualism. Consider me convinced.</p>

<p>Also as a side note, I love Block&#8217;s commitment to the aesthetic that even the case study itself feels right out of a ’90s design playbook, looking like a book scanned in and roughly arranged.    
</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_website_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Website animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_digital.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_mobile_system.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_screen.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Screen.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_signage.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Signage.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_merch_tshirt.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>T-shirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_graphics.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_posters.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Fly posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/PICA_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perth Institute of Contemporary Arts by Block" />
<figcaption>Advertising and exhibition.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>In application it&#8217;s more of what you&#8217;d expect. The logo sitting heroically across the top of posters, typography doing its thing, big hits of lots of different greens, all wrapped up in an edgy style with a sense of controlled-roughness. One thing I am picking up on is the &#8220;arch device&#8221; that sits at the bottom of designs, it does start to get lost a bit as they&#8217;re so small and hard to notice. In the end, they begin to look a little like an error rather than a visual device to build recognition. Then again this has a lot else working for it to achieve that. The website offers a respite from the chaos with a cleaner approach, understandable as they need to prioritise functionality over funk.</p>


<p class="end"> In the end, I&#8217;m quite torn on this. On the one hand it simply doesn&#8217;t fit into my aesthetic preference. But on the other I can totally appreciate what it&#8217;s trying to do and say and the institution it represents. Some people might hate this and think I&#8217;m giving it too much leeway &#8220;because art&#8221;. And I kind of am.  However, I&#8217;ll go back to what I said about the logo and how I couldn&#8217;t really describe it as &#8220;beautiful&#8221;, I think the same for the system too. But beauty is subjective, and I find myself a bit weary of traditionally beautiful brands. Ultimately, branding is about a feeling, it’s about attitude, and this identity has plenty of it. PICA has a clear vision and a strong history to support it. It doesn’t hold back, it challenges, provokes, asks questions, and prides itself on being a partner in bringing bold, new ideas to life. This captures that perfectly for me. Does Art Live Here? 100% it does.</p>    
 
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_perth_institute_of_contemporary_arts_by_block.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_perth_institute_of_contemporary_arts_by_block.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 08:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>