<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for American Bird Conservancy</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/american_bird_conservancy_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for American Bird Conservancy" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://abcbirds.org/news/30th-anniversary/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_american_bird_conservancy.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_american_bird_conservancy.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Ifop by Yuma</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/ifop_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Ifop by Yuma" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://yuma-brandthinking.com/portfolio/ifop/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_ifop_by_yuma.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_ifop_by_yuma.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Mint Condition Nouveau</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/news_ebay_evo.jpg" alt="Mint Condition Nouveau" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://playbook.ebay.com/articles/ebay-embraces-evolution">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Probably one of the last places one would have expected to find good design given that its website and brand are showing their age (30 years!), eBay has introduced a new design language called eBay Evo (short for “evolution”) that began as UX/UI exercise and has expanded to the identity and overall brand experience. Nothing revolutionary but a huge improvement.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/mint_condition_nouveau.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/mint_condition_nouveau.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 10:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“If at First you don’t Succeed, Fry, Fry Again”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/miss_millies_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1988) &#8220;<a href="https://missmillies.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Miss Millie’s</a> has been serving awesome chicken across the South West and Wales for over 30 years. But our roots in the fried chicken industry stretch back even further – to 1965 when our former Chairman, Harry Latham, set up KFC in the UK, alongside his partner Ray Allen. Harry then served as the Managing Director of KFC UK in the 1970’s before opening stores in 1988 in the South West under the Miss Millie’s brand.
As Harry and his family were good friends with Colonel Sanders of Kentucky Fried Chicken, he decided to name the new operation after the Colonel’s daughter, Mildred. The family owned and ran the chain up until it was bought by new management in 2019. Today, Miss Millie’s has 14 branches across the UK in Bristol, Weston-Super-Mare, Yate ,Billericay, Southampton and Walthamstow – with more to come as Miss Millie’s enters an exciting new era, with a new look, new menu, new restaurants, and a new leadership team.&#8221;</p>

                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.heywhat.co.uk/" target="_blank">Hey! What?</a> (Bristol, UK)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.heywhat.co.uk/missmillies" target="_blank">Hey! What? project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>Taking the brand back to its roots, we travelled into the Miss Millie's archives to reflect on the original identity which featured the Mildred mascot (based on Colonel Sander's daughter). Perhaps controversially, we decided that it no longer felt current to have a mascot, so instead concentrated our efforts in crafting a hand-drawn and timeless typographic marque.<br /><br />Our research showed that the original script logo held a lot of brand equity. By reimagining the classic brand identity, we avoided alienating their existing loyal customer base, whilst paying homage to their heritage.<br /><br />Each letter was meticulously redrawn to ensure ultimate legibility and consistency, making it better suited for the digital age. The refreshed signature successfully bridges the gap between nostalgia and modernity, reinvigorating the brand and enhancing its appeal across different demographics.<br /><br />The new refined type system aims to bring flexibility and personality to the brand, much like their audiences' freedom to unapologetically be who they want to be. With the help of the variable font Sharp Grotesk, the brand is able to dial up and down playful vs. functional messaging. Combining the new graphic system, strapline and photography style, the transformed visual identity feels fitting for modern day fried chicken lovers as well as loyal Miss Millie's day ones.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-300216"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_logo_evolution.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Logo evolution.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_logo_animation.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Logo animation (and photography by <a href="https://www.andrepattenden.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">André Pattenden</a>).</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_typography.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_visual_language_tov_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_visual_language_tov_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_visual_language_tov_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_visual_language_tov_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_visual_language_tov_06.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_visual_language_tov_07.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Visual language and tone of voice.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_sauces.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Sauces.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_advertising.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/miss_millies_food_wrap.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Miss Millie’s by Hey! What?" />
<figcaption>Tray liner.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo was nicely executed but I think it leaned too youthful and too consumer-product-y, almost like a brand of cosmetics for teenagers or a brand of artisanal potato chips. The logo before that, with the depiction of Mildred Marie Sanders — daughter of Colonel Harland David Sanders, founder of KFC and inspiration for the Miss Millie's name — was also a little awkward with the high-fashion eyeglasses and thick lathering of lipstick combined with the paper hat. The original logo wasn't amazing but it was certainly the most authentic and straightforward.<span></span> The new logo brings back the original script wordmark on its own, executed with just the right amount of bounciness, weight variance, and simplicity that yields a friendly, warm, and comfort-food-esque presence. Perhaps some of our U.S. audience will have a hard time not seeing the <a href="https://www.mrsfields.com/" target="_blank">Mrs. Fields</a> but given they are not as ubiquitous (if at all) in the UK, it's not an issue. <span></span> The identity has a couple of good things going: Some scrumptious photography of both product and people and some thick and juicy typography using all the widths and weights of <a href="https://www.sharptype.co/typefaces/sharp-grotesk" target="_blank">Sharp Grotesk</a>. Neither is groundbreaking but paired with the monochromatic red color palette and some snappy copywriting, they amount to a convincing and effective fast food offering. Some of the layering and texturing might be missing from the packaging as it feels too minimalist and stark in contrast to the rest of the visual language. Overall, a solid evolution that should be able to stick for more than a couple of years as the two previous identities did and perhaps win some new fans along the way.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_miss_millies_by_hey_what.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_miss_millies_by_hey_what.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 10:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Spur of the Moment”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/tottenham_spurs_new.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 1882, <a href="https://www.tottenhamhotspur.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tottenham Hotspur F.C.</a> — commonly referred to only as Tottenham or Spurs — is a professional football club based in Tottenham, North London, England. Competing in the Premier League, English football&#8217;s top tier, the team has won two league titles, eight FA Cups, four League Cups, and seven FA Community Shields domestically. In European football, they have won one European Cup Winners&#8217; Cup and two UEFA Cups, collecting at least one major trophy in each of the six decades from the 1950s to 2000s. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/lists/soccer-valuations/?sh=23707c62198b" target="_blank" rel="noopener">According to Forbes</a>, Tottenham is the 8th most valuable club <em>in the world</em> behind teams like Real Madrid, Manchester United, and Paris Saint-Germain but ahead of Arsenal, the Spurs&#8217; arch nemesis, a rivalry that dates back over 100 years. This week, Tottenham Hotspur F.C. introduced a “remastered” identity designed by London, UK-based <a href="https://www.nomadstudio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nomad Studio</a> in collaboration with their in-house team.</p>

<span id="more-300210"></span>

<blockquote>The Spurs Club badge stands prouder than ever and is now supported by a simplified silhouette cockerel that allows for a more playful expression of the brand. We worked with icon specialist, Chris Mitchell, to create this new version based on the original he created 18 years ago.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.nomadstudio.com/work/tottenham-hotspur-remastered" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nomad Studio project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_cockerels.png" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Primary (left) and secondary cockerel icons.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019842937?h=f447d95d07&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1&#038;controls=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Differences between primary and secondary icons. Both designed by <a href="https://www.epicicons.com/work/tottenham-hotspur-fc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chris Mitchell</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Spearheading <a href="https://www.tottenhamhotspur.com/the-club/spurs-brand-remastered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the “remastered” narrative</a> where none of the existing assets of the team are being replaced or redesigned is the new simplified cockerel icon that can now appear as a silhouette, given the equity and recognizability of the more detailed version that has been part of the team (in a number of stylistic variations) since the 1920s and standing on a ball since the 1970s. The primary version has also officially dropped the name of the team <a href="https://1000logos.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Tottenham-Hotspur-Logo.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">that previously appeared curved underneath the ball</a>. Both moves give the cockerel more freedom to strut its stuff with less distractions. Sort of…</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_cockerel_versions_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_cockerel_versions_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019491508?h=565daf802f&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019398950?h=5a3c609fb4&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Icon variations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The silhouetted version has been subjected to a number of ludicrous stylistic variations that seem to have no relevance to Tottenham or even football in general. They are just completely random and gratuitous, which is especially jarring in the context of the rest of the remastered assets that are very specific and unique to Tottenham. These renders are all relatively fun to look at but, sadly, irrelevant… they don&#8217;t even appear in the mock-up applications. I guess (or hope) they are meant to demonstrate the potential flexibility of the silhouetted icon and what it <em>can</em> be or do.</p>

<blockquote>We’ve also reintroduced the THFC monogram – a fan favourite from the 1950s that went on to feature heavily through the Club’s badge for many years. We modernised and remastered it, working with type specialist, Miles Newlyn.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.nomadstudio.com/work/tottenham-hotspur-remastered" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nomad Studio project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1029368543?h=9f933bac47&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_monogram.png" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Monogram. Drawn by <a href="https://newlyn.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Miles Newlyn</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The monogram is fantastic. Classic. Well executed. No notes.</p>

<blockquote>Cut to cut through, chant louder, and hit home (&#038; away) harder. Working with F37 Foundry to supercharge the existing Spurs display face. Turning a single display font into a dynamic, variable, super family of fonts that are unmistakably Spurs.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.nomadstudio.com/work/tottenham-hotspur-remastered" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nomad Studio project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_custom_type_02.png" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Existing custom typeface that has been part of the team&#8217;s identity for the last 20 years.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_custom_type_01.png" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019378404?h=e15ca06b0f&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>New variable, display typeface. By <a href="https://f37foundry.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">F37 Foundry</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019378763?h=86db374834&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1020594754?h=c3b6ef3358&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019492212?h=86260ff573&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Custom type family details.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The new display typeface is also excellent, infusing the previously existing flared serif with more drama and exaggerated gestures that give the flaring, well, more flair. Able to expand into extreme widths and italicize the regular way as well as the opposite way, provides ample flexibility to have some fun with the typography, which they do in application as they mix and match widths and italic directions.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_wordmark_01.png" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1019379578?h=20c782e962&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_wordmark_02.png" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Secondary wordmarks.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>A couple of customized wordmarks have emanated from the display typeface, adding some funky ligatures for an even more customized look. The “RS” in “SPURS” is quite nicely done but the “UR” in “HOTSPUR” is slightly awkward as the “U” feels quite large and the “R” quite small. The versus mark is pretty slick.</p>

<blockquote>A new identity built from heat, light and energy. Bringing to life the new Club philosophy in a suite of assets that allow maximum stretch. Colours and Patterns built from iconic elements of THFC’s past, and a suite of hallmarks developed to celebrate key features of the Club including Seven Sister Trees, Bruce Castle, and 1882 (THFC’s founding year).</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.nomadstudio.com/work/tottenham-hotspur-remastered" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nomad Studio project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1020757007?h=5395ac32dc&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1029354105?h=8912355d19&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Icon set.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1022112222?h=2c399e8aee&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Patterns.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>A few other assets complete the identity, starting with a collection of icons that represent different aspects of Tottenham lore and they are all pretty cool and well executed. The patterns… I&#8217;m on the fence about. I like that they are unexpected and untraditional while also adding a contemporary sheen to the identity but they also come across as trying a little too hard to stand out. I&#8217;m going to err on the side of liking them, mostly because of the ones that are curvy and have that blown-out, high-exposure effect.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1020266261?h=f6bd707f23&#038;title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0&#038;color=ffffff&#038;muted=1&#038;autopause=0&#038;controls=0&#038;loop=1&#038;app_id=122963&#038;autoplay=1&#038;loop=1" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Layout system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_instagram_posts.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_program.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Program.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_02.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_05.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_06.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_07.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_08.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_09.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tottenham_spurs_stadium_03.jpg" alt="New Identity for Tottenham Hotspur F.C. by Nomad Studio" />
<figcaption>Stadium experience.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The various elements come together quite well in the applications above. There is a clear cohesiveness among them but there is also enough variety to keep things lively and different. I do like the simpler versions better like the series of posters where it&#8217;s just white assets on top of muted photography versus the ones with the glow-y patterns, even though I said those were the patterns I like. I contain multitudes like that, sorry.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1031334049?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">Overall, this “remastering” cleverly sidesteps any drastic changes that would anger fans and adds plenty of relevant and crowd-pleasing assets with the new icon set while being able to infuse the team with a new visual energy that has an electrifying and exciting aura to it.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_tottenham_hotspur_fc_by_nomad_studio.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_tottenham_hotspur_fc_by_nomad_studio.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 09:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) by Javi Aguilar</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/css_2024_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) by Javi Aguilar" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.coywolf.news/webdev/css-has-a-new-official-logo/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_css_cascading_style_sheets_by_javi_aguilar.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_css_cascading_style_sheets_by_javi_aguilar.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Orlando International Airport by SIX The Agency</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/orlando_airport_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Orlando International Airport by SIX The Agency" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://simpleflying.com/orlando-international-airport-new-logo-digital-rebrand/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_orlando_international_airport_by_six_the_agency.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_orlando_international_airport_by_six_the_agency.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 11:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: A Thing of the Past</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/news_ajax_old_logo_returns.png" alt="A Thing of the Past" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.ajax.nl/artikelen/klassiek-ajax-logo-keert-definitief-terug/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>To coincide with their 125th anniversary next year, Ajax, one of the top (if not <em>the</em> top) football clubs in the Netherlands, will be bringing back a decades-old logo for the 2025/26 season and remain indefinitely as the club&#8217;s official new badge. The logo, which was used from 1928 to 1991 will replace the more contemporary version introduced in 1991. Wish they had gone <a href="https://www.footballkitarchive.com/ajax-amsterdam-logo-history/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">back to the 1911 version tho</a>.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/a_thing_of_the_past.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/a_thing_of_the_past.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Space Out”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/perpetual_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2023, previously OpenShelf) &#8220;<a href="https://perpetual.so/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Perpetual</a> is an intelligent, self-managing inventory solution for the healthcare industry. We’re a diverse group of thinkers, makers, and problem-solvers, passionate about using technology to give time back to people — so they in turn can focus on doing what only humans can do.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://newkid.services/" target="_blank">new kid</a> (Toronto, ON)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                             N/A
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>From a strategy perspective, the key insight that drove brand development is that healthcare workers often feel like they’re in perpetual motion, constantly going back-and-forth between providing care to patients and managing complex inventory systems, all with limited time. By automating inventory management, Perpetual enables healthcare workers to spend more time on care, and less time dealing with cluttered shelves and complex re-ordering processes.<br /><br />With perpetual motion as a guiding principle, the logo was designed using the Fibonacci sequence, with the distance between each block mathematically derived from the famous spiral. The selection of the font LL Unica77, the digital revival of the classic Haas Unica (1980), serves as the cornerstone of the brand’s typographic approach. This typeface, authorized by its original designers, embodies a blend of modernity and timeless elegance, making it an ideal choice for Perpetual's visual communication.<br /><br />And finally, a grid system forms the foundation of the brand’s visual language, inspired by the blocks in the Perpetual logo system and the actual industrial design of the product itself.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-300160"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_logo_construction.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>Logo construction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:125%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_monogram.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Monogram.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_robots_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_robots_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_robots_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Robots in action.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_guidelines.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:62.469135802469136%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_guidelines_02_a.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:62.469135802469136%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_guidelines_02_b.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_business_cards.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>Business cards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_posters.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_posters_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>Posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_website_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_website_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_website_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>App.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%;background:black"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_instagram_posts_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/perpetual_booth.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Perpetual by newkid" />
<figcaption>Booth.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo — apologies for the low resolution — took its name seriously and made every letter “open” by slashing a bunch of strokes at sharp angles, yielding a very uncomfortable wordmark and it was more an interpretation of “open” than “shelf”, which seems like the latter would be the more important aspect to highlight. The new name is a clever choice for a robot automating a task by being in perpetual motion. The logo, in turn, is a clever interpretation of the name with a design that looks as if the letters are in perpetual motion, slowly drifting apart with a static depiction of an “ease in” motion movement. The premise of the logo seamlessly pays off in the animation, bringing the idea to life. Although my gut reaction would be to roll my eyes at the Fibonacci reference for spacing the elements in the logo, it actually works and if you have to gradually space out elements the “1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21…” sequence is as good as it gets.<span></span> The identity takes the squares in the logo and spreads them out in different ways across the applications, whether as large holding shapes for imagery and text or as decorative sprinkles, all in a minimalist style supported by the slick grotesk <a href="https://lineto.com/typefaces/unica77" target="_blank">Unica77</a> for that crisp Swiss style. Looking at the robots and the design language, I'm not exactly sure who their clients are… it's almost like only corporate villains in movies would be interested and able to afford i… oh, wait, I just described the entire healthcare industry. Sarcasm aside, this does seem like a very niché robot system to offer and the identity, with its minimalist, heavily-gridded, black-and-white look makes it seem more obscure and expensive, which, arguably, may be the correct approach. Overall, this has a slight dystopian-sci-fi vibe to it but it's definitely attractive in its own way and positions Perpetual in the high-end range of automation.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_perpetual_by_newkid.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_perpetual_by_newkid.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Something's Afoot(ball)”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/NYC_FC_Logo_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Founded in 2013, <a href="https://www.newyorkcityfc.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York City Football Club (New York City FC)</a> quickly established itself as a formidable presence in <a href="https://www.mlssoccer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Major League Soccer,</a> becoming the first and only MLS team within the five boroughs of New York City. Over its first decade, the club not only secured its place in the league but also captured the hearts of a diverse fanbase spanning across NYC’s unique neighborhoods. But as the club looks to solidify its legacy and prepare for the future — including a new soccer-specific stadium in Queens slated for 2027 — it needed a rebrand to match its ambition. Enter Brooklyn, NY-based <a href="https://gretelny.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gretel,</a> tasked with crafting a bold identity system that balances the grit and energy of New York City with the global aspirations of the club while reimagining what it means to represent New York City in sport — both locally and on the world stage.</p>

<span id="more-300141"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>
The club’s updated badge builds on its subway token-inspired predecessor crafted by Matthew Wolff [and Rafael Esquer] in collaboration with founding fans. The overall structure was optimized for legibility at small scales, while individual elements were refined to work together harmoniously or used independently as a suite of marks.
<br /><br />
A refined monogram sits at the center of the badge, designed with enhanced balance and confident proportions that evoke a strength and pride that matches the bold spirit of the city. Its construction mirrors the geometry and flared serifs in the identity’s subway signage inspired typefaces, featured in the outer ring lettering. The badge is punctuated by a pentagon on each side as a continued reference to the five boroughs of New York City. Developed in a close collaboration between Gretel, Frere-Jones Type, and the New York City FC team.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://gretelny.com/nycfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gretel case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_logo.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_logo_before_after.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>NEW logo and before &#038; after animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_logo_animated.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_subway_token_inspiration.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>NYC subway token inspiration.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Let me preface this review by going on the record as saying that I’m not a soccer fan, and I know about <em>thiiiiiiiis</em> much [moves thumb and forefinger together really closely] about it. My knowledge can be summed up as follows: a) I’m aware that soccer is, in fact, a sport; b) I know it’s the most popular sport in the world and I’m in the minority for not being rabid about it; c) I understand that America is one of the only places in the world that doesn’t call it “football”; d) I played it in gym class in school but never on an actual league; and e) my 5-year-old son just started playing it this year. Oh, and I recently substitute-coached his team’s final game of the season — which, if you’ve ever coached 5-year-olds, you know it basically amounts to cheering them on, encouraging frequent water breaks, and making sure they&#8217;re running in the right direction.</p>

<p>It&#8217;s not that I <em>dislike</em> soccer (I don&#8217;t); it&#8217;s just that people who like soccer, really, <em>really</em> like soccer — ferociously — and I&#8217;m just not one of those people. I go to my son&#8217;s games, coach as-needed, and kick the ball around with him at home, but that&#8217;s about where my involvement with soccer ends. But, as a general sports enthusiast and branding specialist, I <em>do</em> appreciate a well-crafted sports identity, and I think there are some straight-up awesome FC brands out there. As you will see, this rebrand for New York City FC happens to fall into that category.</p>

<p>While the old badge took a swing with some strong elements, its execution didn’t connect. For starters, the interlocking “NYC” monogram was a decent concept, but the composition felt clunky and unresolved. The slab serifs were particularly jarring, creating unnecessary visual interruptions in what should have been a clean and cohesive centerpiece.</p>

<p>The pentagon shapes punctuating the outer ring were a clever nod to the five boroughs, and the vibrant blue and orange color palette was definitely attention-grabbing. But the ho-hum sans-serif type encircling the badge didn’t do it any favors. With so much empty white space between the lettering and the pentagon bullets, the typography felt disconnected — more like a floating afterthought than an anchoring design element.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_monogram_detail.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Badge.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The redesigned badge takes everything the old one got almost right and refines it into a cohesive, polished mark. First off, the introduction of the “Local” variant of the custom “NYCFC” flared-serif typeface by Frere-Jones Type (discussed further down in the review) is a game-changer. The type now fills out the outer ring perfectly, eliminating the awkward white space that plagued its predecessor. It feels deliberate, balanced, and most importantly, at home within the badge.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_logo_system.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Logo system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Taking center stage, the interlocking “NYC” monogram has been redrawn in a complementary flared-serif style that’s <em>way</em> less visually cluttered. The slab-serif chaos is gone, replaced with a cleaner, more harmonious lockup that fits the space rather than fighting against it. The diagonals of the “N” and the left arm of the “Y” now nuzzle up cozily against each other in a way that feels intentional and crafted. These are the kinds of details that elevate the design into something both iconic and undeniably New York.</p>

<p>While the color scheme remains mostly intact, subtle tweaks to the hues make a world of difference. The light blue is lighter, the dark navy is darker, and the orange is brighter — creating a palette with far more contrast and energy. Combined with the removal of the inner white ring, which cuts down on visual clutter, the result is a cleaner, bolder design that feels like a more faithful adaptation of the vintage NYC subway token inspiration. This is a badge that proudly represents the grit and pride of New York City, both past and present.</p>

<blockquote>
To capture the spirit of our club and city, we developed The Five Borough Bond— a creative platform that serves as our core ethos and guiding metaphor.
<br /><br />
The Five Borough Bond embraces contrast and juxtaposition, a wild mix of ever-changing local flavors and iconic legacies. The relentless hustle and colossal scale of the city—edgy, tough and resilient— enriched by the pulsing rhythm and poetic beauty of everyday life, interwoven with unexpected moments made possible through eight million interlocking stories.
<br /><br />
By forging bonds across all five boroughs and celebrating the stories of New Yorkers brought together by NYCFC, we are continuously building the future of our club, our city, and our game.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://gretelny.com/nycfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gretel case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_strategy_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_strategy_02.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Brand strategy and brand voice &#038; tone.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>I&#8217;m a huge proponent of the power of brand strategy, and I believe that defining a thoughtful, insightful strategy — alongside a unique brand voice and tone — is as crucial to the effectiveness of a brand as the visual identity itself. NYCFC’s new creative platform, The Five Borough Bond, nails this balance. It unifies the club’s diverse fanbase by celebrating everything distinctly NYC: the contrasts, the chaos, the culture, and above all, the connections.</p>

<p>The Five Borough Bond leans into the city’s colossal character, weaving together the hustle and resilience of New Yorkers with their charm and quirks. It’s bold, dynamic, and unmistakably tied to NYC&#8217;s DNA. By framing the club’s identity around the unification of all five boroughs, Gretel and NYCFC tap into a unique angle that gives the club a compelling story — one that resonates with both die-hard fans and casual observers alike. As someone who fits squarely into the latter category, I&#8217;m definitely diggin&#8217; it.</p>

<p>This isn’t just a strategy — it’s a celebration of New York. Its grit, grandeur, and eclectic spirit. And when paired with the rebrand’s visual identity, this strategy transforms NYCFC into more than a football club — it becomes a symbol of what makes New York… well, <em>New York.</em></p>

<blockquote>
The team’s custom typeface is a modern imagination of the iconic pre-modernist signage used across the Independent Subway System (IND), which has connected New York City’s five boroughs since its construction in 1932. Concepted in-house and drawn by <a href="https://frerejones.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Frere-Jones Type,</a> ‘NYCFC’ appears in two styles.
<br /><br />
‘Local’ is built on the rectilinear geometry and petit serif flares found in monospaced tile lettering, which is still prominent in stations citywide. ‘Express’ marries the same details with the bold and idiosyncratic proportions featured in the IND’s directional signage. Their interchanged use in combination with inset details and companion pictograms reflects the voice of a team that represents all of New York City – loud, irreverent and cacophonous.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://gretelny.com/nycfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gretel case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_typography_explainer.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_typography_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_typography_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_typography_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>I love that the custom “NYCFC” typeface doesn’t merely replicate the iconic subway system signage that influenced it, but reimagines it for a modern context. It’s a fresh interpretation that feels authentic to NYC while adding a distinctly humanist charm. The flared serifs and quirky details — like the angled terminals on characters such as “C,” “G,” “J,” “S,” and even numbers like “2,” “3,” “5,” “6,” and “9” — give the typeface flavor and personality.</p>

<p>These eccentricities strike a balance between structure and character, perfectly echoing the city it represents: bold, functional, and unapologetically unique. Whether in its “Local” or “Express” variant, the typeface captures the essence of New York by blending history with a contemporary edge.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.66666667%;background:black">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_colors.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Colors.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_icons.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Icons.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
The brand’s mosaic system is a visual representation of the Five Borough Bond — individual components of various shapes and colors, woven together into an interconnected tapestry. Modular by nature, mosaics build and scale into structural elements, camouflage patterns, and generative textures that portray the different neighborhoods across the boroughs. As a system, these brand elements weave together the countless stories that unite the club and the city,  from the pavement to the pitch.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://gretelny.com/nycfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gretel case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_mosaic_inspiration.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_mosaic_generator.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_mosaic_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Mosaic graphic system: Inspiration, generation, implementation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The color system is a bold and lively celebration of New York City, with each hue named in an attempt to evoke a specific aspect and mood of the city: Copper Green (that&#8217;s the copper <em>patina</em> of the Statue of Liberty, which is now green), Skyline Blue, Bright White (this one&#8217;s a stretch, as I visit NYC quite a bit, and there ain&#8217;t much that&#8217;s bright white about it — said lovingly, of course), NYC Orange, Late Night Navy, Excelsior Cobalt, Neon Yellow, and Roosevelt Violet. These colors don’t just look great — they capture the energy and dynamism of NYC. Gretel’s (for the most part) considerate naming and selection of hues create a palette that feels as alive as the city itself.</p>

<p>The icons are a study in simplicity and cohesion. Each pictogram is rendered in a clean, geometric style that’s both functional and visually striking. What’s especially noteworthy is how the flared serifs, introduced in the custom “NYCFC” typeface, make a subtle yet consistent appearance across the icons. It’s a small detail, but one that helps unify the graphic elements and reinforces the identity’s sense of craft.</p>

<p>The mosaic graphic system is an interesting component, as it visually embodies the Five Borough Bond strategy while paying homage to NYC subway tiles and classic taxi checkerboard patterns. Its modular flexibility makes it a dynamic, unifying visual element that adapts seamlessly across scales and contexts.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_subway_digital_ad.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_billboard.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_posters.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>OOH advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_member_newsprint.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Member newsprint.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_social.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Social.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_app.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:49.259259259259259%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_fans.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>App and fans.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Gretel’s flexible and dynamic brand toolkit shines across a broad range of touchpoints, from in-your-face OOH advertising and member newspaper, to animated social content and a sleek app, to crispy fresh apparel and swag. Each element feels like a natural extension of the brand, seamlessly integrating typography, colors, and graphic elements into slick, attention-grabbing layouts. Together, these applications bring the rebrand to life in ways that are bold, lively, and oh-so New York, perfectly showcasing the city’s vibrancy and energy.</p>

<blockquote>
In tandem with the launch of the club’s new identity, New York City FC announced a landmark campaign to construct New York City’s first-ever soccer-specific stadium in Willets Point, Queens – slated for completion in 2027. The stadium will serve as a beacon for soccer’s future across the five boroughs, a permanent home for the club and symbol of the city’s long-term commitment to nurturing soccer players and fans alike for generations to come. Follow the stadium’s development here.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://gretelny.com/nycfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gretel case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_stadium_entrance.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%;background:black">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_stadium_jumbotron.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%;background:black">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_stadium_banner.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Queens stadium proposal.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_shirts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_shirt_back.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_scarf_flag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Merch.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/NYC_FC_badge.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for New York City FC by Gretel" />
<figcaption>Embroidered badge.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">New York City FC’s rebrand is a shining example of how to blend history with modernity, grit with charm, and strategy with execution. From the thoughtfully reimagined badge and custom typography to the vibrant color palette and dynamic applications, every element works harmoniously to tell a story that’s as bold and multifaceted as the city it represents. Gretel’s approach captures the spirit of New York — the grind, the resilience, the diversity — while giving the club a unified identity that speaks to both lifelong supporters and newcomers to the sport. And while this rebrand won&#8217;t cause me to start calling it &#8220;football&#8221; just yet, it definitely has me paying more attention to the sport, so maybe a side hustle as a volunteer coach for my son&#8217;s team next year is in my future.</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_new_york_city_fc_by_gretel.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_new_york_city_fc_by_gretel.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 03:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>