<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for National Black Canadians Summit by Six Cinquième</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/blackcanadiansummit_logo_new.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for National Black Canadians Summit by Six Cinquième" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.sixcinquieme.com/projects/nbcs-2025/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_national_black_canadians_summit_by_six_cinquieme.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_national_black_canadians_summit_by_six_cinquieme.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Swag as Economic Barometer</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/interesting_swag_power.jpg" alt="Swag as Economic Barometer" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://thehustle.co/originals/corporate-swag-will-never-diecorporate-swag-will-never-die">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>The Hustle has a pretty interesting article about the economic power and impact of corporate swag and how well it reflects the state of the economy in general. Also, some sobering stats (under the assumption that they are correct) like it being a $26.1-billion industry or how in 2022 ad spending fell by 6% but promotional swag spending was up 12% or when the industry grew three times quicker than the ad sector and 4 times quicker than the U.S. economy as a whole in 2010. Yikes.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/swag_as_economic_barometer.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/swag_as_economic_barometer.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“The Light at the End of the Tower”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/paris_basketaball_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2018) &#8220;<a href="https://parisbasketball.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paris Basketball</a> is a French professional basketball club based in Paris. The club currently plays in the LNB Pro A, the first division of basketball in France, and the EuroLeague since 2024–25. Paris plays its home games at the Adidas Arena. Three years after its establishment, Paris promoted to the first-level LNB Pro A for the first time, in 2021. In 2024, the team won the LNB Pro A Leaders Cup and the 2023–24 EuroCup titles.&#8221; (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paris_Basketball" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wikipedia</a>)</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            Identity: <a href="https://www.studiotyrsa.com/" target="_blank">Studio Tyrsa</a> (Paris, France)<br />Strategy: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/yard/" target="_blank">Yard</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://parisbasketball.com/en/2024/09/paris-basketball-unveils-new-logo/" target="_blank">Paris Basketball press release</a>
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>We teamed up with Yard who came up with a brief and a strategic approach that consisted in highlighting Paris and its basketball culture, as well as the idea of light. The light for the obvious City of Light, but also the one that puts the spotlight on new talents or the one that dazzles our opponents.<br /><br />We didn’t want use to use the Eiffel Tower at first, but after exploring many other options, we quickly realized that the most beautiful source of light in Paris was at the top of the Tower. The mix of the shape of the ball, the tower and the light on top then became an evidence to us. Using the club’s actual colors allowed us to play with them and create a lighting effect. The light became the center of the entire identity, and is present in both our PARIS wordmarks as a dot on the letter I, or as a shooting star that creates the loop of the P in our monogram.<br /><br />In addition to all these elements we’ve also designed a bespoke typeface, inspired by classic basketball fonts but also old Parisian Specimen we found, available in Regular and Italic. It will allow the club to express itself with a unique tone in a way that is consistent with its identity, whether on the back the jerseys, on the screen of the Arena or any communication assets.</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-298460"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_logo.png" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_logo_full.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Logo construction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="background:black;padding-bottom:125%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation. (Unmute for sound.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_icon.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Icon in full color and single color.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_wordmark_03.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_wordmark_01.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_wordmark_02.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Secondary wordmarks.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_monogram.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Secondary monogram.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_custom_type_01.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_custom_type_02.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Custom typeface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_all_elements.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>All elements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_uniforms_01.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_uniforms_02.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_uniforms_03.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Uniforms.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_launch_event.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Launch event.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo was quite generic with a basic basketball — in a combination of sharp and curved lines that were somewhat poorly drawn — and ill-fitting typography. The name and colors could be changed to any other city and it wouldn't have made a difference. The new logo embraces Paris' number one visual cliché — the Eiffel Tower — and cleverly blends it into the grooves of the basketball through a relatively abstract rendition of the landmark. The addition of the light spark at the top helps draw some attention away from the Eiffel Tower in a positive way so that the logo is not <em>just</em> about the Eiffel Tower and I really like the bright-spark feeling it achieves through the combination of blue, red, and white. The execution of the icon is quite nice too and was probably harder to achieve than it would seem at first glance, mixing the mono-width stroke of the grooves with the thicks and thins of the spark. In heavy contrast with the old typography, the new one goes wide… <em>very</em> wide, wrapping almost the full circumference of the logo and it's mostly good but maybe it ends up being too big.<span></span> The collegiate-looking custom typeface and matching secondary wordmarks are pretty nice as they also have a bit of an urban/industrial feel so it veers away from an American University athletics vibe. The script wordmark is also great but perhaps a little hard to appreciate with so many strokes around it. The monogram starts to feel like a stretch of the concept and the visual language but, like everything else, it is really well done. When seeing all of the assets together the one thing that stands out is that all of the spark elements are different — different angles, different proportions, different skews — and it would have been nice (albeit admittedly difficult) if that was the one element that was more heavily consistent across the myriad styles. Overall, as seen in the uniforms and launch event, everything comes together almost literally in a brilliant way in terms of how luminous the various assets stand out against black backdrops and there is a fun, sport-y energy to all of it.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logos_for_paris_basketball_by_studio_tyrsa.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logos_for_paris_basketball_by_studio_tyrsa.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 510: From Untitled Macao, Micael Micmas, and Purple</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Untitled Macao, Micael Micmas, and Purple”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/friday_likes_510.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 510" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Some eccentricity and quirkiness this week, with work from Macau, João Pessoa, and Stockholm.</p>
<span id="more-298457"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Dino Kiddo by Untitled Macao</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_dinokiddo.jpg" alt="Dino Kiddo by Untitled Macao" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;">Dino Kiddo is a new spin-off-slash-concept from <a href="https://www.instagram.com/dinoburgermacau/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dino Burger</a> in Macau, focusing on hot dogs. (As some of you might remember, <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_395.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">I Liked Dino Burger back in a Friday of 2021</a> — I&#8217;m actually shook this was three years ago as I could have sworn it was so much more recent.) The identity, designed (then and now) by <a href="https://untitledmacao.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Untitled Macao</a>, builds on the quirkiness and eccentricity of the original with a menagerie of crudely-drawn animals — some real, some imagined, some just plan unidentifiable — that are delightful in their weirdness. A funky “Kiddo” logo has been added to the already-weird Dino logo and while the logo shouldn&#8217;t work with its contradicting letterform shapes — some are squiggly, some are not and some are filled in, some are not — and silly googly eyes on top, it&#8217;s perfectly suited for the task. The supporting typography is typeset on weird paths or surrounded by super thick strokes and paired with odd colors but it all just clicks together in its loose approach and basks in its silliness. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://untitledmacao.com/dino-kiddo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Home Burger by Micael Micmas</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_homeburger.jpg" alt="Home Burger by Micael Micmas" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/homeburger.pb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Burger</a> is a burger joint in João Pessoa, a port city in northeastern Brazil, driven by its North Star of “Burger, Fries &amp; Friends”. The identity, designed by local designer <a href="https://www.behance.net/micaelmicmas" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Micael Micmas</a>, is not the most impressive (or cohesive) but, bruh, that “HB” monogram is a thing of beauty and worth celebrating. It would be impressive alone that it managed to blend an “H” and “B” together but to then reveal a hamburger in the negative space? Brilliant. The sign at night is so satisfying too with the dark sky “coloring” the burger in the negative space. As mentioned, the accompanying identity is not amazing but it&#8217;s not bad either… perhaps one too many typefaces without a clear purpose. Nothing a churro couldn&#8217;t make me overlook though. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/199960867/Home-Burger" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Lykke by Purple</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_lykke.jpg" alt="Lykke by Purple" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://www.lykkegardar.se/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lykke</a> is a coffee roaster in Farsta, Sweden, that not just sources its beans from but partners with and invests in farmers around the world. The identity, designed by Stockholm, Sweden-based <a href="https://purplestockholm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Purple</a>, takes matters into their own hands with a charmingly hand-made approach, first in the form of the wobbly rainbow logo and second in the abundance of spray-painted elements that manifest in different ways in the packaging and that also yield a small library of spot illustrations to use across other applications. More than a design system, a playful sensibility extends across the packaging of the multitude of coffee and tea offerings through bright colors, bold typography, and thick hand-drawn elements. If I had to choose one sample to order for keeps it would be <a href="https://www.lykkegardar.se/collections/shop-all/products/ugly-cute" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ugly Cute</a>.  <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://purplestockholm.com/lykke/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_510.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_510.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Next Level Apparel by JAM</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/next_level_apparel_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Next Level Apparel by JAM" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.jam-branding.com/work/next-level-apparel">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_next_level_apparel_by_jam.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_next_level_apparel_by_jam.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Name, Logo, and Identity for Höegh Evi by Brandpie</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/hoegh_evi_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Höegh Evi by Brandpie" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.brandpie.com/work/hoegh-evi">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_hoegh_evi_by_brandpie.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_hoegh_evi_by_brandpie.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Lost in Space</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/nice_space_exploration_logos.jpg" alt="Lost in Space" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://spaceexplorationlogoarchive.webflow.io/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Davide Mascioli, a Designer and Art Director in Rome, Italy, has put together the Space Exploration Logo Archive, a digital archive of over 370 logos related to space exploration from the 1940s to the present day, all available for perusing (and downloading in vector form) at the link. If you prefer your space exploration logos in book form, Davide has also <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/oreri/sela-space-exploration-logo-archive?ref=project_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched a Kickstarter</a> to produce a Risograph-printed publication divided into 5 mini-books, each distinguished by a unique color palette. Yes, please.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/lost_in_space.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/lost_in_space.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“The Eagle has Fallen”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/aeromexico_2024_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1934) &#8220;<a href="https://aeromexico.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Aeromexico</a>, Mexico’s global airline, operates more than 600 daily flights and has its main hub in Terminal 2 of the Mexico City International Airport. Its destinations network features 89 cities on three continents; including 43 destinations in Mexico, 18 in the United States, 17 in Latin America, 4 in Europe, 3 in Canada, and 3 in Asia. The Group&#8217;s operating fleet of 133 aircraft is comprised of Boeing 787 and 737 jet airliners and next generation Embraer 170 and 190 models. In 2012, the airline announced its most significant investment strategy in Mexican aviation history, purchasing 100 Boeing aircraft including 90 MAX B737 jet airliners and 10 B787-9 Dreamliners.  As a founding member of the SkyTeam airline alliance, Aeromexico offers customers more than 1,000 destinations in 177 countries served by the 20 SkyTeam airline partners rewarding passengers with benefits.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.instagram.com/wkmexico/" target="_blank">W+K Mexico</a> (Mexico City, Mexico)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_strategy_and_identity_for_aeromexico_by_mucho.php" target="_blank">2024 Brand New Reviewed post</a><br /><a href="https://www.adlatina.com/publicidad/nuevo-de-la-mano-de-wk-aeromexico-presenta-su-renovada-identidad-visual-y-celebra-la-mexicanidad" target="_blank">Adlatina story</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>According to Jessica Apellániz, chief creative officer of W+K Mexico, the new visual identity and all communication are the result of the company's own renewal and modernization process, with its new purpose as its central axis. "The purpose, elevating the trip to an extraordinary experience, is the narrative line of our main message. We present the feeling of pride that only those who were born here can identify. The recognition that, as Mexicans, as a country and as an airline, we believe in the extraordinary. The communication is a recognition of the size and growth of this brand and its desire to continue elevating and exporting our culture. This is the narrative that inspired the renewal of the brand's image and voice," she said.<br /><br />"The image change reflects our own evolution, a symbol of the rejuvenation of our relationship with all our stakeholders and, above all, with Mexican society. Today, Mexico is bigger, more interesting, varied and richer than ever. That's why we incorporated new textures, colors and materials to our image and spaces, giving us new ways to express ourselves, preserving our traditions and history, ancient and contemporary," he added.<br /><br />For his part, Pablo de Arteaga, president of the agency, concluded: "This project is the result of a close collaboration between Aeroméxico and Wieden+Kennedy México. Since 2023, we have worked hand in hand to bring to life the main communication projects of one of the most emblematic brands in the country. Aeroméxico has allowed us to use all our capabilities as an agency, from our design area, with the development of its new logo and all its applications, to the creation of campaigns that connect deeply with Mexican culture."
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-298403"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_logo_evolution.png" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<figcaption>Icon evolution.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_logo_before_after_large.png" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<figcaption>Logo, before and after, larger comparison.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_icon_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<figcaption>Icon, before and after (large and small).</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_subbrands.jpg" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<figcaption>Sub-brands.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_livery_before_after_large.jpg" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<figcaption>Livery, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_livery_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_livery_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/aeromexico_2024_livery_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Livery for Aeromexico by W+K Mexico" />
<figcaption>Livery.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ztCZIdLknvM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Brand video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C_8YdLzRKiP/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:540px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C_8YdLzRKiP/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;">View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div></div></a><p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C_8YdLzRKiP/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A post shared by Aeroméxico (@aeromexico)</a></p></div></blockquote>
<script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"></script>
<figcaption>Ad in Times Square.</figcaption>
</figure>





                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            Earlier this year, we had a Reviewed post <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_strategy_and_identity_for_aeromexico_by_mucho.php" target="_blank">on Mucho's identity overhaul for Aeromexico</a> and in it I wrote, “It probably wasn’t even on the table but not changing the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eagle_warrior" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eagle Warrior</a> icon was the best decision possible. It’s one of the best airline icons and is so broadly recognized.” Given the timing of Mucho's project release and the relaunch to coincide with Aeromexico's 90th anniversary, it pains me to say that changing the logo WAS on the table and that, for some reason, they didn't give Mucho a shot at it (or maybe the did) and instead opted to give the assignment to an advertising agency that — #sorrynotsorry for the blanket statement — are notoriously bad at doing logo and identity work and this is a prime example.<span></span> The “Eagle Warrior” icon probably hit its apex of epic-ness in 1981 and if I had been writing Brand New in 1988 I would have probably been as upset with the change then as I am now given the shift in design approach and changing the extremely satisfying geometry of the 1981 version (which was the result of it being drawn by hand). The 1998 version was slowly pulling away from the harder geometry of its predecessor with some curvature added to the head-dress and face but it stayed true to its essence and had really become one of the best and most recognizable icons in the country.<span></span> Call me patriotic or nostalgic or close-minded or short-sighted but I abhor the new icon (and wordmark, which I will get to) and I don't think I've used that word in a long time. Perhaps there were some market forces and industry-insider knowledge that demanded a logo change but I personally don't see why there was any need whatsoever as Aeromexico has a good brand reputation and there is no evident design gain from the change. Not in how it reproduces or performs nor in how it represents the airline. The execution of the new icon is not “wrong”… it's arguably well executed but the shift to the wispy gestures, more detailed face, and less abstract approach is literally uncalled for — it does not improve the icon in any way and it even manages to feel cheaper and less sophisticated.<span></span> My disdain for the new icon is enhanced by the atrocious wordmark that has curves in the absolute wrong places and one little wing each on the “A” and “M” to make up for the lack of caps. They look ridiculous. That “I”? Just, no. And that “C”? Someone call it an Uber because it showed up at the wrong party. The wordmark is embarrassingly bad. The only remotely positive thing I can say about the change from the old logo is the removal of the wavy red line because it had no business being there.<span></span> The livery is bad by proxy but, to its credit, the old one wasn't that great either. One thing worth pointing out is the use of the stripe-y motif established by Mucho, which also plays out in the Times Square ad and in a few other loose images I found while Googling. Lastly, there is a new brand video-slash-manifesto clocking in at 2-plus minutes and for anyone that doesn't understand Spanish and you think you might be missing something in translation as you wade through the confusing visual narrative let me assure you, as a Mexican, it's a mess and none of it makes sense. I really don't even know how to sum it up for you. It attempts to be philosophical, patriotic, empowering, epic, and then some, all delivered in what sounds like the longest concrete poetry reading ever leaving a single, lasting thought: WTF?<span></span> Overall, and as no surprise if you've read my rant, this is a terrible, unnecessary redesign that has no evident positive impact on Aeromexico.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_livery_for_aeromexico_by_wk_mexico.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_livery_for_aeromexico_by_wk_mexico.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“A Case Of”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/munchies_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Launched in 2024, <a href="https://www.tastyrewards.com/en-ca/brands/munchies" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Munchies</a> is a new range of snacks in Canada that include potato chips, tortilla chips, and popcorn. For some, this might be a strong crunch of nostalgia as the Munchies are actually quite old, having first appeared in 1981 as the mascots for <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hostess_Potato_Chips" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hostess Potato Chips</a>, a popular brand of chips in the 1970s, ’80s, and ’90s, spurred by a partnership between Hostess and Frito-Lay, before they were discontinued in 1996 and rebranded as Lay&#8217;s. Munchies has been brought back (or more like introduced anew) as its own brand by PepsiCo Foods Canada and its subsidiary Frito Lay Canada with six, permanent flavors, two of which are a nod to the original Hostess versions — Tangy Ketchup and Old School BBQ potato chips — along with Chili Cheese Stampede tortilla chips, Supreme Sour Cream and Onion tortilla chips, Cheeky Cheddar popcorn and Deliciously All Dressed popcorn. The identity and packaging have been designed by LA-, New York-, and Toronto-based <a href="https://vocabulary.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vocabulary</a>.</p>
<span id="more-298400"></span>

<blockquote>Many Canadians will recall Hostess chips, from the 80s and 90s, featuring the Munchies on the bag. The launch of the Munchies chips in 2024 will connect generations, bringing back fond memories of the good old days and feelings of wonder and joy.<br /><br />&#8220;Nostalgia taps into our deepest emotions and memories. When we decided to bring back the Munchies, we knew there was something inherently special about this brand and what it meant to original fans – while introducing the magic to new ones too,&#8221; said Jess Spaulding, Chief Marketing Officer, PepsiCo Foods Canada. &#8220;We&#8217;re excited to see how Canadians welcome the return of the Munchies as they pop up all over the country, in unexpected locations!&#8221;</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/the-iconic-munchies-make-their-magical-return-to-canada-20-years-later-854090053.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PepsiCo press release</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_original_use.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_original_use_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>The Munchies originally appeared on Hostess chips. They did not have their own brand. (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hostess_Potato_Chips" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Source</a>.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Using, National 2 (<a href="https://klim.co.nz/retail-fonts/national-2-compressed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Compressed</a>, I believe) as the starting point, the new logo gets this brand off on the right foot, with a good ol’ fashioned drop shadow, a thick stroke, and a vertiginous angle for some instant consumer brand appeal. The main modifications to National are some inverse flares to the stems of the letters that add a fun bounce to the wordmark and it appears the corners have been subtly rounded. This, along with the stroke treatment feels like it could have used a letterer&#8217;s touch so that it didn&#8217;t feel like a bulk effect from Adobe Illustrator as the resulting letterforms do end up feeling ever so slightly distorted and skewed. Nonetheless, it&#8217;s a fun logo. (I&#8217;m just now noticing some discrepancies between the logo on the packaging and the logo above, which is taken from the SVG on the website and it seems like a couple of drop shadows are missing on the “M” and “i”*).</p>

<p>* I know I can try and ask for the correct version but I actually prefer to work off of the materials that are put out into the world by the client as that&#8217;s what everyone sees.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_character_01.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_character_02.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_character_03.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>Munchies illustrations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Originally drawn by Canadian artist Richard Siu, the Munchies are a trio of goblins that were already fun and quirky to begin with and, while some updates have been made, I am glad they were not given a <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/dora_2_point_0.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dora-</a> or <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/a_sight_for_saur_eyes.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barney-esque</a> update to make them more “contemporary” (heavy on the air quotes). In fact, I would have loved to see an even more authentic redrawing keeping some of that extra fur and stubbier legs or, even more tempting, a de-evolution to a 1960s or 1970s cartoon aesthetic. Still, the new Munchies stay true to the old Munchies and retain their mischievous personality while adopting new behaviors like… turning into a cheese block.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_packaging_all.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>Packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_packaging_promo.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Website promo video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The packaging, unfortunately, is not that great as it looks like a completely different design team was given the logo and illustrations and proceeded to take the brand in a whole other direction with the old-time-y serif, the ribbon device, and the foil-esque border. I think they were trying to be deadpan retro with it but missed the mark as they didn&#8217;t take it far enough and they should have probably just adhered to the visual language on their website (and the promo above) where National 2 is more prominent and more in tune with the illustrations. Colors are nice though.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_activation_canoe.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>Brand activation at Canoe Landing Park.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_advertising_living_room_06.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>To create an experience unique to the Munchies, in Toronto, consumers are also invited to travel through a simpler time machine and relive the charm of the good old days at The Living Room – an immersive experience that fuses the joy of the simpler times and the wonder of the future in one room- opening later this month.<br /><br />From September 17th – 21st guests who visit The Living Room at 253 Queen St West, Toronto will have the opportunity to travel back and forward through time as they take a walk down memory lane (through a speakeasy-like doorway) with notable memorabilia, and of course, plenty of Munchies snacks.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/the-iconic-munchies-make-their-magical-return-to-canada-20-years-later-854090053.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PepsiCo press release</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_activation_living_room_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_activation_living_room_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_activation_living_room_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_activation_living_room_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_activation_living_room_06.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>The Living Room experience.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/munchies_advertising_living_room_grid.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Munchies by Vocabulary" />
<figcaption>More Living Room images.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>With what looks like a very healthy budget, Munchies launched an ambitious pop-up in Toronto with a lot of custom signage and props as well as some fun-looking merch. It&#8217;s hard to tell exactly what decade vibe they are going for but my guess is that, as they try to appeal to a Gen Z/ millennial audience, they are just throwing ALL of the decades at them in the hope that one sticks. To their credit, as a Gen X’er, this does hit some nostalgic notes that are not out of pocket.</p>

<figure class="full">
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DAGsSIWuFMu/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:540px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DAGsSIWuFMu/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;">View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div></div></a><p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DAGsSIWuFMu/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A post shared by nat doumkos (@natdoumkos)</a></p></div></blockquote>
<script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"></script>
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DAEfSY_y4au/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:540px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DAEfSY_y4au/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;">View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div></div></a><p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DAEfSY_y4au/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A post shared by Munchies Canada (@munchiescanada)</a></p></div></blockquote>
<script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"></script>
<figcaption>And a couple of Reels about it.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">Overall, this is a fun product with a fun origin story and a fun introduction effort. At a time where niche consumer products and DTC brands are sprouting everywhere with sophisticated and sometimes esoteric designs — see every brand covered on <a href="https://www.snaxshot.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Snaxshot</a> — it&#8217;s almost a welcome change to see something more mainstream done with conviction (and budget) to appeal to a broader audience with more simple, wholesome, and tried-and-true design approaches and marketing ploys.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_munchies_by_vocabulary.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_munchies_by_vocabulary.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 08:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for VTM</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/vtm_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for VTM" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://communicatie.vtm.be/vtm-nieuws-gaat-complex-nieuws-nog-beter-uitleggen-met-een-nieuw-gezicht-en-toptechnologie">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_vtm.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_vtm.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>