<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for reMarkable</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/remarkable_2024_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for reMarkable" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://remarkable.com/blog/remarkable-unveils-remarkable-paper-pro">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_remarkable.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_remarkable.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: El Office Space</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/nice_duolingo_ny_office.jpg" alt="El Office Space" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/91183352/duolingo-office-nyc-employees-choices-about-how-they-want-to-work">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Headquartered in Pittsburgh, PA, Duolingo recently opened a new office in New York, designed by <a href="https://raptstudio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rapt Studio</a> and not only does it look <em>fabuloso</em> but it also signals a new era for workspaces as they try to lure a whole new workforce generation back to the office.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/el_office_space.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/el_office_space.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 09:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Go Out in a Glaze of Glory”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/drumroll_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2019, previously GreenHouse Foods) <a href="https://eatdrumroll.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Drumroll</a> makes plant-based, mini donuts. “Our snacks are rooted in fun and backed by nutrition. We started off by creating donuts that are delicious, plant-based, low sugar, and high protein without sacrificing taste or texture. Our snacks are gluten-free and keto-friendly, offering a healthy, convenient snack perfect for everyone: on-the-go families, health-conscious individuals, vegans, diabetics, those with celiac, truly anyone can enjoy the healthy indulgent treats we&#8217;ve dreamed up.”</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.takeagander.com/" target="_blank">Gander</a> (Brooklyn, NY)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.takeagander.com/project/drumroll" target="_blank">Gander project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>We created packaging that is first and foremost, delicious and eye-catching. Our silky-smooth wordmark emulates the ewwy gooey chocolate dripping from the donuts. At the center of the brand system, we developed an energetic window based on the hole of the donut. Through this slanted oval, you enter the world of Drumroll which encourages you to enjoy the moment.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-297700"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_logo.png" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_packaging_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Packaging, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_packaging_01.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_packaging_02.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Packaging, straight up.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_packaging_hero_01.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_packaging_hero_02.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_packaging_hero_03.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Packaging, hyped up.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_oval.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_advertising.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_instagram_stories.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Instagram stories.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_photography_01.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_photography_02.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/drumroll_photography_03.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Drumroll by Gander" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old name and logo were a really odd combination… “Green House” is the least appetizing name for something as delicious as tiny glazed donuts and then the logo had a palm tree embedded in the “O”, which for some reason triggered the idea of a sun-tanning salon in Los Angeles. The new name is fun although, also like Green House before it, a bit odd and incongruent but the logo makes up for any lack of association with an extra tasty, chunky, and gooey wordmark with some unconventional letterforms. Today (as with two of the <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_507.php" target="_blank">Friday Likes</a> selections) it's really all about those “R”s… I love how funky they are. I'm not sure about the tilted axis in the “O” that yields an oval (that is then used in the identity) given that ovals aren't the immediate shape that comes to mind when you think “donuts” and they already had a good thing going with the circular counterspaces in the other letters. At least, I wish the axis in the “O” were a better match for the angle of the leg of the “R”. Still, super fun logo.<span></span> The old packaging was pretty decent… I mean, it was nothing special but it had a vibrant color combo and the sprinkle pattern in the background looked good. The new packaging is nice too but perhaps a little too straightforward. The glaze on the donuts looks so good though and I can not begin to tell you how much I want one of these based on the product picture alone. On the boxes, the giant single donut with type orbiting around it is quite fun. For the other applications and the photography, things go in multiple directions and it's hard to tell what the identity actually is. <a href="https://www.instagram.com/drumrolldonuts/" target="_blank">On their Instagram account</a> there are also some applications that look like 1980s print ads (and a little bit like <a href="https://www.instagram.com/vacationinc/" target="_blank">Vacation</a>) with the condensed serif, dense paragraphs, and grainy photography. The latter being all over the place too and it's hard to tell if they are being ironic or joke-y or dead serious — given the young audience depicted in the photos I am guessing they are going for that TikTok absurdity approach. Overall, it's maybe one too many things going on but it's all certainly effusive and the donuts look tasty so you can probably wrap them in any kind of design approach and they would still look craveable.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_identity_and_packaging_for_drumroll_by_gander.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_identity_and_packaging_for_drumroll_by_gander.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 09:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 507: From Untitled Macao, Studio Mast, and Lobster Phone</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Untitled Macao, Studio Mast, and Lobster Phone”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/friday_likes_507.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 507" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Back from our August hiatus with a range of geometrically-infused typography, with work from Macau, Denver, and San Francisco.</p>
<span id="more-297697"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">BOOKED 2023 by Untitled Macao</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_booked2023.jpg" alt="BOOKED 2023" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;">Now in its fifth edition, <a href="https://www.taikwun.hk/booked2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BOOKED</a>  is an art book fair in Hong Kong that welcomes local, regional, and international exhibitors (publishers, artists, booksellers, and organizations) to <a href="https://www.taikwun.hk/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tai Kwun</a>, a former police station compound turned center for heritage and arts. The identity, designed by Macau-based <a href="https://untitledmacao.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Untitled Macao</a>, takes a superbly lo-fi approach with a cast of characters that look like they&#8217;ve been drawn with the least amount of effort in Microsoft Paint in the year 1992. Genderless and feature-less, the humans are depicted with sticks for limbs and torso, ovals for hands and feet, and a combination of shapes for heads, some of them hilariously filled in with a transparent Photoshop background. These are surrounded by equally crude objects and environments in a jarring CMYK color palette (with bonus lime green and orange). To add to the frenetic energy, the typography is awkwardly geometric, typeset super tightly, and overlapped with strokes. It&#8217;s crazy and ugly and I love it. Bonus points <a href="https://untitledmacao.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/%E8%9E%A2%E5%B9%95%E6%88%AA%E5%9C%96-2024-06-14-%E4%B8%8A%E5%8D%8811.40.01.png" target="_blank" rel="noopener">for the clever die-cut badge</a> that looks like a book.  <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://untitledmacao.com/booked-hong-kong-art-book-fair/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Osteria Alberico by Studio Mast</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_alberico.jpg" alt="Osteria Alberico by Studio Mast" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.osteriaalberico.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Osteria Alberico</a> is an Italian osteria in Englewood, CO, near Denver, serving simple, traditional dishes that highlight local and seasonal ingredients and, of course, wine. The identity, designed by Denver-based <a href="https://www.studiomast.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Studio Mast</a>, brings vintage shop signs, restaurant facades, and street signage all the way from Italy to Colorado with a lovely typographic approach that begins with an elegant yet playful Art Deco wordmark with geometric curves in all the right places and in just the right span of circumferences. Those “R”s! The wordmark looks great filled in or stroked and the stroke variation informs a series of stroke-based illustrations and patterns. My favorite element from the identity, though, is the “OA” monogram constructed from the repetition of the name in tiny, spaced out type. The color palette is quite nice too, employing only white, black, a deep tan hue, and a warm gray that are inspired by &#8220;Italy’s architectural heritage, resulting in a curated selection of hues inspired by the ubiquitous stucco and natural stone that define Italian cityscapes&#8221;. They had me at Osteria. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.studiomast.co/projects/osteria-alberico/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Dear Francis by Lobster Phone</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_dearfrancis.jpg" alt="Dear Francis by Lobster Phone" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://dearfranciscoffee.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dear Francis</a> is a coffee roaster in Portland, OR, that sources and roasts coffees from around the world to sell online direct to consumer and in a few pop-ups around town. The identity, designed by San Francisco, CA-based <a href="https://lobsterphone.com/dear-francis" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lobster Phone</a>, goes for a contemporary-ish Art Deco vibe with a multi-color wordmark where simple, geometric shapes assemble and overlap to form the name. Like Alberico above: Those “R”s! And like Alberico too, this wordmark works in full color, filled in as well as in a single-color, stroked version for more economical uses. The small “DEAR” type might be the only odd thing as it doesn&#8217;t feel as well integrated and given that they did create a geometric version of “DEAR”, I&#8217;m surprised they didn&#8217;t got with that as the primary logo. I really like the tumbled versions where “FRANCIS” is rearranged in fun ways but I equally dig the pattern approach and the merch is pretty sweet. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://lobsterphone.com/dear-francis" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_507.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_507.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 09:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Durmart by Gent Osmani</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/durmart_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Durmart by Gent Osmani" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/205456707/Durmart">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_durmart_by_gent_osmani.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_durmart_by_gent_osmani.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Colossal by Firebelly</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/colossal_2024_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Colossal by Firebelly" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.thisiscolossal.com/2024/09/welcome-to-the-new-colossal/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_colossal_by_firebelly.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_colossal_by_firebelly.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Science the S**t out of Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/interesting_science_branding.jpg" alt="Science the S**t out of Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://uxdesign.cc/how-to-brand-science-97f6adb982dc">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Louis Charron, a Brooklyn, NY-based designer that specializes in design for scientists and scientific organizations, breaks down “How to brand science?” in a thoughtful and engaging piece that explores “how science presents itself to the world, and how branding can convey complex, abstract ideas.”
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/science_the_st_out_of_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/science_the_st_out_of_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for Inter&#038;Co by Polar and Plau</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“It’s in Your Best Inter-est”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/inter_co_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2005) &#8220;<a href="https://us.inter.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Inter&amp;Co</a> is a Brazil-based company that developed a global payments platform combining a fully digital backbone with integration with other payments platforms. The Company&#8217;s objective is to operate as a digital multi-service bank for individuals and companies, and among its main activities are real estate loans, payroll credit, credit for companies, rural loans, credit card operations, checking account, investments, insurance services, as well as a marketplace of non-financial services provided by means of its subsidiaries. The Company helps their customers to manage their money, providing a complete digital checking account where the Group can deliver a broad range of financial solutions through the Super App. Through the Super App, Inter &amp; Co Inc&#8217;s clients can shop on-line in a high variety of stores, as well as purchase, for example a plane ticket and book hotels. The company is rapidly expanding, with evidence of continuous progress by sponsoring, and providing the naming rights for a Major League Soccer (MLS) team; now the Inter&amp;Co Stadium in Orlando, FL. Furthermore, it has a growing user base in every state in America.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            Project lead: <a href="https://polar.ltda/" target="_blank">Polar</a><br />Logo and type family: <a href="https://plau.design/" target="_blank">Plau</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/201535143/Inter-Co-Type-System" target="_blank">Plau project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>The international version of the name, Inter &amp; Co., played a crucial role in the typeface creation, as the ampersand was significant both semantically—symbolizing partnership and unity—and graphically. The logo inspired the font, as often happens in brand revision projects. Citrina is the new custom font for Inter. Designed to pair with the bank's namesake font, Inter, the structure of the letterforms is influenced by the geometry of classic fonts like Futura, enriched with art-deco details. It features a generous x-height and striking proportional differences between rounded letters like “o,” “c,” and “e” compared to others (see letter “s”).<br /><br />The typeface has two axes of variation: weight and optical size. For smaller sizes, users can adjust the spacing between letters in addition to the weight. The variable web version helps the development team in maintaining a leaner, more economical design system, reducing the load of multiple files and server requests.​​​​​​​<br /><br />​​​​​​​The new symbol, logo, and typography, combined with a cohesive verbal, visual, and motion language, form the most critical brand assets for the company's new phase. Working in a coordinated manner, these elements differentiate the brand from competitors, reinforce the company as the pioneer it has always been, and pave the way for success in the highly competitive American market.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-297661"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_logo_full.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<figcaption>Logo with “&amp;Co”.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_logo_refinements.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo refinements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_custom_type_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_custom_type_02.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_custom_type_03.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_custom_type_04.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Custom type family.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_visual_language_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_visual_language_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_visual_language_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<figcaption>Visual language.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_3d_graphics_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_3d_graphics_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<figcaption>3D graphics.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_instagram_posts.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_instagram_stories.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram stories.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/inter_co_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Inter&amp;Co by Polar and Plau" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo was generic and mostly inoffensive but even at only five letters they managed to make it look like each one came from a different type family. The new logo introduces an icon that seems very unnecessary as it doesn't add much meaning nor is it particularly interesting but I can see how the client, as a financial institution, maybe wanted something HSBC- or Chase-esque to have as a standalone icon. I guess it could be interpreted as a sun so it's somewhat optimistic. I said the icon feels unnecessary because the new wordmark is so good and being such a small name, it can easily work at small sizes and still remain impactful. Perhaps not so much when “&amp; co” is added, which I am not exactly sure how that extra piece of nomenclature makes good business or strategic sense as both logos and names exist in different contexts and mostly create confusion without clear differentiation of which one serves what purpose.<span></span> Back to the design, though, I love the construction of “inter” and the way the joints of the “n” and “r” are resolved. The “t” is so perfect too. I initially thought the “e” was way too round but it does work quite well to keep the “t” mostly centered. I'm not a big fan of the ampersand or the “co” part as all three glyphs look like they belong somewhere else. The custom type family is excellent, especially in the Medium and Bold weights that echo the wordmark. It's as if <a href="https://nuformtype.com/ozik" target="_blank">Ozik</a> and <a href="https://www.myfonts.com/collections/skia-cc-font-carter-and-cone-type" target="_blank">Skia</a> had a sophisticated, corporate baby.<span></span> Not much in application but what's there is mostly pleasant with the orange and brown hues although there are some unrelated sparks of pastels. There are some fun, translucent 3D graphics and a bevy of holding shapes, both of which seem tangentially related to the logo but not quite. Overall, a simple and unassuming identity for a financial institution with two strong elements in the wordmark and type family but perhaps one too many odd accoutrements to support them. </p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_interco_by_polar_and_plau.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_interco_by_polar_and_plau.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“You Take That Back”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/backslash_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 2016, <a href="https://www.backslash.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Backslash</a> (formerly &#8220;\Art&#8221; pronounced &#8220;backslash art&#8221;) is an art and technology organization and art residency that “funds artists whose practices are nonlinear, unconventional, unexpected, adventurous, intense, surprising, questionable, and primed for engagement with new technologies”. Part of and housed at <a href="https://tech.cornell.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cornell Tech</a> — a digital-age, technology-forward graduate campus of Cornell University in New York, NY — Backslash brings together students, faculty, and artists, both on and off campus, providing grants for works of art and technology that are uniquely unconventional. Along with the revised name, Backslash introduced a new identity this week designed by New York-based <a href="https://cotton.design/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cotton Design</a>.</p>

<span id="more-297654"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>Backslash (“\”)—not to be confused with forward slash (“/”)—is known as an escape character in computer programming, indicating that the characters after the “\” should be interpreted outside the normal mode of input and output to do something special. Formerly known as “\Art,” the old name raised a lot of questions around pronunciation and felt restrictive as Backslash extends beyond just Art. The decision to rebrand as Backslash reflects a clearer focus on pushing boundaries and utilizing technology to transcend traditional approaches. The new name embodies the organization&#8217;s commitment to exploring new frontiers in creative and technological interventions, better aligning with its mission to innovate beyond conventional norms.<br /><br />Leaning into the Backslash, and what the organization deems as “backslash” (as an adjective meaning “nonlinear, unconventional, unexpected, adventurous, intense, surprising, questionable, and primed for engagement with new technologies”), the new identity is, quite literally, all backslashed.<br /><br />The Backslash wordmark is custom drawn with all the stems subtly forming backslashes. Similar to the hidden arrow in the FedEx logo, it is a delightful but subtle detail that becomes impossible to overlook once you notice it. The logo is based on a “backslashed” version of Werk Sans by Trulytype.</blockquote><h3>Cotton Design provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_logo_construction.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Logo construction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>I&#8217;m not sure if the old logo can be categorized as a logo given that it mostly existed only as <a href="https://backslashart.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a header on their old website</a> executed as ASCII art, cleverly extruding “\Art” through the simple combination of forward and backward slashes — fairly impressive to be honest. The new logo is more traditional (and about the only thing that will be “traditional” in this identity), with a simpler wordmark that pays off of the name by back-slanting (or reverse-italicizing) a regular sans serif — <a href="https://trulytype.com/typefaces/werk" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Werk Sans</a> by Trulytype — as well as subtly revealing all of the backslashes in the wordmark by separating the ascender stems of the “b”, “k”, and “h”. It&#8217;s kind of clever but something about the execution is a little off… I think the separating space is too narrow and the way the bowls of the “b” and “h” are sliced is too straightforward. I would have also, myself, considered slicing the “a”s too to give the wordmark even more rhythm. Nonetheless, it&#8217;s an intriguing logo that sets the tone for the rest of the back-slanted identity.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_sans_01.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_sans_02.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_sans_03a.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_sans_03b.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Custom, backslanted version of Werk Sans by Trulytype.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Starting off modestly with the unconventional bent of the identity, the first ingredient is a relatively simple back-slanting of Werk Sans, which could have probably been more than enough to establish both a distinguishing identity and signal that this organization is anything but traditional. The samples above challenge readability but are still manageable and once you get used to the angle it&#8217;s surprising how “easy” it is to read. At tiny sizes like above right, the typesetting would benefit from a slightly bolder weight and looser tracking.</p>

<blockquote>\Type is a unique, custom interactive display typeface that pushes the boundaries of traditional typography. Crafted exclusively from -21° backslashes, the typeface offers a wacky, unconventional aesthetic that’s unlike anything seen before. It comes in four weights and two distinct styles: square and round. Several characters feature multiple glyphs, optimizing legibility and allowing for a versatile range of combinations. In digital applications, \Type becomes interactive, responding to user input by cycling through the weights, transitioning from less legible to more legible versions.<br /><br />The initial concept for \Type involved only one weight, built entirely from backslashes. This limitation delightfully resulted in several characters sharing the same glyph; for example, the lowercase “u,” “n,” and “o” are all represented by two evenly spaced backslashes that meet at the x-height. Surprisingly, even with these constraints, the words remained fully legible due to the context provided by the surrounding letters.<br /><br />The decision to expand \Type into additional weights came after discussions with the Backslash board. While the original weight was deemed essential to Backslash’s identity, the additional weights were introduced to enhance legibility in contexts where clarity is paramount. This expansion ensures that \Type remains functional and versatile across various applications, while still retaining its distinctive and experimental character.</blockquote><h3>Cotton Design provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_01.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Custom typeface, “\Type”.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_02.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_03.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_04.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_05.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_06.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_07.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:62.5%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_08.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Various samples of \Type.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_custom_type_funky_generator.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>\Type generator. You can take it for a spin <a href="https://www.backslash.org/type" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Now, if you really want to be challenged, the identity employs a headline typeface that is drastically abstracted and back-slanted and at its most minimal expression — “Base 2 Slash” — it can become a true test of your patience and tolerance for design-y-ness as it does become nearly unreadable, especially when many of the letters are the exact same shape, like “n, o, u, v” or “c, e”. Like a pixel font, this one gets more readable as more backslash units are used to define the letterforms so by the time you get to “Base 5 Slash”, things get so much easier to read after you&#8217;ve been through the gauntlet of Base 1 through Base 3. As an accessibility and readability exercise this is a nightmare but both Cotton Design and Backslash are 100% committed to it, which is somewhat commendable and the website fully employs this typeface with zero backslash-fucks to give on whether you can read it or not.</p>

<blockquote>As part of the brand identity, an infinite pattern generator was developed, creating weaving-inspired patterns composed solely of backslashes. While the patterns are generated through code, they are crafted to resemble hand-drawn weaves, blending technical precision with artistic flair. This generator not only reflects the technological foundation of Backslash but also pays homage to the artistry that defines the brand.</blockquote><h3>Cotton Design provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns_01.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns_02.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns_03.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns_04.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns_05.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_patterns_06.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Patterns.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>For good measure, the identity throws in some random patterns that make you wonder if there are any words in them given that they are no more or less readable than Base 2 Slash. If you are into conspiracy theories you could theorize that the Coastal Elite Liberals are using these patterns to send hidden messages to advance the Democratic agenda. Sorry, not sure where that came from. Election year I guess.</p>

<blockquote>Along with the brand identity, Cotton designed and developed a new website for Backslash. The website is designed to resemble a museum exhibition wall; given the expressive nature of the typeface and brand elements, the design emphasizes whitespace, vertical layouts, and precise grids to create a balanced and visually engaging experience. The website also features a distinctive diagonal scroll in some sections, set at the signature -21° angle, reinforcing the brand’s unique identity. Additionally, the site includes a few hidden easter eggs: clicking on the “\” character triggers the motion pattern generator, expanding it to fill the entire screen—offering users a true “escape” moment, in line with the spirit of the brand.<br /><br />The website is structured such that it is impossible to visit the website without first viewing one of the artists or artworks. When the Backslash team first approached us, they said “The artists and their work need to come first.” They also said “we don’t care if it’s a little off-putting.”</blockquote><h3>Cotton Design provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_pages_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_pages_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_pages_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_pages_04.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_pages_05.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Various website pages.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_scroll_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_scroll_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_website_scroll_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Diagonal scroll. You can experience that on <a href="https://www.backslash.org/exhibitions" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this page</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>As mentioned, the website does not shy away from the headline font and it&#8217;s the first thing you see when you visit it. Not only that but the home page has no traditional menu or navigation so you get there and you might have no idea what it says and then you have no idea what to do, so you click and then are taken to an artist&#8217;s page and then — but only if you are patient and curious — you discover that the small slash at the bottom left of the page reveals the menu. It&#8217;s all a bit too much but I respect them for doubling, tripling, and quadrupling down on the backslash mindset, down to the diagonal scrolling on some of the pages. One pretty cool feature on the headlines is that when you roll over them, the text cycles through the different Bases of the typeface and then resets back to the most minimal version so they do provide some “accessibility” features to aid readability.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_instagram_posts_a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_instagram_posts_b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_avatars.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Social media avatars.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>In addition to a suite of “Backslash” icons for favicons and profile images on social media, a custom set of colorful and expressive icons were created for the Discord community. These icons allow users to express themselves through the Backslash, with designs ranging from simple color variations to more playful and fun expressions, such as starry themes or pink, cutesy motifs.</blockquote><h3>Cotton Design provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_discord_reactions_a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="video-container"style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%" ><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_discord_reactions_b.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
<figcaption>Discord reactions.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_folder.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Folder.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_composition_books.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Composition books.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_advertising_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_flyer.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Flyer.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_wayfinding.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Wayfinding.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_exhibition.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Exhibit graphics.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The rest of the applications all have a New York-contemporary-art-gallery vibe to them, which is fine and appropriate but when it&#8217;s just type and no imagery, the back-slanted-ness of the layouts is almost overbearing, which makes me think that this would benefit from some kind of design contrast to offset all the minus-21-degree angles when there is no imagery to provide 90-degree normalcy.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_tshirt.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_tote_bag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_hoodie.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_cap.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Swag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_stickers_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/backslash_stickers_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Backslash by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Stickers.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">Overall, this is most definitely unconventional and possibly infuriating to some but as far as honoring the organization&#8217;s MO — which is celebrating and supporting art that is “nonlinear, unconventional, unexpected, adventurous, intense, surprising, questionable” — this is unequivocally successful.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_backslash_by_cotton_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_backslash_by_cotton_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Announced: 2024 BNConf: In-person Registration Deadline Looming</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“And 10 Volunteers Needed!”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/2024_08_31_In_person_Registration_Ending_Soon_BN.jpg" alt="2024 BNConf: In-person Registration Deadline Looming" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>With Summer (un)officially over, the deadline for in-person registration to the 2024 Brand New Conference is looming: Friday, September 27, will be the last day to <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnewconference/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">register</a>.</p>

<p><strong>ALSO!</strong> We are looking for 10 volunteers to add to the 20 signed up and confirmed. More info <a href="https://underconsideration.com/brandnewconference/volunteers.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a> and sign-up form <a href="https://forms.gle/rz9DAqsfuVab9yNv6" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/2024_brand_new_conference_in_person_registration_deadline_looming.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/2024_brand_new_conference_in_person_registration_deadline_looming.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>