<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Catch Me If You Scan”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Microsoft_Security_New_02.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Founded in 1975 by Bill Gates and Paul Allen <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> are&#8230; OK we all know who Microsoft are, they don&#8217;t need an introduction. Microsoft Security, however, might do. Described as &#8220;a suite of tools designed to protect users and organizations from the ever-evolving landscape of cyber threats&#8221;, it is basically the unified brand encompassing the entirety of Microsoft&#8217;s security services across its organisation. This is in part due to Microsoft&#8217;s <a href ="https://www.theverge.com/2024/9/23/24251945/microsoft-security-report-secure-future-initiative">2023 Secure Future Initiative (SFI)</a>: a multi-year effort aiming to revolutionise the way they design, build, test, and operate their products and services, with a focus on achieving the highest security standards. So yeah, all things security and Microsoft in one place and a marker in the ground that they take cyber-threats dead seriously. Microsoft secured the services of <a href="https://koto.studio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Koto</a> to help give their security offering a brand new identity.

<span id="more-308317"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>
This rebrand aims to highlight Microsoft Security’s competitive edge by showcasing its fully comprehensive approach to protection, in a time when cybersecurity is more critical than ever. Moving away from outdated cybersecurity symbols like padlocks, shields, and dark, intimidating colors, the new identity deliberately avoids these design tropes to signal a much more proactive, holistic, and human approach to security. This updated look flows across all marketing, digital, and motion touchpoints, ensuring a consistent and engaging experience.
</blockquote>
<h3>Koto&#8217;s press release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Logo.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />
<figcaption>Microsoft Security logo – NOT done by Koto (as far as I can tell).</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Why show a logo that Koto didn&#8217;t create? Well, to simply remind us that for the most part Microsoft are not a <em>cool</em> company. Iconic, yes. But not cool. That logo is as corporate as they come and I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if people shuddered at the sight of it in anticipation of another experience with a Microsoft product. I think it&#8217;s fair to say Microsoft are often viewed as a bit of a tech relic; the ones that happen to get there first and not the ones taking us forward, at least in an exciting way. However, they have slowly been making in-roads into a cooler space; Koto&#8217;s other work for them (<a href="https://koto.studio/work/copilotpc/">here</a> and <a href="https://koto.studio/work/microsoft-reimagine-action/">here</a>) proves that. And let me tell you, this logo, and all the Microsoft brand equity heft it comes with, does not reflect the quality and craft of the work you&#8217;re about to see.</p>

<blockquote>
Microsoft Security leads the way in digital protection with a comprehensive suite of solutions—ranging from Security, Compliance, and Identity Management to Privacy—designed to protect organizations against an ever-evolving range of cyber threats. Powered by advanced AI and deep threat intelligence, Microsoft secures everything from cloud platforms to endpoints and identities. Their solutions combine predictive threat detection with automated responses, ensuring robust defenses in an increasingly complex digital landscape.
<br><br>
&#8220;Beyond the surface&#8221; embodies a brand strategy rooted in comprehensive protection. Hidden dangers, emerging threats, and activity lurking beneath the surface—Microsoft Security spots it all, ensuring users stay secure. The design system is inspired by the concept of scanning, bringing hidden threats into focus and illuminating the unseen, making the world of security more visible, powerful and accessible.

</blockquote>
<h3>Koto&#8217;s press release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Brand_Idea.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />
<figcaption>Identity concept.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Hero_Laptop.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Scanning visual language.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Logo_Scan.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo scan.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:60%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Scanning.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo scan detail.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 75%; background-color: black;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Logo_Symbol_Scan.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Scanning symbol.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 75%; background-color: black;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MIcrosoft_Security_Product_Scan.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Product imagery scan.</figcaption>
</figure>



<p>As mentioned above, there&#8217;s no old or really new logo to judge here, so we&#8217;ll jump straight in to the visual concept Koto have hinged the identity on. It revolves around the idea of &#8220;look closer&#8221; and is expressed in these awesome x-ray-style heat maps that gently scan across the logo, products, and typography. It is such a simple yet brilliant idea that goes straight to the heart of what Microsoft are trying to convey but done with such slickness and finesse. I love the gentle animation that slides across areas, really reflecting a sense of care and diligence. I love how it&#8217;s not one, big, full-bleed scan but a distinctive bar that goes across; it feels purposeful and focused. I love how the areas highlighted by the scanning mechanic glow and almost burn at the borders, reflecting light bleeding off the edges as the heat-map style gradients shift and move with the scanning bar. I love how the gradient colours nod to the core four colours of the Microsoft logo too, it&#8217;s a smart way to bring it all back to the master brand.</p>

<p>When you have a simple idea tying everything together craft is so important, and you can really sense the work that&#8217;s been put into these animations. They&#8217;re just so satisfying to watch and I found myself staring at them again and again as I wrote this review. With these types of projects, where you&#8217;re lugged with a master brand that perhaps isn&#8217;t the most exciting, there&#8217;s always a challenge in how you build on top of it in an creative way without losing its core essence. I think Koto have nailed that here with a conceptual lid that is slickly executed and captures the core essence of the product.</p>

<blockquote>
Color plays a core role in Microsoft Security’s design, bringing scanned worlds to life. A set of five pre-designed gradient maps offers vibrant color treatments that adapt to various brand displays, infusing each asset with distinct energy and meaning. Leveraging the growing number of people using dark mode, the brand transitions seamlessly between dark and light modes, with backgrounds in either white or navy to maintain a consistent and approachable look.
<br><br>
The scan mechanic introduces a dynamic flow to the typography. As the scan interacts with the text, it subtly reveals words and highlights key messages, adding depth and reinforcing the sense of comprehensiveness, tying it together with the design system. At the edges of the scan, the text adapts smoothly, blending with the background while preserving clarity.
</blockquote>
<h3>Koto&#8217;s press release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Gradients.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Gradients.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Logo_Symbol_Gradients.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Gradient in Microsoft&#8217;s &#8220;window&#8221; symbol.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 75%; background-color: black;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Messaging_Scan.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 75%; background-color: black;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Icons.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Iconography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Design_System.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Visual system.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>Part of the identity package are a series of gradients, a typeface with a similar scanning treatment, icons, and a paired back design system. Similar to the scanning animations, it&#8217;s a tactical, albeit rather obvious, choice to use the colours from the Windows logo as the base for the gradients, which serve as a secondary element to help link back to the visual style of the hero animations. I&#8217;m not entirely sure if the font is a new one or not, but either way it&#8217;s a perfectly fine, safe, techy sans serif and I probably wouldn&#8217;t even tell the difference between this and Microsoft&#8217;s own font if they were different. There is also a few snippets of photography shown here and <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/security">on Microsoft Security&#8217;s website</a>. They&#8217;re OK, fairly product focused, clean and inoffensive, but doesn&#8217;t really capture a unique sense of humanity and is greatly elevated by the visual treatment on top of it.</p>

<p>The design system is where we really start to feel the Microsft-ness of it all. I like how we have a third expression for the gradients; as soft glows that help frame modules. It&#8217;s all very controlled and paired back and if it wasn&#8217;t for the gradients running through them they would probably be a bit boring, but at a low level they work well and feel at home within Microsoft&#8217;s UI ecosystem.</p>

<blockquote>
The scanning mechanic enhances digital experiences, introducing an interactive and engaging element that adapts to even the smallest details. It adds sophistication to data visualizations, infographics, and other UI elements, transforming routine interactions into something more dynamic and memorable.
<br><br>
This identity extends seamlessly into physical spaces, filling real-world environments with light, energy, and vibrancy. The scanning visual translates effortlessly into spatial design, carrying the same sense of energy and connection from the digital world to in-person experiences.
</blockquote>
<h3>Koto&#8217;s press release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 75%; background-color: black;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Chart_Animated.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>

<hr/>

<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Chart_01.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />

<hr/>

<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Chart_02.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />
<figcaption>Charts and data.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 75%; background-color: black;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Module_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>

<hr/>

<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:60%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Module_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>

<hr/>

<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Button_Interaction.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>UI elements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Communication.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />
<figcaption>Photography and graphic system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Advertisement.jpg" alt="New identity for Microsoft Security by Koto" />
<figcaption>Bus shelter ad.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Microsoft_Security_Event_Screens.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Event screens.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>Not a huge amount in terms of applications. We have some charts and data that use the gradient language, some UI elements, and a very notional ad and event screen. All perfectly fine and on note for the identity. Everything I loved initially is what I still love here, but when it gets a bit too stark and corporate (like the bus shelter ad) it sucks the life from the idea a bit &#8211; almost like two separate entities. I can&#8217;t blame Koto for that, they have to work from a particular base here, but I can only imagine if this was for another company, and they had carte-blanche on execution, how much further they would take this great idea.</p>

<p class="end">That said, Koto have managed to take a corporate and stiff brand and added their inimitable touch on top of it; transforming it into something conceptually sound, extremely polished and visually stimulating. This is no mean feat, especially when you&#8217;re working with a corporate behemoth like Microsoft, so hats off to them. In the end, Koto didn’t <em>just</em> create a visual style to wrap this particular set of security services, no — they encrypted it with meaning, firewalled it with control and restraint, and ultimately gave Microsoft Security a visual identity worth protecting.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_microsoft_security_by_koto.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_microsoft_security_by_koto.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“They Made Your Bed, Now Now Lie In It”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/nownow_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>
<a href="https://www.staynownow.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Now Now</a> is a pod hotel from <a href="https://www.dovetailandco.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dovetail + Co</a>, a boutique hospitality collective with seven properties across the U.S. and Bermuda. Situated on the Bowery in Downtown Manhattan, Now Now was designed with the solo traveler in mind, offering compact, single-occupancy rooms with shared bathrooms and open ceilings. The space is located in a restored building originally developed as a lodging house in 1917 (read more about its history and most recent iteration  <a href="https://cromwell-intl.com/travel/usa/new-york-sro-flophouses/white-house-tour.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>) and redesigned by <a href="https://www.islynstudio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Islyn Studio</a>. New York, NY-based agency <a href="https://www.sainturbain.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Saint Urbain</a> developed a full brand identity for Now Now, including naming strategy, logo design, and advertising.
</p>
<span id="more-308143"></span>

<blockquote>
We began the design process with a single thought in mind: &#8220;We are not a destination; we&#8217;re part of the journey.&#8221; Viewing the hotel as a liminal space — an ephemeral point of connection, restoration, and a launching pad for everything NYC has to offer — we shaped an organic, almost otherworldly design direction. The blocky logo incorporates rounded motifs inspired by keyholes and portals, symbolizing gateways to new experiences. When combined with the unique gradient color palette, it evokes a nostalgic, almost Kubrick-esque aesthetic.
</blockquote>
<h3>Saint Urbain provided press release.</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:67%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_logo-gradient_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:67%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_logo-animation_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:67%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_logo-animation_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
Before diving into the review, I want to acknowledge that many of the images you&#8217;ll see feature the hotel&#8217;s interior design which is not being reviewed in this article. That said, it of course plays a crucial role in the overall brand identity, so I&#8217;ve included lots of shots. If you <em>did</em> want my opinion, it&#8217;s stunning and remarkably so for what is essentially a hostel. I&#8217;m not sure if I find it refreshing and exciting or a bit ironically dystopian that a beautifully designed yet reasonably priced hotel exists directly across the street from <a href="https://theboweryhotel.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a hotel</a> that costs a minimum of $600/night and is just down the street from the former location of the legendary music venue CBGB. It&#8217;s a paradox worth applauding and mourning. But, I digress; onto the identity design&#8230;</p> 

<p>
The logo is quite unconventional, bordering on illegible. But I personally value originality and creative flair over legibility, as long as it&#8217;s clear <em>enough</em>. But that value is not often shared with clients so kudos to Dovetail + Co for green-lighting such a bold choice. The letterforms are meant to evoke keyholes and portals, which I definitely buy, even if I originally interpreted it as literal pods of the hotel, with the counters and negative space symbolizing people sleeping in their little cabins. I also get musical notes and maybe even the Thai alphabet? (Or perhaps I finished White Lotus too recently.) Ultimately, any of these interpretations work to create an abstract, global vibe that is grounded in &#8220;everything NY has to offer.&#8221; Multiple interpretations work in its favor.
</p> 


<p>
Where the logo loses me (though just a bit, because I do really like it) is that I&#8217;m not totally convinced it fits the interior design&#8217;s art-deco-meets-Parisian-meets-Japanese vibes. The geometric blocks feel a bit harsh juxtaposed next to the many arches and curves throughout the space. I also find the shapes and lines formed within the letters by the counters and negative space awkwardly uneven, creating a visual imbalance from one letter to the next. (Also, side note, do you really want your hotel&#8217;s logo to evoke a &#8220;Kubrick-esque&#8221; vibe?!) But for its flaws, it certainly manages to capture the essence of the hotel&#8217;s purpose.</p> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_lobby_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_room_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_bathroom_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Hotel interior.</figcaption>
</figure>



<figure class="full">
	<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:66.66666667%">
		<video autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline="" controls="" controlslist="nodownload">
			<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_color-palette_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
		</video>
	</div>
	<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:66.6666666%">
		<video autoplay="" loop="" muted="" playsinline="" controls="" controlslist="nodownload">
			<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_iconography_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
		</video>
	</div>
<div class="clear">
</div>
<figcaption>Color palette and iconography.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:67%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_system_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>System.</figcaption>
</figure>


<blockquote>
Rather than settling on a single brand color, the team developed a broad and expressive palette designed to shift across contexts. From soft neutrals to saturated brights, each tone was chosen to reflect a specific emotional register, from grounded and introspective to energetic and strange. The signature gradient became a unifying element across digital and print, evoking atmosphere more than identity. The palette was also thoughtfully aligned with interior design renderings developed by ISLYN Studio to ensure harmony between the visual identity and physical space.
</blockquote>
<h3>Saint Urbain provided press release.</a></h3>

<p>
The color palette, with its bright, saturated jewel tones, feels like a neon digital reinterpretation of the colors from the interior design, which works really well in elevating the overall aesthetic. It brings a fresh, contemporary feel to the brand while still nodding to the more traditional elements of the space. The vibrant colors inject energy into the identity, aligning nicely with the hotel&#8217;s lively yet sophisticated objective. I&#8217;m not so sure about the gradient. It looks great animated under the logo but can get cheap in other applications, like the border around the check-in screens. It really needs to be used sparingly to maintain the polished feel when it works.
</p> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_keycard_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_keycard-combo_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Keycards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_swag-combo_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Sleep mask and sandals.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_door-sign_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Door hanger.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"  style="padding-bottom:66.666667%;background:black">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_advertising_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:67%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_social-media_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Social media.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
Supporting typography is led by Ginestra, a serif typeface that blends a confident editorial tone with subtle warmth. Originally inspired by 19th-century poster design, the typeface was created by Íñigo Jerez and the agency &#038;Rosàs in memory of Nacho Ginestra. With its condensed form and expressive details, it brings both clarity and character to the brand, while honoring a story rooted in creativity and legacy.
</blockquote>
<h3>Saint Urbain provided press release.</a></h3>

<p>
While  <a href="https://www.xavimauri.com/projects/ginestra-type" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ginestra</a> is a lovely, friendly sans serif that was supposedly inspired by 19th-century poster design, it feels a bit too contemporary for both the hotel design and logo. I appreciate the intention to tone down the weirdness of the logo with a cleaner typeface, but it sort of throws off the vibe. Its subtle quirks, like the sunken tittle on the “i” or the ascender on the lowercase “f”, add character but are maybe not quirky enough to fully complement the playfulness of the logo. The typeface feels like it&#8217;s overcompensating in its attempt to feel youthful, when perhaps a round curvy serif could have achieved a more harmonious balance. Paired with the color palette, it would still appeal to a younger crowd.
</p> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_lobby_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_lobby_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_lobby_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Lobby.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_hallway_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Hallway.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_cozy-room_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_cozy-room_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_cozy-room_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_deck-combo_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>&#8220;Cozy sleeper cabin&#8221; standard room.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_nownever-room_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_nownever-room_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_mural_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_murals_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>&#8220;Now or Never Sleepver Cabin&#8221; room with murals by local artists.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_bathroom_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_bathroom_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_bathroom-combo_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Shared bathroom.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_shared-space_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Shared space.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/nownow_outdoor-sign_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for NowNow by Saint Urbain" />
<figcaption>Outdoor signage.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">     
Overall, the identity captures a unique balance between modernity and elegance, but there are moments where the elements don&#8217;t quite gel. The logo is bold and original and, while I appreciate the intention behind some of the design choices, certain details feel a bit disconnected from the overall aesthetic. The color palette, though, works with the interior design to inject a youthful energy that ties it all together, ultimately crafting a memorable and impactful experience.
</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_nownow_by_saint_urbain.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_nownow_by_saint_urbain.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Announced: Limited Posts until June 23</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Early Summer Break”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/2025_06_01_Summer_Schedule_Wide.jpg" alt="Limited Posts until June 23" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>From here on until June 23rd, there will be limited posts on Brand New as me and my family go on an early Summer vacation. This week, there will only be posts in the Reviewed category, courtesy of our guest writers. Next week, we will be fully closed and there will be no posts. The week of June 16, it will be another Reviewed-only week and then back to normal on June 23.</p>

<p>Since you pay for content and you are not getting content for one week and only half the content for two weeks, those of you on our monthly plan will get a coupon code that can be applied for $0.75 off of your next monthly payment — team plan coupons will amount to 75% off. If you had no intention of renewing next month, email us and we&#8217;ll provide the $0.75 refund (or equivalent for team plans).</p>

<p>For those of you on our annual plan you will get a coupon code that can be applied for $0.50 off of your next annual payment — team plan coupons will amount to 2.5% off. (Annual subscribers who paid via PayPal… sorry, there is no easy way to implement this.)</p>

<p><strong>Code and instructions on how to apply it coming to you via email later today.</strong></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/limited_posts_until_june_23.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/limited_posts_until_june_23.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &#038; Arts Festival by Fiasco</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Britt Happens”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Britt_logo_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p><a href="https://britt.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Britt</a> is a nonprofit performing arts venue located in Jacksonville, Oregon, with a 60-year legacy of hosting world-class music and cultural programming in an intimate outdoor setting. From James Brown to Jurassic 5, BB King to Boy George &#038; Culture Club, the venue has welcomed a wide range of artists to its natural amphitheater nestled among the pines. In celebration of its history and in anticipation of its future, Britt recently underwent a full rebrand led by Bristol, UK-based creative agency <a href="https://fiasco.design/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco.</a> The new identity seeks to capture not just the experience of a live show, but the deep emotional resonance that comes with it: the feeling of connection, community, and place.</p>

<span id="more-308105"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_OLD_identity.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Sampling of OLD identity.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
To truly understand Britt, the Fiasco team headed to the Pacific Northwest to immerse themselves in the landscape, culture, and character of the place. 
<br /><br />
What emerged was the core challenge: not just to design a brand, but to bottle a feeling – the magic of a night under the stars, surrounded by 2,000 strangers who suddenly feel like friends.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://fiasco.design/work/britt-music-arts-festival/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_moodboard.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Moodboard.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_brand_idea.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Brand idea.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
At the heart of the new identity is a clear sense of place. Nestled in a natural amphitheatre among Oregon’s ponderosa pines, Britt’s unique environment is part of what makes it special. This relationship to the land formed the basis of a logo system inspired by native flora and a tradition of woodblock printing.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://fiasco.design/work/britt-music-arts-festival/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_NEW_logo.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_logomark_development.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logomark rationale and development.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_logo_on_video_backgrounds.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo on various backgrounds.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>There’s no way to sugarcoat it — the former Britt identity was, well… let&#8217;s just say… not good. At all. To its credit, the old logo made an <em>attempt</em> to abstractly reference a pine tree, but that conceptual nod was overshadowed by its execution, which landed squarely in clipart territory. The logotype, set in a tall, condensed sans serif, was paired with a casual, scribbly “music &#038; arts festival” modifier that looked like it was lifted from a preloaded font from a 1998 scrapbooking program. The result felt like three not-awesome design choices mashed together in a way that multiplied — not mitigated — their flaws. It had big “Shirley from the volunteer committee just discovered MS Paint” energy. And the surrounding visual identity was even more disjointed. Posters, signage, and web presence lacked cohesion, resulting in an aesthetic that was inconsistent at best, and at worst, directionless. For a venue with such a rich legacy, the branding fell spectacularly short.</p>

<p>The new logo, by contrast, is not just better by default, it’s <em>objectively</em> better. Credit to the Fiasco team for actually making the trip to Jacksonville, Oregon to absorb the place firsthand. Their immersion into the local landscape, character, and cultural fabric is clearly evident in the resulting design direction, which feels grounded and intentional from the jump. The moodboard is rich with regional cues, and the brand idea — “Strike a deeper chord” — hits with the kind of layered resonance you hope for in a rebrand like this.</p>

<p>Starting with the logomark, the woodcut-style illustration depicts the <em>Fritillaria gentneri,</em> a rare flower native to Jackson and Josephine Counties. It’s a detail that not only ties the venue to its geographic roots, but also lends a beautiful imperfection and humanity via the intentionally rough printmaking style. It feels handmade, natural, and warm — everything a good live music venue should be.</p>

<p>The logotype is equally considered. I can&#8217;t tell whether it’s a customized typeface or a fully bespoke build, but it lands with confidence. The letterforms strike a lovely balance between humanist elegance and historic charm, with subtle Art Nouveau nods — like the smaller upper bowl on the “B,” or the sweeping curve of the “R” that loops into a ligature with the “I.” It’s beautiful lettering. That said, as polished as each component is individually, the lockup does leave a bit of disconnect. The organic, woodcut-printed texture of the mark doesn’t quite harmonize with the smooth, clean logotype. So what&#8217;s the solution? Some additional imperfection in the logotype might have helped tie the two together. Alternatively, toning down the illustration would’ve meant dulling the spark that drives the wider identity system — so it’s a trade-off. All minor nitpicks aside, the new logo is an undeniably massive leap forward, and sets the tone for a brand that finally feels worthy of the music it represents.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:75%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_bento_box.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Visual identity overview.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
We developed a visual approach to photography that leans into the sensory experience of Britt – a place where light shifts, music moves, and time slows. A directional blur, grain, and atmospheric overlays hint at the swaying of bodies, golden-hour haze, and fleeting moments that linger in the mind. 
<br /><br />
These textures extend into illustration, with a library of hand-drawn elements inspired by local architecture, signage and craft. Layered into the identity, these weave in the town’s character in every little detail.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://fiasco.design/work/britt-music-arts-festival/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_illustrations_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_illustations_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_illustrations_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Illustrations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
Inspired by Jacksonville’s rich visual heritage – from weatherworn signage to archival prints – we selected a typeface that nods to the past while feeling fresh and accessible. Etna Condensed Extra Bold, with its tall woodblock style and characterful flicks, nods to the past while feeling fresh, accessible, and distinct.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://fiasco.design/work/britt-music-arts-festival/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_typography_01_inspiration.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Typography inspiration.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_typography_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_typography_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_typography_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_typography_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
The colour palette reflects Britt’s broad offering – from orchestral calm to festival vibrancy. Muted neutrals ground the system, while saturated accents and emotionally-driven gradients bring energy, warmth, and depth across every touchpoint.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://fiasco.design/work/britt-music-arts-festival/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_color_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_color_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Color and motion behaviors.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>If the logo is the opening act, the visual identity is the headliner — and this one brings the goods. Britt’s refreshed system leans hard into a woodcut illustration style that feels both place-specific and universally refreshing. In a design era still hung over from the tiny-heads-and-big-limbs sameness of Corporate Memphis, this hand-rendered approach is a welcome pivot. There’s texture, grit, and humanity, and it doesn’t just <em>look</em> like the Pacific Northwest — it <em>feels</em> like it. Whether used as heroes or smaller supporting icons, these carved visuals instantly ground the brand in something tactile and true.</p>

<p>Type choices are equally grounded and thoughtful. Headings are set in <a href="https://www.marksimonson.com/fonts/view/etna/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Etna Condensed,</a> a woodtype-inspired typeface by <a href="https://www.marksimonson.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Simonson</a> (who, coincidentally, designed the now-ubiquitous Proxima Nova) that hits the perfect note between historical and modern. Originally based on the quirky, Victorian Aetna styles of the 1800s, Etna has been updated with a full suite of weights, widths, and extras — from manicules (pointing hands) to stars to small caps — making it a Swiss Army knife of display typography, and a full-on typographic bow to Jacksonville’s heritage. Backing it up are two strong supporting players: <a href="https://kontour.com/typefaces/utile" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Utile Narrow</a> by <a href="https://kontour.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kontour</a> — a slightly flared humanist neo-grotesque sans with warmth and versatility — and <a href="https://playtype.com/typefaces/south-east/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">South East</a> by <a href="https://playtype.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Playtype,</a> which adds some personality with just enough quirk to keep things interesting. Combined, the trio creates a typographic rhythm that’s dynamic but cohesive. Headlines land with punch, body copy hums along, and the hierarchy always feels under control.</p>

<p>Color-wise, Britt’s system draws from its natural surroundings but doesn’t fall into the usual desaturated trap. A dark grayish navy and muted neutrals are juxtaposed with mid-contrast green and blue, and then topped off with some bright pops of orange, yellow, pink, and light blue. But the real showstoppers are the gradients: warm, saturated, emotionally rich blends of these core colors with a subtle grain texture that makes them feel sun-kissed and cinematic.</p>

<p>A few additional details — like woodcut-inspired dingbats, directional swooshes, and little pointing devices — act as visual riffs that carry the handmade theme across layouts without overplaying the motif. It’s a carefully tuned system: expressive but not chaotic, detailed but not overdone. Every piece feels like it belongs to the same setlist.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_OOH_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_OOH_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_wayfinding.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>OOH and wayfinding.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_keychains.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_Merch_T-shirt_alt.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_tote.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Swag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_schedule.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Program.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:62.5%;background:black">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_social_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_social_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<figcaption>Social.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The brand really starts to sing once it’s out in the wild. Across print, merch, signage, and social, the identity system holds together with an ease that suggests everything was built with real-world application in mind. The typographic layouts, in particular, feel grounded in a classic editorial sensibility — like leafing through a well-worn broadsheet from a century ago. There’s a steady, deliberate cadence to the composition: generous line spacing, solid column grids, thoughtful breaks. It all helps reinforce the heritage-inspired tone the identity is aiming for.</p>

<p>The OOH materials keep things simple but sharp, mixing photography, illustration, and type in clean, balanced layouts. The color gradients bring warmth, and the system’s graphic embellishments are used sparingly and smartly. That said, if there’s one area that leaves a bit on the table, it’s the copywriting. The headlines are serviceable, but for a brand centered on emotional connection — with a platform as strong as “Strike a deeper chord” — the language could’ve gone further. It’s not a miss, but it’s not quite a standing ovation either. A little more tonal swagger would’ve helped elevate the messaging to the same level as the visuals.</p>

<p>As for the swag and other peripheral applications, they do the job. The tote bag, tee, and hat all look on-brand, with identity elements applied cleanly and without fuss. The newspaper-style printed schedule is a particularly nice touch that reinforces the editorial theme. The only real head-scratcher is the set of keychains, which feel oddly off-brand. Given how much of the system leans into tactile craft and natural textures, these glossy plastic or enamel pieces just don’t carry the same handmade charm. Something in leather, wood, or etched metal would’ve better extended the identity’s material language.</p>

<blockquote>
Designed to reflect the intimacy and atmosphere of the live experience, the new website supports ticketing, artist discovery, membership growth, and storytelling in one cohesive platform.
<br /><br />
From the first scroll to final click, the site captures the warmth and spirit of the hill – translating Britt’s unique sense of place into a digital space that feels inviting, intuitive, and full of life.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://fiasco.design/work/britt-music-arts-festival/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fiasco case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_website_mobile_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Britt Music &amp; Arts Festival by Fiasco" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_website_mobile_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Website: mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_website_desktop_01_wireframe.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Britt_website_desktop_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Website: desktop.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The new website is where this identity truly finds its rhythm. It’s not just that every element — from type to illustration to color — is on display and used with deliberate care, it’s that they’re animated with just the right balance of subtlety and flair. Motion principles are thoughtfully applied, enhancing the visual experience without overwhelming it, and the inclusion of clever micro-interactions adds a tactile layer to the UX that feels both intuitive and inviting. It’s a rare example of a site that doesn’t just showcase a brand — it extends and amplifies it. The result is an experience that draws users in and keeps them exploring, swiping, and scrolling with a sense of emotional connection that’s hard to fake.</p>

<p class="end">Overall, while a few elements could benefit from a touch more refinement, those are minor quibbles in a rebrand that otherwise hits all the right notes. From its deep sense of place to its celebration of texture, tone, and history, the new Britt identity is a striking leap forward. It finally gives the venue the kind of visual soul its programming has long deserved — one rooted in community, creativity, and connection. And when all of that comes together harmoniously, it doesn’t just look right, it feels right.</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_britt_music_arts_festival_by_fiasco.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_britt_music_arts_festival_by_fiasco.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 02:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for M80 Rádio by DJ In-House</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/m80_radio_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for M80 Rádio by DJ In-House" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://marketeer.sapo.pt/m80-lanca-novo-rebrandind-da-marca-mais-vibrante-atual-e-digital/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_m80_radio_by_dj_in_house.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_m80_radio_by_dj_in_house.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Home is where the Brand is</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/interesting_house_logos.jpg" alt="Home is where the Brand is" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.housedigest.com/1869284/monograms-trend-home-logo-southern-living/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Does your home have its very own logo? If not, you are falling behind on a new trend where some homeowners are creating logos (along with corresponding stationery and other swag) for their house — a trend that perhaps began with Airbnb listings that, in an effort to attract more guests, gave their home a brand. (Sample images via <a href="https://www.southernliving.com/home-logos-trend-8737528" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>Southern Living</em></a>.)
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/home_is_where_the_brand_is.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/home_is_where_the_brand_is.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&#038;Eric</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“New Look, Who Dish?”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/little_dish_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2006) “<a href="https://www.littledish.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Little Dish</a> was founded on the belief that children deserve to eat nutritious, fresh food they&#8217;ll love, and that busy parents deserve a helping hand with mealtimes. That&#8217;s why we use wholesome ingredients, cooked as you would at home, to make truly delicious food for kids. Little Dish has been the pioneer of fresh food for kids for 20 years, and now has an award-winning range of healthy ready meals for children aged one to ten years old, available in supermarkets nationwide.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.derekanderic.co.uk/" target="_blank">Derek&amp;Eric</a> (London, UK)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.derekanderic.co.uk/project/littledish" target="_blank">Derek&amp;Eric project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>Our goal was to evolve the identity into a narratively driven design ecosystem – a welcoming and relatable draw for kids and a useful tool for parents. This world is formed around a new family of fantastical animals, each elevated with the ‘main character energy’ needed to grab attention and deliver engaging experiences, imbued with unique personality traits and playful props.<br /><br />The foundations of brand recognition and personality have been enhanced by the creation of a literal ‘Little Dish’ icon, carrying a shelf blocking purple brand colour and overflowing with reassuringly vibrant and healthy ingredients. Together, these elements form the basis of a visual identity ready to help families have happier, healthier mealtimes.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-308074"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_type_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Isolated typography, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:56.73758865248227%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_illustration_a.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_illustration_b.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_illustration_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Illustration.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_old.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Samples of old packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Packaging, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Sample packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_with_ingredients_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_with_ingredients_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_with_ingredients_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_with_ingredients_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_with_ingredients_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Packaging with illustrated ingredients.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_hero_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_hero_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_hero_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_packaging_hero_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Hero shots.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_advertising.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_website.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_kids_2up_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_kids_2up_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_kids_2up_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_kids_2up_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_kids_2up_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/little_dish_kids_2up_06.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Little Dish by Derek&amp;Eric" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Various kid-related things.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            I'm trying to understand the link of the speech bubble to the name of the brand in the old logo but I'm not sure if there is any relation or maybe I'm just missing something obvious. In any case, as a logo, it was fun and engaging with the circular speech bubble holding the wordmark and both sporting a rugged texture. The new logo maintains the typographic composition — which is quite nice as “little” nestles so perfectly within the ascenders — but cleans up the edges for a smoother finish and places the name within a dish filled with nutritious vegetables. The vegetables are important in this composition as it means that the container that “little dish” lives within is actually a big dish, so there is a nice subtle playfulness to it, aside from being a more relevant choice than a speech bubble.<span></span> The old packaging was arguably fine and perhaps validated the speech bubble as the animal illustration in each variety told you what the product was, which was a little disconcerting in its own right: “Hey, I'm a chicken, you are about to eat me!”. The illustrations were maybe a little old school, like from a classic children's book and the supporting type was maybe too child-like, which, I get it, it's a product for children so it makes sense but as a parent I might be a little turned off by its cliché-ness.<span></span> The new packaging replaces the edible animals with a new crew of animals people don't eat (or at least not regularly) as dinosaurs, elephants, polar bears, and turtles now roam on the packaging and interact with the logo (which cleverly updates the contents of the dish to reflect the ingredients). The supporting typography, <a href="https://www.sharptype.co/typefaces/doyle" target="_blank">Doyle</a> (also used in the logo), works so much better than the old hand-drawn look while providing a much more polished (yet still fun) presence. Overall, this has the right balance of child-like joy and wonder with the understanding that parents are the ones choosing it in the end so it still has to have some level of maturity and sophistication that is satisfyingly conveyed by all of the different elements at play here.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_little_dish_by_derekeric.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_little_dish_by_derekeric.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 537: From My Creative, Vault49, and Glasfurd &amp; Walker</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From My Creative, Vault49, and Glasfurd &amp; Walker”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/friday_likes_537.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 537" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>A trio of bottles of all shapes, sizes, and colors this week, with work from Carluke, New York, and Vancouver.</p>
<span id="more-308071"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">MilHòc by My Creative</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_milhoc.jpg" alt="MilHòc by My Creative" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/whiskymilhoc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MilHòc</a> — which translates as “Corn” in Gascon — is a French single-grain whisky distilled in the village of Peyrehorade in the Armagnac region in Southwester, France, where Armagnac brandy is produced (so they are in good company). The packaging, designed by Carluke, Scotland-based <a href="https://wearemycreative.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">My Creative</a>, draws inspiration from the distillery&#8217;s terroir where, among other crop fields and in between ridges and furrows, the whisky&#8217;s corn field lies in the middle and is abstractly represented in the bottle&#8217;s label, highlighted in a copper foil stamp. The serif wordmark, echoes the angular design of the terroir while adding a sense of luxury. Not that it needs much, given the lovely custom bottle with ridges on the sides to allude to the terroir once again but also to the shape of the still while featuring the lovely monogram in raised glass at the bottom of the front of the bottle. A bonus, subtle feature is the lovely paper that the labels are printed on, which has an earthy, rugged texture that further links the product to the soil it comes from. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://wearemycreative.com/milhoc-whisky" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Edmond’s Honor by Vault49</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_edmondshonor.jpg" alt="Edmond’s Honor by Vault49" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://edmondshonor.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Edmond’s Honor</a> is a new premium bourbon whiskey developed by <a href="https://www.pronghorn.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pronghorn</a>, a company that fosters “the next generation of entrepreneurs, executive leaders and founders within the spirits industry through sustainable investment, incubation and recruitment”. The packaging, designed by New York, NY-based <a href="https://www.vault49.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vault49</a>, features a custom bottle where an abstract depiction of an orchid of the genus Vanilla is raised and a die-cut label in the shape of a hand reaches for it. It&#8217;s not a gratuitous design as the whisky is named after <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edmond_Albius" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Edmond Albius</a>, who, despite being born into slavery, at the age of 12 revolutionized vanilla cultivation by hand-pollinating orchids. Abstracting hands is never easy but this one is quite successfully done and the typography and other graphic elements flow naturally within. The contrast of the black hand rising from the white label on top of the copper-colored spirit and accentuated by gold is all kinds of satisfying. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.vault49.com/work/edmonds-honor" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Vigie by Glasfurd &amp; Walker</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_vigie.jpg" alt="Vigie by Glasfurd &amp; Walker" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://drinkvigie.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vigie</a> is a limoncello crafted in California that aims to capture “the essence of European leisure with a dash of revelry and a touch of splendor”. The packaging, designed by Vancouver, BC-based <a href="https://glasfurdandwalker.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Glasfurd &amp; Walker</a>, brings a Mediterranean flair to the U.S. West Coast through a lovely high-contrast, sans serif wordmark and a charming sun illustration. While both elements are excellent in their own regard I think the highlight of the bottle is the contrast of the perfectly chosen green hue and the bright yellow liquid within the stour bottle. It looks criminally refreshing. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://glasfurdandwalker.com/project/vigie/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_537.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_537.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Colere by Ideogramma</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/colere_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Colere by Ideogramma" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.ideogramma.com/colere.html">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_colere_by_ideogramma.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_colere_by_ideogramma.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Direct Ferries by We All Need Words and NotOnSunday</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/direct_ferries_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Direct Ferries by We All Need Words and NotOnSunday" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://weallneedwords.com/direct-ferries-brand-strategy/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_direct_ferries_by_we_all_need_words_and_notonsunday.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_direct_ferries_by_we_all_need_words_and_notonsunday.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>