<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for MSI 24 by Studio Dumbar/DEPT.</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Extra! Extra! Red All About It!”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/MSI_Logo_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MSI 24 by Studio Dumbar/DEPT." />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>The <a href="https://lolesports.com/en-US/news/msi-2024-primer" target="_blank" rel="noopener">2024 Mid-Season Invitational (MSI)</a> is the ninth edition of <a href="https://www.riotgames.com/en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Riot Games’</a> flagship tournament for <a href="https://www.leagueoflegends.com/en-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">League of Legends (LoL),</a> a globally popular <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiplayer_online_battle_arena" target="_blank" rel="noopener">multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA) game.</a> As a key mid-year event, MSI brings together the top teams from each region, drawing millions of viewers worldwide and offering a substantial prize pool that often reaches into the hundreds of thousands of dollars. For Riot Games, this tournament is crucial, showcasing elite gameplay while strengthening League of Legends’ position at the forefront of the esports world.</p>

<p>This year, Riot Games partnered with Rotterdam-based <a href="https://studiodumbar.com/work" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Studio Dumbar/DEPT</a> to create a fresh brand identity for MSI. Known for their expertise in dynamic visual systems, Studio Dumbar/DEPT aimed to capture the energy and intensity of the competition while uniting the global League of Legends community.</p>

<span id="more-298746"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>
Our design package had to be rigorous and robust: a host of different vendors would work with it before and during the tournament, across a multitude of touch-points. It had to be expansive too, encompassing a staggering number of templates and assets for motion, socials, print, event graphics, and more. MSI 24 was defined by the tagline, Become the Unknown. To support this, Riot Games sought visuals with a mysterious, dangerous, powerful tone. This attitude became the guiding principle for our work.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://studiodumbar.com/work/msi-24" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Studio Dumbar/DEPT. case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI23_OLD_identity.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MSI 24 by Studio Dumbar/DEPT." />
<figcaption>Sampling of OLD identity.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_Logo.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MSI 24 by Studio Dumbar/DEPT." />
<figcaption>NEW logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_logo_animated.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo, animated.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:125%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_logo_system_animated_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_logo_system_animated_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_logo_system_animated_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo system, animated.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Since 2021, each annual MSI logo lockup has kept its core logomark — a mysterious circular emblem that looks like a mashup of a winged creature, a sci-fi/fantasy sword tip, and maybe even a grim reaper’s hood. (If you&#8217;re interested in seeing the evolution of the MSI logo since 2015, <a href="https://logos.fandom.com/wiki/League_of_Legends_Mid-Season_Invitational" target="_blank" rel="noopener">click here.</a>) It’s an abstract, sinister design that perfectly balances strength with just a hint of danger. While this emblem remains consistent each year, the surrounding elements — like the typography and the tournament theme/tagline — get a refresh to suit the vibe of each event. Last year’s theme was “Defy,” which came through loud and clear in the MSI 2023 logo lockup and visual identity with its rebellious, cyberpunk aesthetic. The aggressive, digital-in-a-post-apocalyptic-future typeface, paired with graffiti-like tags, gritty textures, and manga-styled character illustrations, screamed Neo Tokyo attitude, letting everyone know this tournament was all about shattering any preconceived notions of what an esports event could be. The edgy, futuristic, street-art vibe was daring, bold, unapologetic, and just straight-up badass. I am <em>so</em> far outside of the target audience, it&#8217;s not even funny, but had I been exposed to any of these marketing materials last year, I 100% would have checked it out just to see what all the hype was about.</p>

<p>The MSI 2024 logo system, with its theme “Become the Unknown,” marks a bold evolution in the event’s visual identity, intricately linked to Studio Dumbar/DEPT’s eerie and mesmerizing design element called “The Aberration” — their visual embodiment of “The Unknown.” This shimmering, spectral aura forms the backbone of the branding, with the logo itself seemingly emerging from and dissolving back into this mysterious force. The ultra-tight kerning, reminiscent of The Designers Republic typography from the ’90s, and the fluid, blobby, almost liquefied letterforms suggest a transformation in progress, as if we’re catching these shapes just as they momentarily solidify after forming from the nebulous, unpredictable nature of The Aberration. The edges and corners of the letters blur and melt into each other, making the whole design feel like a fleeting glimpse into something otherworldly and ever-changing.</p>

<p>Juxtaposed against this spectral vibe is the stark black and red color palette, carried over from the previous year, creating a high-contrast visual punch that grounds the otherwise ethereal quality of The Aberration. The intense red slices through the darkness with urgency, while The Aberration itself pulses with a spectrum-like gradient, introducing an almost aural or holographic effect that feels alien, ominous, unsettling. Studio Dumbar/DEPT has crafted a visual language that’s not just bold and eye-catching but also symbolic of the tournament’s gameplay — a journey into the unknown — where every element appears to be in a constant state of flux, teetering between the familiar and the uncharted. Go ahead and toss your graphic design textbooks out the window. This is an aesthetic that’s unconventional, uncomfortable, and rule-breaking, and that’s exactly the point.</p>

<blockquote>
We devised a powerful and engaging framework for visuals: bold, expressive typography; a primary colour palette dominated by black and red; Journey Data visuals resembling a futuristic, Ul-inspired textural layer; and Empyrean Shapes – graphic icons inspired by LoL lore. We created a rich and immersive motion language; at its core, The Aberration &#8211; a graphic interpretation of the Unknown that can be slow and ominous, sporadic and reactive, or more linear and up tempo, depending on the application&#8217;s requirements. Organic and spectral, The Aberration provides a consistent thread throughout the visual identity. Along with The Aberration, we also modelled and animated our first LoL champion, Nocturne.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://studiodumbar.com/work/msi-24" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Studio Dumbar/DEPT. case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_tagline.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MSI 24 by Studio Dumbar/DEPT." />
<figcaption>Tagline.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_graphic_elements_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="video-container" style="float:right; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_graphic_elements_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Animated graphic elements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_motion_behaviors_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_motion_behaviors_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Motion behaviors.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_layouts_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Layouts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_bracket.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brackets.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_Nocturne_01_model.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_Nocturne_02_full_render.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Nocturne character.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The visual identity system for MSI 2024 is nothing short of a sensory overload — in the best possible way. It’s a system that’s bursting with energy, layering bold elements to create a spectacle that demands attention. Studio Dumbar/DEPT’s use of killer motion design, combined with “Journey Data” visuals that resemble a futuristic HUD-like textural layer, creates an immersive experience that feels straight out of a sci-fi action sequence. Watching it all unfold, it’s like viewing the tournament’s evolving landscape from inside the helmet of a mech suit, where every piece of data flickers and recalibrates in response to the ever-changing chaos of the battlefield. This UI-inspired data layer doesn’t just sit passively in the background; it dynamically frames everything — the logo system, fluid typography, The Aberration, and even Studio Dumbar/DEPT’s menacing original character, Nocturne — heightening the sense that we’re navigating the dangerous and unpredictable world of The Unknown.</p>

<p>The “Empyrean Shapes,” graphic icons inspired by LoL lore, add a sharp, almost threatening edge to the design, punctuating the visuals with cryptic symbols that feel both mystical and dangerous. Then there’s Nocturne, Studio Dumbar/DEPT’s 3D-modeled LoL champion, whose presence is unsettling and foreboding. With its holographic coloring, Nocturne seems to materialize directly from The Aberration, acting as its physical embodiment. Alongside Nocturne, The Aberration serves as the pulsating core of the visual identity. It&#8217;s amorphous and spectral, and shifts from slow and ominous to sporadic and reactive, depending on the needs of each application. Together, these elements form a cohesive and dynamic system that ties everything back to the MSI 2024 theme. This is a high-stakes, immersive experience that feels like stepping into a digital battlefield. It&#8217;s intense, unpredictable, and exhilarating.</p>

<blockquote>
We delivered a fool-proof package with in-depth guidelines, assets and templates to service the many outside vendors working on MSI 24, The scope and rigour of our design package ensured a rich and seamlessly branded framework for the tournament, both online and off-line — from a motion-led campaign on social media, through live online broadcasts and onwards, to the final showdown.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://studiodumbar.com/work/msi-24" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Studio Dumbar/DEPT. case study</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_title_cards.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Title cards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_key_visual.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Key visual.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The “Key Visual” animated sequence above is the perfect embodiment of MSI 2024’s visual identity coming together in one dynamic, cohesive display. It seamlessly fuses the fluid motion design, flickering HUD-like Journey Data, Empyrean Shapes, and the aura of The Aberration into a mesmerizing visual experience. As Nocturne emerges from the swirling depths of The Aberration, the typography and graphic elements pulse and shift around it, creating a sense of constant transformation and movement. This sequence feels like the heartbeat of the entire MSI 2024 identity, capturing this year&#8217;s theme with intensity and excitement. It’s an electrifying spectacle that makes you feel like you’re standing on the precipice of something exciting and powerful, yet unpredictable and menacing. I&#8217;ve watched this sequence <em>so many</em> friggn&#8217; times while writing this review, and now that I can legally get shroom gummies delivered to my door, there&#8217;s a part of me that wants to do precisely that and then watch this sequence 100 more times.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_gameplay_01_players.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_gameplay_02_transitions.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>The action!</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:63.25%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_Instagram_stories.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_flags.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MSI 24 by Studio Dumbar/DEPT." style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Instagram stories and flags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_website.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MSI24_sizzle_reel.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Sizzle reel.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ETQ9LME7UzQ?si=vKSHe1O5SPo3jpbf" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div>
<figcaption>Explainer video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">Studio Dumbar/DEPT has crafted a truly intense visual identity for MSI 2024. It&#8217;s an electrifying blend of bold elements that feels like a living, breathing, entity. From the mesmerizing fluid motion and flickering HUD-like data visuals to the sharp, Empyrean Shapes and the ominous presence of Nocturne, every piece of this identity works together to reinforce the theme of Becoming the Unknown. I’m no gamer, but I can appreciate that this is a seriously kick-ass identity that gamers and rabid LoL fans would surely enjoy. It’s unconventional, unsettling, and pushes boundaries in a way that’s as thrilling as what I imagine the gameplay to be; a visual identity that doesn’t just tell you about the MSI tournament, but pulls you into its chaotic, unpredictable world.</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_msi_24_by_studio_dumbar_dept.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_msi_24_by_studio_dumbar_dept.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Wrapsody in Green”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wrap_Logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>
The Waste and Resources Action Programme, aka <a href="https://www.wrap.ngo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">WRAP</a>, is a UK-based global environmental action non-governmental organization (NGO) focused on addressing the inefficiencies in product and food systems to promote &#8220;Circular Living&#8221;. Through technical expertise and impartial evidence, WRAP develops solutions to sustainability issues and leads initiatives to reduce CO2 emissions, minimize waste, restore natural ecosystems, and improve the quality of life for people. WRAP&#8217;s approach involves collaboration with businesses, other NGOs, and governments, aiming to create the systemic change necessary to tackle the urgent environmental challenges faced by communities worldwide. They worked with London, England-based <a href="https://www.amongequals.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Among Equals</a> to create a new logo and identity, WRAP&#8217;s first rebrand in over a decade.

<span id="more-298708"></span>

<blockquote>
The new identity is built around an evocative brand idea – WRAP is &#8220;fixing the world&#8217;s broken systems&#8221; – with a logo that subverts a very familiar, almost archetypal, globe to bring those broken systems to life, and hint at the journey to fix them. The design captures the urgency of WRAP&#8217;s ambition to move the world away from unsustainable &#8220;take-make-dispose&#8217; linear production systems towards more sustainable, circular ones.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="URL" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Among Equals press release</a></h3>



<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_old-identity.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Samples of OLD identity.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The old logo, despite a valiant attempt to incorporate an infinity symbol that aptly represents WRAP&#8217;S &#8220;Circular Living&#8221; model, was pretty bad. While using the infinity symbol to form the bowls of the &#8216;A&#8217; and &#8216;P&#8217; was a decent idea (if somewhat trite) the execution is rough. The wobbly curves, uneven spacing, and don&#8217;t even get me started on that that tiny sliver of a terminal on the &#8220;A&#8217;. It, along with the old identity, felt like a bland and banal government brand. Not ideal for an NGO.
</p> 

<blockquote>
The logo is packed with meaning. It would have been easy to create a clean, geometric shape but we went for something bolder. The disruption is strongest in the top left and settles in the bottom right, symbolising a journey from broken to fixed. It&#8217;s bold, challenging, and reflects the need for change, while also saying change is possible. This tone is reflected throughout the new identity.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="URL" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Among Equals press release</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>New logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_logo_animation_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Icon variants.</figcaption>
</figure>



<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_logo_details.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Logo details.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The new wordmark, on the other hand, takes a much stronger and bolder approach. It subtly nods to its predecessor with the arched crossbar on the &#8216;A,&#8217; but with a much more confident stance. Yet it plays a supporting role to the icon: an untangling globe meant to symbolize &#8220;[bringing] broken systems to life, and hint at the journey to fix them.&#8221; While my initial impression was of a ball of yarn, a peeling onion, or maybe even a shredded Christmas ornament, the concept is solid and pertinent for the brand. The idea of &#8220;broken&#8221; is consistently reinforced throughout the identity&#8217;s copy. And you could argue all of the aforementioned items are waste that WRAP aims to transform and renew. Is the icon a little odd on its own without the wordmark? Yes. Do we need 25 nearly identical variations of it? Probably not. But it is evocative and compelling enough to spark curiosity about the brand. Not to mention, it&#8217;s a significant improvement over its predecessor.
</p> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_color-palette.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_iconography_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_iconography_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Iconography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_pattern_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Pattern.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The illustration/iconography system, as well as the patterns seen across applications, build off the untangling globe motif. The pattern gets more visibility than the illustrations from what I gleaned on the website, which I&#8217;d say is a missed opportunity because they&#8217;re quite cool. I&#8217;d love to see these scaled out, maybe one object transforming into another, rather than just being &#8220;fixed&#8221;&mdash;a result you might expect from a recycling initiative. I <em>think</em> the flowy 3D shoelaces and tangled wire renderings are meant to reflect the various landscapes and textures found in the photography. Like, they are the photography&#8217;s textures compacted into broken cords? Which, okay sure, but this added imagery feels more confusing than cohesive. The pattern or icons layered on top of the photography stands well on its own, without the need to jump on the 3D rendering trend.
</p> 

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_typography_1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_typography_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Typography samples.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
Photography plays a huge role in evoking these broken systems. High angle shots capture the vast landscapes that are affected by unsustainable production methods while close-up macro ones show a different perspective on the day-to-day consumer goods that WRAP exists to improve &#8211; from plastic bottles to clothing and food. These unfamiliar ways of looking at the systems and products we depend on every day challenge people’s understanding of our impact on the world.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="URL" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Among Equals press release</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_typography_3.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_typography_4.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_photography_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Typography with photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
I could look at and find inspiration in photography all day. From the colors and textures to shapes and patterns, it works beautifully as a background to layer other elements on top of. While high-angle drone shots aren&#8217;t the most original choice for an environmental brand, WRAP&#8217;s use is particularly effective, especially when layering the &#8220;broken&#8221; logo or icon over a tomato or farm silo. It brings the concept to life in a really satisfying way.
</p> 

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_guest-pass.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Guest pass.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:100%;background:white">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_posters.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_website_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/wrap_website_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for WRAP by Among Equals" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">     
The overall identity and strategy are solid and effective&mdash;a massive improvement from the old look. Not only is it relevant and easy to grasp despite its somewhat abstract nature, it puts a fresh spin on the usually overplayed &#8220;green&#8221; aesthetic. It feels surprisingly timeless, and probably won&#8217;t need to be <em>recycled</em> for another 10 years. A truly sustainable brand identity.
</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_wrap_by_among_equals.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_wrap_by_among_equals.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“A Small Batch of Big Changes”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Launched in 1999, the <a href="https://kybourbontrail.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kentucky Bourbon Trail</a> is a tourism program which winds throughout the state, connecting a wide range of distillery tours and tastings into a single index. Originally a collaboration between Kentucky&#8217;s seven largest distilleries, over the past twenty-five years the trail has been steadily growing, adding national brands and smaller craft businesses into the mix. Today there are 46 stops in total, spanning over 300 miles of Kentucky and attracting a reported 2.5 million visitors last year. The route has grown so sprawling, in fact, that a field guide to track all the stops was launched in 2021, only to be retired three years later <a href="https://kybourbontrail.com/field-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">due to the increasing difficulty of visiting each distillery</a>. Which is a tremendous loss to me, personally, as a lifelong fan of road trips and passport stamp promotions.</p>

<p>To celebrate the quarter century anniversary, the <a href="https://kybourbon.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kentucky Distillers&#8217; Association</a> commissioned Brentwood, Tennessee-based studio <a href="https://www.lewiscommunications.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lewis Communications</a> to craft a new brand identity and website.</p>

<span id="more-298690"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>
The distilleries on the trail have created new and elevated experiences that are bringing in a more affluent guest. To better reflect today&#8217;s experience there was a need for a new brand identity that conveyed a joyful sense of discovery, elevated adventure, and attainable luxury.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.lewiscommunications.com/work/kentucky-bourbon-trail" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lewis project summary.</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_logo.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<!-- <figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="[wbcr_php_snippet id='187']archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_logo_variants.jpg" alt="[wbcr_php_snippet id='189']" />
<figcaption>Logo variants.</figcaption>
</figure> -->

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_logoanimation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>There&#8217;s a lot going on in the old logo, and almost all of it works. It&#8217;s conceptually strong &#8211; the somewhat bold, very condensed sans serif on the words <em>KENTUCKY</em> and <em>TRAIL</em> evoke the slats of a barrel. These frame the word <em>Bourbon</em>, which is rendered in a fluid script, lighter in both color and weight. The cursive quirk of including the trailing spurs on the <em>O</em>s in <em>Bourbon</em> makes the whole word feel more cohesive, giving the same sharp terminals to every letter except the lowercase <em>B</em>. If I had to pick it apart, I would start with the spacing. Some iterations of the logo had a <a href="KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_oldlogo+barrel.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">barrel illustration along the bottom edge</a> to fill out the footprint. You could charitably describe the logo sans-barrel as &#8220;dynamic,&#8221; or uncharitably as &#8220;uncomfortable.&#8221; But overall it looks like exactly what you&#8217;d expect from a tour called the Kentucky Bourbon Trail, and I&#8217;ve got nothing against it.</p>

<p>The updated logo is all balance, all the time. The custom wordmark is exceptionally modern with just the right amount of art deco notes. All the low legs, high shoulders, and narrow bowls give it an industrial feel that reflects in the copper coloring. It&#8217;s a strong mark that gives distillery vibes without having to rely on the literal imagery of its predecessor. I&#8217;m not crazy about the enlarged ®, which is further emphasized with its slow fade-in at the end of the logo animation above. But it&#8217;s on trend, it aligns nicely with the <em>O</em> in the line above, and it&#8217;ll hopefully stave off <a href="https://www.wuky.org/local-regional-news/2011-11-17/dispute-over-kentucky-bourbon-trail-settled" target="_blank" rel="noopener">any further trademark disputes</a>. While the new logo does feel much more luxurious, it also feels considerably less Kentucky. I&#8217;d imagine that&#8217;s intentional &#8211; the state tourism board can pick up the civic signifiers. This brand&#8217;s all about the bourbon, baby.</p>

<blockquote>
Wherever you are, join us at 4pm (16:00) in your time zone at WorldBourbonToast.com. We&#8217;ll be live streaming around the world for 24 hours, with a toast in every time zone. (So even if you join us earlier or later, you can still take part in the fun.)
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://kybourbontrail.com/worldbourbontoast/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">World Bourbon Toast landing page.</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video controls controlsList="nodownload" poster="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_wwtoast_poster.jpg">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_wwtoast.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>World Bourbon Toast highlight reel.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Coinciding with the 25th anniversary and the launch of the new brand, the World Bourbon Toast was a 24-hour livestream event on September 17th in which Kentucky celebrities and distillery reps jumped online to give a toast every hour, on the hour &#8211; with call-ins to Japan, England, France, and Ireland when their local 4pm rolled around. Even though the event and highlight reel were put together by Lewis, there isn&#8217;t much of the brand on display aside from the logos. So I&#8217;ve included it here at the top; partly because it serves as a good tone-setter for the drinks and drink culture at the heart of the identity, and partly just to give proper kudos to Lewis for orchestrating a brand launch party that is also a 24-hour live broadcast. I wouldn&#8217;t wish those logistics on my worst enemy.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_type_gtamerica.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_type_gtamericamono.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_type_signifier.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_color.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The type and color choices stick to the affluent vibes established by the logo. <a href="https://www.grillitype.com/typeface/gt-america" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grilli Type&#8217;s GT America</a> is a personable, no-nonsense sans serif base which allows <a href="https://klim.co.nz/retail-fonts/signifier/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Klim Type Foundry&#8217;s Signifier</a>’s sharp angles and attractive contrasts to really sing. You can see notes of both typefaces in the construction of the logo. Whether the wordmark was made to match the typefaces or the typefaces were selected to match the logo, it&#8217;s an admirable ensemble.</p>

<p>The color choices are as obvious as they are appropriate. It&#8217;s Kentucky Bourbon, so the main color selection is drawn from Kentucky bluegrass and copper whiskey stills. No need to reinvent the color wheel. The real creativity is in the secondary palette &#8211; a very saturated red and yellow and a very desaturated blue and orange round off the set in very few colors that nonetheless offer a lot of opportunities for contrast and expression. We&#8217;ve witnessed palette selections swing from single ownable shades in the mid 2010s to all colors all the time in the early 2020s. This feels like a elegant balance &#8211; a handful of hues to actually use.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_ad_billboard1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_ad_billboard2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Billboards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_ad_cheers.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_ad_kentucky.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Print ads.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>By legal definition, bourbon whiskey is at least 51% corn. So is this copywriting. You could maybe get away with extremely on-the-nose wordplay like <em>bottled dreams</em> and <em>kindred spirits</em> if you committed hard and put them center stage, but tucking them away in small blocks spread across photos of the state welcome sign and disembodied hands clinking glasses dilutes any impact they could have had. Which is a baffling shortfall of this identity, considering&#8230;</p>

<blockquote>
The new KBT™ brand and website launched to raised glasses from across Kentucky and the globe. Leveraging earned media coverage across national and international markets, we reintroduced bourbon’s birthplace to millions of eyeballs and set the stage to welcome even more discerning palates.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.lewiscommunications.com/work/kentucky-bourbon-trail" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lewis project summary.</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_website1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_website2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_website3.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>&#8230;the radically different (and much more appropriate) approach to photography and copywriting seen on the website. Much more emphasis is given to the locations that make this list of locations appealing. In fairness, slogans like <em>Yours to Explore</em> and <em>Trail Tips</em> are allowed to be pithier and less specific when viewed altogether on a website. A single printed layout has much less space to sell you on the concept. But the resulting digital presence winds up being much more in-line with the elevated feel of the rest of the brand than any of the print applications.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_shortsleevetee.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_hoodie.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
	<hr>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_longsleevetee.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Apparel.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The apparel designs beautifully split the difference between maintaining the dignity of the brand while making it feel right at home on the gift shop rack. I&#8217;m digging the 25th-anniversary XXV roundel, which looks for all the world like it should be stenciled on the end of a barrel.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_bag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Merch bags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_glassware.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Glassware and flask.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_hat.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Hats.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_merch_pinspatch.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Pins and patch.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_sign.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Participant plaque.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_businesscards.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kentucky Bourbon Trail by Lewis" />
<figcaption>Business Cards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video controls controlsList="nodownload" poster="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_brandshowcaseposter.jpg">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/KentuckyBourbonTrail2024_brandshowcase.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand showcase.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>This case study presents an interesting challenge &#8211; how do you make a brand for bourbon that can serve as an umbrella for dozens of businesses in an industry that&#8217;s already so steeped in a specific culture? How do you communicate to tourists the idea of bourbon without stepping on the toes of Bulleit or James Beam or Marker&#8217;s Mark or any of the dozens of other distilleries represented, each with their own take on the same theme?</p> 

<p class="end">In elevating the tone of the trail while losing some of the folksier elements tied to the prior brand, Lewis has taken all the best equities of the Kentucky Bourbon Trail and distilled them into an identity which is equal parts elegant, enticing, and unobtrusive. It&#8217;s an accomplishment worth celebrating, and I&#8217;d drink to that.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_kentucky_bourbon_trail_by_lewis.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_kentucky_bourbon_trail_by_lewis.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Phi-Lo and Behold”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Philo_Logo_before_after.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p><a href="https://www.philo.com">Philo</a> is an American internet TV service based in San Fransisco, California. Philo streams more than 70 live channels and 75,000+ on-demand titles for $28/month. Founded by two students at Harvard in 2010 as an experimental dorm-room project, the company now has 100 employees and has grown to over one million subscribers. Philo sits in direct competition with <a href="https://www.sling.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sling</a>. In 2024, they partnered with New York, NY- and Los Angeles, CA-based <a href="https://www.siblingrivalry.com/">Sibling Rivalry</a> to create a new visual identity and overall brand positioning.</p><span id="more-298677"></span>

<blockquote>
Leaning into a streamlined brand identity and customer-obsessed ethos, Sibling Rivalry positioned Philo as an antidote to the complexity of a tumultuous market: &#8220;Our goal was to clarify and amplify what makes Philo so special, setting the stage for the company’s continued growth as an entertainment brand,&#8221; says Bo Bishop, Executive Director of Creative Strategy at Sibling Rivalry.
<br /><br />
One of the main findings during the rigorous strategy process was that it was challenging for consumers to understand exactly what Philo offers – a mix of live TV, on-demand content, and free channels. The complexity of offering multiple options to different people could actually be leveraged as a core strength, enabling Philo users to customize packages and combine all the best ways “to TV” in one service. 
<br /><br />
This single, compelling idea, representing Philo’s overarching brand purpose, informed all creative decisions throughout the rebrand project and sets the tone for customers’ overall experience with the brand. &#8220;The advantage was very clear to me&#8230;they’re the only service offering all these convenient, intuitive ways to watch what you love,” says Bishop. As such, Sibling Rivalry decided to “lean into the simplicity and joy of TV,” he adds.
<br /><br />
This resulted in the creation of a new memorable, directional tagline, ‘A better way to TV’, which positions Philo as a better means to access great entertainment. 
<br /><br />
&#8220;The language had to be clean, direct, and conversational—making Philo feel like a TV fan talking to other TV fans,” says Lauren Hartstone, Executive Creative Director &#038; Partner at Sibling Rivalry. “Where traditional streaming can have a technical, dry feel, we wanted Philo to feel like a brand that gets you, with a little bit of humor and fun.” 
</blockquote>
<h3>Sibling Rivalry Press Release.</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Old_Identity.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Samples of old identity.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Looking across the old advertising and social media posts for Philo helped me to realize why I wasn&#8217;t able to remember this company. Aside from the logo, everything felt like a one-off campaign. Their identity was lacking the structure and form in the designs we&#8217;ve come to expect from memorable brands (color, type, messaging, compositions, etc.). Despite this (and to Philo&#8217;s credit), they have found success. And&#8230;there is a small bit of charm in the old logo. The cut bowl in the &#8220;p&#8221; and the matching cuts in the lowercase, thin-stroked sans serif are well executed. It just lacked oomph.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Logo.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>NEW logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The new logo is a much bolder serif, bordering on slab serif. I appreciate that it maintains the DNA of the old logo, matching the lowercase geometric lettering. Yet, it reads much better, particularly in smaller sizes, which makes sense. There are some small details that could be refined, the &#8220;p&#8221; and the &#8220;o&#8221; seem to sit high on the baseline. And the &#8220;i&#8221; feels a bit too cute. Per Sibling Rivalry, this logo and the animations were created by the in-house Philo team. Certainly an outside typographer could have tightened this up a bit better, but overall, I think this is a move in the right direction.</p>

<blockquote>
The rebrand emphasizes Philo’s brand voice with an attitude that’s confident, sophisticated and witty. Philo now talks directly to audiences in a tone that’s refreshingly personal and conversational to stand out from the more corporate, straight-laced approach of big-box streamers and drive long-term emotional connections.    
<br /><br />The identity takes the existing Philo logo and animations, and builds on it with striking core brand elements including a signature color palette of black, white and magenta; a suite of hand-drawn illustrations; and a new approach to typography.  
<br /><br />
The organic, gestural, and whimsical illustration style gives Philo a distinctive charm, infusing humor and personality into its identity with its elegant, single-stroke black linework on a clean white background. These illustrations can be used together or individually, offering flexibility and scalability for various applications.
</blockquote>
<h3>Sibling Rivalry Press Release.</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Illustration_Overview.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Illustration_People.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Illustration_Objects.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Illustration_Strokes.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Illustrations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Illustration_Generes.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Genres.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The illustrations introduce a set of exciting characters, objects and strokes that provide a much-needed anchor to the identity. I really like the hand-drawn quality and the imperfectness in the renderings. While some may say they remind them of something&#8230;and they likely do, I&#8217;ll contend that they do enough to be something unique. In that they perfectly capture enough whimsy to complement the identity. For me, the genre frames are the most interesting. But, for a company without a clear product, these serve as perfect stand-ins for both the product and the consumer, so that Philo can tell a story. </p>

<p>The black, white and magenta work well together and nicely contrast the full-color photography from movie still frames.</p>


<blockquote>
The identity features a simple, bold, dynamic rectangular frame as a central graphic element that can become synonymous with the Philo experience. The shape expands, moves, builds, frames and reveals footage while “paying homage to all the ways we watch TV”, says Bishop.
</blockquote>
<h3>Sibling Rivalry Press Release.</h3>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Composition.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Message</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Composition_3.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Composition_2.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Brand voice.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The illustrations are paired in compositions with a well-suited headline set in <a href="https://verycoolstudio.com/typefaces/honey">Honey</a> by California-based foundry <a href="https://verycoolstudio.com/">Very Cool Studio</a>. Secondary type appears in <a href="https://displaay.net/typeface/roobert-collection/roobert/">Roobert</a> by <a href="https://displaay.net/">Displaay Type Foundry</a>. Aside from a few kerning issues, like in &#8220;tt&#8221; and &#8220;TV&#8221;, both typefaces complement the illustrations nicely.</p>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Overview.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Materials.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Materials.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>As the parts are combined with photography, the identity comes into focus. The black, white, gray, and magenta create variety, harmony, and moments of pop.</p>

<p>On the illustrated frames, I lean towards the more expressive instances, the people lay across type, over frames filled with underlining and circling words. On the photographic frames, the full-image formats are too dominant and I almost miss the identity altogether. As these two types of compositions sit next to each other, they start to feel either/or-ish. With compositions focused on either illustration or photography. While I don&#8217;t really want to see them come together, I wonder if there is enough of a connection. For instance, the Yellowstone image in the bottom left against the &#8220;easy&#8221; graphic almost start to feel too different. Perhaps a more intentional use of the magenta could bridge them.</p>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 65.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Logo_animation_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Motion samples.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The animations are snappy and quick. I tend to like the color swipe version more, but both are sufficient.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Digital.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Digital.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Social.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Social_2.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Socials.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Philo_Ad.jpg" alt="New Identity for Philo by Sibling Rivalry" />
<figcaption>Ad.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The website, digital ads, and social media posts each do their job at reconfiguring the illustrations and messages. I see the same either/or issues with the social media posts as I do above. And, again, I wonder if color could help harmonize the two types of designs.</p>

<p>It is also interesting to see the hand holding the photographic-styled remote (in the second social panel), as this introduces something new to the above set. We see this visual expanded in the video below.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1014789875?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Brand video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The illustrations finally come to full life in the above video. They have been itching to be animations, and the video shows how much more personality, life, and fun can be injected into the stills.</p>

<p class="end">And those illustrations are the stars of this identity&#8230;and justly so. They offer something to base an identity on. This was sorely missing. Along with a proper tone of voice. Thankfully they both are now felt. I wish the colors had a more significant role in the story. I like the colors chosen, but they come across as decorative instead of communicative. Reimagining how they are used could help unify the work and signal Philo more distinctly. Streaming TV is becoming a crowded field. Positioning as your friendly, straight-forward streaming provider could create an endearing moment that might make the difference.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_philo_by_sibling_rivalry.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_philo_by_sibling_rivalry.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 04:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Stamp of Approval”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Postcard_logo_before_after-v4.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Founded in 2018 and formerly known as Oasis: Beauty Kitchen, <a href="https://www.wearepostcard.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Postcard</a> are a sustainable hair, body, and all around self-care beauty brand based in Singapore. Postcard&#8217;s founder Hilda had battled with various skin conditions and found no respite in existing skin-care products and treatments, thus Postcard was born. Starting off in her own kitchen, the products gained recognition across Singapore for their eco-friendly, organic hair, skincare, and lifestyle products, and their strong stance on sustainability. Now, Postcard wants to bring its products to more people and encourage a simpler approach to self care. Helping Postcard revitalise their brand to reach a global audience were Leeds, UK-based <a href="https://www.robot-food.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robot Food.</a></p>

<span id="more-298601"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_before.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Samples of previous identity and packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
Robot Food’s strategic expertise has helped transform Postcard’s brand identity, positioning it as a destination for all essential self-care supplies. The brand’s mission centres around fostering a lifestyle of mindful consumption, reducing waste, and lessening the pressures of everyday life. 
<br><br>
The brand’s aim is to make self-care personal again, encapsulated by Robot Food’s creative platform, “Wish you were here” that positions the brand as an inviting space where worries wash away and indulging in less is a lifestyle to aspire to. 
</blockquote>
<h3>Robot Food Press Release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_full_v2.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Full logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_textured.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Textured version of the logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_stacked.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_icon.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Stacked and icon versions of the logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The previous logo suffered from the typical trope you get from small scale, artisan-level manufacturers, with a distressed and &#8220;hand made&#8221; look to it, no doubt emphasising the &#8220;hand made&#8221; nature of the product. However, as a company that is no longer actually made in the founder&#8217;s kitchen, but rather their &#8220;Beauty Kitchen&#8221; (I&#8217;m guessing more of a formal set up), the old logo wasn&#8217;t quite fit for purpose; feeling too humble, too apologetic, more market stall than global shelves. The new name and logo completely revamp their look and story, leaning into the benefits of their products and selling a more care-free lifestyle. The logotype immediately evokes an Art Deco feeling, adopting a Futura-esque typeface that wouldn&#8217;t feel out of place on vintage travel posters.</p>

<p>There&#8217;s nice tension between the heavily geometric “O” and “C’ and the other condensed letters. I also like how the “P”, “A”, and “R” all feature a sweet upward curve in the counters and crossbar. Also featured is a textured version of the logo which continues the theme from the previous identity, except now with more fidelity, making it feel like it&#8217;s been really stamped. All in all, for a fairly simple bit of type it goes a long way to transport you to a golden era of travel which reflects the strategy nicely.</p>

<blockquote>
&#8220;Our challenge was to develop a brand identity that maintained the authenticity of Postcard’s sustainable roots, without straying into the classic eco-friendly tropes. We focused on reframing indulgence as something that doesn’t have to be wasteful, and tapped into the growing desire for “life with less pressure,” by celebrating environments, both at home and in nature.” 
</blockquote>
<h3>Martin Widdowfield, Creative Director at Robot Food</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_introduction.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo and brand introduction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_stamps.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_illustrations.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Illustrated stamps.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_soap_02.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Stamp and soap products.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_faces_stamp.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Imagery cropped in stamp.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:127%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_messaging.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:127%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_messaging_stamp.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Messaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_design_02.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_design_03.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_design_01.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Postcards.</figcaption>
</figure>
 
<p>The identity elements aptly double down on the vintage travel concept with whimsical messaging set across two Google Fonts – <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Staatliches" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Staatliches</a> and <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Special+Elite" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Special Elite</a>. Also featured is a soft, pastel colour palette, a postage stamp holding shape, and some passport-inspired travel stamps. The standout feature, however, is the illustrated stamps, which tie into the packaging design – more on those below.</p>

<p>I was pleasantly surprised too when I discovered the two brand fonts were from Google as they are such a perfect fit. The condensed and impactful Staatliches gives messaging a thud and harmonises with the logo. And the typewriter-inspired Special Elite is a simple way to short-cut you to a vintage aesthetic. One criticism, and this goes for any distressed font, is that when Special Elite is used big the textured nature feels too vectorised and jagged and lacks the soft ink feeling it&#8217;s trying to achieve. Thankfully it&#8217;s quite well controlled across the system itself.</p> 

<p>Suffice to say all of these gel well together and further enhance the brand&#8217;s travel-inspired story. It&#8217;d be fair to argue they&#8217;ve gone a bit over the top with the postcard idea, even verging into cliché, but these are merely the ingredients, and I think they come to life really well on the main vehicle for the brand, the packaging.</p>

<blockquote>
Robot Food’s inviting packaging design and product names, such as &#8216;Clear Skies&#8217; and &#8216;Icy Peaks,&#8217; reflect serene places in nature, whereas the new Postcard logo features organic quirks inspired by vintage store signage. The logo’s textured look and feel mimics hand-printing techniques, like stamps, creating an imperfect effect that reflects the brand&#8217;s artisanal roots.<br><br>
In addition, stamp illustrations bring out the personality of each product, adding a rich, exploratory nature to the brand. These stamps are designed as a collection of postal stamps from around the world, inspired by a singular illustration style. They are intentionally simple, never too ornate or complex, as though they were sketches capturing moments from the locations they represent. 
</blockquote>
<h3>Robot Food Press Release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_fragrance_packaging.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Fragrance range.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_bottle_02.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_bottle_03.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_bottle_01.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Individual fragrances.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_product_range.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Packaging full range.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The packaging is where the idea really comes to life, providing the perfect format for the illustrations that aim to visually evoke the scents within. For me this feels like a designer&#8217;s dream; simple and charming illustrations, boiled down to a little stamp-sized canvas. What&#8217;s really lovely is how each stamp adopts its own colour theme and individual depiction but are all united by brush style and general colour hues. I just adore them, they feel like proper posters and something you&#8217;d be happy to hang on your wall. So, yeah a lot to love here. I also think they win out practically too; it&#8217;s the type of abstract design that will have people naturally attracted to the packaging just out of sheer curiosity. The rest of the range of packaging all remain consistent with a milky off-white background that gives the stamps a neutral canvas to pop from. It&#8217;s also where the use of the typewriter font feels most effective; at smaller size and evoking Postcard&#8217;s artisanal roots.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_website.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Website (designed in collaboration with Hungry Sandwich Club).</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_soap_01.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Bar of soap.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_wrapping.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Wrapping paper and an ACTUAL postcard!</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>With the packaging being the main applications there&#8217;s naturally not a lot extra on show here, though I suspect this would translate very well to merchandise, posters, social, and the like. What we do have showcases the broad range of identity elements with the website being the best example of it all. On reflection, when seeing it all together the passport stamp elements appear to get a little less love than the others brand elements, being used far more sporadically across applications, which I&#8217;m actually OK with as it&#8217;s an idea that&#8217;s been done quite a bit and only really adds a little more to an already rich visual system.</p>

<p class="end">In conclusion, Robot Food have done a fantastic job of evolving Postcard from a humble and local market to a more global one. The craft and beauty delivered through the illustrations, and all the additional elements that fill this lively brand, feel boutique with a European-ness about them. It&#8217;s a rebrand that skilfully channels a spirit of vintage wanderlust, giving Postcard the perfect identity to be sent to the rest of the world.</p>
 
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/stamp_of_approval.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/stamp_of_approval.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 06:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“La Belle Época”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/epoca_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>

Founded in 1990 and acquired by Magazine Luiza Group in 2013, <a href="https://www.epocacosmeticos.com.br/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Época Cosmetics</a> is one of Brazil’s largest beauty brands. Their extensive digital catalog boasts over 16,000 SKUs, offering a diverse range of products that includes skincare, perfumes, makeup, and hair care, with a focus on bringing imported items to the Brazilian market. Recently, in response to a desire to engage more authentically with their audience, Época introduced a new logo and identity design led by the Rio de Janeiro, Brazil-based agency
<a href="https://plau.design/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Plau Design</a>.
</p>
<span id="more-298567"></span>


<blockquote>
In collaboration with the brand&#8217;s creative team, we defined the new positioning: &#8220;Sua melhor Época é o agora.&#8221; – roughly translated to “This is your best time”. This concept highlights an accessible, achievable beauty that already exists within each person at that point in time, one that can be enhanced by Época’s products. In parallel, we developed the concept of &#8220;care tech,&#8221; representing the practicality and innovation that make the shopping experience more accessible and intuitive. Época simplifies access to world-class products through inclusive, simple and engaging communication.
</blockquote>
<h3>Text provided by Plau Design</h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_logo_new_reverse.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Logo reversed.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The old wordmark— a blocky, modern monospaced sans in all caps— was generally inoffensive from a design standpoint (as long as you’re not too anal about kerning), but without the tagline to provide context, “beauty brand” would have ranked pretty low on my list of guesses of what the company actually was (definitely losing out to “vaguely sinister space-age corporation from a sci-fi movie” or “Elon Musk’s estranged Brazilian cousin’s cybersecurity company”).
</p>
<p>
The new wordmark, designed from scratch by Plau (who specialize in type design), aligns much better with the brand’s personality and industry (although for reasons I can’t identify, it comes off as vaguely pharmaceutical to me? Which at least hits closer to the mark than previous one). The unicase approach gives the logo its own unique, memorable flavor right off the bat, with the little eyelashes on the “e” creating a fairly ownable monogram in its own right. I will say that the “e” in general feels a bit clunky compared to the other letters— the crossbar connection feels heavy compared to the inktraps on the “p” and the “a,” and I wish the eyelashes had been given a more deliberate treatment so as to better echo some of the more delicate features of the custom typeface, rather than simply using a monoline rounded stroke that feels mismatched with how thoughtfully crafted the rest of the letters are. That said, a huge overall improvement from its predecessor.
</p>


<blockquote>
From tone of voice to an energetic color palette, versatile graphic elements in static and in motion, and a proprietary, impactful custom typeface were necessary to get the brand points across. Época typeface font, a unicase that blends uppercase and lowercase letters at the same height, comes in five weights and adds even more dynamism to the brand. Born from the new logo, it carries its curves wherever it’s applied.
</blockquote>
<h3>Text provided by Plau Design</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_1.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_2.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_3.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_4.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Custom display font.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" >
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_color.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_icons.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Icons.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_motion_brands.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_motion_categories.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Visual language applied to brands and categories carried by Epoca.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_photography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_bentobox.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand bento box.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_brandbook.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand book.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>
The brand’s proprietary typeface — which was developed from the wordmark— does the heavy lifting throughout the identity, and could quickly get tedious if not for its five weights and the icons strategically interspersed throughout the compositions. Unicase type is hard to pull off without coming across as either ChAoTiC or RiDiCuLoUs, so kudos to Plau for putting together something that not only walks the line between playful and practical but also successfully serves as the cornerstone of the entire brand AND maintains some modicum of legibility in the process. Is it my favorite thing ever to look at? No. But does it suit the goals of the company and do oodles of work for brand recall? Absolutely.
</p>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_bizcard_OOH.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_OOH_1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_OOH_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_OOH_3.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Business card and OOH applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_social_1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_social_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_social_3.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Socials.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_website_desktop.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_website_mobile.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Website on desktop and mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 62.609%"">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_keychain.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Keychain.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The brand comes together pretty nicely in its applications, managing to own its signature pink without looking like a Barbie knockoff. The simple icon set shows great versatility when combined with some motion and layering, and the sneak peeks of real-life brand activations look very legit. I’d argue there are a few cases where a secondary typeface could have helped reduce clutter and let Época Display stand out more, but overall, the hyper-recognizability of the proprietary typeface (see: sky banner in the social examples) definitely outweighs any minor issues with overuse.
</p>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_brand_video.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand identity video. (Unmute for audio.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">
All things considered, this identity feels like an appropriate and very necessary upgrade for a major online retailer looking to level up their brand recall and carve out a unique personality for themselves in a noisy marketplace. Take a versatile graphic system that is simple and agile enough to evolve with the landscape and pair it with a signature typeface that can carry 95% of the brand personality on its own, and I suspect that Época is set up to endure through the next epoch of beauty and then some. 
</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_epoca_by_plau_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_epoca_by_plau_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 05:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Coming Full Circle”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ricard_2024_Logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Introduced in 1932 by a young <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paul_Ricard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paul Ricard,</a> who was just 23 at the time, <a href="https://www.ricard.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ricard</a> is the ultimate French pastis — an anise and licorice-flavored aperitif that has become synonymous with sunny afternoons in Provence. Fast forward to today, and Ricard isn’t just a French favorite, it’s the best-selling anise-based spirit in the world, moving over 40 million liters annually. As part of the Pernod Ricard family (the same people behind Absolut, Chivas Regal, and Martell), Ricard has solidified its legacy in both French and global spirits culture.</p>

<p>In 2018, Ricard partnered with Paris, France-based agency <a href="https://yorgo.co/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Yorgo&#038;Co</a> to introduce a sleek new identity — without touching its iconic bottle. (<a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Covered on Brand New at the time</a>.) Now, Yorgo&#038;Co is back again with a refreshed take on this classic brand, aiming to maintain its storied past while giving it a contemporary twist. With Ricard already dominating the French spirits market, this rebrand isn’t just about a fresh look; it’s about continuing the brand’s legacy while staying relevant to new generations.</p>

<span id="more-298522"></span>

<blockquote>
In late 2023, Ricard asked us for a refresh of the brand’s graphic codes, and we found ourselves in a unique situation: redesigning a logo we had created 7 years earlier. Yorgo drew a new sun icon to replace his ’R’ made of sunrays : a minimal, and generous circle, rising (or setting) behind our 2017 wordmark.
<br /><br />
In the new brand codes, we redefined the usage of the exclusive typefaces we had previously delivered, and brought a more intense golden yellow. We also introduced a graphic pattern that plays with the historic Ricard frame, a bolder mention of the founding date, and we designed  wide range of communication items, from sun loungers to hooded sweatshirts
</blockquote>
<h3>Yorgo&#038;Co provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_OLD_identity.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Sampling of OLD identity.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Logo.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>NEW logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Before_After_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Before and after animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Inspiration_01_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Inspiration_02_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo inspiration.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>To fully understand how we got here — why we’re now looking at a yellow circle as Ricard’s logo — it’s important to appreciate the history, meaning, and evolution of this iconic mark, as chronicled above in the inspiration videos, as well as <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here in this review from 2018.</a> Spoiler alert: it’s all about the sun.</p>

<p>The old-old logo literally radiated sunshine with its intricate sunburst design, and celebrated Ricard’s heritage with a framed semi-serif typeface that confidently said, “I’ve been around since 1932, and I have the legacy to prove it.” When Yorgo&#038;Co. stepped in for the 2018 redesign, they smartly retained that sunny disposition but gave it a modern edge. The sunburst got a haircut; it became a half-circle, still playful, but with a wink toward minimalism. Plus, that clever nod to the “R” hidden in the rays? Well played, Yorgo. You modernized it without losing the warmth. Released from its frame, the logotype also got a refresh, with the introduction of custom, extended sans-serif letterforms.</p>

<p>Fast-forward to 2024, and things have gotten even… simpler? Bolder? Possibly both. The new design cuts through all the visual noise, leaving us with… a yellow circle. Yep, just a plain ol’ circle. And I’ll admit, my Libra-ness is in full swing here, as I&#8217;m totally on the fence about all this. On one hand, I wonder if this is taking reductionism too far. Have we really come… wait for it… <em>full circle</em> to the point where logos are the most basic of geometric shapes? Are people actually supposed to look at this dot and immediately think “Ricard”? Without the logotype accompanying it, it’s just… a yellow circle. But then again, maybe that’s the genius of it. No one else is sporting a lone yellow circle logo, and in today’s sea of visual clutter, maybe that makes it uniquely ownable. <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:USA_Today_%282020-01-29%29.svg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USA Today,</a> <a href="https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Mastercard-logo.svg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard,</a> and, more industry-relevant, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martini_%26_Rossi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Martini &#038; Rossi / Martini,</a> have pulled off a similar trick, so why not Ricard? This is brand simplification to the extreme, and sometimes, perhaps the boldest move is to strip away all the extraneous adornment, and get to the heart of what defines a brand. In Ricard&#8217;s case, it&#8217;s not just the sun, but a celebration of the sun, and the feeling of being in Provence, sipping pastis under a warm Mediterranean sky.</p>

<p>I do, however, lament the departure of the 2018 sunburst-R hybrid. Yes, it was a little hard to read — especially on a white background where the thin yellow rays kind of got lost — but it was pretty clever. It managed to pack a lot of brand identity into those delicate rays, and I respect that. But I understand the move away from it. This new, simplified mark does scream modernity and accessibility, and gone are the intricate details that get lost at smaller sizes. Now, the bright yellow circle, paired with the lighter blue logotype, says, “Hey, I’m not your grandparents’ stuffy old drink.” The shift to a lighter blue might seem small, but it softens the look just enough, making it approachable without sacrificing that classic Ricard vibe. So all in all, I get this evolution. But do I get it because I now know Ricard&#8217;s history and its equity in marks that reference the sun? For younger audiences experiencing Ricard for the first time who don&#8217;t have the benefit of this history, will <em>they</em> get it? And maybe more importantly, will getting it matter to them? Or is the new logo just a circle, and who friggin&#8217; cares?</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_01.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_02.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_03.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_04.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pattern.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Pattern.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>This refresh is all about simplification, and that filters down to the visual identity, which is basically just type. Not that that&#8217;s a bad thing, as plenty of great brand identities rely almost exclusively on type. And the typography on display here is great. BUT — there was no accompanying information from Yorgo&#038;Co about type, and admittedly, I didn&#8217;t scrutinize it too carefully, but, from a  cursory look, it appears that all of this typography is repurposed from Yorgo&#038;Co&#8217;s 2018 refresh. Again, not a bad thing. In fact, it&#8217;s a good thing; it means the type is working for Ricard, and it&#8217;s definitely working for me. Plus, we now get some new colorful animations for the case study.</p>

<p>The visual identity also introduces a typographic pattern, which is basically just the logomark repeated on both white and yellow backgrounds. In my opinion, this is the weak link in all of this material. Not only does it feel like filler to me, but it directly contradicts the extreme simplification happening in the logo, by reintroducing visual noise. And as you will see from the materials farther down in the review, this pattern receives <em>A LOT</em> of attention across the various touchpoints, and I&#8217;m struggling to see why. With such a ballsy move to reduce the logomark to a yellow circle, I can&#8217;t, for the life of me, understand why this busy logotype pattern was given such visual dominance. Perhaps a lot transpired behind the scenes that we&#8217;ll never understand, but if I had successfully convinced a client of this caliber to approve a freakin&#8217; <strong>CIRCLE</strong> as the new, modern expression of the Ricard brand, I&#8217;d be going out of my way to find all sorts of creative ways of introducing that yellow circle everywhere. And it <em>does</em> pop up here and there as you will see, and in a handful of creative ways, but not nearly as much as this head-scratcher of a pattern.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Rolling_Glass.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Highball_Glasses.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Various_Glasses.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Various glasses.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Cups.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Cup_Sweat.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Cups.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>While not a new feature, I really appreciate how all of Ricard’s glassware — even the plastic cups — continue to feature a “dose line.” For those unfamiliar, this mark indicates the proper pour of the alcohol, with the rest of the glass being filled with ice-cold water to create the signature “louche,” or cloudiness, that occurs when pastis mixes with water. Pastis was born from the absinthe ban of the early 1900s and is essentially absinthe without its defining ingredient: wormwood. Absinthe, known for its high alcohol content (typically 45-75% ABV), traditionally requires a precise pour, measured by a <a href="https://cdn11.bigcommerce.com/s-d9fkz13/images/stencil/1280x1280/products/1629/8082/Pontarlier-uncut-product-gift-box-1435-GIMP__15661.1642360124.jpg?c=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bulbous portion on the stem of its glass.</a> Although pastis has a lower ABV, around 45%, the ritual of dosing and louching with water remains the same. It’s a subtle but meaningful historical nod to the drink’s origins that persists to this day, and I love that Ricard continues to honor this tradition.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_Before.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_During.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_After.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>The Pour: Before, during, and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Glass_Sweat.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Schwetty glass.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The remainder of this identity ostensibly boils down to Logo and Pattern on Stuff — and a healthy reliance on the gorgeous navy and yellow colors — and aside from the pattern overuse, I generally feel like the simplicity and restraint on display throughout these materials helps reinforce the bold modernity Yorgo&#038;Co are going for.</p>

<p>But that pattern, though. For example, the tray below would have been <em>infinitely</em> more striking if it were just a yellow circle with a navy logotype in the center. Or those flags — what if, instead of flags, they were warm yellow, orb string lights? And that hoodie below is awesome, but, for me, the pattern all over the inside and on the strings is overkill. The same goes for the pour spout (why not just a yellow circle with a navy logomark in the center?). The chairs suffer the same fate with unnecessary pattern usage. It&#8217;s just all too much gratuitous adornment for an otherwise very clean and polished brand identity.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Tray.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Tray.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Flags.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Flags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Hoodie.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Gorgeous_Outdoor_Product_Shot_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Gorgeous_Outdoor_Product_Shot_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Gorgeous_Outdoor_Product_Shot_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Gorgeous outdoor product shots.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Outdoor_Bar.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Outdoor bar.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p><strong>THIS</strong> right here is a perfect example of what&#8217;s going right for this brand refresh. <strong>This</strong> is how you own a yellow circle of a logo. And this is exactly how I&#8217;d love to spend a Saturday afternoon, if I were like 25 years younger with little to no life obligations. This bar is straight up awesome, and I love the boldness — and simplicity — on display here.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Chairs_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Chairs_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Chairs_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Chairs.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Umbrella.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Thatched_Umbrella_Flags.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Umbrella and flags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Crate.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Crate.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_Spout.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Water_Pitcher.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Bar_Cups_Carafe.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Various bar accoutrements: Pour spout, water pitcher, cups.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The water pitcher above is another shining example of how you own and reinforce such a bold logo move. I absolutely love it.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>T-shirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_Outside.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Hoodie outside.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Sweatshirt_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Sweatshirt_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Crewneck sweatshirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Outdoor_Product_Shot_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Outdoor_Product_Shot_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Outdoor product shots.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_Closeup_or_Flag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>It&#8217;s either a closeup of the t-shirt or a flag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>In the end, Ricard’s latest redesign is a bold and strategic leap into the future. By holding onto the sun — whether in its intricate sunburst form or as this sleek minimalist circle — the brand stays true to its roots while embracing a fresh, modern aesthetic. Ricard has always been about capturing the essence of sunny afternoons, good company, and the perfect aperitif, and this new design honors that spirit with a simplicity that feels both timeless and contemporary. The iconic blue-and-yellow palette remains, evolving just enough to keep the brand feeling vibrant while preserving its equity.</p>

<p class="end">With this redesign, Ricard positions itself perfectly for a new generation of drinkers. This ain&#8217;t your grandpa&#8217;s pastis; it’s modern, approachable, and effortlessly cool. While I may miss the clever sunburst-R hybrid, the clean, confident yellow circle signals a brand ready for its next chapter. Hopefully, by finding the sweet spot between tradition and modernity, it’ll continue to shine.</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco_2.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco_2.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Announced: Limited Posts this Week &#038; Next</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Back to Regular Schedule Oct. 14”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/2024_09_30_Limited_Posts_BN.jpg" alt="Limited Posts this Week &amp; Next" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>With the <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnewconference/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brand New Conference</a> happening next Thursday and Friday I will not have time to prepare the full range of posts this week and next but our guest writers will fill in with Reviewed posts from Monday through Thursday. We will be back with full content on October 14. Thank you for your patience with this.</p>

<p>Speaking of the conference… Live Webcast registration closes next Tuesday, October 8!</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/limited_posts_this_week_next.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/limited_posts_this_week_next.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“All the Ball Things”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/goodsport_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>
Founded by Jordan Mahy, <a href="https://www.goodsportbhm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Good Sport</a> is a Birmingham, AL-based film and photo studio that provides local brands and businesses with video strategy and high-quality content. They worked with fellow Birmingham, AL-based <a href="https://www.wearematey.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matey</a> on a new identity, including a new name, to transition from an independent practice to a full-fledged content company.
</p>
<span id="more-298451"></span>

<blockquote>
Mahy&#8217;s deep-rooted conviction to champion local businesses gave birth to his new company. This conviction became the company&#8217;s key differentiator within the film and photo industry &#8211; Content for local businesses should be, above all, practical and easy to understand. We identified attributes that embodied this philosophy — community-focused, uplifting, and positive — and used them to shape the brand&#8217;s tone of voice, positioning, name, and identity.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.wearematey.com/work/good-sport" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matey Project Page</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_horizontal.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_drop-shadow_animated.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Logo with drop shadow.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_monogram.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Monogram.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_mascot.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Mascot logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_suite.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Logo suite.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The old logo, under the former name &#8220;Mahy Visuals,&#8221; was functional, set in an inoffensive sans serif framed in crop marks that suggested something vaguely technical. The previous name was fine but probably not great for SEO purposes—Google kept asking if I meant &#8220;math,&#8221; &#8220;make,&#8221; or maybe &#8220;Matt.&#8221; Needless to say, &#8220;Good Sport&#8221; is a more distinct and ownable upgrade.
</p> 
<p>
There&#8217;s plenty to discuss regarding the new logo suite—it features four variations (five if you include the drop shadow variant). I&#8217;d say that&#8217;s one or two too many, but fortunately, they are all done well and quite charming. The custom lettered primary logo has a handcrafted feel, with some slightly quirky characters and a little flourish kick on the &#8216;R&#8217;. It especially pops with a bold drop shadow, giving a retro-inspired vibe that sets the tone for the brand. There&#8217;s a clever monogram that incorporates an &#8216;S&#8217; within the negative space of the &#8216;G&#8217;. Viewing it now, the two letters in one are extremely obvious and hard to unsee, but I actually didn&#8217;t even notice the &#8216;S&#8217; at first. It had a nice surprise factor for me, often an indicator of a good monogram.
</p> 
<p>
Next up to the plate, there&#8217;s a set of mascots formed from the &#8216;G&#8217; and &#8216;S,&#8217; which are undeniably sweet but perhaps one of the variants that could stay on the bench. Then again, what&#8217;s a good sports team without a mascot? (Actually, as a Dodgers fan, I take that back.) While delightful, they aren&#8217;t used much throughout the applications. Maybe they&#8217;d work better if they had a more significant role—like a modern-day <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Office_Assistant" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Clippy</a>, guiding users throughout the web experience. Lastly, there&#8217;s a logo lock-up that introduces two new fonts, which continues to make some of these choices feel a bit excessive. Why not stick with the primary logo typeface here? But again, despite the possible superfluity, each logo is well-crafted so it&#8217;s hard to be mad.
</p> 

<blockquote>
We arrived at the name and tagline Good Sport &#8211; a film and photo studio that Roots for the Home Teams. The Good Sport brand draws inspiration from baseball&#8217;s golden age—an era when communities came together to cheer on a celebrate local wins. This theme permeates every aspect of the brand, from its friendly mascots and classic monogram logo to its website featuring case studies designed as custom baseball cards. Even the promotional leave-behind—peanuts grown and roasted in Mahy&#8217;s hometown—reinforces the message: Good Sport is here to champion local businesses.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.wearematey.com/work/good-sport" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matey Project Page</a></h3>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_color-palette.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_typography_1.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_photography_3.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_case-study-cards.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Case study cards.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_brand-guidelines.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Brand guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
In case it wasn&#8217;t obvious from the logo suite, the entire identity draws from the golden age of baseball, including classic baseball card layouts for case study thumbnails, a &#8220;root for the home team&#8221; slogan, and even some roasted peanuts, answering the age-old brand question, &#8220;Will it peanut?&#8221; The secondary fonts further bolster the retro goodness featuring the lovely condensed Sandcastle JNL by <a href="https://www.fontspring.com/foundry/jeff-levine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeff Levine</a> and the vintage-inspired script Lonsdale by <a href="https://typodermicfonts.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Typodermic</a>. Both integrate seamlessly with the identity, enhancing the throwback vibe. Highway and Neue Haas by <a href="https://www.linotype.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Linotype</a> also make appearances, which again raises the question: are there one too many fonts? But to be fair, Neue Haas does serve as the primary body font on the website, so it at least makes sense in context.
</p> 

<p>
The color palette is a timeless mix of muted primary tones that amount to a masculine vibe, with the exception of hot pink. I&#8217;d love to see more of it in use but I can find only one instance in one of the case study card layouts. I personally love a good hot pink getting thrown into a more masculine identity. It would inject some unexpected nuance and dynamism into an otherwise subdued color scheme.
</p> 


<p>
With all these elements plus the name, you can&#8217;t blame me for concluding that the company solely focuses on sports-themed visuals. That, however, is not the case at all, with a portfolio that spans a wide range of industries, from bookstores to tea to hospitals. I do wonder if this heavy emphasis on the sports aesthetic could limit future client acquisition or expansion. While the tone they want to convey is certainly here — “light-hearted, team-focused, and passionate” — is it all a bit too kitschy?
</p> 


<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_business-cards_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Business card.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_postcard_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Postcard.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 60.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_video.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_3.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_mobile_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_peanuts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Peanuts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_spray-paint.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Mascot logo spray paint.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_sticker.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Sticker.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_hat.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Hat.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">     
Even as a baseball lover (did I mention &#8220;go Dodgers&#8221;?) I remain skeptical if going all-in on a baseball theme for a company that is not strictly about the sport is the best long-term strategy. That said, if I were a potential client, I&#8217;d much rather see this type of creativity and thinking outside the (batter&#8217;s) box. Good Sport&#8217;s video production itself evokes some of the hallmarks of classic baseball: nostalgia, romance, the warmth of late summer evenings. Plus, the identity is simply really well-made. In that sense, it all works for a production house that delivers classic, high-quality work.
</p>


                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_good_sport_by_matey.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_good_sport_by_matey.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for National Black Canadians Summit by Six Cinquième</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/blackcanadiansummit_logo_new.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for National Black Canadians Summit by Six Cinquième" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.sixcinquieme.com/projects/nbcs-2025/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_national_black_canadians_summit_by_six_cinquieme.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_national_black_canadians_summit_by_six_cinquieme.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>