<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Stamp of Approval”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Postcard_logo_before_after-v4.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Founded in 2018 and formerly known as Oasis: Beauty Kitchen, <a href="https://www.wearepostcard.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Postcard</a> are a sustainable hair, body, and all around self-care beauty brand based in Singapore. Postcard&#8217;s founder Hilda had battled with various skin conditions and found no respite in existing skin-care products and treatments, thus Postcard was born. Starting off in her own kitchen, the products gained recognition across Singapore for their eco-friendly, organic hair, skincare, and lifestyle products, and their strong stance on sustainability. Now, Postcard wants to bring its products to more people and encourage a simpler approach to self care. Helping Postcard revitalise their brand to reach a global audience were Leeds, UK-based <a href="https://www.robot-food.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robot Food.</a></p>

<span id="more-298601"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_before.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Samples of previous identity and packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
Robot Food’s strategic expertise has helped transform Postcard’s brand identity, positioning it as a destination for all essential self-care supplies. The brand’s mission centres around fostering a lifestyle of mindful consumption, reducing waste, and lessening the pressures of everyday life. 
<br><br>
The brand’s aim is to make self-care personal again, encapsulated by Robot Food’s creative platform, “Wish you were here” that positions the brand as an inviting space where worries wash away and indulging in less is a lifestyle to aspire to. 
</blockquote>
<h3>Robot Food Press Release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_full_v2.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Full logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_textured.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Textured version of the logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_stacked.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_logo_icon.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Stacked and icon versions of the logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The previous logo suffered from the typical trope you get from small scale, artisan-level manufacturers, with a distressed and &#8220;hand made&#8221; look to it, no doubt emphasising the &#8220;hand made&#8221; nature of the product. However, as a company that is no longer actually made in the founder&#8217;s kitchen, but rather their &#8220;Beauty Kitchen&#8221; (I&#8217;m guessing more of a formal set up), the old logo wasn&#8217;t quite fit for purpose; feeling too humble, too apologetic, more market stall than global shelves. The new name and logo completely revamp their look and story, leaning into the benefits of their products and selling a more care-free lifestyle. The logotype immediately evokes an Art Deco feeling, adopting a Futura-esque typeface that wouldn&#8217;t feel out of place on vintage travel posters.</p>

<p>There&#8217;s nice tension between the heavily geometric “O” and “C’ and the other condensed letters. I also like how the “P”, “A”, and “R” all feature a sweet upward curve in the counters and crossbar. Also featured is a textured version of the logo which continues the theme from the previous identity, except now with more fidelity, making it feel like it&#8217;s been really stamped. All in all, for a fairly simple bit of type it goes a long way to transport you to a golden era of travel which reflects the strategy nicely.</p>

<blockquote>
&#8220;Our challenge was to develop a brand identity that maintained the authenticity of Postcard’s sustainable roots, without straying into the classic eco-friendly tropes. We focused on reframing indulgence as something that doesn’t have to be wasteful, and tapped into the growing desire for “life with less pressure,” by celebrating environments, both at home and in nature.” 
</blockquote>
<h3>Martin Widdowfield, Creative Director at Robot Food</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_introduction.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo and brand introduction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_stamps.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_illustrations.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Illustrated stamps.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_soap_02.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Stamp and soap products.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_faces_stamp.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Imagery cropped in stamp.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:127%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_messaging.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:127%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_messaging_stamp.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Messaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_design_02.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_design_03.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_design_01.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Postcards.</figcaption>
</figure>
 
<p>The identity elements aptly double down on the vintage travel concept with whimsical messaging set across two Google Fonts – <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Staatliches" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Staatliches</a> and <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Special+Elite" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Special Elite</a>. Also featured is a soft, pastel colour palette, a postage stamp holding shape, and some passport-inspired travel stamps. The standout feature, however, is the illustrated stamps, which tie into the packaging design – more on those below.</p>

<p>I was pleasantly surprised too when I discovered the two brand fonts were from Google as they are such a perfect fit. The condensed and impactful Staatliches gives messaging a thud and harmonises with the logo. And the typewriter-inspired Special Elite is a simple way to short-cut you to a vintage aesthetic. One criticism, and this goes for any distressed font, is that when Special Elite is used big the textured nature feels too vectorised and jagged and lacks the soft ink feeling it&#8217;s trying to achieve. Thankfully it&#8217;s quite well controlled across the system itself.</p> 

<p>Suffice to say all of these gel well together and further enhance the brand&#8217;s travel-inspired story. It&#8217;d be fair to argue they&#8217;ve gone a bit over the top with the postcard idea, even verging into cliché, but these are merely the ingredients, and I think they come to life really well on the main vehicle for the brand, the packaging.</p>

<blockquote>
Robot Food’s inviting packaging design and product names, such as &#8216;Clear Skies&#8217; and &#8216;Icy Peaks,&#8217; reflect serene places in nature, whereas the new Postcard logo features organic quirks inspired by vintage store signage. The logo’s textured look and feel mimics hand-printing techniques, like stamps, creating an imperfect effect that reflects the brand&#8217;s artisanal roots.<br><br>
In addition, stamp illustrations bring out the personality of each product, adding a rich, exploratory nature to the brand. These stamps are designed as a collection of postal stamps from around the world, inspired by a singular illustration style. They are intentionally simple, never too ornate or complex, as though they were sketches capturing moments from the locations they represent. 
</blockquote>
<h3>Robot Food Press Release</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_fragrance_packaging.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Fragrance range.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_bottle_02.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_bottle_03.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_bottle_01.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Individual fragrances.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_product_range.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Packaging full range.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The packaging is where the idea really comes to life, providing the perfect format for the illustrations that aim to visually evoke the scents within. For me this feels like a designer&#8217;s dream; simple and charming illustrations, boiled down to a little stamp-sized canvas. What&#8217;s really lovely is how each stamp adopts its own colour theme and individual depiction but are all united by brush style and general colour hues. I just adore them, they feel like proper posters and something you&#8217;d be happy to hang on your wall. So, yeah a lot to love here. I also think they win out practically too; it&#8217;s the type of abstract design that will have people naturally attracted to the packaging just out of sheer curiosity. The rest of the range of packaging all remain consistent with a milky off-white background that gives the stamps a neutral canvas to pop from. It&#8217;s also where the use of the typewriter font feels most effective; at smaller size and evoking Postcard&#8217;s artisanal roots.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_website.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Website (designed in collaboration with Hungry Sandwich Club).</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_soap_01.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Bar of soap.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Postcard_postcard_wrapping.jpg" alt="New name, logo, identity and packaging for Postcard by Robot Food" />
<figcaption>Wrapping paper and an ACTUAL postcard!</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>With the packaging being the main applications there&#8217;s naturally not a lot extra on show here, though I suspect this would translate very well to merchandise, posters, social, and the like. What we do have showcases the broad range of identity elements with the website being the best example of it all. On reflection, when seeing it all together the passport stamp elements appear to get a little less love than the others brand elements, being used far more sporadically across applications, which I&#8217;m actually OK with as it&#8217;s an idea that&#8217;s been done quite a bit and only really adds a little more to an already rich visual system.</p>

<p class="end">In conclusion, Robot Food have done a fantastic job of evolving Postcard from a humble and local market to a more global one. The craft and beauty delivered through the illustrations, and all the additional elements that fill this lively brand, feel boutique with a European-ness about them. It&#8217;s a rebrand that skilfully channels a spirit of vintage wanderlust, giving Postcard the perfect identity to be sent to the rest of the world.</p>
 
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/stamp_of_approval.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/stamp_of_approval.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 06:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“La Belle Época”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/epoca_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>

Founded in 1990 and acquired by Magazine Luiza Group in 2013, <a href="https://www.epocacosmeticos.com.br/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Época Cosmetics</a> is one of Brazil’s largest beauty brands. Their extensive digital catalog boasts over 16,000 SKUs, offering a diverse range of products that includes skincare, perfumes, makeup, and hair care, with a focus on bringing imported items to the Brazilian market. Recently, in response to a desire to engage more authentically with their audience, Época introduced a new logo and identity design led by the Rio de Janeiro, Brazil-based agency
<a href="https://plau.design/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Plau Design</a>.
</p>
<span id="more-298567"></span>


<blockquote>
In collaboration with the brand&#8217;s creative team, we defined the new positioning: &#8220;Sua melhor Época é o agora.&#8221; – roughly translated to “This is your best time”. This concept highlights an accessible, achievable beauty that already exists within each person at that point in time, one that can be enhanced by Época’s products. In parallel, we developed the concept of &#8220;care tech,&#8221; representing the practicality and innovation that make the shopping experience more accessible and intuitive. Época simplifies access to world-class products through inclusive, simple and engaging communication.
</blockquote>
<h3>Text provided by Plau Design</h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_logo_new_reverse.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Logo reversed.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The old wordmark— a blocky, modern monospaced sans in all caps— was generally inoffensive from a design standpoint (as long as you’re not too anal about kerning), but without the tagline to provide context, “beauty brand” would have ranked pretty low on my list of guesses of what the company actually was (definitely losing out to “vaguely sinister space-age corporation from a sci-fi movie” or “Elon Musk’s estranged Brazilian cousin’s cybersecurity company”).
</p>
<p>
The new wordmark, designed from scratch by Plau (who specialize in type design), aligns much better with the brand’s personality and industry (although for reasons I can’t identify, it comes off as vaguely pharmaceutical to me? Which at least hits closer to the mark than previous one). The unicase approach gives the logo its own unique, memorable flavor right off the bat, with the little eyelashes on the “e” creating a fairly ownable monogram in its own right. I will say that the “e” in general feels a bit clunky compared to the other letters— the crossbar connection feels heavy compared to the inktraps on the “p” and the “a,” and I wish the eyelashes had been given a more deliberate treatment so as to better echo some of the more delicate features of the custom typeface, rather than simply using a monoline rounded stroke that feels mismatched with how thoughtfully crafted the rest of the letters are. That said, a huge overall improvement from its predecessor.
</p>


<blockquote>
From tone of voice to an energetic color palette, versatile graphic elements in static and in motion, and a proprietary, impactful custom typeface were necessary to get the brand points across. Época typeface font, a unicase that blends uppercase and lowercase letters at the same height, comes in five weights and adds even more dynamism to the brand. Born from the new logo, it carries its curves wherever it’s applied.
</blockquote>
<h3>Text provided by Plau Design</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_1.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_2.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_3.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_typography_4.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Custom display font.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" >
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_color.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_icons.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Icons.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_motion_brands.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_motion_categories.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Visual language applied to brands and categories carried by Epoca.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_photography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_bentobox.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand bento box.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_brandbook.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand book.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>
The brand’s proprietary typeface — which was developed from the wordmark— does the heavy lifting throughout the identity, and could quickly get tedious if not for its five weights and the icons strategically interspersed throughout the compositions. Unicase type is hard to pull off without coming across as either ChAoTiC or RiDiCuLoUs, so kudos to Plau for putting together something that not only walks the line between playful and practical but also successfully serves as the cornerstone of the entire brand AND maintains some modicum of legibility in the process. Is it my favorite thing ever to look at? No. But does it suit the goals of the company and do oodles of work for brand recall? Absolutely.
</p>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_bizcard_OOH.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_OOH_1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_OOH_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_OOH_3.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Business card and OOH applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_social_1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_social_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_social_3.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Socials.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_website_desktop.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_website_mobile.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Época by Plau Design" />
<figcaption>Website on desktop and mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 62.609%"">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_keychain.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Keychain.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The brand comes together pretty nicely in its applications, managing to own its signature pink without looking like a Barbie knockoff. The simple icon set shows great versatility when combined with some motion and layering, and the sneak peeks of real-life brand activations look very legit. I’d argue there are a few cases where a secondary typeface could have helped reduce clutter and let Época Display stand out more, but overall, the hyper-recognizability of the proprietary typeface (see: sky banner in the social examples) definitely outweighs any minor issues with overuse.
</p>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/epoca_brand_video.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Brand identity video. (Unmute for audio.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">
All things considered, this identity feels like an appropriate and very necessary upgrade for a major online retailer looking to level up their brand recall and carve out a unique personality for themselves in a noisy marketplace. Take a versatile graphic system that is simple and agile enough to evolve with the landscape and pair it with a signature typeface that can carry 95% of the brand personality on its own, and I suspect that Época is set up to endure through the next epoch of beauty and then some. 
</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_epoca_by_plau_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_epoca_by_plau_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 05:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Coming Full Circle”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ricard_2024_Logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Introduced in 1932 by a young <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paul_Ricard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paul Ricard,</a> who was just 23 at the time, <a href="https://www.ricard.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ricard</a> is the ultimate French pastis — an anise and licorice-flavored aperitif that has become synonymous with sunny afternoons in Provence. Fast forward to today, and Ricard isn’t just a French favorite, it’s the best-selling anise-based spirit in the world, moving over 40 million liters annually. As part of the Pernod Ricard family (the same people behind Absolut, Chivas Regal, and Martell), Ricard has solidified its legacy in both French and global spirits culture.</p>

<p>In 2018, Ricard partnered with Paris, France-based agency <a href="https://yorgo.co/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Yorgo&#038;Co</a> to introduce a sleek new identity — without touching its iconic bottle. (<a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Covered on Brand New at the time</a>.) Now, Yorgo&#038;Co is back again with a refreshed take on this classic brand, aiming to maintain its storied past while giving it a contemporary twist. With Ricard already dominating the French spirits market, this rebrand isn’t just about a fresh look; it’s about continuing the brand’s legacy while staying relevant to new generations.</p>

<span id="more-298522"></span>

<blockquote>
In late 2023, Ricard asked us for a refresh of the brand’s graphic codes, and we found ourselves in a unique situation: redesigning a logo we had created 7 years earlier. Yorgo drew a new sun icon to replace his ’R’ made of sunrays : a minimal, and generous circle, rising (or setting) behind our 2017 wordmark.
<br /><br />
In the new brand codes, we redefined the usage of the exclusive typefaces we had previously delivered, and brought a more intense golden yellow. We also introduced a graphic pattern that plays with the historic Ricard frame, a bolder mention of the founding date, and we designed  wide range of communication items, from sun loungers to hooded sweatshirts
</blockquote>
<h3>Yorgo&#038;Co provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_OLD_identity.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Sampling of OLD identity.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Logo.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>NEW logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Before_After_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Before and after animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Inspiration_01_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Inspiration_02_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo inspiration.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>To fully understand how we got here — why we’re now looking at a yellow circle as Ricard’s logo — it’s important to appreciate the history, meaning, and evolution of this iconic mark, as chronicled above in the inspiration videos, as well as <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here in this review from 2018.</a> Spoiler alert: it’s all about the sun.</p>

<p>The old-old logo literally radiated sunshine with its intricate sunburst design, and celebrated Ricard’s heritage with a framed semi-serif typeface that confidently said, “I’ve been around since 1932, and I have the legacy to prove it.” When Yorgo&#038;Co. stepped in for the 2018 redesign, they smartly retained that sunny disposition but gave it a modern edge. The sunburst got a haircut; it became a half-circle, still playful, but with a wink toward minimalism. Plus, that clever nod to the “R” hidden in the rays? Well played, Yorgo. You modernized it without losing the warmth. Released from its frame, the logotype also got a refresh, with the introduction of custom, extended sans-serif letterforms.</p>

<p>Fast-forward to 2024, and things have gotten even… simpler? Bolder? Possibly both. The new design cuts through all the visual noise, leaving us with… a yellow circle. Yep, just a plain ol’ circle. And I’ll admit, my Libra-ness is in full swing here, as I&#8217;m totally on the fence about all this. On one hand, I wonder if this is taking reductionism too far. Have we really come… wait for it… <em>full circle</em> to the point where logos are the most basic of geometric shapes? Are people actually supposed to look at this dot and immediately think “Ricard”? Without the logotype accompanying it, it’s just… a yellow circle. But then again, maybe that’s the genius of it. No one else is sporting a lone yellow circle logo, and in today’s sea of visual clutter, maybe that makes it uniquely ownable. <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:USA_Today_%282020-01-29%29.svg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USA Today,</a> <a href="https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Mastercard-logo.svg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard,</a> and, more industry-relevant, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martini_%26_Rossi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Martini &#038; Rossi / Martini,</a> have pulled off a similar trick, so why not Ricard? This is brand simplification to the extreme, and sometimes, perhaps the boldest move is to strip away all the extraneous adornment, and get to the heart of what defines a brand. In Ricard&#8217;s case, it&#8217;s not just the sun, but a celebration of the sun, and the feeling of being in Provence, sipping pastis under a warm Mediterranean sky.</p>

<p>I do, however, lament the departure of the 2018 sunburst-R hybrid. Yes, it was a little hard to read — especially on a white background where the thin yellow rays kind of got lost — but it was pretty clever. It managed to pack a lot of brand identity into those delicate rays, and I respect that. But I understand the move away from it. This new, simplified mark does scream modernity and accessibility, and gone are the intricate details that get lost at smaller sizes. Now, the bright yellow circle, paired with the lighter blue logotype, says, “Hey, I’m not your grandparents’ stuffy old drink.” The shift to a lighter blue might seem small, but it softens the look just enough, making it approachable without sacrificing that classic Ricard vibe. So all in all, I get this evolution. But do I get it because I now know Ricard&#8217;s history and its equity in marks that reference the sun? For younger audiences experiencing Ricard for the first time who don&#8217;t have the benefit of this history, will <em>they</em> get it? And maybe more importantly, will getting it matter to them? Or is the new logo just a circle, and who friggin&#8217; cares?</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_01.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_02.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_03.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Typography_04.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pattern.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Pattern.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>This refresh is all about simplification, and that filters down to the visual identity, which is basically just type. Not that that&#8217;s a bad thing, as plenty of great brand identities rely almost exclusively on type. And the typography on display here is great. BUT — there was no accompanying information from Yorgo&#038;Co about type, and admittedly, I didn&#8217;t scrutinize it too carefully, but, from a  cursory look, it appears that all of this typography is repurposed from Yorgo&#038;Co&#8217;s 2018 refresh. Again, not a bad thing. In fact, it&#8217;s a good thing; it means the type is working for Ricard, and it&#8217;s definitely working for me. Plus, we now get some new colorful animations for the case study.</p>

<p>The visual identity also introduces a typographic pattern, which is basically just the logomark repeated on both white and yellow backgrounds. In my opinion, this is the weak link in all of this material. Not only does it feel like filler to me, but it directly contradicts the extreme simplification happening in the logo, by reintroducing visual noise. And as you will see from the materials farther down in the review, this pattern receives <em>A LOT</em> of attention across the various touchpoints, and I&#8217;m struggling to see why. With such a ballsy move to reduce the logomark to a yellow circle, I can&#8217;t, for the life of me, understand why this busy logotype pattern was given such visual dominance. Perhaps a lot transpired behind the scenes that we&#8217;ll never understand, but if I had successfully convinced a client of this caliber to approve a freakin&#8217; <strong>CIRCLE</strong> as the new, modern expression of the Ricard brand, I&#8217;d be going out of my way to find all sorts of creative ways of introducing that yellow circle everywhere. And it <em>does</em> pop up here and there as you will see, and in a handful of creative ways, but not nearly as much as this head-scratcher of a pattern.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Rolling_Glass.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Highball_Glasses.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Various_Glasses.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Various glasses.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Cups.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Cup_Sweat.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Cups.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>While not a new feature, I really appreciate how all of Ricard’s glassware — even the plastic cups — continue to feature a “dose line.” For those unfamiliar, this mark indicates the proper pour of the alcohol, with the rest of the glass being filled with ice-cold water to create the signature “louche,” or cloudiness, that occurs when pastis mixes with water. Pastis was born from the absinthe ban of the early 1900s and is essentially absinthe without its defining ingredient: wormwood. Absinthe, known for its high alcohol content (typically 45-75% ABV), traditionally requires a precise pour, measured by a <a href="https://cdn11.bigcommerce.com/s-d9fkz13/images/stencil/1280x1280/products/1629/8082/Pontarlier-uncut-product-gift-box-1435-GIMP__15661.1642360124.jpg?c=2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bulbous portion on the stem of its glass.</a> Although pastis has a lower ABV, around 45%, the ritual of dosing and louching with water remains the same. It’s a subtle but meaningful historical nod to the drink’s origins that persists to this day, and I love that Ricard continues to honor this tradition.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_Before.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_During.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_After.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>The Pour: Before, during, and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.66667%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Glass_Sweat.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Schwetty glass.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The remainder of this identity ostensibly boils down to Logo and Pattern on Stuff — and a healthy reliance on the gorgeous navy and yellow colors — and aside from the pattern overuse, I generally feel like the simplicity and restraint on display throughout these materials helps reinforce the bold modernity Yorgo&#038;Co are going for.</p>

<p>But that pattern, though. For example, the tray below would have been <em>infinitely</em> more striking if it were just a yellow circle with a navy logotype in the center. Or those flags — what if, instead of flags, they were warm yellow, orb string lights? And that hoodie below is awesome, but, for me, the pattern all over the inside and on the strings is overkill. The same goes for the pour spout (why not just a yellow circle with a navy logomark in the center?). The chairs suffer the same fate with unnecessary pattern usage. It&#8217;s just all too much gratuitous adornment for an otherwise very clean and polished brand identity.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Tray.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Tray.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Flags.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Flags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Hoodie.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Gorgeous_Outdoor_Product_Shot_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Gorgeous_Outdoor_Product_Shot_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Gorgeous_Outdoor_Product_Shot_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Gorgeous outdoor product shots.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Outdoor_Bar.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Outdoor bar.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p><strong>THIS</strong> right here is a perfect example of what&#8217;s going right for this brand refresh. <strong>This</strong> is how you own a yellow circle of a logo. And this is exactly how I&#8217;d love to spend a Saturday afternoon, if I were like 25 years younger with little to no life obligations. This bar is straight up awesome, and I love the boldness — and simplicity — on display here.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Chairs_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Chairs_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Chairs_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Chairs.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Umbrella.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Thatched_Umbrella_Flags.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Umbrella and flags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Crate.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Crate.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Pour_Spout.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Water_Pitcher.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Bar_Cups_Carafe.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Various bar accoutrements: Pour spout, water pitcher, cups.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The water pitcher above is another shining example of how you own and reinforce such a bold logo move. I absolutely love it.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>T-shirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Hoodie_Outside.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Hoodie outside.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Sweatshirt_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Sweatshirt_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Crewneck sweatshirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Outdoor_Product_Shot_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_Outdoor_Product_Shot_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>Outdoor product shots.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Ricard_T-Shirt_Closeup_or_Flag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Ricard by Yorgo&#038;Co" />
<figcaption>It&#8217;s either a closeup of the t-shirt or a flag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>In the end, Ricard’s latest redesign is a bold and strategic leap into the future. By holding onto the sun — whether in its intricate sunburst form or as this sleek minimalist circle — the brand stays true to its roots while embracing a fresh, modern aesthetic. Ricard has always been about capturing the essence of sunny afternoons, good company, and the perfect aperitif, and this new design honors that spirit with a simplicity that feels both timeless and contemporary. The iconic blue-and-yellow palette remains, evolving just enough to keep the brand feeling vibrant while preserving its equity.</p>

<p class="end">With this redesign, Ricard positions itself perfectly for a new generation of drinkers. This ain&#8217;t your grandpa&#8217;s pastis; it’s modern, approachable, and effortlessly cool. While I may miss the clever sunburst-R hybrid, the clean, confident yellow circle signals a brand ready for its next chapter. Hopefully, by finding the sweet spot between tradition and modernity, it’ll continue to shine.</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco_2.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_ricard_by_yorgoco_2.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Announced: Limited Posts this Week &#038; Next</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Back to Regular Schedule Oct. 14”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/2024_09_30_Limited_Posts_BN.jpg" alt="Limited Posts this Week &amp; Next" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>With the <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnewconference/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brand New Conference</a> happening next Thursday and Friday I will not have time to prepare the full range of posts this week and next but our guest writers will fill in with Reviewed posts from Monday through Thursday. We will be back with full content on October 14. Thank you for your patience with this.</p>

<p>Speaking of the conference… Live Webcast registration closes next Tuesday, October 8!</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/limited_posts_this_week_next.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/limited_posts_this_week_next.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“All the Ball Things”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/goodsport_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>
Founded by Jordan Mahy, <a href="https://www.goodsportbhm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Good Sport</a> is a Birmingham, AL-based film and photo studio that provides local brands and businesses with video strategy and high-quality content. They worked with fellow Birmingham, AL-based <a href="https://www.wearematey.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matey</a> on a new identity, including a new name, to transition from an independent practice to a full-fledged content company.
</p>
<span id="more-298451"></span>

<blockquote>
Mahy&#8217;s deep-rooted conviction to champion local businesses gave birth to his new company. This conviction became the company&#8217;s key differentiator within the film and photo industry &#8211; Content for local businesses should be, above all, practical and easy to understand. We identified attributes that embodied this philosophy — community-focused, uplifting, and positive — and used them to shape the brand&#8217;s tone of voice, positioning, name, and identity.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.wearematey.com/work/good-sport" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matey Project Page</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_horizontal.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_drop-shadow_animated.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Logo with drop shadow.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_monogram.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Monogram.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_mascot.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Mascot logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_logo_suite.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Logo suite.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The old logo, under the former name &#8220;Mahy Visuals,&#8221; was functional, set in an inoffensive sans serif framed in crop marks that suggested something vaguely technical. The previous name was fine but probably not great for SEO purposes—Google kept asking if I meant &#8220;math,&#8221; &#8220;make,&#8221; or maybe &#8220;Matt.&#8221; Needless to say, &#8220;Good Sport&#8221; is a more distinct and ownable upgrade.
</p> 
<p>
There&#8217;s plenty to discuss regarding the new logo suite—it features four variations (five if you include the drop shadow variant). I&#8217;d say that&#8217;s one or two too many, but fortunately, they are all done well and quite charming. The custom lettered primary logo has a handcrafted feel, with some slightly quirky characters and a little flourish kick on the &#8216;R&#8217;. It especially pops with a bold drop shadow, giving a retro-inspired vibe that sets the tone for the brand. There&#8217;s a clever monogram that incorporates an &#8216;S&#8217; within the negative space of the &#8216;G&#8217;. Viewing it now, the two letters in one are extremely obvious and hard to unsee, but I actually didn&#8217;t even notice the &#8216;S&#8217; at first. It had a nice surprise factor for me, often an indicator of a good monogram.
</p> 
<p>
Next up to the plate, there&#8217;s a set of mascots formed from the &#8216;G&#8217; and &#8216;S,&#8217; which are undeniably sweet but perhaps one of the variants that could stay on the bench. Then again, what&#8217;s a good sports team without a mascot? (Actually, as a Dodgers fan, I take that back.) While delightful, they aren&#8217;t used much throughout the applications. Maybe they&#8217;d work better if they had a more significant role—like a modern-day <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Office_Assistant" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Clippy</a>, guiding users throughout the web experience. Lastly, there&#8217;s a logo lock-up that introduces two new fonts, which continues to make some of these choices feel a bit excessive. Why not stick with the primary logo typeface here? But again, despite the possible superfluity, each logo is well-crafted so it&#8217;s hard to be mad.
</p> 

<blockquote>
We arrived at the name and tagline Good Sport &#8211; a film and photo studio that Roots for the Home Teams. The Good Sport brand draws inspiration from baseball&#8217;s golden age—an era when communities came together to cheer on a celebrate local wins. This theme permeates every aspect of the brand, from its friendly mascots and classic monogram logo to its website featuring case studies designed as custom baseball cards. Even the promotional leave-behind—peanuts grown and roasted in Mahy&#8217;s hometown—reinforces the message: Good Sport is here to champion local businesses.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.wearematey.com/work/good-sport" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matey Project Page</a></h3>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_color-palette.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_typography_1.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_photography_3.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_case-study-cards.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Case study cards.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_brand-guidelines.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Brand guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
In case it wasn&#8217;t obvious from the logo suite, the entire identity draws from the golden age of baseball, including classic baseball card layouts for case study thumbnails, a &#8220;root for the home team&#8221; slogan, and even some roasted peanuts, answering the age-old brand question, &#8220;Will it peanut?&#8221; The secondary fonts further bolster the retro goodness featuring the lovely condensed Sandcastle JNL by <a href="https://www.fontspring.com/foundry/jeff-levine" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeff Levine</a> and the vintage-inspired script Lonsdale by <a href="https://typodermicfonts.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Typodermic</a>. Both integrate seamlessly with the identity, enhancing the throwback vibe. Highway and Neue Haas by <a href="https://www.linotype.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Linotype</a> also make appearances, which again raises the question: are there one too many fonts? But to be fair, Neue Haas does serve as the primary body font on the website, so it at least makes sense in context.
</p> 

<p>
The color palette is a timeless mix of muted primary tones that amount to a masculine vibe, with the exception of hot pink. I&#8217;d love to see more of it in use but I can find only one instance in one of the case study card layouts. I personally love a good hot pink getting thrown into a more masculine identity. It would inject some unexpected nuance and dynamism into an otherwise subdued color scheme.
</p> 


<p>
With all these elements plus the name, you can&#8217;t blame me for concluding that the company solely focuses on sports-themed visuals. That, however, is not the case at all, with a portfolio that spans a wide range of industries, from bookstores to tea to hospitals. I do wonder if this heavy emphasis on the sports aesthetic could limit future client acquisition or expansion. While the tone they want to convey is certainly here — “light-hearted, team-focused, and passionate” — is it all a bit too kitschy?
</p> 


<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_business-cards_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Business card.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_postcard_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Postcard.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 60.25%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_video.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_3.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_website_mobile_1.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_peanuts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Peanuts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_spray-paint.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Mascot logo spray paint.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_sticker.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Sticker.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/goodsport_hat.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Good Sport by Matey" />
<figcaption>Hat.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">     
Even as a baseball lover (did I mention &#8220;go Dodgers&#8221;?) I remain skeptical if going all-in on a baseball theme for a company that is not strictly about the sport is the best long-term strategy. That said, if I were a potential client, I&#8217;d much rather see this type of creativity and thinking outside the (batter&#8217;s) box. Good Sport&#8217;s video production itself evokes some of the hallmarks of classic baseball: nostalgia, romance, the warmth of late summer evenings. Plus, the identity is simply really well-made. In that sense, it all works for a production house that delivers classic, high-quality work.
</p>


                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_good_sport_by_matey.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_good_sport_by_matey.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for National Black Canadians Summit by Six Cinquième</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/blackcanadiansummit_logo_new.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for National Black Canadians Summit by Six Cinquième" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.sixcinquieme.com/projects/nbcs-2025/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_national_black_canadians_summit_by_six_cinquieme.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_national_black_canadians_summit_by_six_cinquieme.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Swag as Economic Barometer</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/interesting_swag_power.jpg" alt="Swag as Economic Barometer" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://thehustle.co/originals/corporate-swag-will-never-diecorporate-swag-will-never-die">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>The Hustle has a pretty interesting article about the economic power and impact of corporate swag and how well it reflects the state of the economy in general. Also, some sobering stats (under the assumption that they are correct) like it being a $26.1-billion industry or how in 2022 ad spending fell by 6% but promotional swag spending was up 12% or when the industry grew three times quicker than the ad sector and 4 times quicker than the U.S. economy as a whole in 2010. Yikes.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/swag_as_economic_barometer.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/swag_as_economic_barometer.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“The Light at the End of the Tower”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/paris_basketaball_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2018) &#8220;<a href="https://parisbasketball.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paris Basketball</a> is a French professional basketball club based in Paris. The club currently plays in the LNB Pro A, the first division of basketball in France, and the EuroLeague since 2024–25. Paris plays its home games at the Adidas Arena. Three years after its establishment, Paris promoted to the first-level LNB Pro A for the first time, in 2021. In 2024, the team won the LNB Pro A Leaders Cup and the 2023–24 EuroCup titles.&#8221; (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paris_Basketball" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wikipedia</a>)</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            Identity: <a href="https://www.studiotyrsa.com/" target="_blank">Studio Tyrsa</a> (Paris, France)<br />Strategy: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/yard/" target="_blank">Yard</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://parisbasketball.com/en/2024/09/paris-basketball-unveils-new-logo/" target="_blank">Paris Basketball press release</a>
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>We teamed up with Yard who came up with a brief and a strategic approach that consisted in highlighting Paris and its basketball culture, as well as the idea of light. The light for the obvious City of Light, but also the one that puts the spotlight on new talents or the one that dazzles our opponents.<br /><br />We didn’t want use to use the Eiffel Tower at first, but after exploring many other options, we quickly realized that the most beautiful source of light in Paris was at the top of the Tower. The mix of the shape of the ball, the tower and the light on top then became an evidence to us. Using the club’s actual colors allowed us to play with them and create a lighting effect. The light became the center of the entire identity, and is present in both our PARIS wordmarks as a dot on the letter I, or as a shooting star that creates the loop of the P in our monogram.<br /><br />In addition to all these elements we’ve also designed a bespoke typeface, inspired by classic basketball fonts but also old Parisian Specimen we found, available in Regular and Italic. It will allow the club to express itself with a unique tone in a way that is consistent with its identity, whether on the back the jerseys, on the screen of the Arena or any communication assets.</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-298460"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_logo.png" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_logo_full.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Logo construction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="background:black;padding-bottom:125%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation. (Unmute for sound.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_icon.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Icon in full color and single color.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_wordmark_03.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_wordmark_01.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_wordmark_02.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Secondary wordmarks.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_secondary_monogram.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Secondary monogram.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_custom_type_01.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_custom_type_02.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Custom typeface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_all_elements.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>All elements.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_uniforms_01.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_uniforms_02.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_uniforms_03.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Uniforms.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/paris_basketball_launch_event.jpg" alt="New Logos for Paris Basketball by Studio Tyrsa" />
<figcaption>Launch event.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo was quite generic with a basic basketball — in a combination of sharp and curved lines that were somewhat poorly drawn — and ill-fitting typography. The name and colors could be changed to any other city and it wouldn't have made a difference. The new logo embraces Paris' number one visual cliché — the Eiffel Tower — and cleverly blends it into the grooves of the basketball through a relatively abstract rendition of the landmark. The addition of the light spark at the top helps draw some attention away from the Eiffel Tower in a positive way so that the logo is not <em>just</em> about the Eiffel Tower and I really like the bright-spark feeling it achieves through the combination of blue, red, and white. The execution of the icon is quite nice too and was probably harder to achieve than it would seem at first glance, mixing the mono-width stroke of the grooves with the thicks and thins of the spark. In heavy contrast with the old typography, the new one goes wide… <em>very</em> wide, wrapping almost the full circumference of the logo and it's mostly good but maybe it ends up being too big.<span></span> The collegiate-looking custom typeface and matching secondary wordmarks are pretty nice as they also have a bit of an urban/industrial feel so it veers away from an American University athletics vibe. The script wordmark is also great but perhaps a little hard to appreciate with so many strokes around it. The monogram starts to feel like a stretch of the concept and the visual language but, like everything else, it is really well done. When seeing all of the assets together the one thing that stands out is that all of the spark elements are different — different angles, different proportions, different skews — and it would have been nice (albeit admittedly difficult) if that was the one element that was more heavily consistent across the myriad styles. Overall, as seen in the uniforms and launch event, everything comes together almost literally in a brilliant way in terms of how luminous the various assets stand out against black backdrops and there is a fun, sport-y energy to all of it.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logos_for_paris_basketball_by_studio_tyrsa.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logos_for_paris_basketball_by_studio_tyrsa.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 510: From Untitled Macao, Micael Micmas, and Purple</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Untitled Macao, Micael Micmas, and Purple”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/friday_likes_510.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 510" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Some eccentricity and quirkiness this week, with work from Macau, João Pessoa, and Stockholm.</p>
<span id="more-298457"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Dino Kiddo by Untitled Macao</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_dinokiddo.jpg" alt="Dino Kiddo by Untitled Macao" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;">Dino Kiddo is a new spin-off-slash-concept from <a href="https://www.instagram.com/dinoburgermacau/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dino Burger</a> in Macau, focusing on hot dogs. (As some of you might remember, <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_395.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">I Liked Dino Burger back in a Friday of 2021</a> — I&#8217;m actually shook this was three years ago as I could have sworn it was so much more recent.) The identity, designed (then and now) by <a href="https://untitledmacao.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Untitled Macao</a>, builds on the quirkiness and eccentricity of the original with a menagerie of crudely-drawn animals — some real, some imagined, some just plan unidentifiable — that are delightful in their weirdness. A funky “Kiddo” logo has been added to the already-weird Dino logo and while the logo shouldn&#8217;t work with its contradicting letterform shapes — some are squiggly, some are not and some are filled in, some are not — and silly googly eyes on top, it&#8217;s perfectly suited for the task. The supporting typography is typeset on weird paths or surrounded by super thick strokes and paired with odd colors but it all just clicks together in its loose approach and basks in its silliness. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://untitledmacao.com/dino-kiddo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Home Burger by Micael Micmas</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_homeburger.jpg" alt="Home Burger by Micael Micmas" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/homeburger.pb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Burger</a> is a burger joint in João Pessoa, a port city in northeastern Brazil, driven by its North Star of “Burger, Fries &amp; Friends”. The identity, designed by local designer <a href="https://www.behance.net/micaelmicmas" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Micael Micmas</a>, is not the most impressive (or cohesive) but, bruh, that “HB” monogram is a thing of beauty and worth celebrating. It would be impressive alone that it managed to blend an “H” and “B” together but to then reveal a hamburger in the negative space? Brilliant. The sign at night is so satisfying too with the dark sky “coloring” the burger in the negative space. As mentioned, the accompanying identity is not amazing but it&#8217;s not bad either… perhaps one too many typefaces without a clear purpose. Nothing a churro couldn&#8217;t make me overlook though. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/199960867/Home-Burger" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Lykke by Purple</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_lykke.jpg" alt="Lykke by Purple" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://www.lykkegardar.se/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lykke</a> is a coffee roaster in Farsta, Sweden, that not just sources its beans from but partners with and invests in farmers around the world. The identity, designed by Stockholm, Sweden-based <a href="https://purplestockholm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Purple</a>, takes matters into their own hands with a charmingly hand-made approach, first in the form of the wobbly rainbow logo and second in the abundance of spray-painted elements that manifest in different ways in the packaging and that also yield a small library of spot illustrations to use across other applications. More than a design system, a playful sensibility extends across the packaging of the multitude of coffee and tea offerings through bright colors, bold typography, and thick hand-drawn elements. If I had to choose one sample to order for keeps it would be <a href="https://www.lykkegardar.se/collections/shop-all/products/ugly-cute" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ugly Cute</a>.  <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://purplestockholm.com/lykke/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_510.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_510.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Next Level Apparel by JAM</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/next_level_apparel_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Next Level Apparel by JAM" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.jam-branding.com/work/next-level-apparel">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_next_level_apparel_by_jam.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_next_level_apparel_by_jam.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>