<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Perkins Restaurant &#038; Bakery by Aria Group and Dunn&#038;Co.</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/perkins_food_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Perkins Restaurant &#038; Bakery by Aria Group and Dunn&amp;Co." />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240625939362/en/Perkins-Restaurant-Bakery-Reintroduces-Itself-as-Perkins-American-Food-Co.-Revealing-Bold-New-Brand-Identity">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_perkins_restaurant_co.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_perkins_restaurant_co.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Leak of Faith</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/news_jaguar_inhouse_team_memo.jpg" alt="Leak of Faith" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.thedrive.com/news/leaked-memo-reveals-jaguar-designers-were-worried-about-rebranding-years-ago">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Autocar India acquired a copy of a leaked letter from Jaguar’s internal design team to Gerry McGovern, Jaguar Land Rover&#8217;s Chief Creative Officer, that dates back to 2022 and was signed by approximately 25 members. In it, the team expresses their disappointment of not being given the task — which was reportedly given to external consultants Accenture Interactive (who? what?) — and of the discrepancy of the new logo and the ambitions of the new era.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leak_of_faith.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leak_of_faith.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Brice for Impact”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/back_to_nature_logo_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1960) &#8220;Founded in California, <a href="https://www.backtonaturefoods.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Back to Nature</a> features a portfolio of plant-based, non-GMO products such as cookies, crackers, granola and nuts &#038; trail mix categories. We got our start in a tiny health food store in California and helped plant the seeds of today’s natural foods movement before it was cool. Today we’re still living the good life, remaking America’s favorite snacks with honest-to-goodness ingredients. Radiating good vibes and a sunshine state of mind, we are committed to delivering super tasty snacks. That’s Back to Nature snacking all the way. Simple joys, no regrets, happy days.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.lovecreative.com/" target="_blank">LOVE</a> (Manchester, UK)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                             N/A
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>LOVE was briefed to revitalize the brand to drive consumer awareness in an increasingly saturated market, informing a cohesive, insight-led strategy alongside sunny new creative, for a brand that felt “full of” instead of “free-from”.<br /><br />The redesign features a refreshed logo inspired by the Californian sunrise, incorporating Back to Nature’s iconic leaf as a tribute to its pioneering role in the natural food movement, with typography tapping into vintage-style sign writing, reminiscent of old-school screen prints. A striking color palette and flavor-forward product photography bring the packaging to life, emphasizing taste and quality while connecting with today’s consumers.<br /><br />The rebrand also debuted a new tagline, “Tasty Snacks Since Way Back,” paired with a confident, easy-going tone of voice that highlights the brand’s rich history while making it approachable and current. Targeting a new audience of “Snack Surfers” – real people browsing the aisles – the new identity captures a ‘modern retro’ look that channels the laid-back spirit of 1960s California, where Back to Nature was born–blending nostalgia with contemporary appeal.<br /><br />The packaging overhaul spans over 30 product SKUs, including cookies, crackers, nuts, and granola, and uses a palette of vivid, punchy colors—individually chosen for their visual links to the West Coast—for an irresistible on-shelf presence. A whole suite of key brand assets was also crafted, including an array of bold stickers designed to ramp up brand personality.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-302085"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_identity_overview.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Identity overview.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_photography.gif" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Packaging, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_before_after_in_the_wild.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Packaging, before and after, caught in the wild by <a href="https://lancecraig.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lance Craig</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_hero_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_hero_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Cookies and crackers packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Cookies packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_03_crackers.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_04_crackers.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Crackers packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_05_granola.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_06_granola.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Granola packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_07_nuts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_packaging_detail_08_nuts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Nuts packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/back_to_nature_instagram_posts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Back to Nature by LOVE" />
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo wasn't particularly well executed and it had a very generic look to it with its script-ish type and large embedded leaves but it certainly looked the part of an organic food brand. The new logo is more playful and engaging but perhaps a little too trendy and generic in a new kind of way in the context of all the direct-to-consumer brands on the market that use quirky typography, many of them down to the choice of <a href="https://www.myfonts.com/collections/brice-font-studio-sun?refby=ucllc" target="_blank">Brice</a>. As fun as Brice is it is now, unfortunately, heavily overused and has lost any semblance of originality or uniqueness. On the flipside, that same abundance of it has transformed it into an easy visual shorthand for fun consumer brands that something more relatively mainstream like Back to Nature can easily adopt. Brice diatribe aside, this is actually a fun, attractive logo that cleverly integrates a leaf into the “K” and neatly stacks the three words of the name into a cohesive unit. I feel like the arched typography needed a whole lot more finesse and TLC to get some of those curves and flares to flow a little bit better.<span></span> The packaging is a huge improvement, mostly thanks to abandoning that burlap texture in the background that made the cookies and crackers look like they would be the driest thing you could put into your mouth and that the products would taste… <em>organic</em> (e.g. I'm sure their “classic creme” cookies pale in comparison to the flavor explosion of a chemically-enhanced Oreo). The packaging now simply looks fun and attractive by sidestepping all the strong, Non-GMO visual signals the old packaging was giving out. The tone-on-tone approach across the different flavors looks good and the new photography makes the products look more craveable.<span></span> The one really odd thing is the sliver of a highlight and inner drop shadow on the logo and all of the typography… I have the feeling the feedback during testing was that the tone-on-tone approach didn't <em>pop</em> enough so they had to resort to this approach to separate the logo and type from the background and I bet it looked infinitely better without them. In real life, as evidenced by Lance's photo from the field, the highlight and shadow almost look like an off-register printing mistake. Overall, few complaints aside, this is actually a very strong evolution for the product's shelf presence that makes it infinitely more attractive to an ever-more, more visually-discerning consumer.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_back_to_nature_by_love.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_back_to_nature_by_love.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 521: From Indego Design, OStudio, and Zoo Studio</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Indego Design, OStudio, and Zoo Studio”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/friday_likes_521.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 521" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>A trio of super-short names — arguably all of them having only three letters each if we didn&#8217;t count the possessive “s” and apostrophe in Ohm’s — presented in strikingly different aesthetics, with work from Macau, Riyadh, and Barcelona.</p>
<span id="more-302082"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">BOL by Indego Design</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_bol.jpg" alt="BOL by Indego Design" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.bolmacau.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BOL</a> is a fashion brand that combines &#8220;Japanese urban laziness and functional practical style&#8221; to offer the “perfect blend of urban sentiment and outdoor style”, all of which sounds like the vibe I never knew I was aiming for in life. The identity, designed by Macau, China-based <a href="https://indegodesign.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Indego Design</a>, is built around a unique “B” design that is hard to tell where it starts and where it ends or what its negative space is and what its positive space is but it&#8217;s most certainly eye-catching. There is also a bit of a discrepancy between the description of the brand and this far more tightly structured and controlled design that isn&#8217;t particularly <em>lazy</em> but I&#8217;m assuming that&#8217;s of less concern to the audience and, on its own, it&#8217;s a super slick packaging system, thanks in part to the combination of that smokey blue color and the “B” in a bold, black. The secondary wordmark is pretty cool too and, more importantly, the clothes slap. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://indegodesign.com/project/57" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Ohm&#8217;s Cafe by OStudio</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_ohms.jpg" alt="Ohm's Cafe by OStudio" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ohms_cafe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ohm&#8217;s Cafe</a> is a cafe and bakery in Buraydah, Saudi Arabia, serving beautifully created pastries and rich drink concoctions. The identity, designed by Riyadh, Saudi Arabia-based <a href="https://ostudio.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OStudio</a>, introduces a lovely wordmark with a couple of exaggerated strokes in the ascender of the “h” and the curvature of the “m” that not only give it plenty of personality but that are also reminiscent of Arabic script, down to the diamond-shaped apostrophe. The logo looks particularly good on cups as its wide proportions wrap around them but then the tall “h” nicely fills up the space. The mint, black, and white color palette is simple, elegant, and a great backdrop for all of its food and caffeine offerings. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://ostudio.net/portfolio/ohms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Gil by Zoo Studio</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_gilbakery.jpg" alt="Gil by Zoo Studio" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://forngil.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gil</a> is a family-owned bakery in Barcelona, Spain, now in its fourth generation of family ownership, which has revitalized the company&#8217;s breads and won plenty of awards for them as it serves the city from three locations. The identity, designed by Barcelona-based <a href="https://zoo.ad/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zoo Studio</a>, leads with a simple, bold wordmark that has been customized from the free <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Fraunces" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fraunces</a> with a bigger, round-ier tittle that gets perfectly nested in the tightly-spaced logo. The chunky logo is paired with more Fraunces but in its light weight and the quirky script, <a href="https://commercialtype.com/catalog/candy_darling" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Candy Darling</a> — <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnewconference/2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a personal favorite</a>. These are all delivered in a minimalist and elegant black and white color palette with some solid typographic hierarchy while some of the packaging (not shown above) adds straight-up photography of the products that look great against the black and white in their natural light brown colors. Oh to be in Barcelona this morning… <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://zoo.ad/project/gil-forn-de-pa-i-pastisseria/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_521.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_521.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 10:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Jack Data by Antoine Peltier</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/jackdata_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Jack Data by Antoine Peltier" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://antoinepeltier.com/projets/jackdata-analyse-donnees">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_jack_data_by_antoine_peltier.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_jack_data_by_antoine_peltier.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Transamerica by Total Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/transamerica_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Transamerica by Total Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.transamerica.com/press-release/transamerica-launches-vibrant-new-look-its-brand-reinforcing-pledge-help-middle">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_transamerica.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_transamerica.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Burnett to the Ground</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/news_leo_constellation.jpg" alt="Burnett to the Ground" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.publicisgroupe.com/en/news/press-releases/publicis-groupe-launches-leo-a-new-creative-constellation-uniting-publicis-worldwide-and-leo-burnett">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Parent company Publicis Groupe has announced it will unite two of its flagship companies, Publicis Worldwide and Leo Burnett, under one new name: Leo. Billed as a “creative constellation” the new company will have 15,000 employees in offices in 90 countries and has been “designed to drive exponential creativity in the age of AI for the world’s biggest global brands”. A 5-minute launch film, embedded in the comments below, goes further into the change. 
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/burnett_to_the_ground.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/burnett_to_the_ground.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 10:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Ready to Launch”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/rocket_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1985) &#8220;<a href="https://www.rocketcompanies.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rocket Companies</a> is a Detroit-based fintech platform company including mortgage, real estate and personal finance businesses Rocket Mortgage, Rocket Homes, Rocket Close, Rocket Money and Rocket Loans. With more than 65 million call logs each year, 10 petabytes of data and a mission to Help Everyone Home, Rocket Companies is well positioned to be the destination for AI-fueled homeownership. Known for providing exceptional client experiences, J.D. Power has ranked Rocket Mortgage #1 in client satisfaction for primary mortgage origination and mortgage servicing a total of 22 times – the most of any mortgage lender.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.otherway.com/" target="_blank">Otherway</a> (London, UK)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.otherway.com/work/rocket" target="_blank">Otherway project page</a><br /><a href="https://www.rocketcompanies.com/press-release/rocket-companies-unifies-under-the-rocket-brand-with-new-visual-identity/" target="_blank">Rocket press release</a><br /><a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_rocket_mortgage_by_lippincott.php" target="_blank">2016 Brand New Noted post</a>
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>At the heart of the rebrand, the new Halo logo marks a significant evolution of Rocket’s original branding, building on the strong recognition the company has already established. This reimagined logo blends elements of the past with an optimistic vision for the future. The Halo itself is a universal symbol of trust, representing the support and commitment Rocket offers to its clients, employees, and the wider community. The inclusion of the letter ‘R’ at the heart of the logo not only anchors the brand’s identity but also conveys a sense of progression and innovation, reflecting Rocket’s embrace of technology and AI in the homeownership journey.<br /><br />The updated Rocket wordmark draws inspiration from the company’s history but has been carefully redrawn to look towards the future. The refined design brings a new level of detail and craftsmanship to the name, moving away from block capitals to title case.<br /><br />To ensure consistency across all touchpoints, we collaborated with font foundry TypeType to create two bespoke typefaces that reflect the brand’s values and vision. WNTL (What’s Not To Like) is a modern sans serif that exudes freshness, innovation, and approachability. In contrast, Bowtie is a classic serif, designed to inspire trust and reassurance while maintaining warmth and character. Both typefaces are named in honour of Dan Gilbert’s late son, Nick Gilbert, reflecting the personal and emotional connection at the heart of Rocket’s mission.<br /><br />A core component of the new identity is a clear and agile grid system, built for design at scale – designed to unify the brand across all touchpoints. Tested for usability from button to billboard, this system allows in-house design teams and external agencies to work seamlessly together, ensuring greater consistency and familiarity for customers.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-302045"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_sub_brands.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<figcaption>Sub-brands.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_sub_brands_a.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_app_icon_b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Sub-brands and app icon.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_custom_type_sans_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_custom_type_sans_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_custom_type_sans_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Custom typeface “What&#8217;s Not To Like”. By <a href="https://typetype.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TypeType</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_custom_type_serif_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_custom_type_serif_02_a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_custom_type_serif_02_b.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Custom typeface “Bowtie”. By <a href="https://typetype.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TypeType</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_photography.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="background:black;padding-bottom:66.6666667%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_layout_system.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Layout system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Rocket Companies by Otherway" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="background:black;padding-bottom:100%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_advertising_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/rocket_conference_stage.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Conference stage.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1047301402?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo, designed by <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_rocket_mortgage_by_lippincott.php" target="_blank">Lippincott</a>, was mostly fine, embedding a slightly ambiguous “O” — in the sense that it's meaning or intention weren't 100% clear — that, to me, showed an abstracted individual in its negative space but it also looked a bit like an upside down power button or a speedometer. It was kind of clever how the “O” looked like the “C” next to it but rotated and it didn't sacrifice readability. The one issue with the logo is that it emphasized the “O” too much as opposed to the initial “R”. The new logo addresses this by extracting the main graphic device from within the wordmark and transforming it into a standalone icon that doubles as an “R” in its negative space.<span></span> Nicknamed “Halo”, the new icon's ambitions are overly lofty, supposedly representing “a universal symbol of trust,” where the “circular form creates a protective arc, representing the journey to homeownership and the building of prosperity and generational wealth.” It's a nice thought but, um, no, none of that at all is actually achieved by the icon. Maybe it will, one day, based on the various Rocket companies creating that association but, for now, it's just an abstract “R”, which is fine as it provides the company a somewhat distinctive graphic asset to unify all of its offerings. The wordmark, typeset in the new custom sans serif, looks pretty good and the word “Rocket” looks so much better in regular title case than the more oppressive all-uppercase treatment in the old logo. All of the sub-brands in the matching sans serif work fine, although some of those will be super long so I wouldn't be surprised if, in a few years, they introduce a new treatment where the secondary words are executed differently. (Actually, <a href="https://www.rocketcompanies.com/our-companies/" target="_blank">looking at their website</a>, it seems sub-brands are stacked, leaving the icon feeling a little XL.)<span></span> Most of the identity so far seems to rely on the custom sans serif so time will tell how the custom serif is integrated. It feels a little too editorial to match well with the sans but, yeah, we'll see. Also, try not to cry when you see the video at the end that explains where the names of the two typefaces came from. The identity is a little barebones with just the sans serif typeface and some rounded-cornered frames for photography. Nothing out of the ordinary but the photography is kind of endearing and I'm somewhat touched by the main message of “Help everyone home”… it's an interesting play on the word “home” to transform it into a verb. Overall, it seems Rocket has big ambitions of becoming a loved brand that <em>owns</em> the category of homeownership and its role in achieving the American Dream, which the logo and identity, so far, fall a little short on but a promised, upcoming ad in the Super Bowl might help.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_rocket_companies_by_otherway.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_rocket_companies_by_otherway.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 10:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“If not WHEN, when?”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/when_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>
Founded in 2022, <a href="https://www.whenfertility.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">WHEN</a> is Australia’s first fertility MedTech company to offer at-home egg count testing. Combining their globally patented collection technology with access to leading fertility experts, WHEN aims to provide people with tools and knowledge to help them better navigate their fertility and reproductive journeys. In 2024, the company launched a new identity designed by Sydney, Australia-based <a href="https://universalfavourite.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Universal Favourite</a>.
</p>
<span id="more-302007"></span>


<blockquote>
The WHEN wordmark sits at the heart of the visual identity. Clear and confident, it anchors the brand as a dependable figure in the health and medical space. Paired with an organic cell shape that reacts to the world around it, the wordmark and logoform are a perfect foil to the other. Together, they represent standing strong amid the ever-changing nature of life.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://universalfavourite.com.au/work/when-fertility-branding" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Universal Favourite project page</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_00_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Wordmark.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"  style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_01_logo_animated.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Wordmark within organic cell shape logoform, animated.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_02_logo_manifesto.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Brand manifesto.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>
The WHEN wordmark could not be any more straightforward. Made up of four of the alphabet’s simplest capital letters set in a nondescript grotesk (<a href="https://abcdinamo.com/typefaces/diatype" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dinamo&#8217;s ABC Diatype</a>, to make it non-nondescript… more on that shortly), it could likely be recreated by a 3rd grader with access to Microsoft Word in all of 16 seconds and most of us would be none the wiser. But as we have all reminded clients and friends and parents and coworkers and strangers on the internet time and time again: a brand is so much more than just a logo.
</p>
<p>
I actually love this minimalist, brutalist type treatment for a disruptor brand in an industry that typically comes off as too calm and too pleasant and too saccharinely feminine. The all caps treatment gives an edgy, almost harsh confidence to a word that is often posed as a question — the perfect metaphor for the brand’s goal to empower the consumer with the knowledge and tools to answer that question themselves. And by pairing the wordmark with an organic, amoebic blob, the harshness is softened ever so slightly, indicating a much more nuanced brand than the wordmark alone would suggest.
</p>


<blockquote>
WHEN&#8217;s typeface is ABC Diatype. It&#8217;s used for everything—from wordmark to body copy. Chosen for its modernity and scientific edge, it brings calm and clarity to everything we say. Paired with a colour palette of lemon and neutrals, the identity feels light and warm against an industry so often cold and clinical.
<br><br/>
Our primary photography style uses intimate portraits and close crops to focus on the subject’s internal thoughts and feelings. We aim to capture moments that feel like a natural extension of everyday life, empowering and relatable in their familiarity. As a secondary style, we splice natural textures and fluid forms with our portraits, like fragments of memory telling the story of a person’s inner world.
<br><br/>
To further enhance this sense of intimacy, a series of icons were developed to capture the different states of mind one might feel around this sensitive and personal topic. Following the same visual language as the logo, these icons add flexibility and expression to the brand, especially when used with the intimate portraiture.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://universalfavourite.com.au/work/when-fertility-branding" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Universal Favourite project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_03_color_type.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Typeface and color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_04_photography_type.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Photography and typography examples.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_05_icons.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Icon set.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_06_bento.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>UI examples that showcase visual system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_08_print.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_09_print.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Print applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>
The visual language of the brand feels like a very natural extension of the logo system. A one-typeface brand can be pretty hard to pull off — especially with a product that requires a lot of text in the form of scientific explanation — but the mix of type and negative space, combined with thoughtful text placement and large scale imagery all creates a balanced simplicity that maintains visual intrigue, and manages to avoid veering too far into early-days-of-the-internet-aesthetic territory.
</p>
<p>
I have personally always been a fan of the neutral-palette-plus-neon-pop approach to color, and think that it works well here for the same reasons the logo works — it’s not the expected pink, purple, and/or blue that tends to dominate the space, but it still suits the compassion-meets-science ethos of the brand. It is a fairly trendy palette and potentially runs the risk of feeling dated in a few years, but given how simple the majority of the identity is, I’d argue the neon is a necessary burst of energy to keep the identity feeling fresh. Shout out to the packaging designers though, because I can’t imagine that’s a fun one to work with in print.
</p>


<blockquote>
An important first touchpoint was the at-home testing kit—the Egg Count Check. The kit is split into three sections: Prepare, Collect, and Send. We designed the packaging experience to follow the same logical structure, ensuring the steps were simple to follow and easy to use. Inspired by the sleek aesthetic of our favourite tech brands, the kit’s box takes a rigid form with special attention paid to premium print finishes. We also created a custom instruction booklet to guide the user through the process, designed and illustrated in-house.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://universalfavourite.com.au/work/when-fertility-branding" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Universal Favourite project page</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_10_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_11_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_12_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_13_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_14_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_15_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_16_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_17_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_18_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_19_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_20_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Test kit packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_22_retail_storefront.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Brick and mortar storefront.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_21_retail_sign.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>Retail sign.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_23_OOH.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_24_OOH.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_25_OOH.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_26_OOH.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<hr/>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_27_OOH.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for When Fertility by Universal Favourite" />
<figcaption>OOH applications.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>
The applications come together pretty seamlessly and generally serve to further cultivate the brand’s clean, calming-yet-legitimate energy. My one criticism here is that the lifestyle photography, while immaculately vibey and aesthetic, isn’t doing a whole lot to add to the brand story beyond looking pretty— it’s actually kind of giving generic medication advertisement (i.e. woman spinning around in a field while 200 grisly potential side effects are listed at breakneck speed), making me wish they had played it a little less safe in that arena.
</p>

<blockquote>
The brand name itself is a question—when? But it’s also a statement of intent. We worked with copywriter Amy Scott to develop a verbal concept exploring the idea of an inner monologue, giving voice to the questions we ask ourselves but perhaps never verbalise. The brand speaks as an empathetic expert, both insightful and inclusive. By creating space for open conversation and asking the questions people ask themselves, we show no matter where they’re at in their fertility journey, they’re not alone.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://universalfavourite.com.au/work/when-fertility-branding" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Universal Favourite project page</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_28_social.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Social media examples.</figcaption>
</figure>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_29_website.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>
WHEN doesn’t only set to change fertility testing, but to also facilitate an aspirational platform that aims to drive community and empowering conversation around fertility. The brand was crafted to grow into a multidimensional platform for fertility information access and support. We helped design the first step of this journey through WHEN Matters—a curated blog for sharing real fertility stories and credible medical expertise to ensure no one with ovaries was left feeling alone on their journey.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://universalfavourite.com.au/work/when-fertility-branding" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Universal Favourite project page</a></h3>


<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_30_blog_logo.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Wordmark for blog.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_31_blog.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Blog.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/when_32_blog_stories.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Examples of stories featured on the blog.</figcaption>
</figure>


<p>
We do get one small surprise with the blog sub-branding, where the introduction of a serif into the wordmark (gasp) adds a considered, editorial feel that takes it from “blog” to “publication.” Given that a big part of the company’s mission is education and knowledge-sharing, this distinction seems like a wise play that gives them room to grow beyond just the product side of the business. 
</p>
<p class="end">
Having witnessed the myriad of complex and nuanced emotions surrounding the reproductive planning process, I can easily imagine ten dozen ways that a brand operating in this delicate space could have gone devastatingly wrong. However, Universal Favourite has crafted an artful balance with WHEN— organic yet structured, compassionate yet scientific, disruptive yet approachable — that I suspect will take it far in winning over the trust of its audience.
</p>


                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_when_fertility_by_universal_favourite.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_when_fertility_by_universal_favourite.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Announced: First Round NYC 2025: Speakers Announced</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Early-bird Prices end February 16”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/First_Round_2025_NYC__Full_Lineup_WIDE.jpg" alt="First Round NYC 2025: Speakers Announced" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Speakers announced for <a href="https://underconsideration.com/firstround/2025-new-york/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Round in New York on May 9, 2025</a>!

<h6>Speakers</h6>
<p>
Thomas Wilder of <a href="https://wolffolins.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wolff Olins</a><br />
Jennifer Kinon of <a href="https://www.championsdesign.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Champions Design</a><br />
Aporva Baxi &amp; Simon Dixon of <a href="https://www.dixonbaxi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DixonBaxi</a><br />
Jessie McGuire of <a href="https://www.thoughtmatter.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ThoughtMatter</a><br />
Alec Tear of <a href="https://alectear.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alec Tear Ltd</a><br />
Veronica Fuerte of <a href="https://heystudio.es/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hey</a><br />
Gabriela Carnabuci &amp; Claren Walker of <a href="https://portorocha.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PORTO ROCHA</a><br />
Blayne Clark &amp; Marlon Darbeau of <a href="https://praktis.design/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Praktis Design</a><br />
Carolina Ortiz of <a href="https://espina.studio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Espina Studio</a><br />
Jon Contino of <a href="https://continostudio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Contino Studio</a><br />
Abby Haddican of <a href="https://www.abbyhaddican.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Abby Haddican Studio</a> and
Julie Kucinski of <a href="https://www.pitchwell.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pitchwell</a><br />
Nick Ace of <a href="https://www.wearecollins.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">COLLINS</a>
</p>

<p>&mdash;</p>

<p><strong>Early-bird prices will end on February 16.</strong></p>
<p>&mdash;</p>

                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/first_round_nyc_2025_speakers_announced.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/first_round_nyc_2025_speakers_announced.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>