<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Mophie</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/mophie_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Mophie" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2024/10/31/2972830/0/en/new-look-same-power-mophie-unveils-new-brand-identity-redesigned-website-and-logo.html">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_mophie.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_mophie.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Taco Bell goes Decade-nt</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/nice_taco_bell_decades.jpg" alt="Taco Bell goes Decade-nt" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.tacobell.com/newsroom/taco-bell-brings-back-nostalgic-fan-favorites-in-nationwide-decades-menu">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Starting October 31, Taco Bell is reviving five of the most demanded nostalgic menu items from its first five decades, which will include the ’60s Tostada, the ’70s Green Sauce Burrito, the ’80s Meximelt, and the ’90s Gordita Supreme. To go along with these, limited-edition stainless-steel Decades Cups and limited-edition Decades Hoodies will be released.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/taco_bell_goes_decade_nt.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/taco_bell_goes_decade_nt.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Better off Red”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chicago_stars_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2006, previously Chicago Red Stars) &#8220;<a href="https://chicagoredstars.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chicago Stars Football Club</a> (Chicago Stars FC or just Chicago Stars), are a professional women&#8217;s soccer club based in Bridgeview, Illinois, a suburb of Chicago. A founding member of the Women&#8217;s Professional Soccer (WPS) league, they have played in the National Women&#8217;s Soccer League (NWSL) since 2013. The Red Stars play their home games at SeatGeek Stadium in Bridgeview. In October 2022, they held the record for the longest active playoff streak (2015–2022) in the NWSL. On October 23, 2024 the team announced a name change to ‘Chicago Stars Football Club’, dropping ‘Red’ and adding ‘Football Club’, to take effect during the 2024–25 offseason.&#8221; (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicago_Red_Stars" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wikipedia</a>)</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.rabeandbirch.com/" target="_blank">Rabe x Birch</a> (Beacon, NY)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://chicagoredstars.com/stars/" target="_blank">Chicago Stars FC brand page</a><br /><a href="https://chicagoredstars.com/news/chicago-red-stars-unveil-new-name-and-crest/" target="_blank">Chicago Stars FC press release</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>The new Chicago Stars FC logo will continue to honor Chicago with iconic elements, most notably, the red star at the heart of the crest. Similar to the stars on the Chicago flag that represent meaningful moments in Chicago history, the star at the center of the crest represents the club’s players: past, present and future. Placing the players at the heart of the club has been a priority for the new Chicago Stars FC ownership group since the start of their tenure last year, and the star on the crest is a symbolic representation of that commitment.<br /><br />More subtle nods to Chicago include the curved shape at the top of the crest that is meant to resemble the marquees found across the city including that of the Chicago Theatre and the Wrigley Field marquee; the site of the Red Stars’ record-breaking Red Stars Takeover Wrigley Field match. The blues that fill the crest also hold a subtle nod to the city as the adjoining of the “Night Sky” and “Great Lake” blues symbolize the meeting between the land and lake.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-299629"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_logo.png" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_logo_type.png" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<figcaption>Standalone wordmark.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_merch_01.jpg" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_merch_02.jpg" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_merch_03.jpg" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_merch_04.jpg" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_merch_05.jpg" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<figcaption>Lots of merch.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/chicago_stars_city_launch.jpg" alt="New Logo for Chicago Stars Football Club by Rabe x Birch" />
<figcaption>Launch promos.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hlhJsdVyhQ0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Intro video.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            While there was no official statement on why exactly “Red” was dropped from the name, <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/athletic/5866012/2024/10/23/chicago-red-stars-new-name-logo/" target="_blank">this article in <em>The Athletic</em></a> sheds some light: “Often people shorten our name to ‘Red Stars’, and then the ‘Chicago’ goes away. So by removing ‘Red’ from the name, the short version will be ‘Chicago Stars’, so that we keep that connection with our city.” With so many other sports teams that have “Stars” as their name or part of their name, it seems counterintuitive to get rid of the one thing that made this “Stars” different. The counter argument to that is that now “Chicago” is what makes this “Stars” special and, to their credit, Chicago Stars works so much better with the other local teams: Chicago Bulls, Chicago Cubs, Chicago Bears. So, it has its pros and cons.<span></span> The old logo was okay but it did cram a lot of different elements and styles into one crest with the city flag's elements and colors, some bonus stripes and strokes, and a couple of typefaces lacking any cohesion. The new logo simplifies things with a cleaner and simpler design featuring a single red star supported by smaller navy stars that help shape a soccer ball. The condensed “STARS” looks great as it arches over the ball and it's so fortuitous that the “TAR” letters can all be easily cropped on the bottom to match the circumference of the ball while the two “S”s sit comfortably on the sides without requiring any curvature.  The “CHICAGO” bit at the top is a nice nod to <a href="https://accidentallywesanderson.com/places/the-chicago-theatre/" target="_blank">one of the city's most recognizable landmarks</a> while the curve at the top of the crest echoes the shape <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=wrigley+field+marquee&amp;sca_esv=36885d2c0b4f145e&amp;udm=2&amp;biw=1934&amp;bih=1078&amp;sxsrf=ADLYWIIfX3aghey5l7-CjYCezKVYwT2S1w%3A1730465231303&amp;ei=z80kZ5mcEobPp84PltP02Qc&amp;ved=&amp;uact=5&amp;oq=wrigley+field+marquee&amp;gs_lp=EgNpbWciFXdyaWdsZXkgZmllbGQgbWFycXVlZTIFEAAYgAQyBRAAGIAEMgUQABiABDIFEAAYgAQyBRAAGIAEMgUQABiABDIFEAAYgAQyBBAAGB4yBBAAGB4yBBAAGB5I3xBQsAZYqw9wAngAkAEAmAGQAqABuAaqAQU0LjAuMrgBA8gBAPgBAZgCCKAC0AbCAgoQABiABBhDGIoFwgIGEAAYBxgemAMAiAYBkgcFNi4wLjKgB8kh&amp;sclient=img" target="_blank">of Wrigley Field's marquee</a>. Subtle details that anchor the logo to the city without being literal or pandering to their audience. The standalone wordmark with the red star underneath looks great too.<span></span> Not much in application for now — as this identity will not roll out until the beginning of the 2025 season in March — but the initial round of merch is quite nice. The combination of navy and light blue with sparks of red and white is a winning combination and the logo works perfectly in full color or single color variations. Naturally, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DBeCBUguHBr/" target="_blank">fans are upset</a>, summed up by one comment that is able to capture every soccer fan's reaction to every logo redesign ever: “this sucks the logo sucks change is bad”. Overall, the change to the name seems beneficial even if it will take some time to phase out the “red” but it does bode well for establishing the Chicago Stars in the same realm as other local teams, and the logo is a nice improvement that takes a less literal approach to repurposing the city's flag, which can be an often overused symbol for Chicago-based businesses, organizations, and tourist souvenirs.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_chicago_stars_football_club_by_rabe_birch.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_chicago_stars_football_club_by_rabe_birch.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 513: From Touch, Boo Republic, and Chad Michael Studio</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Touch, Boo Republic, and Chad Michael Studio”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/friday_likes_513.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 513" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Wrapping around bottles is the only common trait between these wildly different packaging projects with work from Edinburgh, Thessaloniki, and Dallas.</p>
<span id="more-299626"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Landfall by Touch</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_landfall.jpg" alt="Landfall by Touch" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;">Crafted by <a href="https://stornowaydistillers.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stornoway Distillers</a>, a distillery in Scotland&#8217;s Isle of Lewis, Landfall is their first product — a contemporary, citrus-forward gin distilled with hand-foraged Hebridean botanicals, including heather and Bladderwrack seaweed. The packaging, designed by Edinburgh, Scotland-based <a href="https://www.thetouchagency.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Touch</a>, features an excellent wordmark with an unconventional and rather original stencil approach that cuts a notch at the top and a notch at the bottom in the exact same locations, yielding a very cool, modular look. It also manages to exude a certain maritime vibe that connects with the distillery&#8217;s coastal location. The label and bottle top sport the distillery&#8217;s logo, also created by Touch, which is quite nice itself. This gin is welcome to make landfall on my tonic any time it wants. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.thetouchagency.co.uk/work/landfall-gin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Local Revival by Boo Republic</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_localrevival.jpg" alt="Local Revival by Boo Republic" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://localrevival.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Local Revival</a> is a small brand of bath products made somewhere in California, offering soap and bodywash made with natural ingredients like olive oil, aloe vera, shea butter, and jojoba oil and free from harsh detergents, filler ingredients, and artificial fragrances. The identity designed by Thessaloniki, Greece-based <a href="https://www.boorepublic.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Boo Republic</a>, is “inspired by the diverse landscapes of California” and “draws from the heart of surf culture, the hiking lifestyle, and the awe-inspiring majesty of nature”. This takes shape in the form of a chunky wordmark that is accompanied by a thick- and wobbly-stroked plant icon, both of which exude organic-ness. On the packaging, a series of almost abstract illustrations in the same choppy style fill in most areas and are complemented by a condensed sans serif, all for a good metaphorical lathering of organic-looking design elements. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/207327735/Local-Revival" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Paradísse by Chad Michael Studio</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_paradisse.jpg" alt="Paradísse by Chad Michael Studio" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://www.drinkparadisse.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paradísse</a> is a premium liqueur based on <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fassionola" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fassionola</a>, a somewhat mysterious red-colored syrup that was frequently used in tropical (“Tiki”) drinks during the 1930s. The packaging, designed by Dallas, TX-based <a href="https://chadmichaelstudio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chad Michael Studio</a>, takes those tropical cues to a more luxurious extreme with a stunning bird illustration that looks just as great in detailed print form as it does in abstracted, raised-glass form on the bottom of the bottle. The wordmark has maybe one too many quirks but it definitely conveys an exotic look. The red color of the liqueur is so nicely contrasted by the blue, postage-stamp-silhouetted oval and the large cream-colored block. The supporting typography is also excellent, further adding texture to the already rich design. I wonder how this would mix with Landfall?  <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://chadmichaelstudio.com/portfolio/paradisse-liqueur/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_513.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_513.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Safelite by Quake</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/safelite_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Safelite by Quake" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://wearequake.com/projects/safelite">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_safelite_by_quake.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_safelite_by_quake.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Name, Logo, and Identity for 248 Growth Partners by Hulsbosch</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/248_growth_partners_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for 248 Growth Partners by Hulsbosch" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.248partners.com/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_248_growth_partners_by_hulsbosch.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_248_growth_partners_by_hulsbosch.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 13:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: United We Crest</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/news_cambridge_united_crest_winner-1.jpg" alt="United We Crest" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.cambridgeunited.com/NewCrest">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>In July, <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/united_we_vote.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cambridge United FC presented three directions</a> designed by <a href="https://www.footballbranddesigner.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Christopher Payne</a> for fans to vote on and for stakeholders to provide feedback on. After holding multiple in-person events to receive input and offering an online survey that received over 2,500 responses, the winning direction has been announced (after finessing some details and expanding the identity). It will begin to be used in the 2025/26 season. Masterclass in avoiding fan backlash.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/united_we_crest.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/united_we_crest.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Hold on Tight”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/leggs_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1969) &#8220;In 1969, <a href="https://www.leggs.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">L’eggs</a> was the secret project of Hanes executive Robert Elbertson with one aim: build a brand for the new American woman. The brand became a nearly instant success with its unique, colorful packaging, the beautiful in-store displays, and clever taglines: “Nothing beats a good pair of L’eggs”. For over 55 years, we&#8217;ve been dedicated to crafting beautiful products that embody quality in every step–and today, we’re returning to our roots to make you fall in love with your L’eggs all over again. Today, L’eggs designs innovative solutions that spark confidence–from energizing graduated compression to advanced sculpting with 360 Contour.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            Creative Direction: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/cami.tellez/" target="_blank">Cami Tellez</a> (in-house)<br /> Brand identity, art direction, and packaging: <a href="https://familyoffice.is/" target="_blank">Family Office</a><br />Logo refinement: <a href="https://cobbco.design/" target="_blank">Cobbco</a> and <a href="https://commercialtype.com/" target="_blank">Commercial Type</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://familyoffice.is/work/leggs" target="_blank">Family Office project page</a><br /><a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/91218552/cami-tellez-parade-underwear-revive-leggs" target="_blank">Fast Company article on the relaunch</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>[No] matter your age, the story of L'eggs reads like a history. Customer research conducted as part of the brand transformation demonstrated a massive generational gap in brand recognition. Our rebrand sets out to amplify the original DNA that made the brand great, and set in stone L'eggs' status as an iconic American brand of more than half a century.<br /><br />The original L'eggs wordmark was designed by Roger Ferriter at Lubalin, Smith, Carnase. In attempting to update a mark of such historical significance — it's been featured in countless design and typography books, exhibitions, classrooms, and reference boards — the immense work of Britt Cobb, Jonny Sikov, and Commercial Type founder, Christian Schwartz was enlisted. Many variations, thoughts, experiments, and anchor points were moved and resulted in the logo that has, as of launch, already been printed on thousands of packages of L'eggs tights.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-299576"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_archival.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_original.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Archival images.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_logo_before_after_overlay.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Before and after, overlay comparison.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_logo_small_inverse.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Logo, smaller and inverse.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_logo_construction.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Logo construction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:66.666666666666667%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_color_palette.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:66.666666666666667%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_typography.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Color palette and typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="float:left; width:50%;padding-bottom:66.666666666666667%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_01a.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_01b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_02a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_02b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_03a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_03b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_05a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_05b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" style="float:left; width:50%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_art_direction_6.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Art direction and photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.6666667%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_packaging_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_packaging_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_packaging_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_instagram_posts.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/leggs_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for L’eggs by Family Office" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            Before writing this post I don't think I have thought about L’eggs since my childhood as it was a staple in my mom's closet and its logo <a href="https://www.cooperhewitt.org/2016/01/24/which-came-first-the-product-or-the-egg/" target="_blank">and egg-shaped packaging</a> seemed to be in every store in every shopping mall in America in the 1980s. Pressed for an answer, I would have said the brand had ceased production and gone off the market as I don't have any recent memory of seeing this product in the wild so I was surprised to learn that it has been around all this time, with, amazingly, the same logo as when it launched. For me, it's one of those logos that's sort of ingrained in my mind but it wasn't until today that I looked at it more closely.<span></span> Drawn without a computer at the time, it obviously had its limitations and quirks, which, to be honest, I had not really noticed until seeing the new logo, but the lower half of the “g”s were enormous, their counterspaces too small, and the “s” too squished. The new logo is an excellent evolution that maintains everything that is recognizable about it and polishes all the curves and proportions for a much more balanced design. The biggest change of shifting to a lowercase “l” might be the most controversial but I think it's a smart move that makes for a cleaner logo and allows the “g”s to be the main attraction while the “l” now, arguably, fits the “e” like a silky pair of tights that contour to its shape. The apostrophe's spacing is much better now too and the “s” now has as much presence as the rest of the letters.<span></span> Application- and identity-wise, unfortunately, there is not much to see or be excited by. The color palette is fine. The typography is fine. The packaging is fine. While my gut instinct would be to wish that the identity brought back the 1970s and ’80s magazine-ad look, I do realize that might not play as well with modern-day consumers but this all feels a little too safe and not that much different from private label brands from places like Target, where this will be primarily sold. The logo does a lot of the heavy lifting in making this look unique but in the context of the pared-back typography and fashion-y photography it looks a bit out of place. The photography and art direction, by the way, are quite nice. Overall, I feel like this needed a big swing to make a big impact to announce its reinvigoration and its attempted return to earn a place in consumers’ minds and, while the legacy of the logo might be enough to invite fresh curiosity and it's all quite pleasantly done, I'm not sure if this is all distinct, unique, or novel enough to rise to the challenge.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_leggs_by_family_office.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_leggs_by_family_office.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 09:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Easier Said than Dune”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/martistel_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p><a href="https://martistel.com" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Martistel</a> is a new intralogistics company based in Dubai that launched publicly in March 2024 at the MODEX supply chain trade show. Intralogistics, I learned this week, is what moving your physical products around inside your company is called. Martistel makes robots, containers, and software to help companies with warehouses fit as much stuff as possible into those warehouses. Their brand was designed by <a href="https://shuka.design" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Shuka</a>, “a brand transformation bureau” with offices in Almaty, Kazakhstan; Berlin, Germany; and Sydney, Australia.</p>

<span id="more-299435"></span>

<blockquote>Martistel is an innovator in intralogistics from Dubai. The company specializes in optimizing warehouse spaces. With over 30 patented technologies, Martistel offers unique solutions, like a pallet grouping method and a shuttle robot. The robot can handle five containers at once, up to 225 kg, and works in temperatures from +2 to +50°C. Martistel’s warehouse simulator can optimize multi-level spaces of 500 to 1500 stacks in just three minutes.</blockquote>
<h3>Shuka supplied text</h3>

<p>Shuka&#8217;s notes also say a bunch of stuff about ‘fractal branding’ and outer space logistics and big things next to small things and nakedness. I didn’t really get it. Let’s go straight to the logo.</p>

<figure class="full"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_logo_on_orange.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka" /><figcaption>Logo on orange.</figcaption></figure>

<p>This wordmark is a retro-futuristic unicase wonder that clearly takes inspiration from Arabic script. My first impression was: cool vibe, good sense of place – I love it. Then I looked closer. It has all the things going on. The eight triangular negative shapes and the tittle have all been blunted but not rounded. The &#8220;T&#8221;s have angled left edges that have not been blunted or rounded. The counters are rounded. But none of them are rounded the same way (!!!). The &#8220;R&#8221; and &#8220;T&#8221; sit awkwardly together. My considered impression is that this wordmark is a hot mess.</p>

<p>Does it say intralogistics? I dunno. I looked at a bunch of intralogistics company websites and they were absolutely as dull as you would expect. They look nothing like Martistel. Martistel&#8217;s logo looks like it could be name of late ’90s rave. And what is a rave but a lot of moving around in a warehouse? Perfect. Final impression: I love it.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo with animation.</figcaption></figure>

<p>Note: You’re going to see a number of things about space as we go through. They seem to have an ambition to do warehouse optimisation in space. My made-up backstory is that when the founders walked out of the cinema after watching <em>Wall-E</em> they said, &#8220;We’re building that company.&#8221;</p>

<p>Like the logo, the headline font is unicase, 205TF’s <a href="https://www.205.tf/Font/87/maax-unicase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Maax Unicase</a>. With its mix of round counters and squared-off notches, it must be the inspiration for the wordmark. I like its energy. I think the &#8220;a&#8221; is gorgeous. The numerals are super. Keep an eye out for the 2. It’s my favourite.</p>

<p>The font does have two big problems: &#8220;t&#8221; and &#8220;W&#8221;. The &#8220;W&#8221; has that overlapped double &#8220;V&#8221; construction and it’s Too Much Letter. Send it back to the shop and cut cut it down to a size that plays nicely with the others. On the subject of playing, the &#8220;t&#8221; is like that kid who went into sports because his sports hero dad (named &#8220;T&#8221;) died tragically in his prime and the kid is determined to live up to &#8220;T&#8221;’s legacy. So it’s the crunch moment of the game and &#8220;t&#8221; says, &#8220;Coach, put me in! I can do it!&#8221; Against his better judgement, the coach subs &#8220;t&#8221; into the game and, unlike a movie, it turns out that he really can’t do it. After his disgrace on the field, &#8220;t&#8221; quits sports and goes into children&#8217;s entertainment. This &#8220;t&#8221; has a space to fill but its lowercaseness can’t do it properly. It breaks the flow of whatever word it’s in. &#8220;t&#8221; needs to go find work in a different font.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_headline_01.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Headline on dunes.</figcaption></figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_headline_02.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Different headline on different dunes.</figcaption></figure>

<p>The only graphical element of the brand is a set of crystals that are usually animated. Sometimes they are scaled up to enormous and used as an interesting backdrop for text. There’s no explanation of what the crystals are for or what they mean. They are a nice but random decoration. The animation is good. Maybe that’s enough.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_crystals.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>The Martistel crystals.</figcaption></figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_slogan.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Martistel&#8217;s slogan, with crystals.</figcaption></figure>

<p>Martistel’s colours are pure Arabian desert. It’s a happy, optimistic palette. I look at it and think, <em>Space warehouses – yes, that’s totally possible!</em></p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_brand_elements_01.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Brand elements.</figcaption></figure>

<p>Now the robots. According to the Martistel website, their “cute and capable robots” can carry a stack of up to five totes (crates). Cute things carrying stacks was of course predicted by Dr. Seuss in his seminal 1961 sci-fi novel <em><a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_10_apples.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ten Apples Up On Top</a>.</em> I love it when technology catches up to imagination.</p>

<figure class="full"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_robot.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka" /><figcaption>Robot, with its top off.</figcaption></figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_stacks.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>How it stacks up.</figcaption></figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_robot_in_action.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Robots at work.</figcaption></figure>

<p>The robot looks like it could have been designed by Teenage Engineering, so it gets all the thumbs up from me. The livery – is it called livery on a robot? – is where Shuka demonstrate that they made good choices with the colour and type. I truly believe this robot is hardworking, cheerful, and competent. The explainer is clear. The robot in action is nicely filmed and fascinating to watch. This is quality warehouse robot content.</p>

<p>Here’s everything all together:

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_brand_overview.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Brand overview.</figcaption></figure>

<p>There&#8217;s not too much more to see.</p>


<figure class="full"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_reception_mockup.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka" />
<figcaption>A reception desk that may or may not exist.</figcaption></figure>

<figure class="full"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_trade-show_stand_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka" /><figcaption>Trade show stand.</figcaption></figure>

<figure class="full"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_trade-show_stand_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Martistel by Shuka" /><figcaption>Robot, with its top back on.</figcaption></figure>

<p>The trade show stand is minimal. Shuka says it was “created at near-light speed”. I guess deadlines were super tight. The stars are the robots doing stacking, so I doubt people were bothered by the sparseness.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay="autoplay" loop="loop" muted="" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_website.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption></figure>

<p>The website looks like everything you’ve already seen with the addition of <a href="https://www.205.tf/?search=maax+raw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Maax Raw Bold</a> for body copy. Because why not? They aren’t posting any essays.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video poster="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_brand_slideshow_poster.jpg" controls="controls" width="300" height="150">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/martistel_brand_slideshow.mp4" type="video/mp4" />
</video></div>
<figcaption>Here’s everything again but with sound, so it’s different.</figcaption></figure>

<p>Some elements of this brand don&#8217;t make sense. Some details aren’t quite right. But I think overall it&#8217;s a big win because Martistel have cute robots and – this is the serious and important point – the company looks and feels completely different from the other companies selling warehouse robots.</p>

<p>They understand what a lot of B2B companies don&#8217;t: they are selling to people. I&#8217;m a person, and they got my attention. If I was a person with an un-optimised warehouse, I guarantee I would be filling out that form to get my <a href="https://martistel.com/space-tour-booking" target="_blank" rel="noopener">free trip to Dubai for a Martistel demo</a>. I think this package will serve them well for the next few years as they get off the ground (and possibly into space).</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_martistel_by_shuka.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_martistel_by_shuka.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Archivi Olivetti by Cappelli Identity Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/archivi_olivetti_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Archivi Olivetti by Cappelli Identity Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://mailchi.mp/cappellidesign/press-release-archivi-olivetti-en">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_archivi_olivetti_by_cappelli_identity_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_archivi_olivetti_by_cappelli_identity_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>