<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Kustomer by Pedroza</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/kustomer_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Kustomer by Pedroza" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.pedrozasf.com/portfolio-kustomer">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_kustomer_by_pedroza.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_kustomer_by_pedroza.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Announced: The Follow-up: The End</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Going off the Air”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/the_followup_going_off_the_air.png" alt="The Follow-up: The End" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Given the lack of episodes in the past 6 months and the spotty publishing schedule in the past year it may come as no surprise — although it&#8217;s probably no less disappointing — that we are ending <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/the_follow_up" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Follow-up podcast</a>. We started back in the distant past of 2020 during the pandemic at a time when our live events were on hold and showed no signs of coming back. Luckily, that part of our business bounced back in 2022 but, along with their return, has been an increased level of difficulty in planning and executing live events that demands much more of our time and attention than before. (Not to pass blame but post-pandemic it seems a lot of businesses, vendors, and providers forgot how to do their job or at least provide proper customer service so every little task is now harder and more expensive than it used to be.) Point being, we have to prioritize our time and resources as we try to navigate as efficiently as possible this inflation-ridden hellscape we call The Economy and, unfortunately, the time required to put together each episode is too consuming. Thank you to all the designers and clients who participated in the recordings and to any and all who listened to one of our 86 episodes!</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/the_follow_up_the_end.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/the_follow_up_the_end.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 13:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Den-marks the Spot</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/news_denmark_coat_of_arms_before_after.png" alt="Den-marks the Spot" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/jan/06/danish-king-changes-coat-of-arms-in-apparent-rebuke-to-donald-trump">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Redesigned for only the fourth time since 1819, Denmark has introduced a new rendition of its coat of arms that now features a more prominent polar bear and ram to represent Greenland and the Faroe Islands respectively as a signal of the kingdom&#8217;s commitment to those two territories. While the media has been touting this as the King of Denmark trolling Donald Trump and his recently expressed desire to make Greenland a part of the U.S., the redesign was actually first commissioned in January of 2024 so the timing is (perhaps) mostly coincidence.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/den_marks_the_spot.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/den_marks_the_spot.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“What Tozi is What Toget”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/tozi_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2024) &#8220;<a href="https://tozifoods.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tozi Azteca Superfoods</a> is a family-founded, Mexican-American food and beverage company inspired by heritage and the spirit of the Aztec goddess Toci, the goddess of health. From our blue corn and amaranth tortillas to refreshing aguas frescas sweetened exclusively with agave syrup, every product is made with clean, natural ingredients that honor our roots and nourish our community. For us, Tozi is more than a brand; it’s a celebration of health, family, and the enduring power of Mexican superfoods, backed by both ancestral wisdom and modern science, to heal and connect.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.ifonly-creative.com/" target="_blank">If Only Creative</a> (California)<br /><a href="https://www.bysofiallaguno.com/" target="_blank">Sofia Llaguno</a> (San Francisco, CA)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.ifonly-creative.com/work/tozi-azteca-superfoods" target="_blank">If Only Creative project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>If Only Creative's approach to the rebrand was rooted in four fundamental principles: honoring Mexico's culinary heritage and indigenous superfoods, celebrating Latina entrepreneurs and their contributions to the culinary landscape, promoting nutrient-rich, organic, and non-GMO products, and educating consumers about the benefits of indigenous superfoods and supporting sustainable practices.<br /><br />In addition to a streamlined wordmark, Sanchez-Dunning and company redesigned Tozi's logo, transforming the brand's original illustration of a goddess into a simplified icon. The revamped logomark visually connects the brand to its heritage and core values. Influenced by Aztec stone sculptures and the gods, they looked at the shapes and symmetry of many of the statues and stone carvings that were prevalent at the height of the Aztec Empire. Further, architecture from that era inspired many of the graphics on the packaging and served as a framing device for the visual identity system.<br /><br />Above Tozi's headdress, the studio added icons for some of the product's primary ingredients–corn, amaranth, and agave. Notably, it's a future-forward system that the brand can use as they expand their offerings or venture into other categories where they can use the star ingredient as a visual cue.<br /><br />The carefully chosen typefaces reinforce the brand personality. Isola, the primary typeface, offers a bold yet elegant feel for headlines and body copy. Silverspoon, a supporting typeface, adds a touch of playfulness to subheadings. While decidedly modern, it also carries sweeping lines that harken back to Aztec art.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-301795"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_old.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Samples of old packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_icon.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Icon.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_icon_colors.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Color variations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_icon_with_icons.gif" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Icon with flavor icons.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_labels.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Labels.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_aguas_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_aguas_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_aguas_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_aguas_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Aguas frescas.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_tortillas_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_tortillas_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Tortillas.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_chips_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Chips.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_packaging_all.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>All.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/tozi_overview.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Tozi by If Only Creative and Sofia Llaguno" />
<figcaption>Identity overview.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo had good intentions but it fell short in execution in both the illustration and wordmark. The former suffering mostly from really odd proportions and the latter from an unfortunate combination of mismatched weights and poor spacing. The new logo separates the icon from the wordmark and evolves each of them into drastically improved versions. The wordmark now has more presence thanks to the chunky letters and while it's not perfectly resolved (as it could still be a tad thicker) the superscript “O” is better balanced. The new icon now focuses solely on the head and head-dress of the depiction of Aztec deity, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toci" target="_blank">Toci</a>, through a bold, simple, and striking drawing although the earring can feel a little big and distracting, especially in contrast to the eye.<span></span> The packaging has a solid foundation with the unconventional holding shapes that adapt to the proportions of the bottles or plastic bags and help frame the information but they all feel a little unfinished once it's populated. I think part of the problem is a lack of a more prominent hierarchy — especially in the aguas frescas packaging — as all of the elements are equally small and none of them stand out or recede enough to let the more important elements take center stage. The chips and tortilla bags are a little more overt with the product description but the brand name and the identity's visual assets almost pass unperceived. Overall, this is certainly a big improvement over the old logo and packaging and the design captures a good Mexican flair without resorting to more traditional clichés.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_tozi_by_if_only_creative.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_tozi_by_if_only_creative.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 520: From Audrie Kapinus, Whatever Studio, and Kamilla Oblakova</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Audrie Kapinus, Whatever Studio, and Kamilla Oblakova”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/friday_likes_520.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 520" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Some lively and charming packaging this week, with work from Brooklyn, Chicago, and possibly somewhere in Spain.</p>
<span id="more-301792"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Mez by Audrie Kapinus</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_mez.jpg" alt="Mez by Audrie Kapinus" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://mezfoods.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mez</a> is a non-chocolate chocolate bar that is made from the fruit of the mesquite tree which is described as having a chocolatey, sweet, and cinnamony taste that Mez then turns into a trio of delicious-sounding concoctions. The packaging, designed by Brooklyn, NY-based <a href="https://www.audriekapinus.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Audrie Kapinus</a>, features a lovely combination of typography and spot illustrations that mix into an elegant series of boxes with a charming vintage patina. The shortness of the name allows the high-contrast sans serif wordmark to appear extra large on the front as it sits atop the richly textured illustrations with the ingredients (which are then transformed into a fun pattern on the interior of the packaging). The flared serif for the flavor names could be one typographic variation too many but it works perfectly with the rest of the typography. <a href="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/60639129b7d464537b3990cd/1f4cb422-68e6-40bb-bab1-e927fd7bbc8e/Artboard+4-100.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The glow-up in contrast to their old packaging is quite dramatic</a>.  <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.audriekapinus.com/work/mez-foods" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Spritzi by Whatever Studio</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_spritzi.jpg" alt="Spritzi by Whatever Studio" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://drinkspritzi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spritzi</a> is an effervescent cold brew drink available plain or infused with flavors like grapefruit citrus and strawberry dragonfruit. The packaging, designed by Chicago, IL-based <a href="https://whatever.studio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Whatever Studio</a>, is spearheaded by a great script wordmark that spans the height of the can on one side while a friendly, anthropomorphic spot illustration of the flavor profile happily struts on the other side. I kind of love that the illustrations look like they are all wearing pants. So proper. I wish there was some better visual relation between the logo and the illustrations either by integrating the dotted texture on the wordmark or shaping the illustrations with a higher contrast line instead of the thin stroke. Nonetheless, this all looks fizzy AF. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://whatever.studio/project/spritzi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Matcha Y&#8217;all by Kamilla Oblakova</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_matchayall.jpg" alt="Matcha Y'all by Kamilla Oblakova" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://matchayall.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Matcha Y&#8217;all</a> is a matcha and mushroom blend created by two sisters in Austin, TX. Hence, the “y’all”. The packaging, designed by Spain(?)-based <a href="https://www.behance.net/kamillaoblakova" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kamilla Oblakova</a>, answered the founders&#8217; brief of mixing a cowgirl and a matcha cup with Texan flair perfectly by, well, placing a cowgirl on top of a matcha cup and riding it like a bull at a rodeo. Accompanied by some unexpectedly fun typography, the packaging manages to have that Texas flair as well as that earthy, hippie matcha vibe. Believe it or not, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/watch/?v=875122294362555" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this was actually a project commissioned through 99designs</a>, which is probably the best project I&#8217;ve seen coming from a 99designs commission. A hearty <em>yeehaw</em> to all involved! <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/214602657/MATCHA-YALL-drink-mix-Branding-packaging" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_520.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_520.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Pexels</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/pexels_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Pexels" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DDwfF6hI3SU/?img_index=3">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_pexels.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_pexels.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Wagtime by Studio Ping Pong</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/wagtime_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Wagtime by Studio Ping Pong" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://studiopingpong.com/project/wagtime/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_wagtime_by_studio_ping_pong.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_wagtime_by_studio_ping_pong.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: A Puffer you can’t Refuse</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/news_offseason_puffs.jpg" alt="A Puffer you can’t Refuse" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.fanaticsinc.com/press-releases/emma-grede-the-nfl-kristin-juszczyk-and-fanatics-announce-the-launch-of-apparel-of-brand-off-season">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Launched in collaboration by Emma Grede, the National Football League, Kristin Juszczyk, and Fanatics, <a href="https://www.offseasonbrand.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Off Season</a> is a new luxury fashion brand offering a premiere collection of unisex puffer jackets inspired by a selection of iconic NFL teams. Pricey but kind of slick.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/a_puffer_you_cant_refuse.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/a_puffer_you_cant_refuse.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Frame of Reference”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2010, previously The Sustainable Production Alliance) “The <a href="https://www.sustainableentertainmentalliance.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sustainable Entertainment Alliance</a> is a consortium of the world’s leading film, television and streaming stakeholders dedicated to advancing sustainability initiatives through advocacy, education, and innovation while reducing the entertainment industry’s overall environmental impact. As the impacts of climate change become increasingly pronounced, the entertainment industry holds a pivotal role in representing the changing climate and clean economy transition in the stories we tell on-screen, and comprehensively reducing our environmental impact across our operations and the work we do behind the camera. The Sustainable Entertainment Alliance is committed to supporting the industry towards a future that is not only sustainable in practice but also supports stories that reflect the realities of climate and sustainability for global audiences.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://cotton.design/" target="_blank">Cotton Design</a> (New York, NY)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://cotton.design/work/sustainable-entertainment-alliance" target="_blank">Cotton Design project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>The Alliance’s new logo symbolizes the power of collaboration. Four brackets—evoking a film camera’s focus points—converge at the center, representing the coming together of studios in a unified effort, and radiate outward as ripples to signify widespread impact. This design doubles as both a visual metaphor and a strong, recognizable symbol that can stand alone, establishing the Alliance as a recognized emblem of sustainability in the industry.<br /><br />The mark expands into a versatile and recognizable brand pattern, with ripples radiating outward in dynamic variations of thickness, length, and overall visual effect to be applied across a wide range of brand assets. Recognizing that the Alliance team isn’t composed of designers, Cotton developed an easy-to-use generator to simplify the process of creating tailored patterns.<br /><br />The system is designed to be both flexible and easy to apply, even for a non-designer team. Clear guidelines outline approved foreground-background color combinations, including a palette of dark, light, and bright options. Two contrasting but complimenting typefaces were chosen to give the team a range to apply their voice. Most importantly, the system employs a simple top-left-aligned grid on most applications for consistency and clarity. Fundamentally, applying the brand is as straightforward as selecting a foreground-background combination, choosing one of the two fonts, and placing the logo. The generative pattern does the rest.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-301759"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_concept.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo concept.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_system.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Logo system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_animation_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_animation_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:57.407407407407407%;float:left; width:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_interaction_a.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:57.407407407407407%;float:left; width:50%"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_logo_interaction_b.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Logo interactions.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_typography.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_color_palette.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_guidelines.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_generator.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Generator. You can play with it <a href="https://sea-pattern-generator.netlify.app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_generator_samples.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Generator samples.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_2up_letterhead.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_2up_business_cards.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Letterhead and business cards.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_brochure.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Brochure.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_magazine_covers.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Magazine covers.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_badges.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Badges.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_website.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_ppt_deck.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>PowerPoint deck.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_instagram_posts.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_instagram_stories.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Instagram stories.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_banners.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Banners.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_poster_a.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_poster_b.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>Posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_tote_bag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Tote bag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/sustainable_entertainment_alliance_beanie.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Sustainable Entertainment Alliance by Cotton Design" />
<figcaption>Beanie.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            While there is nothing inherently wrong anywhere on this project, nothing stands out particularly strongly either and other than the name, this lacks any evident connection to the entertainment industry. The closest it gets is the icon that references a “film camera’s focus points” but by being drawn in a square format it quickly loses that reference and then the additional low-hanging-fruit concepts of collaboration and impact further take it into generic, corporate territory. The final composition of the icon with the radiating corners ends up being rather awkward too and its size relationship with the wordmark makes it feel clunky. Typeset in <a href="https://fonts.floriankarsten.com/fk-grotesk-neue" target="_blank">FK Grotesk Neue</a>, the wordmark is fine and does the best it can with the extra long name.<span></span> The icon does gain some interest as the primary building block and graphic device for the identity when parsed through the custom generator that can yield some interesting compositions, especially when having a big open space in the center for typography to sit in. The layouts where the frames are angled start to gain additional interest as they break from the more expected, straightforward treatments — something like the poster that promotes “The Montreal Sustainability Forum” is quite good. The green-on-green color palette is fine but, like the icon, seems like such an obvious choice for sustainable-anything. Overall, this could be for a solar panel company or some other environmentally-concerned entity unrelated to the entertainment industry but it's a serviceable identity that gets the job done and sends all the correct signals.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_sustainable_entertainment_alliance_by_cotton_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_sustainable_entertainment_alliance_by_cotton_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Take it or Weave It”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/norwich_university_of_the_arts_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 1845 as the Norwich School of Design, <a href="https://norwichuni.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Norwich University of the Arts</a> is a public university in Norwich, Norfolk, UK, that specializes in art, design, media, architecture, and performance providing practice-based arts and technology education. Situated in the center of historic Norwich, the university spans across 13 buildings that house studios, media labs, and creative spaces for their nearly 3,000 students hailing from over 40 different countries. At the end of 2023, Norwich University of the Arts introduced a new identity designed by London, UK-based <a href="https://www.northdesign.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">North</a> that began implementation in 2024.</p>
<span id="more-301754"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<blockquote>Research revealed that Norwich has long been rooted in craft and experimentation, dating back to the 16th century when Flemish communities, known as ‘The Strangers,’ sought refuge in the city. In exchange for a new home, they shared their weaving and textile knowledge, playing a vital role in shaping and revitalising the city.<br /><br />Norwich’s rich history remains relevant, positioning the city as a creative hub where everyone is welcome to learn, exchange, and grow. This idea was woven into the creative work, highlighting the ambition and creativity that runs through all the University’s courses.<br /><br />At the heart of the new identity is the guiding concept of ‘Creative Exchange,’ reflecting the University’s shared mindset and commitment to ongoing exploration, collaboration, and growth. The identity embodies Norwich&#8217;s history and the curiosity that drives new conversations and challenges conventional thinking.<br /><br />The design system includes a custom typeface designed by North that represents versatility and craftsmanship, reflecting the creativity and exchange central to both the University and the city&#8217;s vibrant spirit. Blending traditional and digital art forms, the font and visual language showcase the diverse disciplines at Norwich University of the Arts. The dynamic forms evoke research, experimentation, and computational arts, fully embodying the concept of ‘Creative Exchange’.</blockquote><h3>North provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_textile_reference.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Textile reference.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.6666667%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_logo_construction.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo construction.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>This project is very much outside my typical cut-off date given that it was first released in Summer of 2023 and while a few online publications covered it, I was not aware of it but now we have the benefit of a more complete case study. It&#8217;s also a fun project, so I had a harder time saying no to it. Anyway… the old logo, designed in 2009 by <a href="https://studio-sutherland.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Studio Sutherland</a>, was kind of interesting with the tilted “N” creating some strong tension with the full name underneath. It almost felt like someone leaning back on a chair and you are just nail-bitingly waiting for them to fall back. It didn&#8217;t quite scream arts university though and wasn&#8217;t particularly exciting.</p>

<p>The new logo fixes those two shortcomings with a great custom wordmark that is a patchwork of graphic elements that are evocative of any number of artistic techniques, from cross-stitching to pixelation to quilting. While it&#8217;s not the first time we see an approach like this — <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_calgary_tourism_economic_development_by_daughter.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a recent example being this Calgary project</a> — one aspect of this that I really like is how they treated the rounded corners, where the graphic unit is gradually rotated instead of being used straight, so this gives the otherwise mechanical approach a more human and organic touch. Letters like the “U” and “R” in “UNIVERSITY” break the modularity and make the logo far more interesting and engaging as well as less static. The “S” in “ARTS” starts to get a little questionable but it&#8217;s a small price to pay.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.6666667%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_custom_type_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_custom_type_02a.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Custom typeface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The premise of the logo is expanded into a custom typeface that can cycle through 12 different graphic units for a seemingly endless range of options and graphic expressions that still manage to yield a cohesive, modular system that doesn&#8217;t feel completely haphazard. Some units are more interesting than others, some are more readable than others, some are more pleasant than others but it&#8217;s the mixing and matching of these stark contrasts that makes the premise work.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_digital_expressions.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Digital expressions.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>I think the above were just proof of concept that things can flex extra weird as none of these seem to be in use anywhere. Not complaining… actually, yes complaining because I would love to see more of it in application.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_print_materials.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Print materials.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_prospectus.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Prospectus.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_newspaper.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Newspaper.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_poster_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_poster_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>One of the aspects of the typography I like the most is how well it can be layered in different ways, whether it&#8217;s the custom type with other typography, imagery, color, or even with itself (in different graphic units) to create an endless range of design approaches that are all tied through the energy and modularity of the custom typeface. Just as well, something as straightforward as the arrangement directly below with “OPEN DAYS 2024” neatly stacking 4-letter words, each in a different graphic unit is very pleasing.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_window_display.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Window graphics.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_banner_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_banner_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Banners.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_wayfinding_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_wayfinding_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_wayfinding_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Wayfinding.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_interiors.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Interior.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_screen.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Screen.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_tshirt.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>T-shirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_tote_bag_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_tote_bag_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Tote bags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The one unclear aspect is the color palette… obviously there is the yellow but then there are glimpses of a blue, that bright green screen, a brick red, and some of the posters shown earlier in the post had some wacky color combos, so it seems that it&#8217;s a bit of a free-for-all, which could work but perhaps the custom typeface already provides so much flexibility that making the color approach so malleable is maybe <em>too much</em> flexibility.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/norwich_university_of_the_arts_social_content.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Norwich University of the Arts by North" />
<figcaption>Some event images from their social media pages.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1045149258?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">Overall, this is a great, energetic system with a lot of graphic flair that highlights the art and design focus of the university but it also has enough rigor and boundaries to signal that this is a serious educational institution.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_norwich_university_of_the_arts_by_north.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_norwich_university_of_the_arts_by_north.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>