<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Im(peach) Kroger</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/sad_kroger_peach_truck.jpg" alt="Im(peach) Kroger" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.tennessean.com/story/money/2024/06/18/kroger-apology-use-of-nashville-peach-trucks-images-marketing/74134469007/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Kroger was caught red-handed after it swiped <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CSEyYoAHI4S/?utm_source=ig_embed&#038;ig_rid=98aea0f6-d8d4-4c0d-9919-eb9e1a3e94cf&#038;img_index=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">an Instagram image from Nashville, TN-based Peach Truck</a> and Photoshop’d it to pass as their own. Kroger apologized and claimed the image wasn&#8217;t approved to be released, which is what someone says when they&#8217;ve been caught.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/impeach_kroger.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/impeach_kroger.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“A Chip off the Old Chalk”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/gosh_new.jpg" alt="New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1997) &#8220;<a href="https://www.gosh.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity</a> (GOSH Charity) stops at nothing to help give seriously ill children childhoods that are fuller, funner and longer. For the hundreds of children from all over the UK who are treated by Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) every day, for children with rare or complex illnesses everywhere, for this generation and all those to come. GOSH has been transforming the lives of seriously ill children since opening its doors in 1852 and has always depended on charitable support. GOSH Charity funds groundbreaking research into children’s health, cutting-edge medical equipment, child-centred medical facilities and the support services children and families going through the toughest journey of their lives urgently need. But there is so much more we need to do. Together with our supporters, we can give seriously ill children the best chance, and the best childhoods, possible. Because we believe no childhood should be lost to serious illness.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            Identity: <a href="https://stuartstuart.com/" target="_blank">Stuart Gough</a><br />Brand narrative: <a href="https://www.pentagram.com/" target="_blank">Pentagram</a><br />Brand motion: <a href="https://jkrglobal.com/" target="_blank">Jones Knowles Ritchie</a><br />Strategy: <a href="https://www.weareimpero.com/" target="_blank">Impero</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                             N/A
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>The organisation has partnered with independent creative director Stuart Gough and the Brand Narrative team at Pentagram, led by Ashley Johnson and Ruth Jamieson, to unveil a new brand identity and narrative platform, built on a brand strategy developed by creative agency Impero. Global branding agency Jones Knowles Ritchie (JKR) brought the brand to life through motion under the leadership of Tom Gould. The charity’s in-house team managed the delivery of the project.<br /><br />Developed under the 'Courageous Champion' archetype, the brand identity draws on the iconic logo's heritage, originally created in 1987 for the Wishing Well Appeal and inspired by a patient’s drawing. The updated logo retains its charm and authenticity while introducing elements for a distinct, digitally native identity system.<br /><br />As part of the brand refresh, GOSH Charity is also unveiling a new tone of voice and core brand language. The new voice emphasises collectivism, championing everyone who contributes to the charity's impact; determination, reflecting the charity’s commitment to ensuring no childhood is lost to serious illness; and a child-centred approach.<br /><br />New animal illustrations, inspired by the ward names at Great Ormond Street Hospital, and unique to the charity’s brand identity, represent the collective efforts of the “doers” who are transforming the lives of seriously ill children under the hospital’s care. When animated they give a sense of movement and togetherness as well as representing the fun and playful spirit at the heart of the brand’s renewed focus on childhood. The ability to animate the animal characters, as well as the new brand assets, has been a key consideration throughout the project, as the charity looks to create greater impact on digital channels.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-295427"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_logo.png" alt="New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity" />
<figcaption>Existing logo. (Lock-up is different from original but elements remain the same.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_identity_overview_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_identity_overview_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Identity overview.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_icon_set.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Icon set.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_typography.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_instagram_post.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram post.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_instagram_story.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Instagram story.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_digital_card.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Something else digital.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_advertising_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_advertising_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_advertising_03.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_advertising_04.jpg" alt="New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_sweatshirt.jpg" alt="New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity" />
<figcaption>Sweatshirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/gosh_tote_bag.jpg" alt="New Identity for Great Ormond Street Hospital Charity" />
<figcaption>Tote bag.</figcaption>
</figure>




                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            Although the provided text mentions the logo was updated, there really wasn't any update to it other than the lock-up, with a bigger icon and a centered arrangement on the wordmark. You can still see the old lock-up on their website. Other than slightly eerie eyes, it's a great icon and it serves as the springboard for a new library of illustrations and thick, chalk-like scribbles and squiggles. The animal illustrations are adorable but they also have a kind of mischievous personality without meaning any harm, of course — a crocodile handling a patient chart or a bird with a doctor's head mirror is as if the zoo broke out and went all <em>Night at the Museum</em> at the hospital. Their fun, confident, and playful swagger in motion has a contagious optimistic quality to it.<span></span> The typography also takes a cue from the logo with a bold and friendly sans serif and while it's perfectly fine and well suited for the illustrations I feel like there is a disconnect between the logo and the headlines. Like, they are very similar but not similar enough and also not distinct enough. Nitpicks aside, it's all good and I love the motion treatment where a letter first appears in chalk and then quickly pops into the sans serif. The tone of voice is solid but not particularly galvanizing and making the benefit of donating to their cause irrefutable. The primary message, “Until no childhood is lost to serious illness”, took me a couple of reads to parse… it's not an immediate gut punch, despite the reality being otherwise. Overall, this is a great identity with a strong message and, above all, it's kind of amazing that this vast group of contributors was able to come together on different areas and deliver a cohesive result that should serve the charity more than well for years to come.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_great_ormond_street_hospital_charity.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_great_ormond_street_hospital_charity.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 502: From The Young Jerks, Herefor Studio and Herman-Scheer, and Monumento</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From The Young Jerks, Herefor Studio and Herman-Scheer, and Monumento”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/friday_likes_502.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 502" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Some fun typography across three sets of packaging this week, with work from Brooklyn, Honolulu, Venice, and Monterrey. </p>
<span id="more-295424"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Medly by The Young Jerks</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_medly.jpg" alt="Medly by The Young Jerks" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://www.drinkmedly.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Medly</a> scours the Mediterranean to find the best wines from sustainable and regenerative farms and puts four glass bottles&#8217; worth of organic wine inside a 100% BPA-free pouch. The identity and packaging, designed by Brooklyn, NY-based <a href="https://youngjerks.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Young Jerks</a>, carry a laissez-faire vibe from logo to illustrations, with a relaxed, vacation-y attitude. The jumbled, hand-drawn logo conveys the organic quality of the wines and is very nicely executed with all of the letters nestling into each other quite comfortably. The illustrations with the hat-toting dude are fun and quirky. The detail of the sailor-esque striped shirt is pretty appropriate too. Some bonus spot illustrations (<a href="https://www.drinkmedly.com/pages/about-us" target="_blank" rel="noopener">like in this page</a>) round out a very enjoyable visual language. Sadly, no full project page but between the Instagram post linked here and Medly&#8217;s website you can get a full picture. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/C8XRIWQpYBm/?img_index=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Quite Nice by Herefor Studio and Herman-Scheer</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_quitenice.jpg" alt="Quite Nice by Herefor Studio and Herman-Scheer" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://quitenice.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Quite Nice</a> offers prebiotic, protein-packed, oatmeal single-servings for breakfast (or any time you are craving some resistant starch) in a variety of flavors and is gluten- and glyphosate-free. The identity and packaging, designed in collaboration by Brooklyn, NY- and Honolulu, HI based <a href="https://www.hereforstudio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Herefor Studio</a> and Venice, CA-based <a href="https://www.herman-scheer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Herman-Scheer</a>, goes for a fun combination of the trendy squiggly-letter logo and some softly-textured illustrations. You know this is coming but the logo is… quite nice. The extra wide “N” might be the only thing I question but it&#8217;s still a good solution to make the two words stack evenly. I really like the two different “E”s and how the squiggly one matches the curls of the “Q” and curves of the “N”… it has an unexpected balance to it given that it&#8217;s so uneven and asymmetrical in so many ways. The illustrations are unified through the leaves-slash-vines as each flavor intertwines the main ingredient among them. If I had another concern it would be that, in part because of the leaves, this ends up looking more like tea than oats but it&#8217;s still lovely around, aided by the warm color palette. Like Medly above, no project page but combo of Instagram link and client website will get you what you need. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/C8Xv8GUSRbY/?img_index=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Gourmais by Monumento</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_gourmais.jpg" alt="Gourmais by Monumento" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;"><a href="https://eatgourmais.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gourmais</a> is a premium cracker brand that makes gluten-free, plant-based polenta crisps baked with different flavors. The identity and packaging, designed by Monterrey, Mexico-based <a href="https://monumento.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Monumento</a>, adopt an upscale, sort of 1960s’ swing, Austin Powers-lite colorful aesthetic with its big circles sitting in front of abstract polenta chips, creating a tasty-looking pattern. The dark green as the anchor color adds a touch of luxury, along with the italic logo with heavy bottoms and a groovy script initial “G”. Not completely sold on the illustration on the side of the package but it&#8217;s definitely not bad in any way. The supporting script and sans serif typography is well balanced and the brand even comes with a clever pun in “Amaising”, using the Italian word for “Corn” to describe the cracker&#8217;s taste. Pun approved. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.behance.net/gallery/180403145/GOURMAIS" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_502.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_502.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 09:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“A Rewarding Time”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Airtime_Logo_before_after.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 2015, <a href="https://www.airtime.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Airtime</a> is a UK-based telecommunications company that partners with major retail brands to offer its members a rewards-based app, designed for the mobile generation. For their members, it provides a chance to earn (up to £50/month) by shifting their shopping to Airtime. That credit then directly goes to offsetting the member&#8217;s mobile bill. For the retail partners, they work to &#8220;connect, incentives and influence sales.&#8221; With over 3.5 million members and 200+ brands, they are the fastest growing rewards program in the UK. They partnered with London, UK-based <a href="https://odabranding.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ODA</a> on brand strategy, naming, visual identity, and brand guidelines.</p>
<span id="more-295411"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Old_identity.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Old identity (from website).</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>I can understand the struggle of designing for a brand that needs to be both visible (and memorable), while also being invisible (to let the retail experience shine). And the prior design attempted to walk this line. We have all seen a lot of these go-to approaches before: the minimal lowercase logo, the hospital-scrub green and the wide-open spaces on the website. Unfortunately through today&#8217;s eyes it feels very dated. And the small text, smaller logos and limited photography create a very empty page. Which all points to something that lacks a clear visual pull. It needs a personality to make it memorable.</p>

<blockquote>
We cre­at­ed a brand that took them from a func­tion­al prod­uct to an emo­tive brand plat­form that makes time spent on mobiles more valu­able for everyone.
<br /><br />
The first port of call was to drop ​‘Rewards’ from the name and couch the visu­al iden­ti­ty in the idea that every­day moments can be more rewarding.
<br /><br />
The new brand has enabled them to stand for more than just rewards, tak­ing them out of the world of cash­back and into the epi­cen­tre of expe­ri­en­tial tech, fin­tech and mobile life.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://odabranding.com/work/airtime" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ODA press release</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Logo_detail.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Logo detail.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.666666%;">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The new logo comes in with a much better resolved typographic approach. Rendered in a friendly, rounded-corner sans serif, the lead-in &#8220;A&#8221; pleasantly jumps off the page. The logo is set with a two-color approach to separate &#8220;Air&#8221; and &#8220;time&#8221;. While abrupt, I get why designers seek to improve the reading of a word (particularly a word smash, like this). But by rule, I prefer always allowing for a single-color option. Personal idiosyncrasies aside, the new logo feels well balanced, active, and much better executed. With its thicker, mono-stroke it also performs much better in the limited space of mobile/app applications.<p/>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Typography.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Typography_2.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Supporting the logo is Uplifting Sans. This custom type is an all-cap sans serif that shares an overall personality with the logo but as a complete alphabet set with notably sharper corners. The base set is fairly straight forward. Where things get different—and likely divisive—is with the mixed-case special characters, that, as ODA puts it, &#8220;injects moments of visible joy into the tone of voice.&#8221; I get it. I see what they are trying to do. But, it doesn&#8217;t quite feel fully resolved into the Uplifting Sans character set.<p/>

<p>My main issue with the special characters largely comes down to the reading flow. With such compact lettering, some of these characters create inconsistent spacing that starts to break up some words. Particularly, the &#8220;T&#8221; and the &#8220;P&#8221; take up a lot of horizontal space. This also waterfalls into my second issue with the special characters. I don&#8217;t like that they are mixed case. Similarly, this just creates flow issues that affect the readability. The &#8220;h&#8221;, &#8220;y&#8221; and &#8220;i&#8221; lowercase characters seem unnecessary. And my final issue is with using the &#8220;A&#8221; from your logo as the special character &#8220;A&#8221;. I appreciate that the special characters work to build out a secondary typeface based on the logo&#8217;s &#8220;A&#8221;, but in this use, I really want to see the &#8220;A&#8221; in the logo preserved for the logo alone.<p/>

<p>All of this probably sounds like I hate it. And yet, I don&#8217;t. In many of the following instances it does just what it needs to do, interjecting a lightness to otherwise heavy blocks of copy. It just doesn&#8217;t hit it out of the park for me.</p>

<blockquote>
We brought the emo­tion of emo­jis to the moments of reward, putting the emo­tion­al expe­ri­ence into focus through own­able brand expressions.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://odabranding.com/work/airtime" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ODA press release</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Icons_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Icons.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Icons.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The emoji-as-icon-set approach is interesting to me. What I think they get right is thinking about these in the environment of the digital app and extending the phone interface into something that bridges the experience. However, I wonder how many in the &#8220;mobile generation&#8221; resonate with these icons. The cartoony quality is playful and fun, but my first thought went to user testing (and that is not something I can answer here). What I do like about them is how they nicely expand the color palette. This fixes an issue with the prior brand identity. Overall, the icons are cohesive, expressive, and help create a unique experience. So here, they get top marks.</p>

<p>The icons also join the special characters to replace some letters. Largely replacing vowels like &#8220;O&#8221;s and &#8220;A&#8221;s the icons are most successful when they directly relate to the words they interact with. I have concerns about this running away from them, but as is, they work nicely in short, single instances to add dimension to simple statements.</p>

<blockquote>
An empow­er­ing style of pho­tog­ra­phy focussed on reward­ing the mobile gen­er­a­tion, mak­ing Air­time for every­one, not just the penny-pinchers.
<br /><br />
Cel­e­brat­ing the effort­less every­day moments was brought to life by cel­e­brat­ing the small rewards in our sec­ondary pho­tog­ra­phy style, mak­ing them feel heroic.</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://odabranding.com/work/airtime" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ODA press release</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Photography.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Photography_2.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The photography does a really nice job of mixing optimistic lifestyle and themed-product photography into a complementary set. Relying on blue and yellow backgrounds really works well against the skin tones to create cohesion. I hope they can maintain this look as they expand into photography that represents the other seasons (so the images match the time of year). Maintaining the blue skies in winter may require a bit of Photoshop.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Grid.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Grid layout.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Helping to put this all together is a grid system that uses a three column grid to break up the compositions into a 1 to 2 ratio. It is a straightforward approach that does help to establish hierarchy and a constant rhythm across pieces, and it will be useful as the identity expands.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Website.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Mobile.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Website and mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_App_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_App.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>The app.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Digital.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Digital collection.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>As we see this all come together, the pieces all start to fit nicely into the compositions. While there are not a lot of supporting images, what is shown does a good job to provide a personality that celebrates shopping. The black, blue, yellow, and white work together in various compositions without any one feeling too dominant. And as long as the statements are short, nothing feels overwhelming.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Ads.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Airtime_Ads_2.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo and Identity for Airtime by ODA" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The advertising is where we see the addition of the logo within the compositions. In these instances it feels like a consistent tagline is needed to help connect the dots. Maybe it is just me&#8230;since I am not part of the mobile generation. But I want there to be a simpler way for them to say what they do. Often, it starts to get a bit wordy, which doesn&#8217;t quite work on a billboard. This may be because there is such a small sample of ads, so I am looking a bit too closely. Regardless, the compositions are bold and eye catching. Thinking back to the old identity, this is quite an elevation.</p>

<p class="end">To round out, I am happy. It feels happy. The mix of type, icon, image, and color make the brand look the part of an establish and trusted company that wants to help you shop. There is room for improvement. I will hold off with a wait-and-see on their aim of becoming the &#8220;epi­cen­tre of expe­ri­en­tial tech, fin­tech and mobile life&#8221; because there is just not enough yet to weigh in (and that&#8217;s a big claim). Yet, there is a personality that was sorely missing. There is a confidence. And that is exciting to see. The rest, well, that&#8217;s up… in the air.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_airtime_by_oda.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_airtime_by_oda.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Statehouse Ohio by Together</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/statehouse_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Statehouse Ohio by Together" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.gotogether.agency/work/statehouse/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_statehouse_ohio_by_together.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_statehouse_ohio_by_together.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 17:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Being Health by The Working Assembly</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/being_health_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Being Health by The Working Assembly" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.beinghealth.co/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_being_health_by_the_working_assembly.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_being_health_by_the_working_assembly.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 17:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Fashion but Make it Fonts</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/funny_style_fonts.jpg" alt="Fashion but Make it Fonts" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C8aIcZ1N_Hq/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Wisdom Kaye, a model, director, stylist, photographer, videographer, and all-around social media personality, takes on the challenge of styling himself as different typefaces. The 41-plus million views his reel has gotten are warranted.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fashion_but_make_it_fonts.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/fashion_but_make_it_fonts.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Brighter than the Sun of its Parts”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/protergia_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2011) &#8220;<a href="https://www.protergia.gr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Protergia</a> is Metlen Energy &amp; Metals Electricity and Natural Gas provider, the largest private energy company in Greece, and is active in the supply of electricity and gas by offering modern and reliable services. Protergia offers combined electricity and gas products and serves more than 500.000 electricity supply account numbers throughout the country. The sophisticated way Protergia offers its products, the innovation in its services and the green design focus with friendly service, paves a new way to energy for thousands of households and businesses.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://someoneinlondon.com/" target="_blank">SomeOne</a> (London, UK)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://someoneinlondon.com/projects/protergia" target="_blank">SomeOne project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>We wanted to qualify Protergia’s new position as the customer champion that can tempt customers away from an unhappy experience with their existing supplier who’s either too big to care or too small to make a difference.<br /><br />The logo includes a graphic interpretation of the sun, an iconic shorthand that can be used through the brand. The word mark is based upon the font Codec Warm by Zeta fonts, with crafted letter form creating a unique identifier for the brand.<br /><br />Our photography style captures the positivity of the the sun. Imagery of our customers are captured during golden hour, taking on the warm orange hues of the Protergia sunshine gradient.<br /><br />Our brand character Gia (which is phonetically akin to ‘hi’ in Greek – γεια! ) takes shape from our sun symbol within the wordmark. Gia is here to guide Protergia customers along their energy supply journey – from chatbots within the Protergia app, to TopTips on social media platforms.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-295344"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_icon_with_photography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Icon with photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_tagline_sun_gradient.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Tagline and sun gradient.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_tagline_sun_photography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Tagline and sun photography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_icon_set.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Icon set.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_mascot_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_mascot_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>“Gia”, the mascot.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_instagram_stories.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Instagram stories.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_app.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>App.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_welcome_kit.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Welcome kit.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_bags.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Bags.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_tracksuit_keychain.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Tracksuit and keychain.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/protergia_launch_event.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Protergia by SomeOne" />
<figcaption>Launch event.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yj-31OFnNNY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Launch event video. Worth scrubbing through the video to see the event space shift from blue to orange.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zcZAFj8MPiA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>TV spot. By <a href="https://www.thenewtons.gr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Newtons</a>. Unexpected song choice.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The old logo was not very good, mostly due to that poor wordmark that had so much going on with a combination of super circular characters and then the super narrow “r”s, an “i” with the smallest tittle ever recorded, and that “e”. The one good thing it had going is that the “e“ aligned at the center with the gradient bar underneath and the icon above — which, to its credit, did have a proper <em>energy provider</em> abstraction to it — but, yeah, that type was not good. The new logo sticks to the all lowercase approach, which manages to work nicely with the balance of the descenders of the “p” and “g” and it also maintains the same single storey construction of the “g” and “a”. Obviously, the big shift is the integration of an icon into the wordmark with the “o” being replaced by an abstract sun icon. It's a very well executed approach that makes a lot of optical decisions to make the sun look like a glyph that belongs with the others in weight and proportion.<span></span> The identity then goes in a number of directions, all orbiting around the sun… first there is the icon that can work on its own outside of the wordmark and that interacts rather nicely with photography. Then there is the sun gradient, which is literally warm and fuzzy. Finally there is the photography that includes a sun shining in the background, echoing the orange and yellow color palette and furthering those warm and fuzzy feelings. All of these, paired with the blue/purple typography and other graphic accents, make for a happy, optimistic combination. The icon also transforms into a mascot-slash-avatar with little eyes and a cute spinning animation. Not sure if it's <em>too</em> cute and whether it takes away from any gravitas the icon might have achieved.<span></span> As noted in the caption of the launch event, give it a quick scrub… the shift in lighting from blue to orange is quite nice, making what could have been an annoying gimmick into something quite memorable with a slow burn of the shift. Also, that TV spot… with Guns N' Roses' <em>Paradise City</em> sent me. At first I was, like, “Wait, is that the song I think it is…?” and the moment the whistle blew I started headbanging. I have no idea what the payoff is, since it's literally Greek to me, but 🤘. Overall, the few applications shown are engaging and energetic and look the part of a utility company with a decent balance of approachability and corporate-ness.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_protergia_by_someone.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_protergia_by_someone.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“This, too, Shall Mass”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/massart_2024_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 1873, <a href="https://massart.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Massachusetts College of Art and Design</a>, typically referred to as MassArt, is the only public independent college of art and design in the United States and one of its oldest art schools. What began as a school to teach drawing — spurred by The Massachusetts Drawing Act of 1870 that required most cities in the state to provide drawing instruction in public schools and mechanical drawing instruction to persons over 15 years old through evening schools — today is a comprehensive art and design institution that spans 18 undergraduate and nine graduate programs, certificates, continuing education, and post-baccalaureate study with a campus, located in Boston’s arts district, that includes nearly a million square feet of classroom, studio, exhibition, and living spaces for a student body of nearly 2,000 and a faculty of 300-plus. Recently, MassArt introduced a new identity designed by local firm, <a href="https://www.moth.design/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Moth Design</a>.</p>
<span id="more-295337"></span>

<blockquote>Every corner of MassArt vibrates with energy and excitement. To effectively illustrate the institution’s vibrancy and openness, we created a system leveraging a flexible and fun identifier: the elastic M. Unfussy and limitless in form, the elastic M, paired with fresh typography and a versatile color palette, allows for an unlimited set of configurations while remaining cohesive in voice.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.moth.design/projects/massart/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Moth Design project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/massart_2024_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The old logo, also designed by Moth Design* <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/massterful_identity.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">in the very distant past of 2008</a>, was really good in its ability to integrate yet also differentiate the two words that make up the logo by the simple gesture of cutting the “S” short and at the same angle as the “A”. It wasn&#8217;t the most exciting or “artistic” of logos but it was pretty effective and the cut angle then informed the rest of the identity.</p>

<p>The new logo aims to add some more artistic flair to the wordmark and it succeeds for the most part with the quirky “M” but unfortunately it ends up being the letter with the least prominence and body mass as the rest of the letters which feel wider and heavier. The unconventional design of the “S”s, where they feel like they are tipping forward, and their tight kerning in contrast to the “A”s to their sides, makes them stand out too much. The “R” also does this tipping-forward thing as its bowl reaches all the way to the right at the same distance as its leg (in most cases, the leg of the “R” extends to the right ever so slightly to anchor it better). It&#8217;s a decent logo and at first glance it looks good but I feel like it needed to commit more strongly to either being weirder or normal-er.</p>

<p>* Founded by a MassArt alum, Moth Design also designed <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_maam_by_moth_design.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the college&#8217;s museum identity</a> and <a href="https://www.moth.design/projects/massart-150/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the college&#8217;s 150-year-anniversary identity</a>.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/massart_2024_logo_full_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Full name logo, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/massart_2024_logo_full.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Full name logo. Refined by MassArt faculty member <a href="https://djr.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">David Jonathan Ross</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The full name logo is… a lot. The wide structure of the primary logo becomes too much when applied to 34 letters instead of just 7 and, through no fault of Moth Design or David Jonathan Ross, the line breaks created by the length of “MASSACHUSETTS” makes it a very hard set of words to work with. In this case my inclination would be to move “ART” to the second line but I am sure that, philosophically, no one wanted to separate art from design. Beyond that, though, there are still some odd design choices, like the “E”s with all the horizontal strokes being the same length instead of the middle one being the shortest and the top one shorter than the bottom one. The horizontal strokes added to the “I” hint at a desire to make this more monospace-ish but it&#8217;s not. The “TT” being the sole ligature is also distracting. It brings me no joy to nitpick this so much as it&#8217;s clearly a tough task but I feel like they painted themselves into a corner with some typographic design decisions that were not the most flexible.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_generator.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Elastic “M” generator.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_dynamic_m_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_dynamic_m_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_dynamic_m_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Elastic “M” in use.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>On the opposite end of the flexibility scale, the identity introduces what they are calling “Elastic ‘M’s”, which are kind of cool, fun, and artsy… and makes me think that, perhaps, the original design pitch involved including these “M”s into the wordmark and having them be all kinds of weird and have different ones appear in different places but that&#8217;s a hard trick to implement and not the most effective in establishing brand recognition. The “M”s are good as a supporting element and help add some interest to the layouts. I like that they don&#8217;t immediately read as “M”s and that it might be more of a subconscious delivery to viewers. I do wonder if the super thin stroke approach is the best use for these… I can see on the generator that they can be executed bolder, which makes them look a little more exciting and interesting.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_typography.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_photography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Photography. By MassArt alum <a href="https://tonyluong.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tony Luong</a>.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_guidelines.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_report_cover.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Report cover.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_business_card.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Business card.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_advertising.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Not a whole lot in application. The type choices are strong, particularly <a href="https://www.thedesignersfoundry.com/romek" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Romek</a>, which has some really nice proportions and it has a book-ish vibe but it&#8217;s also friendly. The identity goes for that mix of serif and sans serif in similar weights which requires a lot of fine-tuning to work and the left and center ads above <em>almost</em> pull it off. I think the issue is that the sans, <a href="https://rgtype.fontdue.com/fonts/ciron" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ciron</a>, is ever so slightly heavier. The business card provides a better example of mixing the typefaces in different sizes and then adding the two logos as bold contrasts.</p>

<blockquote>The new and improved MassArt.edu began with a meticulous content strategy and information architecture process. The result? A radically streamlined website structure, a tailored landing page strategy to highlight programmatic offerings, and an editorial homepage feature to showcase the people, work, and events that define MassArt’s essence.</blockquote><h3><a href="https://www.moth.design/projects/massart/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Moth Design project page</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 42.25%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_Website_Hover_Cursor.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Website cursor effect.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_Website_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_Website_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_Website_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_Website_04.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Website.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_Website_mobile.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Website on mobile.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>A lot of energy seems to have gone into the website and, while I have not been the most supportive of some of the design decisions, the website does look pretty great. It feels artsy, it feels design-y, it feels academic. It&#8217;s exciting, it&#8217;s serious, and it packs a lot of information in each page through some really strong typographic hierarchy and solid layouts. Also, props for resisting the urge to do the cursor trail effect on ALL the website and instead they just limited it to the feature section in the home page — it leaves me wanting more of it instead of making me wish the website just died.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_various.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Various applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_swag_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/MassArt_2024_swag_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for MassArt by Moth Design" />
<figcaption>Swag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">Overall, the various nitpicks expressed in this opinion can just be personal preference of how certain things could be designed, which doesn&#8217;t mean anything here is right or wrong and, in the end, the identity does portray the college in an artistic way but also in a very professional and put together way, giving parents more confidence in their kids going to <em>art school</em>.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_massart_by_moth_design.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_massart_by_moth_design.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Wei-Chuan USA</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/wei_chuan_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Wei-Chuan USA" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.instagram.com/weichuanusa.inc/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_wei_chuan_usa.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_wei_chuan_usa.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>