<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for James Beard Foundation by Siberia</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/james_beard_foundation_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for James Beard Foundation by Siberia" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://siberia.io/work/jamesbeard/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_james_beard_foundation_by_siberia.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_james_beard_foundation_by_siberia.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: O’Bay Giant</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/nice_show_bay_love.jpg" alt="O’Bay Giant" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://benloiz.com/work/show-bay-love/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>This isn&#8217;t a traditional identity project and it&#8217;s for a one-time use so it wasn&#8217;t quite right for a regular post on Brand New but it&#8217;s still worth a peek as there is a myriad nice things in this event branding by Ben Loiz Studio for the 2025 edition of the <a href="https://www.hoopbus.com/show-bay-love" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hoop Bus Show Love Series</a> — an “event series that brings together basketball enthusiasts of all ages and skill levels to celebrate the sport and give back to the community” — which took place in the Bay Area during last month&#8217;s NBA All-Star Week.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/obay_giant.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/obay_giant.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 10:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Loose Change”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/publicis_toronto_new.png" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1926) &#8220;At <a href="https://www.publicis.ca/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Publicis</a> we believe that change is shaped by those who are brave enough. Through our people, clients, and industry, we have the power to change minds, change tastes, and change hearts. We carry the power to change with us every day. Join us and we’ll lead the change together. Our [Canada] team of 750 change lovers continues to grow by the day giving us a strength that’s tempered by diverse expertise and unrelenting spirit. We apply intelligence, technology, and creativity in equal measure, ensuring that we continue to lead the change by making good on our promise to deliver it.&#8221;</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            In-house</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://live.standards.site/publicisbrandguideline" target="_blank">Publicis Canada guidelines</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>In 1926, Marcel Bleustein-Blanchet carved the first marks of Publicis, symbolizing a belief in leading change rather than reacting to it. Nearly a century later, Publicis Toronto embraced this philosophy by co-creating a new typeface—merging Marcel’s original letterforms with contributions from every team member. This collective approach transformed more than typography; it forged a living identity that bridges past and future. Rooted in history yet designed for evolution, the typeface became the cornerstone of Publicis Toronto’s new visual identity, embodying the agency’s commitment to shaping change rather than being shaped by it.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-304144"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_historic_photo.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Company founder Marcel Bleustein-Blanchet.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_custom_type_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_custom_type_02.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_custom_type_03.gif" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_custom_type_04.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_custom_type_05.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Custom typeface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_guidelines.gif" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Guidelines.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_type_compositions_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_type_compositions_02.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Type compositions.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_brochures.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_print_01.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_print_02.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Print materials.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_poster_tubes.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Poster tubes.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_instagram_stories_01.gif" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_instagram_stories_02.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Instagram stories.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_advertising.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/publicis_toronto_newsprint_coffee_cup.jpg" alt="New Identity for Publicis Canada done In-house" />
<figcaption>Newsprint and cup.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1061846562?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction video.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            The photo of Founder Marcel Bleustein-Blanchet pointing at the logo on the door of his office has certainly made an impact on the company, <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_publicis_worldwide_by_publicis_north_america.php" target="_blank">having informed</a> its current logo in use since 2015 and now serving as inspiration for a new custom typeface that drives the identity for Publicis Canada. I was told this could expand to the rest of Publicis but I don't see how that might be happening with the impending launch of “Leo”, which merges Publicis Worldwide and Leo Burnett and that, given that the way these large holding companies work, I'll admit I can't tell if Publicis Canada does its own thing independent of Publicis Worldwide, independent of Publicis Groupe but that, to be honest, I don't lose any sleep over. Back to the design…<span></span> Unlike the logo, that tamed the swashes and exotic curves of the original drawing, the typeface embraces them and reinterprets them into a relatively restrained typeface, by which I mean, this could have easily been a train wreck if taken to a more literal extreme but, instead, the result is a rather unique serif typeface with plenty of flair and some rather groovy characters like the “a” or the “g” or the “u”. At times it can come across as a little too whimsical in use, looking like something you would see on a fairy tale book cover but compositions like the hero “Lead the change” line with the Publicis lion icon as the period is kinda cool.<span></span> The applications shown are more mock-up-y than the usual mock-ups so I have a hard time taking it as seriously because the likelihood of any of these existing in real life as shown is minimal, which is not to say the applications are bad… on the contrary, they are all quite attractive in their red and black combo but, in the end, there is nothing particularly tangible about them. Makes for <a href="https://www.instagram.com/publiciscanada/" target="_blank">some distinctive social media content</a> though. Overall, a somewhat entertaining exercise to look at and, to their credit, an unexpected aesthetic to be embraced by a large ad agency but given the uncertainty of the Publicis brand as it merges with the Leo Burnett makes it hard to get too invested in it.
</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_publicis_canada_done_in_house.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_identity_for_publicis_canada_done_in_house.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 10:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: Friday Likes 528: From Tavern, Glasfurd &amp; Walker, and OurCreative.</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“From Tavern, Glasfurd &amp; Walker, and OurCreative.”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/friday_likes_528.jpg" alt="Friday Likes 528" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Three standalone bottles of spirits from around the world come together in this cocktail of Friday Likes with work from Brooklyn, Vancouver, and Leeds.</p>
<span id="more-304139"></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Old Grand-dad by Tavern</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_oldgranddad.jpg" alt="Old Grand-dad by Tavern" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;">First brewed in 1882 by Basil Hayden Sr., <a href="https://www.beamdistilling.com/our-brands/old-grand-dad-bourbon" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Old Grand-dad</a> (as Mr. Basil came to be known) is a bourbon with a recipe passed on through generations and distilled with a higher percentage of rye. In late 2024, the James B. Beam Distilling Company released Old Grand-Dad 16-year, its oldest expression yet. For this special edition, the packaging, designed by Brooklyn, NY-based <a href="https://tavern.agency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tavern</a>, goes all out with stunning, custom and/or customized typography that is as richly layered as I am sure this bourbon is. Leading the charge is a hatched, arched, and drop-shadowed “Old Grand-dad” that crowns the rest of the inline typography below it, which in turn lay on top of a giant, red “16” in the background. The class-act continues through the neck of the bottle with a gold wax rendition of an “OGD” monogram held in place by a gold ribbon, all hinting at the aged liquid gold inside. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://tavern.agency/ogd16" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Bellamie by Glasfurd &amp; Walker</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_bellamie.jpg" alt="Bellamie by Glasfurd &amp; Walker" />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:60px!important;"><a href="https://bellamieaperitif.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bellamie</a> is an apéritif created by UK-based Marie Voirin and is “inspired by the French &#8216;Guignolet&#8217; liqueur and its signature ripe cherry flavour” that has been crafted using the Montmorency sour cherry. The packaging, designed by Vancouver, BC-based <a href="https://glasfurdandwalker.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Glasfurd &amp; Walker</a>, is an ode to all things Art Nouveau, most evident in the swirly whirly logo and all its exaggerated curves that is surrounded by the classic ornate floral motifs of the style but carefully redrawn to include cherries. Glasfurd &amp; Walker also designed the bottle, which is the highlight of the project — not to take away from the rest of the elements but, I mean, look at it — taking inspiration from perfume bottles to create a ridged, tapered bottle with a thin strip at its center to place the elegant label and capped off with a dramatic copper top. Don&#8217;t skip on scrolling all the way to the footer of their website to see a lovely Art Nouveau-shaped glass and at the link there is a charming monogram as well. This project is basically all cherry-on-top all the time. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://the-brandidentity.com/project/glasfurd-walkers-belle-%C3%A9poque-inspired-design-for-bellamie-deserves-a-place-on-your-drinks-bar" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span>

<h1 class="friday_likes">Pico by OurCreative.</h1>
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_pico.jpg" alt="Pico by OurCreative." />

<p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:30px!important;">Created by Leeds, UK-based Double Six Drinks, <a href="https://doublesixdrinks.com/collections/pico?srsltid=AfmBOookQFfCbWc8rfbhXt5MRa5IJLE50YC7zmkKQ5Ksio-rSTJ1trPJ" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Pico</a> is a is Mexican, distilled agave spirit that is imported, blended, finished, and bottled in Leeds — as such it can not be called a Tequila given that it&#8217;s not produced in Tequila, Jalisco, as it is a protected designation of origin (like Champagne). The packaging for this “Tequilana” (as it can be referred to), designed by Hull- and Leeds-based <a href="https://www.our-creative.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OurCreative.</a>, takes an unconventional approach to not just most tequilas but to most spirits, with a rugged, layered, grungy aesthetic achieved by layering a very specific set of images — including but not limited to Yorkshire’s mines and the Blue Weber agave plant — that combine to tell the story, legacy, and tradition of the spirit. The collage is accentuated on the bottle with a die-cut that highlights each layer with a different width, all anchors by a white box at the bottom with sturdy, elegant typography. It might not be official Tequila but I wouldn&#8217;t mind making one of these bottles <em>mine</em>. <span class="pagination_divider"></span><span class="small_caps"><a href="https://www.our-creative.com/work/pico" target="_blank" rel="noopener">See full project</a></span></p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_528.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/friday_likes_528.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 09:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Fast Forward by Two Are</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/fastforward_logo_before_after-1.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Fast Forward by Two Are" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://two-are.com/work/fastforward">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_fast_forward_by_two_are.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_fast_forward_by_two_are.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 11:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Name and Logo for Yetch Studio</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/yetch_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Name and Logo for Yetch Studio" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DGUvOyGpHyB/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_and_logo_for_yetch_studio.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_and_logo_for_yetch_studio.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 11:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Will the Riyal Saudi Currency Please Stand Up</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/news_riyal_before_after.png" alt="Will the Riyal Saudi Currency Please Stand Up" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.sama.gov.sa/en-US/Currency/SRS/Pages/default.aspx">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Approved by Salman bin Abdulaziz Al Saud, King of Saudi Arabia, the Saudi Central Bank has introduced a new symbol for the country&#8217;s Riyal currency. The design was “inspired by Arabic calligraphy, which represents the Arabic language – one of the jewels of human civilization” and “the name ‘Riyal’ extending the historical legacy of the Saudi currency, first issued in 1346 AH”. <a href="https://www.sama.gov.sa/en-US/Currency/SRS/Pages/Guidelines.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A set of guidelines goes</a> deeper into the meaning, construction, and use of the new symbol.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/will_the_riyal_saudi_currency_please_stand_up.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/will_the_riyal_saudi_currency_please_stand_up.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 10:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“What Say You?”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/ditu_logo_new.png" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 2025) <a href="https://ditutv.lat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ditu</a> is Colombia&#8217;s first FAST (Free Ad-Supported Streaming Television) platform, created by Caracol Televisión, Colombia’s leading TV network. A completely free TV platform, users can enjoy soap operas, series, documentaries, live broadcasts, sporting events, and much more Colombia&#8217;s national TV and is available on Android, iOS, and Samsung TV.</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://aluzian.com/" target="_blank">Aluzian</a> (Bogota, Colombia)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://aluzian.com/works/ditu/" target="_blank">Aluzian project page</a>

                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>DITU is an invitation: “DI TÚ” (You Say) what you want to watch! “DI TÚ” what you dream of, and see it on DITU! We needed a short, catchy name with attitude. That’s how DITU was born—a phrase that connects and makes you want to watch more.<br /><br />We designed a bold, dynamic, and digital-first logo. In a world where brands are always in motion, DITU comes to life with its moving “T”—a playful, cheeky detail that reinforces the brand’s promise and dynamic spirit.<br /><br />Typography with “sabor”: Expressive, curvy, and full of movement. Every letter shape reflects the energy and excitement of the brand, carefully designed to shine in digital environments.<br /><br />Inspired by the diversity of content and formats, we created a versatile and expressive design system. DITU thrives on any screen, maintaining a vibrant, eye-catching presence across all devices.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-304104"></span>

 <script>

/**
 * Stop all iframes or HTML5 <video>'s from playing
 */
var stopVideos = function () {
	var videos = document.querySelectorAll('iframe, video');
	Array.prototype.forEach.call(videos, function (video) {
		if (video.tagName.toLowerCase() === 'video') {
			video.pause();
		} else {
			var src = video.src;
			video.src = src;
		}
	});
};

</script>

<style>

.pausevideos {
    margin: 20px 0 30px;
    display: block;
    font-size: .8em;
font-family: 'ABCSocial';
font-variation-settings: "wdth" 100, "wght" 370, "slnt" 0;
-webkit-font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
font-feature-settings: "ss02" 1, "ss04" 1, "ss05" 1, "lnum" 1, "liga" 1;
text-transform: uppercase;
letter-spacing:.15em;
font-style: normal;
font-weight: normal;
    cursor: pointer;
    border: 1px solid rgba(242,24,24,.5);
    background: transparent;
    color: rgba(242,24,24,1);
    padding: 12px 15px 10px;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

.pausevideos:hover {
border: 1px solid rgba(0,0,0,.3);
color:rgba(0,0,0,.85);
background:white;
	-webkit-transition: all 250ms ease;
    -moz-transition: all 250ms ease;
    transition: all 250ms ease;
	text-decoration:none;
}

</style>

<button onclick="stopVideos();" class="pausevideos">pause all videos</button> 

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_logo.png" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_logo_with_parent_brand.png" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Logo with parent brand.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_logo_animation_mnemonic.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation and mnemonic. (Unmute for sound.)</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_color_palette.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_custom_type_01.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_custom_type_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Custom typeface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_icon_set.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Icons.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_graphic_system_01.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_graphic_system_02.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Graphic system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_advertising_04.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_app_icon.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" style="float:left; width:49%;" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_avatar.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" style="float:right; width:49%;" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<figcaption>App icon and social media avatar.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_instagram_posts.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_instagram_stories.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Instagram stories.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_ui_01.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_ui_02.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_ui_03.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_ui_04.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_ui_05.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>User interface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_remote.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Remote control.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="quarter">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/ditu_tote_bag.jpg" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Ditu by Aluzian" />
<figcaption>Tote bag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1062997061?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction video.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            As an English speaker, I can't help but put an “R2” before the name and get endless joy from it. As a Spanish speaker, I can very much appreciate what they are going for by combining two words — “di” (which means “say” in English) and “tu” (which means “you”) — from common parlance into a short, memorable, catchy name. The logo is a simple yet playful wordmark in a chunky sans serif that straddles the line between unicase and not-unicase as the “t” could be read as either a lowercase “t” with its top cut off or an uppercase “T” with the bottom curled. Both interpretations would be valid, both instances are readable, and both options have a fun charm to them. Having said that, I feel like it's not 100% resolved, mostly on the bottom curve where I want it to somehow have a better relationship with the bottom parts of the stems of the “d” and “u”. Still, like the name, it's short, punchy, and effective.<span></span> The identity introduces a custom condensed grotesque-ish sans serif designed in collaboration with <a href="https://www.instagram.com/bastardatype/" target="_blank">Bastarda Type</a>, which, <a href="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/the_year_in_review_part_2_recurring_trends_2024.php" target="_blank">as last year proved</a>, is always a popular choice and this one doesn't disappoint. I could have done without the cutesy tittles over the “I”s, “i”s, and exclamation and question marks but that doesn't mean they are out of place for an entertainment brand. Shoutout to that “G” tho. It's hot. The color palette, using shades of purple with bright blue accents looks great and it positions Ditu into owning a color range like Netflix's reds or Hulu's greens.<span></span> The primary graphic device for the identity is a series of stacked, staggered, and skewed rounded-corner rectangles that allude to the various screen proportions the platform is available on. These would probably be undecipherable without said explanation but they still make for fun backgrounds and holding shapes that add some subtle dynamism to the applications. The little icon characters come out of left field and are somewhat gratuitous but, again, not entirely uncalled for. Overall, this is a solid identity that has a friendly and accessible vibe that should help attract a large enough audience to put that Free Ad-Supported model to work.
</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_ditu_by_aluzian.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_ditu_by_aluzian.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 10:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“’Pack to the Future”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Haglofs_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Founded by Wiktor Haglöf in 1914, <a href="https://www.haglofs.com/en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Haglöfs</a> is a Swedish outdoor performance brand. What started as one man&#8217;s pursuit of a different kind of backpack (his first design was sewn by his next-door neighbor, Maria Långberg) has become a global leader in outdoor gear known for rugged dependability and eco-conscious design. For those not familiar with the brand, it fits alongside Arc’teryx and Fjällräven. Think technical designs and premium performance. Haglöfs worked with Stockholm, Sweden-based branding and design agency <a href="https://www.stockholmdesignlab.se/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stockholm Design Lab</a> to redesign their logo and brand platform, which is set to launch over the next year.</p><span id="more-304089"></span>

<blockquote>
The iconic Haglöf symbol has been refined, and the new wordmark is playing on the tension between the past and the future, between the organic and the engineered. They are not just branding elements for Haglöfs products and services but also embody their legacy, signifying their commitment and pride in Haglöfs brand’s responsibility.
<br /><br />
Separating the Haglöfs wordmark from the symbol unlocks greater flexibility and versatility in product applications, breaking the static monotony of a fixed logotype lockup and allowing for more dynamic and engaging expressions.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.stockholmdesignlab.se/work/hagloefs" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stockholm Design Lab case study.</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Logo_Closeup.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>New wordmark.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Symbol_animated.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Monogram animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Symbol_animation.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Monogram, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The old identity, paired a straightforward sans serif wordmark with a prominent &#8220;H&#8221; symbol. Despite this being the primary lockup, this composition struggles in the way all vertical-meets-horizontal shapes struggle. It just never feels quite right. The pairing of the two elements also highlights all the ways they are dissimilar. Most prominently the symbols rounded terminals versus the wordmarks flat ones and the inconsistent stroke weight. While I love the stitch-like quality of the symbol, it was time for a refresh.</p>

<p>The new identity does two things absolutely brilliantly. It returns to a typeface that feels inline with its heritage. The custom typeface is lovely, credit to <a href="https://lettersfromsweden.se/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Letters from Sweden</a>. The double-story &#8220;a&#8221; and &#8220;g&#8221; work perfectly next to each other. I love the overhang on the &#8220;f&#8221;. The second thing is the separation of the symbol from the wordmark. The split allows the symbol to remain largely intact, just with a slightly stronger stroke. (I see this as particularly noteworthy for a company that emphasizes it commitment to <a href="https://haglofsrestored.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">restoring and repairing</a> equipment as maintaining a key visual element reenforces that timeless thread.) To connect the two elements, the ball terminal from the typeface is sized to match the symbol. I admit that I was taken back a bit when I first saw the two together. But I quickly changed my mind. It is a fantastically unexpected pairing.</p>

<blockquote>
The bespoke Haglöfs typeface draws inspiration from the typography tradition that emerged at the outset of the 20th century, coinciding with the founding of Haglöfs.
<br /><br />
Haglöfs custom numeral typeface is clearly linked to the Haglöfs symbol. It serves as a supplementary asset that enhances and broadens the brand’s technical expression, avoiding excessive use of the symbol.
<br /><br />
The color palette enables us to create a nuanced, unique identity by playing on the contrast between nature and tech.
</blockquote>
<h3><a href="https://www.stockholmdesignlab.se/work/hagloefs" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stockholm Design Lab case study.</a></h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Typography.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Typography_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Color.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Colors.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Photography.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<hr />
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom:66.66666667%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Photography_2.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Photography and footage.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The custom type family contains three typefaces: Haglöfs Display, Haglöfs Text, and Haglöfs Mono. The display and text typefaces are wonderful. While I do wish there was a bit more word spacing, the quality that they bring to the overall identity is significant. I am probably most surprised, though, by the mono typeface. While it serves to add a technical quality, it doesn&#8217;t have the same sensitivities that the other two have. As result, it feels like the odd one out. The last bit of typography is the numeral typeface. Constructed with dots and dashes, it feels like a play on Morse code. I like what it brings to the family, however I am hesitant about its potential for overuse.</p>

<p>Colors mostly fall from white to warm gray to black. There are three exceptions: green, red, and yellow. They provide the necessary punches of color to contrast the rest of the neutrals. As you will see in a minute, the red becomes the primary color, and it is a very successful pairing with the range of grays. The colors also drive the photography. Or perhaps it is the other way round. Regardless, the muted (and sometimes grainy) photography reflects back to an earlier time period. Pushing the photography to feel historic achieves the goal of &#8220;playing on the tension between the past and the future.&#8221;</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Print.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Print applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Book.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Book_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Booklet.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The print applications in collection achieve a beautiful harmony. There is a nice sense of scale in how the designs maintain a strong sense of hierarchy and order throughout the pieces. Aside from a lovely layout, the individual pages are thoughtfully tended to. It feels delightfully vintage, in the best way possible.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Social.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Social_2.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Social media.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Posters.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Posters.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Instagram stories and posts and street posters all combine lovely type layouts with photography. I think what is noteworthy about these examples is the variety achieved with such a small set of assets. I particularly like how the three posters sit together.</p>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="background:black;padding-bottom:100%">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Apparel.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Apparel.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Details.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Apparel details.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The monogram cleverly appears in the apparel detail, which makes the overall identity all the more enjoyable.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Bag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Haglöfs by Stockholm Design Lab" />
<figcaption>Bag.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Summary.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<hr />
<div class="video-container">
<video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload">
<source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/Haglofs_Summary_02.mp4" type="video/mp4">
</video>
</div>
<figcaption>Summary videos.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">I cherish the saying, &#8220;There is no such thing as bad weather, only bad clothes.&#8221; In refreshing Haglöf, SDL has been able to present a pleasant response to that sentiment. By creating two sets of complementary parts, one championed by the wordmark, the other of by the symbol, the identity walks a tight line between feeling too traditional and feeling too loud. The success is that both parts fit together. Combined they create something that feels new and different in the hyper-competitive outdoor gear category. As they continue to rollout the identity, I encourage them to pay close attention to keeping that line, regardless of the forecast.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_haglofs_by_stockholm_design_lab.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_haglofs_by_stockholm_design_lab.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 05:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for In The Park by BonTemps</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/inthepark_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for In The Park by BonTemps" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DFqPzogRefW/?img_index=1">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_in_the_park_by_bontemps.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_in_the_park_by_bontemps.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 18:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>