<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"  xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
        <channel>
	    <title>Brand New — Private to Pratik Ringshia</title>
    	<link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew</link>
    	<description>Opinions on corporate and brand identity work</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2020</copyright>
        <generator>Wordpress</generator>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <webfeeds:logo>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:logo>
        <webfeeds:accentColor>f21818</webfeeds:accentColor>
        <webfeeds:analytics id="UA-161036-4" engine="GoogleAnalytics"/>
        <webfeeds:cover image="https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/brand_new_cover_feedly.jpg"/>
        <webfeeds:icon>https://underconsideration.com/brandnew/_images/bn_monogram_feedly.svg</webfeeds:icon>

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.5.2" -->

                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Name, Logo, and Identity for Paddle UK by Arch Creative</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/paddle_uk_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Name, Logo, and Identity for Paddle UK by Arch Creative" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://archcreative.co.uk/work/paddle-uk-british-canoeing-case-study/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_paddle_uk_by_arch_creative.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_name_logo_and_identity_for_paddle_uk_by_arch_creative.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo and Identity for Planu by Holman\Design</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/planu_logo_new.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Planu by Holman\Design" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.holman.design/portfolio/planu-logo-design-and-branding">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_planu_by_holmandesign.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_planu_by_holmandesign.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Be That as it Mayo</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/quirky_mayo_fragrance_will_lewis.jpg" alt="Be That as it Mayo" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://willlevisnumber8.com/products/will-levis-n08">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Will Levis, who started his NFL career as quarterback for the Tennessee Titans in the 2023 season, is the first athlete to sign with Unilever, scoring a lifetime deal with Hellman&#8217;s Mayonnaise in his rookie year. This odd pairing came about for Levis&#8217; appreciation for mayo, which goes as far as putting it in his coffee in place of milk or creamer. (He also eats bananas whole, with their peel.) This week, the partnership yielded another unexpected result: The eight-dollar, Parfum de Mayonnaise, with notes of tart lemon, mayonnaise accord, parsley, coffee undertones, musk, and creamy vanilla. I would like to spread some of that on your sliced bread, if you know what I mean (because I don&#8217;t). <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TPRTAcFIFQ8" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The promo video is worth a watch too</a>.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/be_that_as_it_mayo.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/be_that_as_it_mayo.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“What YouSee is What YouGet”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/yousee_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Est. 1995) &#8220;<a href="https://yousee.dk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouSee</a> is the largest quadruple play service provider in Denmark, and is a part of Nuuday which is a spun-off company from TDC Group, the largest telecommunications company in Denmark which was split into two separate companies. YouSee currently has 994,000 customers.&#8221; (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/YouSee" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wikipedia</a>)</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.inyourdreams.design/" target="_blank">In Your Dreams</a> (Copenhagen, Denmark)</p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                             N/A
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>While trying not to lose brand recognition from the old Visual Identity this redesign seeks to humanize a world of TelCo. with a concept of "Moving you". The concept is expressed in moving design elements. The slight movements in the custom typography and iconography are inspired by the human calligraphic strokes. The custom typography youNik, is developed with Co-Type – A custom take on their great Aeonik.<br /><br />The brand identity is intentionally not over designed - nor under designed. It seeks to find that balance between differentiation and timeless longevity. Only major expressive element is our moving gradients. The intention of the gradients are to create a desirable pulse to the brand design. They are supposed to open up the design, and very quickly leave the attention to the media, message or product. Colors are meant to be diverse yet have a strong brand recognition. youSee Green seeks to highlight the important information, e.g. prices or features. The background colors comes from breaking down a gradient ranging from DarkGreen to Light. So that media can feel the same but still be their own.<br /><br />Generally it has been a major design task to design as many elements, grids and layouts so that they could solve as many task as possible, and yet be understandable. Creating a design system that fits every format, with great attention to keeping a strong alignment across the visual brand landscape.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-296987"></span>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_logo_system.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Logo system and icon set.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_typography_01.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_typography_02.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_layout_system.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Layout system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_color_palette.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Color palette.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_website.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_website_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_instagram_posts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Various digital applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_advertising_bag.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/yousee_various.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for YouSee by In Your Dreams" />
<figcaption>Various analog applications.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/998910880?title=0&#038;byline=0&#038;portrait=0" width="360" height="203" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction video.</figcaption>
</figure>
                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            Both old and new logos are interchangeable and could easily replace each other as the before and after versions, which is not to say they are bad but to say that they are the same solution — sans serif wordmark — in different interpretations and equally acceptable in yielding the most basic of logos so depending on your personal preferences one will be better than the other as, conceptually, both are the same. Personally, I favor the new one as it feels less dated — for now (ask me again in 20 years) — and more techie. The subtle curve on the descender of the “y” is a nice touch and I wonder if something similar could have been done to the “e”s so that the “y” wasn't such an outlier and to create a more customized wordmark.<span></span> If, so far, you are on board with the regular weight Neo Grotesque vibes, then the identity takes you to your final destination with no stops, introducing a customized version of CoType Foundry's popular <a href="https://cotypefoundry.com/our-fonts/aeonik/" target="_blank">Aeonik</a> that now features some curvy gestures like the “y” in the logo, which is a mixed bag of results… it works well in lowercase letters but it gets a little silly in uppercase letters like the “K” and the “G”. Nonetheless, a subtle way of creating a unique look. (Really digging the arrows.) Not seen as much in recent years, the identity uses a neon green as the primary color and it looks pretty cool when paired with the dark olive green, avoiding the more typical radiation combo of neon green and black. The gradients are kind of random but they sure are nice to look at.<span></span> The layout system and few applications shown have that great Neo Nordic sensibility that is hard to resist and I would pay good money for my SIM card to be neon green. Overall, this is a slick and relatively avant garde identity considering it's for an internet, TV, and mobile service company that would be way too weird in — as a point of contrast for the majority of our audience — the American market in contrast to the likes of Verizon and AT&amp;T. For Danes, though, it's just another Tuesday.
</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_yousee_by_in_your_dreams.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_yousee_by_in_your_dreams.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“Jack of Ale Trades”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blackjack_brew_co_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 2012, <a href="https://www.blackjack-beers.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Blackjack Brew Co</a> is a microbrewery in Manchester, UK&#8217;s Northern Quarter near Angel Meadows. This last fact is important as it informs part of the identity and its history is, um, notable too: &#8220;Of all the terrible slums created by the Industrial Revolution,” <a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/books/features/my-forefather-s-life-in-manchester-s-slums-discovering-family-roots-in-the-hell-on-earth-of-angel-meadow-a6896021.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reads this sub headline</a>, “Angel Meadow in Manchester was the worst – a violent Dickensian nightmare ridden with crime and disease that even Friedrich Engels called &#8216;hell on earth&#8217;.&#8221; <a href="https://thealeinkaleigh.wordpress.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/blackjack-brew-tap-2.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Housed in a railway arch</a> and started as a one-man operation, the brewery has slowly grown to a thriving hub and is considered one of the pioneers of Manchester’s brewery tap culture. Recently, Blackjack Brew Co introduced a new identity and packaging designed by local firm, <a href="https://weareensemble.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ensemble</a>.</p>
<span id="more-296978"></span>

<blockquote>A firm favourite amongst the traditional Manchester scene, Blackjack needed a brand that aligned with their strengths, sitting perfectly between the traditional world of CAMRA pubs, with floral pump clips and metal tankards, and the increasingly saturated world of progressive craft beer. It’s the meeting points of this tradition and modernity that we wanted to celebrate BJBC’s visual aesthetic.</blockquote><h3>Ensemble provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_old_identity.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Samples of old identity and packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<blockquote>As a brewery proudly started and housed in a historical but forgotten part of Manchester, Angel Meadow, Blackjack had something that most other breweries of 12 years don’t have — a heritage story, not of their beer, but their neighbourhood.</blockquote><h3>Ensemble provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_logo.png" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.6666666%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_logo_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Logo animation-slash-logo with stuff.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_icon.png" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Icon.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The old logo had a lot going on with a somewhat detailed drawing of a Jack from a deck of cards holding a beer mug, flanked by a spade and some shape to the right that I can not make out. Was it also a pirate, though? Or Don Quixote? Or some other obvious historic character I am too ignorant to recognize? The typography was technically fine but a little on the amateurish side and the color combination was both very un-beer-like and off-putting. The new logo adopts a more bad-ass personality with a striking new wordmark that takes the best traits from <a href="https://www.myfonts.com/products/mt-kino-342464?refby=ucllc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MT Kino</a> — and there aren&#8217;t that many — to create a great piece of custom lettering that feels so much more appropriate for an urban microbrewery housed in a railway arch.</p>

<p>I love the contrast of the thick, straight angled strokes with the subtly curved shorter bits in letters like the “C” and “E” as well as the ever-so-slightly curved crossbar of the “A”s. The “W” might be the only odd character as it feels too heavy in its center area. The mysterious character has been evolved in a much more minimalist style, allowing it to exist in smaller sizes and adopt a secondary role. As cool as it is, I do wish it followed more of the style of the wordmark and be less streamlined and symmetric. Still it pairs really well with the wordmark, filling it that space in between “BREW” and “CO”.</p>

<blockquote>The process began with documenting, recreating and regenerating the found type of the area, from the decorative headstones of the meadow’s burial field and the Victorian stonework of the Ragged school, right through to the street signs and the more recent hand-painted signage of their taproom.<br /><br /> This gave life to a bespoke typeface, inspired by the neighbourhood around the brewery, BlackJack Meadow. A condensed sans serif with all the quirks and nuance of the days of old, crafted to bring texture to the stories of the Jack. Beyond the typeface, stories and tales from the area, both known and unknown, are brought to life across the core range of beers, paired with a new naming system that celebrates the very cobbled streets that Blackjack raised from.</blockquote><h3>Ensemble provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_custom_type_01.png" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_custom_type_02.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Custom typeface.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The custom typeface is fantastic… I really like how it has a hand-drawn quality to it because of the quirkiness of some of the letters but it&#8217;s evenly drawn all around — straight lines are straight and curved strokes are smooth. That “Q” is to die for and the numerals are great. Bonus points for the custom “ABV” glyph built into the font as that will surely get a lot of use and now they can just type it out as easily as a ™ or ®.</p>

<blockquote>With over 42 beers produced annually, the final design solution needed to be built on a bulletproof system, allowing for the quick production of at least 2 new beers per month. To enable this, we created a clean, concise design system that could create diversity across the ranges, whilst allowing us to create new can designs, simply, that would stay within the range but allow enough flexibility for each can to be distinct in its own right.</blockquote><h3>Ensemble provided text</h3>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="padding-bottom: 66.6666666%;"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_labeling_system.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Can labeling system.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_01.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Cans.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Like the old logo, the old packaging was technically fine with proper hierarchy and a well-balanced design but the colors were so odd and the typography was just too generic. The new can labels come in a variety of compositions that offer some flexibility for the large amount of different beers the brewery creates on a consistent basis. The wordmark can be used big, small, or shortened to “BJC” and the icon can be used in different positions to fill in the space as needed. The version where it lives inside the stem of the “B” is pretty cool. With such a great custom typeface I am surprised they introduce a ton of display typefaces for the beer names, as I&#8217;m not sure they add much value to the packaging and end up eclipsing the custom typeface, which ends up being relegated to an informational, supporting role. Color combos are still a little whack but definitely more engaging than before.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_various_02.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_various_03.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_various_04.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_various_05.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_various_06.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_packaging_various_01.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Various packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_various_01.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/blackjack_brew_co_various_02.jpg" alt="New Logo, Identity, and Packaging for Blackjack Brew Co by Ensemble" />
<figcaption>Even more various packaging and other various stuff.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">The applications beyond the can labels take good advantage of the medley of elements to have some fun with the identity, mixing and matching them in different sizes and combinations. The pint glasses are particularly cool and the tote bag with the big “BJC” and big custom type is great (which is what would have been nice to see as well in the labels). Overall, a great evolution with a grittier and more confident persona that feels decidedly more of the place where these beers are being created and enjoyed.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_blackjack_brew_co_by_ensemble.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_blackjack_brew_co_by_ensemble.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Capula Investment Management</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/capula_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Capula Investment Management" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://www.capulaglobal.com/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_capula_investment_management.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_capula_investment_management.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Spotted: New Logo for Samplia</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/samplia_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo for Samplia" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://samplia.com/">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                                                                
                                            <p><strong>About Spotted posts</strong><br />
                                            No further images are included. No opinion is given. Not even a punny title. These are just… spotted. Best available link to learn more about the change (or the company) provided in the link above. If you don’t see “VISIT LINK” above there is no link available. Poll and comments are open.</p>
                                            
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_samplia.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_for_samplia.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Linked: Oh Hiii There</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/nice_hiiibrand_winners_2023.jpg" alt="Oh Hiii There" />
                                
                                
                                
                                    <hr />

                                    <h2><a href="https://hiiibrand.com/winners">Visit Link</a></h2>

                                    <hr />

                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                
                                            <p>Some really nice work to be found among the winners of the 2023 Hiiibrand Awards. A lot of work from Asia that we don&#8217;t normally cover on Brand New (due to language barriers) that includes some pretty cool, out-there stuff.
</p>
                                            
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/oh_hiii_there.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/oh_hiii_there.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Noted: New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“A Drop Shadow of its Former Self”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/kitkat_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
                                
                                
                                
                                        
                                            <p>(Introduced 1935) &#8220;<a href="https://www.hersheyland.com/kit-kat" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kit Kat</a> (stylised as KitKat in various countries) is a chocolate-covered wafer bar confection created by Rowntree&#8217;s of York, England. It is produced globally by Nestlé (which acquired Rowntree&#8217;s in 1988), except in the United States, where it is made under licence by the H. B. Reese Candy Company, a division of the Hershey Company (an agreement Rowntree&#8217;s first made with Hershey in 1970). The standard bars consist of two or four pieces composed of three layers of wafer, separated and covered by an outer layer of chocolate. Each finger can be snapped from the bar separately. There are many flavours of Kit Kat, including milk, white, and dark chocolate.&#8221; (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kit_Kat" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wikipedia</a>)</p>
                                            <p><strong>Design by</strong><br />
                                            <a href="https://www.sterlingbrands.com/" target="_blank">Sterling Brands</a></p>

                                            <p><strong>Related links</strong><br />
                                             N/A
                                            <p><strong>Relevant quote</strong><br /><em>The renewed brand identity celebrates the crispy, creamy taste of Kit Kat, activating the brand with the upbeat, kinetic energy of Kit Kat’s iconic “break”.
</em></p>
                                            <p><strong>Images</strong> (opinion after)</p>

                                            <span id="more-296936"></span>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container" style="background: rgb(212,2,2);"><video autoplay loop muted playsinline controls controlsList="nodownload"><source src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_logo_before_after_animation.mp4" type="video/mp4">Your browser does not support the video tag.</video></div>
<figcaption>Before-to-after logo animation.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_bar.gif" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Logo on bars.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging_before_after.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Packaging, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Packaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging_bar_coding.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Flavor “bar coding”.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging_new_flavor.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging_others.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Some flavor variations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging_hero_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Hero shot.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_packaging_messaging.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Messaging.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/kitkat_instagram_posts.jpg" alt="New Logo and Packaging for Kit Kat by Sterling Brands" />
<figcaption>Instagram posts.</figcaption>
</figure>

                                            <p><strong>Opinion</strong><br />
                                            (Note: This design only applies to Kit Kat in the U.S.). The old logo was pretty good for a mainstream candy bar… it had a solid typographic foundation, some decent shadowing, and it had stayed true to <a href="https://1000logos.net/kit-kat-logo/" target="_blank">its long-standing design</a> of the large “K”s with “it” and “at” nestled within. Like many mainstream consumer goods, it adopted a swoosh at some point, which was the main and only drawback of the old logo as it clashed in style, construction, and shadowing with the type. The new logo sticks to the same winning formula but manages to add some retro flair that makes this new logo look like a resurrection from some old logo in the brand's archives and executed for a new audience. However, that's not the case and this is actually a relatively drastic departure from anything that has come before it.<span></span> The biggest changes being exchanging the double-storey “a” for a single-storey and removing the curl of the “t”, two gestures that have been there forever. The move allows for the letters to be nestled in even tighter and closer, which then allows for the new drop shadow to encase all of the letters without any breaks. The swoosh has also been removed in favor of a simple, tilted, oval stroke in white that matches the thickness of the thinner part of the drop shadow. It now looks more classic than it has in the past. <span></span> The packaging evolution for the core product is not as drastic, simply replacing the old logo for the new one but there is a clever new system for other flavors — and, boy, does Kit Kat like to introduce flavors — that employs four monochromatic bars to hint at the flavor profile (e.g., pinks for pink lemonade and mints for mint). I say it's clever because the four stripes echo the four bars that make up a classic Kit Kat. The supporting graphics for the flavor variations are not the best but you can't win every battle in mainstream packaging. A couple of additional applications hint at other uses of the four stripes and there is some odd combination of typography but given the small sample set, we won't get into it. Overall, it's a solid evolution that maintains everything that is recognizable about the brand and builds on the growing appreciation of nostalgia as it adopts a design reminiscent of simpler, more innocent times.</p>

                                                                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_kit_kat_by_sterling_brands.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_packaging_for_kit_kat_by_sterling_brands.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
                    <item>
                        <title>Reviewed: New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house</title>

                        <description>                            
                        
                            <![CDATA[

                                <h1>“It’s Crunch Time”</h1>
                                
                                                                    <img src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/wp/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/crunchyroll_logo_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
                                
                                
                                
                                                                                
                                        
                                            
                                            <p>Established in 2006, <a href="https://www.crunchyroll.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crunchyroll</a> is an American entertainment company that champions the art and culture of Anime through a subscription video on-demand service, events that bring its community together, theatrical distribution of international titles, and sale of manga titles and collectibles and merchandise. Founded by a group of University of California, Berkeley, graduates, the company was initially a pirate site but slowly acquired titles legally through proper licensing. Going through a couple of owners, it was acquired by Sony Pictures Television in 2020, which had acquired another similar company in 2017 — Funimation, founded by Gen Fukunaga — and merging the two under the Crunchyroll name. Today, Crunchyroll is an independently operated joint venture between U.S.-based Sony Pictures Entertainment and Japan’s Aniplex, a subsidiary of Sony Music Entertainment (Japan) Inc., both subsidiaries of Tokyo-based Sony Group Corporation and, as of last week, its streaming service, which offers offers 50,000 episodes and more than 25,000 hours of anime series, music, and movies, has officially crossed 15 million monthly paying subscribers. At Comic-Con last month, Crunchyroll introduced a new identity designed in-house.</p>

<span id="more-296931"></span>

<blockquote>The new look, feel, and sound of Crunchyroll reflects the joy that anime brings fans worldwide and is focused on an ethos of fun and celebration. Development of the new brand identity package was led by Crunchyroll’s Markus Gerdemann (Senior Vice President, Marketing) and Norman Rabinovich (Vice President, Creative Services), and includes:
<br /><br />
<strong>Logo</strong><br />
The updated logo, featuring a more balanced eye symbol and a revamped wordmark, modernizes the brand and enhances approachability and boldness.
<br /><br />
<strong>Typography</strong><br />
The new font set, Crunchyroll Atyp, blends classic and modern elements, improving readability and supporting diverse characters for Crunchyroll’s global audience.´
<br /><br />
<strong>Color System</strong><br />
Vibrant orange symbolizes passion and energy, complemented by black, white, and taupe for versatility and sophistication, reflecting anime&#8217;s dynamic nature.
<br /><br />
<strong>Glyph System</strong><br />
With over 139 glyphs inspired by anime and manga, the new glyphs add depth and personality, enhancing communication and connection with fans.
<br /><br />
<strong>Mnemonic / Sonic Design</strong><br />
The new seven-second audio-visual mnemonic captures the immersive experience of Crunchyroll, combining anime-inspired sound design with playful and engaging elements, reinforcing the brand&#8217;s joyful and mischievous spirit.
<br /><br />
<strong>Illustration and Patterns</strong><br />
Collaborating with Japanese artists, new textures and patterns reflect anime storytelling&#8217;s depth and complexity, creating an authentic and immersive brand experience.</blockquote><h3>Crunchyroll provided text</h3>
<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_icon_before_after.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Icon, before and after.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_logo.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Logo.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_logo_color_variations.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Color variations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Don&#8217;t quote me on this but based on what I was able to find online, the name of the company refers to, literally, a crunchy roll, an American sushi delicacy and <a href="https://logos.fandom.com/wiki/Crunchyroll" target="_blank" rel="noopener">its original logo</a> was pretty much a graphic depiction of said roll. In 2012, maintaining the overall construction of the original, the icon seems to have shifted to what I interpret to be an eye, which are such a significant element of anime but I really have no idea of that is its intention. In any case, the icon evolution is fine although I am not sure if entirely beneficial as the wider spacing between the crescent shape and the circle inside in the old logo provided a better contrast at small sizes. The wordmark, to me, is an instant improvement simply by moving away from the old spurless sans that had such a wonky rhythm. The bolder, geometric sans serif isn&#8217;t particularly exciting nor evocative of anime in any way. It also makes the long name even longer but, technically, again, it&#8217;s fine.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_typography.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Typography.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_glyphs_01.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_glyphs_02a.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_glyphs_02b.gif" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" style="float:left; width:50%" />
<div class="clear"></div>
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_glyphs_03.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_glyphs_04.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_glyphs_05.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Glyphs.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>To the wordmark&#8217;s credit, I think it&#8217;s easy to see — as you begin to scroll through the project — why it&#8217;s so “generic”, which is not to say it&#8217;s bad but it&#8217;s just not special, allowing the identity elements to be the actual special sauce. In the same vein as the wordmark, the typeface choice for the identity, <a href="https://www.myfonts.com/collections/atyp-font-suitcase-type-foundry?refby=ucllc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Atyp</a>, isn&#8217;t a breakout star but it does provide a neutral and unassuming typographic foundation on which to add the custom glyphs, which are loads of fun and set up a precedent for an endless library of glyphs to be created in years to come, expanding the playfulness of the identity. The simplicity of the typeface allows for the glyphs to stand out but its sturdiness also means the glyphs don&#8217;t eclipse it altogether and its neutrality means that all the glyphs can easily stand in for any of the letters in the messaging.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_manga_01.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_manga_02.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_manga_03.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_manga_04.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_manga_05.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_manga_06.png" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Manga textures and illustrations.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Another great element is the library of single-color, manga-inspired patterns and illustrations that can be used in black on top of the limited color palette of orange and tan, which works beautifully to yield a kind of frugal presence where it would have been easy and tempting to drench this in color but since the content itself is so colorful, establishing this minimal color palette helps establish a strong Crunchyroll brand. Same as the glyphs, these patterns and illustrations can expand over the years to keep the identity fresh and I imagine both could also be used for collaborations with specific titles, blending glyphs and/or images related to an anime property into the Crunchyroll system.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_03.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_04.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_05.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_06.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_07.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_08.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_09.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_advertising_10.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Advertising.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p>The applications are bold and energetic. I&#8217;m not sure if glyphs on top of patterns is too much and both elements compete for attention but the effusiveness of the style is certainly there. One small detail that I&#8217;m really digging is the use of thick borders on just two sides of the layout (like in the third from top advertising image above) or the treatment where there are some comic-strip-like double-lines as if the layouts were zoomed in on multiple panels.</p>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_sticker_01.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<hr />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_sticker_02.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Sticker.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_tshirt.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>T-shirt.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/crunchyroll_pin.jpg" alt="New Logo and Identity for Crunchyroll done In-house" />
<figcaption>Pin.</figcaption>
</figure>

<figure class="full">
<div class="video-container"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xZcTCtyh6RA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<figcaption>Identity introduction video.</figcaption>
</figure>

<p class="end">In motion, the identity gets even more engaging and exciting with subtle infusions of anime style gestures applied to their own elements — I can&#8217;t get enough of anytime a little cloud goes puff and the animated patterns are pretty awesome. Overall, aside from the ho-hum logo evolution, this packs a punch that should help Crunchyroll establish its own brand but have it be clearly linked to manga and anime by speaking the same visual language but with their own spin. I should also acknowledge that I do not know the first thing about anime or manga so all of the above is perhaps some sort of offense to those cultures in its reductiveness so my enthusiasm for it might be due to my general ignorance about it, which is perhaps a positive signal that this identity could also help attract manga and anime beginners.</p>
                                                                                
                                        
                                        
                            ]]>

                                                        
                        </description>

                        <link>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_crunchyroll_done_in_house.php</link>
                        <guid>https://www.underconsideration.com/brandnew/archives/new_logo_and_identity_for_crunchyroll_done_in_house.php</guid>
                        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
                    </item>
                    
            	
        </channel>
    </rss>