<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 21:03:26 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>More Advanced AI Siri Functionality Not Coming to iOS 18 Until 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-advanced-ai-siri-functionality-not-coming-to-ios-18-until-2025.2427773/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 13:29:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning a major AI overhaul for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-30/apple-ios-18-siri-ai-update-will-let-users-control-features-in-apps-with-voice"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> says that the update will let &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; control all individual features in apps for the first time, expanding the range of functions the personal assistant can perform.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do things like open specific documents, move a note from one folder to another, delete an email, summarize an article, email a web link, and open a particular news site in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>. Apple plans to use AI to analyze what people are doing on their devices, automatically enabling &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features.<br/>
<br/>
To make this happen, Apple engineers had to rearchitect &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s underlying software with large language models or LLMs, which is also the technology that's been used for chatbots like ChatGPT. Apple has been working on a deal with OpenAI to integrate OpenAI's ChatGPT technology into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, and it is also in talks with Google about incorporating Gemini, but &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality likely relies on Apple's own LLM work.<br/>
<br/>
At launch, the new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality will be limited to Apple apps, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will only be able to respond to one command at a time. Eventually, Apple wants &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to be able to respond to multiple commands, such as capturing a photo and then sending it to someone in a message.<br/>
<br/>
While the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features will be introduced at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a>, Apple reportedly does not plan to launch them in September when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; sees an initial release. Instead, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be overhauled in a future &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update that's set to be introduced in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Basic AI tasks in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will be processed on device, but more advanced capabilities will rely on Apple's cloud servers. Gurman previously said that Apple would power all of the initial &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; features on-device without relying on cloud technology in order to preserve privacy, but rumors have shifted in recent weeks. Part of Apple's new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; technology will include code for determining whether a request can be processed on device or requires Apple's servers. On-device &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; AI capabilities will largely require an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or later to work, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or later for iPadOS 18 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-cloud-ai-features-privacy-protections/">The Information</a></em>, Apple's AI servers will be powered by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Ultra and M4 chips, with Apple planning to use the Secure Enclave to "to help isolate the data being processed on its servers so that it can't be seen by the wider system or Apple." Gurman says that Apple will also provide customers with an "intelligent report" that explains how information is kept safe.<br/>
<br/>
We'll hear all about the AI functionality coming to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; in just over 10 days. &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; is set to begin on Monday, June 10.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/">More Advanced AI Siri Functionality Not Coming to iOS 18 Until 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-advanced-ai-siri-functionality-not-coming-to-ios-18-until-2025.2427773/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spatial Puzzle Game &#039;Where Cards Fall&#039; Now Available on Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/where-cards-fall-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spatial-puzzle-game-where-cards-fall-now-available-on-apple-vision-pro.2427771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 13:09:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/where-cards-fall-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing to add to its lineup of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> games on the Vision Pro, today adding puzzle game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/where-cards-fall/id1466331487?platform=vision">Where Cards Fall</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/where-cards-fall-apple-arcade.jpg" alt="" width="1286" height="724" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952862" /><br/>
Where Cards Fall has previously been available on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and Mac, and it won an Apple Design Award back in 2020. A dreamlike spatial puzzle game, Where Cards Fall is a coming-of-age story that tasks players with building houses of cards to bring memories to life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the game features full 3D depth and immersion, and players can use tactile, accessible controls designed specifically for the Vision Pro. There are more than 50 puzzles to solve using imagination and strategic thinking.<br/>
<br/>
Where Cards Fall is <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-arcade/">part of Apple Arcade</a>, which is priced at &#36;6.99 per month and is also available with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription bundle. For the monthly price, up to six people that are part of a family group can access games, and there are more than 200 titles available. New subscribers can get a three-month trial with the purchase of an Apple device or a one-month trial.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/where-cards-fall-vision-pro/">Spatial Puzzle Game &#039;Where Cards Fall&#039; Now Available on Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spatial-puzzle-game-where-cards-fall-now-available-on-apple-vision-pro.2427771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares New Ads Promoting Apple Card</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-shares-new-apple-card-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-new-ads-promoting-apple-card.2427761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:40:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-shares-new-apple-card-ads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a trio of short ads designed to promote the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, which is Apple's credit card that continues to be limited to the United States.<br/>
<br/>
The Sock, Sweater, and Ladder spots all highlight different &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; features. Sock focuses on the Daily Cash back reward, Sweater demonstrates the option to see past purchases, and Ladder shows the ease of paying an &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; balance through the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Card Sweater Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ynwBRLN3bms" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Card Sock Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jk_29kXLboc" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Card Ladder Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q04S_NkRHGw" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
All three ads feature the tagline "Reboot your credit card" and link to <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-card/">the Apple Card website</a> so that potential customers can get more information.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; has been available in the U.S. since 2019, and it integrates with the Wallet app for easy purchase management. Daily Cash back, which is delivered same-day, is one of the key features. Customers get one percent cash back from standard physical card purchases, two percent for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> purchases, and three percent cash back at select partner stores and Apple retail locations.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-shares-new-apple-card-ads/">Apple Shares New Ads Promoting Apple Card</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-new-ads-promoting-apple-card.2427761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Available for &#36;714.00 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-available-for-714-00-on-amazon.2427758/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:24:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a low price on three models of the Apple Watch Ultra 2, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;714.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. Right now only Amazon has this sale, and it does not require a coupon in order to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-watch-ultra-2-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939712" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Models on sale at this price include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Green/Grey Trail Loop (S/M)</a>, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FRH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Blue/Black Trail Loop (S/M)</a>, and the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Indigo Alpine Loop (Small)</a>. Stock on the Blue/Black Trail Loop has been dwindling this afternoon, but the other two models appear well stocked as of writing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Although we tracked a steeper discount on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 back in March, that sale was a bit of a fluke and only ever appeared for one model and has never returned. This makes today's discounts at Amazon solid second-best prices on the high-end wearable, and they can be delivered as soon as this weekend for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
There are a few other Apple Watch deals going on right now for anyone interested in cheaper models. You can get the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> and the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Available for &#36;714.00 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-available-for-714-00-on-amazon.2427758/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Brings Tap to Pay on iPhone to Italy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy.2427755/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 09:35:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Italy</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Tap to Pay on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> <a href="https://www.apple.com/it/newsroom/2024/05/apple-introduces-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-italy/">today launched in Italy</a>, allowing individual sellers, major retailers, and small businesses to use the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a contactless payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/tap-to-pay-iphone-italy.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952842" /><br/>
Retailers are able to take advantage of the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to accept credit and debit card payments, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> and other digital payment options. Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; does not require additional hardware and it replaces hardware-based payment systems such as the Square Reader.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is available to payment platforms and payment app developers in Italy. Adyen, myPOS, Nexi, Revolut, Stripe, SumUp, and Viva are all supporting Tap to Pay, and Fabrick, Numia, and Sella will also be adding Tap to Pay integration in the near future. Starting today, Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be used in all Apple retail stores in Italy as well.<br/>
<blockquote>"Tap to Pay on iPhone has revolutionized the checkout experience in many types of businesses in Europe and other countries, and we are happy to partner with payment platforms to support merchants in Italy by offering them a simple, secure and private way to accept contactless payments via iPhone and a partner-enabled iOS app, without the need for additional devices," said Jennifer Bailey, Vice President of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet at Apple. "Over 4.3 million small and medium-sized companies in Italy have long played a key role in the country's economy and, together with payment platforms, developers and developers of apps and payment networks, we are making it easier than ever for Italian businesses of all sizes to accept contactless payments and continue to grow their business."</blockquote><br/>
When a customer makes a purchase, a merchant that supports Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can accept payment by having the customer bring their credit card, debit card, prepaid card, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple Watch, or other digital wallet close to the merchant's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The transaction is completed through NFC, with processing done using the Secure Element for security purposes.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; requires an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS or newer model, and a contactless card or device also needed. Contactless cards from American Express, Global Discover Network, Diners, Mastercard, and Visa will work.<br/>
<br/>
Italy is the 11th country where Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is available. Apple previously rolled out the feature in the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, Australia, Japan, the Netherlands, Brazil, France, Taiwan, and Ukraine.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/italy/">Italy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy/">Apple Brings Tap to Pay on iPhone to Italy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy.2427755/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Satechi Launches Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/satechi-multi-display-docking-station/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station.2427745/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/satechi-multi-display-docking-station/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Satechi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Satechi today announced the launch of its latest Mac accessory, the <a href="https://satechi.net/products/thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station">Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station</a>. The Docking Station uses DisplayLink software technology to allow a Mac to connect to up to four external monitors, plus it offers 96W power delivery and Thunderbolt 4 transfer speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/satechi-thunderbolt-dock.jpg" alt="" width="1579" height="888" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952797" /><br/>
Made from a space gray aluminum that is meant to match Apple devices, the hub supports up to four extended monitors at 4K/60Hz resolution, or one display at 8K/60Hz. With four displays, two can be connected through Thunderbolt 4 and two through HDMI. Satechi says that this feature is designed to address the single display limit of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>, and M3 chips. &zwnj;M1&zwnj;, &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, and M3 MacBook Pro models support up to three displays with Satechi's dock, while the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> supports four when in clamshell mode. Machines with Pro and Max chips support up to four displays through the hub.<br/>
<br/>
The hub provides 96W power delivery to the host machine, which is enough to charge even the 16-inch MacBook Pro. Each of the three Thunderbolt 4 downstream ports also offer 15W for charging iPhones, Apple Watches, and other accessories, with two ports able to be used at one time for charging purposes. The Thunderbolt 4 ports facilitate data transfers at speeds up to 40Gb/s, and there are two USB-A ports that support transfer speeds up to 10Gb/s. a UHS-II SD card reader is available as well, and it is capable of transferring up to 312MB/s.<br/>
<br/>
Satechi says the dock supports daisy-chaining up to six devices, providing 32Gb/s native PCIe support for external GPUs and Thunderbolt-based storage devices.<br/>
<br/>
The Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station can be <a href="https://satechi.net/products/thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station">purchased from the Satechi website</a> for &#36;300.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/satechi/">Satechi</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/satechi-multi-display-docking-station/">Satechi Launches Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station.2427745/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Kicks Off Rare Sale With Up to 25% Off Popular Audio Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-kicks-off-rare-sale-with-up-to-25-off-popular-audio-accessories.2427743/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:02:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos today has begun its <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Father's Day sale</a>, offering steep discounts on select home theater audio equipment. This includes record low prices on the Sonos Arc soundbar (&#36;719), as well as various discounted bundles, all of which are rare deals we haven't tracked since earlier in the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/sonos-deals-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934823" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Sonos. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale has a good balance between individual Sonos products and bundles that should help elevate your home theater setup with various soundbars, subwoofers, and speakers. Highlights of the event include the <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Sonos Arc for &#36;719</a> (&#36;180 off) and <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sonos Sub Gen 3 for &#36;639</a> (&#36;160 off), which are rarely discounted outside of holiday events like this one. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 25% OFF</div>Sonos Home Theater Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've accumulated a few of the devices in the sale below, but be sure to <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">browse this landing page</a> on the Sonos website for everything being discounted.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Speakers and Soundbars</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-sl">Roam SL Portable Speaker</a> - &#36;127, down from &#36;159</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100">Era 100 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;199, down from &#36;249</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/move-2">Move 2 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;336, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-300">Era 300 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;359, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/beam">Beam (Gen 2) Soundbar</a> - &#36;399, down from &#36;499</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sub (Gen 3) Subwoofer</a> - &#36;639, down from &#36;799</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Arc Soundbar</a> - &#36;719, down from &#36;899</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Bundles</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc-mount-set">Arc + Wall Mount Bundle</a> - &#36;798, down from &#36;978</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/multiroom-entertainment-set-arc-and-move-2">Arc + Move 2 Speaker Bundle</a> - &#36;1,055, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/personal-entertainment-set-sonos-ace-arc">Arc + Sonos Ace Headphones Bundle</a> - &#36;1,168, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/3-1-entertainment-set-beam-sub">Beam + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,038, down from &#36;1,298</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/surround-set-arc-era-100-pair">Arc + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,117, down from &#36;1,397</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-arc-sub">Arc + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,358, down from &#36;1,698</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/premium-immersive-set-beam-sub-era-100-pair">Beam + Sub + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,436, down from &#36;1,796</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/">Sonos Kicks Off Rare Sale With Up to 25% Off Popular Audio Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-kicks-off-rare-sale-with-up-to-25-off-popular-audio-accessories.2427743/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Logitech Expands &#039;Designed for Mac&#039; Range With New Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range-with-new-accessories.2427739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Logitech</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Logitech today introduced a new lineup of Mac accessories, including the latest MX series keyboards and mice, as well as an ergonomic keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Wave-Keys-for-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951949" /><br/>
The new range comprises the MX Keys S for Mac, MX Keys S Combo for Mac, MX Anywhere 3S for Mac, MX Keys Mini for Mac in Space Gray, and the Ergo Wave Keys for Mac. The products offer dedicated macOS keyboard layouts and colors that complement Apple hardware. <br/>
<br/>
The MX Keys S for Mac features comfortable, precise typing with smart illumination that adjusts to ambient light and hand proximity. The keyboard also includes Smart Actions via the Logi Options+ app, enabling users to automate repetitive tasks and streamline their workflows. The MX Keys S can connect to three different Apple devices simultaneously, allowing for easy switching with the press of a button. It is available in Space Gray and Pale Gray, and incorporates post-consumer recycled plastic in its construction.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/MX-Keys-S-for-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951948" /><br/>
The MX Keys S Combo for Mac includes the MX Keys S keyboard, MX Master 3S for Mac mouse, and an MX Palm Rest, designed to provide an integrated solution for high-performance Mac users. The mouse features quiet clicks, a high-precision 8K DPI sensor, and the MagSpeed Electromagnetic wheel for fast, precise scrolling. Both the keyboard and mouse come with customizable options via the Logi Options+ app, allowing for personalized shortcuts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/MX-Anywhere-3S-for-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951946" /><br/>
The MX Anywhere 3S for Mac is a compact mouse designed for portability and high performance. It features ultra-fast scrolling, quiet clicks, and an advanced 8K DPI tracking sensor that works on virtually any surface, including glass. The mouse is built to withstand the rigors of mobile work and includes a USB-C quick charging feature, providing up to 70 days of use on a full charge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/MX-Keys-Mini-for-Mac-Space-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951947" /><br/>
The MX Keys Mini for Mac is a minimalist keyboard optimized for Mac users, now available in Space Gray to match Apple devices. It offers smart illumination, precise typing, and software customization that allows users to create app-specific profiles and shortcuts. This keyboard is designed to improve ergonomics by aligning the shoulders and allowing the mouse to be placed closer to the keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
Rounding out the new lineup is the Ergo Wave Keys for Mac, Logitech's first ergonomic keyboard specifically designed for Mac users. It features a unique wave design and a cushioned palm rest, developed by the Logi Ergo Lab to provide day-long comfort. The keyboard is said to promote better posture and reduces strain on the wrists.<br/>
<br/>
Logitech's new Mac accessories will be available globally this month <a href="http://www.logitech.com">via its website</a> and other retailers. The MX Keys S for Mac sells for &#36;109.99, the MX Keys S Combo for Mac costs &#36;199.99, the MX Anywhere 3S for Mac is priced at &#36;79.99, the MX Keys Mini for Mac costs &#36;99.99, and the Wave Keys for Mac costs &#36;59.99.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/logitech/">Logitech</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range/">Logitech Expands &#039;Designed for Mac&#039; Range With New Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range-with-new-accessories.2427739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>More Details About iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Revealed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed.2427731/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:00:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>AppleInsider</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to introduce new AI features including Smart Replies for messages and a generative retouch tool for photos in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, a new report claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Silicon-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-947754" /><br/>
A new article from <em><a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/05/30/ios-18-project-greymatter-will-use-ai-to-summarize-notifications-articles-and-much-more">AppleInsider</a></em> today revealed some further detail about several of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;'s widely anticipated AI features. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is rumored to receive some major upgrades including:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li><strong>Improved Responses</strong>: Significantly updated response generation capabilities with a new smart response framework that takes into account entities such as people, companies, calendar events, locations, dates, and more.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Enhanced Voices</strong>: "More natural" voices with better text-to-speech functionality.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Cross-Device Media Controls</strong>: Use &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on one device to control playback on another, such as via the Apple Watch for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. This feature is not expected to arrive until later in 2024.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Catch Up</strong>: Users can request an overview of their recent notifications via &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
A range of other AI-powered features are also in the works for specific apps in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>Smart Replies</strong>: Allows users to reply to messages and emails with automatically generated text responses.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Transcription and Summarization</strong>: New AI tools for the Notes app allowing users to edit audio in the app, transcribe audio, and summarize text.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Math Notes</strong>: Support for proper mathematical notation in the Notes app with Calculator app integation. Math Notes will allow the Notes app to recognise mathematical equations and come up with solutions and generate graphs.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Keyboard Math Predictions</strong>: Input enhancements for mathematics enabling the completion of complex mathematical expressions when recognised as part of text input, similar to predictive text or inline text completion.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Clean Up</strong>: Remove objects from photos using generative AI. This tool will replace Apple's current "Retouch" feature.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Generative Playground</strong>: Application that uses generative AI to create and edit images with an iMessage app extension. It is currently designed for Apple's internal test environments only, but indicates that there are plans to allow users to generate images and then share them via iMessage. This could be related to rumored plans to allow users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">generate custom emojis</a>.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2 will also apparently gain an improved predictive text model thanks to integration with Apple's Transformer LM, as well as a redesigned Voice Commands UI. Updates to the Calendar and Freeform apps, as well as System Settings for macOS, are also said to be planned. Apple's selection of new AI features are expected to be previewed during the company's WWDC keynote on June 10. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/appleinsider-com/">AppleInsider</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed/">More Details About iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Revealed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed.2427731/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Japanese &#039;My Number Card&#039; Digital IDs Coming to Apple&#039;s Wallet App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/japan-my-number-card-apple-wallet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/japanese-my-number-card-digital-ids-coming-to-apples-wallet-app.2427716/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 20:45:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/japan-my-number-card-apple-wallet/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Japan</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/newsroom/2024/05/apple-announces-first-international-expansion-of-ids-in-apple-wallet-in-japan/">announced</a> that support for national My Number Card IDs in Japan will be coming to Apple's Wallet app "late next spring," marking the first expansion of digital IDs in Apple Wallet beyond the United States [<a href="https://www-apple-com.translate.goog/jp/newsroom/2024/05/apple-announces-first-international-expansion-of-ids-in-apple-wallet-in-japan/?_x_tr_sl=auto&_x_tr_tl=en&_x_tr_hl=en-US">Google translation</a>].<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-wallet-japan.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952805" /><br/>
Over 100 million Japanese residents currently have My Number Card IDs, which enable them to receive services at over 60,000 convenience stores around the country, through online portals, and in other settings such as hospitals and government agencies. <blockquote>"The deployment of Apple Wallet's ID feature outside the United States is an important step in our vision of replacing traditional physical wallets with easy, secure, and private mobile wallets. We will make the My Number Card available in Apple Wallet from the second half of next spring, and we will present your ID while making full use of the security and privacy protection features built into the iPhone. We are very pleased to provide a convenient and convenient way for everyone living in Japan," said Jennifer Bailey, vice president of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet.</blockquote>Once loaded into Apple Wallet, a user's My Number Card can be accessed within the app by authenticating with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, and the ID can then be presented either face-to-face or to a card reader, enabling access to medical services, governmental services, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/30/tim-cook-japan-user-privacy-discussions/">discussed My Number Card integration</a> during one of Cook's trips to Japan back in late 2022. At the time, Cook said Apple had some concerns over user privacy and security around the IDs, but it appears those concerns have been satisfied to a sufficient enough degree that Apple is now on board with supporting the IDs in its centralized Wallet app. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/japan/">Japan</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/japan-my-number-card-apple-wallet/">Japanese &#039;My Number Card&#039; Digital IDs Coming to Apple&#039;s Wallet App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/japanese-my-number-card-digital-ids-coming-to-apples-wallet-app.2427716/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Halide Camera Team Launches Kino Pro Video App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/kino-camera-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halide-camera-team-launches-kino-pro-video-app.2427704/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:52:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/kino-camera-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The developers behind popular photography app Halide <a href="https://www.shotwithkino.com/">today announced the launch of Kino</a>, an app designed for capturing cinematic video. Kino has the tools that professionals need while also providing guidance to amateur videographers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/kino-camera-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952794" /><br/>
Kino offers a one-tap video recording feature with support for a range of color presets. The Instant Grade feature allows users to choose presets created by experts or import their own LUTs. By applying color grading while recording, Kino saves time by removing the need for editing.<br/>
<br/>
An AutoMotion feature helps users capture cinematic movement in a shot by using a 180-degree shutter angle by default. When enough ambient light is available, the Auto label will turn green to indicate that it is an ideal time to capture motion.<br/>
<br/>
While the Kino interface is designed to be simple to use, there are a number of pro tools that can be selected. There are options for adjusting exposure with RV adjustment and AE, and WB lock, or there is a full manual mode for control over shutter speed and ISO.<br/>
<br/>
The app includes quick access tools for adjusting resolution, framerate, encoding, and more, plus there is a level grid, RBG waveform for adjusting exposure, and focus peaking for changing focus. Kino is able to store video recordings in the Files app instead of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app for easier video management.<br/>
<br/>
For those new to video recording, there are a series of lessons that can be used to learn all of the available features that are in Kino.<br/>
<br/>
Kino can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for &#36;9.99, a discount of 50 percent off of the standard price. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> is required. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/kino-pro-video-camera/id6472380172">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/kino-camera-app/">Halide Camera Team Launches Kino Pro Video App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halide-camera-team-launches-kino-pro-video-app.2427704/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumor Recap: Over 20 New Features to Expect as WWDC Nears</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-rumor-recap-ahead-of-wwdc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-recap-over-20-new-features-to-expect-as-wwdc-nears.2427700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:04:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-rumor-recap-ahead-of-wwdc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 is just around the corner, with Apple set to unveil the software update during its WWDC keynote next month. Below, we recap new features and changes rumored for iOS 18, which is projected to be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/ios-18-big-expectations/">"biggest" update in the iPhone's history</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
iOS 18 is rumored to include new AI features for Siri and many apps, and Apple plans to add RCS support to the Messages app for an improved texting experience between iPhones and Android devices. The update is also expected to introduce a more customizable Home Screen and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/">other user interface design changes</a>, new features in apps like Apple Maps and Calculator, additional accessibility features, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
WWDC 2024 will begin with Apple's keynote <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">on June 10 at 10 a.m. Pacific Time</a>, and the iOS 18 beta should be made available to members of the Apple Developer Program immediately following the presentation. A public beta is typically released in July, and the update should be widely released to all users in September.<br/>
<br/>
For additional information, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smarter Siri and Generative AI</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
iOS 18 is rumored to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new AI features</a> for Siri, Spotlight, Shortcuts, Apple Music, Messages, Health, Numbers, Pages, Keynote, and more, according to sources such as <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman and <em>The Information</em>'s Wayne Ma.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO Tim Cook has repeatedly teased that the company is working on generative AI, and plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">share details "later this year,"</a> and Apple's marketing chief Greg Joswiak also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-ios-18-ai-wwdc-2024/">hinted at AI</a> in a social media post about WWDC 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Generative AI surged in popularity in late 2022, when OpenAI released ChatGPT, a chatbot that can respond to questions and other text prompts. The company has also expanded into generative AI tools for images and videos. Other companies like Google and Microsoft have also pushed into the generative AI space, and the technology is quickly evolving.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/ios-18-reportedly-wont-have-apple-chatbot/">not expected to include an Apple-designed chatbot</a>, but a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/apple-finalizing-deal-openai-chatgpt-ios-18/">partnership with OpenAI</a> will reportedly be announced at WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Customizable Home Screen</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPhone-Home-Screen-Gradient-Blank-Spaces-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943087" /><br/>
iOS 18 will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-more-customizable-home-screen-rumor/">"more customizable" Home Screen</a>, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> exclusively reported that iOS 18 will finally allow users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/">place app icons anywhere on the Home Screen grid</a>. This means that users will be able to create blank spaces, columns, and rows between app icons. This basic feature has long been available on Android smartphones, and now Apple is bringing it to the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone users can already customize the Home Screen with apps such as Shortcuts and Widgetsmith, which can be used to create "blank" app icons and widgets, but Apple's official solution will be much more convenient.<br/>
<br/>
It was also reported that iOS 18 will allow users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/ios-18-to-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons/">change the color of app icons</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Accessibility Features</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-18-Hover-Typing-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950842" /><br/>
Earlier this month, Apple previewed many new accessibility features coming later this year with software updates like iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS 15, and visionOS 2. The announcement came one day ahead of Global Accessibility Awareness Day.<br/>
<br/>
Some of the new features coming to the iPhone <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-18-accessibility-features/">include Eye Tracking</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/apple-reduce-motion-sickness-feature/">Vehicle Motion Cues</a>, Music Haptics, and Vocal Shortcuts. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-18-accessibility-features-for-carplay/">CarPlay will also be getting more accessibility features</a> with iOS 18, including Sound Recognition, which will allow drivers or passengers who are deaf or hard of hearing to turn on alerts to be notified of car horns and sirens.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Apple Maps Features</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/apple-maps-3d-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="896" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-841030" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> previously revealed two potential new Apple Maps features coming with iOS 18: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/">custom routes</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/27/ios-18-topographic-maps/">topographic maps</a>.<br/>
<br/>
With the custom routes feature, Apple Maps users would be able to choose specific roads to travel on while navigating, for reasons such as familiarity or scenic views. This feature is expected to be available in the U.S. only at launch. Google Maps already allows users to create custom routes on the web, and then view them on an iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
Topographic maps first debuted on the Apple Watch last year with watchOS 10, and code suggests that the feature will be expanded to the iPhone, Mac, and Vision Pro with iOS 18, macOS 15, and visionOS 2. These maps include details such as trails, contour lines, elevation, and points of interest for hiking and other outdoor uses.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>RCS Support in Messages App</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
In November, Apple announced that it would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">support the cross-platform messaging standard RCS</a> in the Messages app on the iPhone starting "later" in 2024, so it will likely be an iOS 18 feature based on that timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
RCS support should result in the following improvements to the default messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices:<ul><br/>
 <li>Higher-resolution photos and videos</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages</li><br/>
 <li>Typing indicators</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts</li><br/>
 <li>Wi-Fi messaging</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats, including the ability for iPhone users to leave a conversation that includes Android users</li></li><br/>
</ul>These features are already available for iMessage and in many third-party messaging apps, such as WhatsApp and Telegram. RCS support on the iPhone will extend the features to green bubbles in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Rumors Per App</h2><br/>
<ul><li><strong>Apple Music:</strong> With iOS 18, Apple Music will reportedly be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">auto-generate playlists</a>, and there is also a rumor about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-apple-music-song-transitions/">smarter song transitions</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Calculator:</strong> iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS 15 are rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macos-15-revamped-calculator-app/">revamped Calculator app with several new features</a>, including a sidebar that lists recent calculations, an improved interface for converting units, integration with the Notes app, and more. That means the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">Calculator app will finally be available on iPads</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Calendar:</strong> Two apps rumored to be integrated on iOS 18 are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/ios-18-calendar-reminders-integration-rumor/">Calendar and Reminders</a>. This would allow users to schedule and organize reminders directly within the Calendars app, without needing to open the Reminders app.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Freeform:</strong> iOS 18 is rumored to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/ios-18-macos-15-freeform-app-scenes/">add a new "Scenes" option to Apple's drawing app Freeform</a>. This feature would allow users to select specific sections ("scenes") on the canvas for easier navigation.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Health:</strong> Apple is reportedly planning new AI-powered features <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-15/apple-s-ai-plans-github-copilot-rival-for-developers-tool-for-testing-apps">for its Health app</a>, but no specific details are known yet.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Keynote, Numbers, and Pages:</strong> Alongside iOS 18, Apple reportedly plans to update its iWork suite of productivity apps with new generative AI features for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">auto-generating slides in Keynote, writing faster in Pages, and more</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mail, Photos, and Fitness:</strong> These apps will reportedly be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ios-18-notes-mail-photos-fitness-rumors/">"overhauled" with iOS 18</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">AI-powered photo retouching</a> is reportedly coming to the Photos app with iOS 18, and the Mail app could gain <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">suggested replies to emails</a>, but no other specific details are known yet for these apps.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Messages:</strong> In addition to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support</a>, it has been rumored that the Messages app will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">use generative AI to auto-complete sentences</a> more effectively, and to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">auto-generate custom emojis</a> for users based on the content of messages.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Notes and Voice Memos:</strong> With iOS 18, the Notes app is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">be able to display mathematical notation</a>, allowing users to include more types of algebraic equations and formulas in notes. The app is also rumored to gain a built-in audio recording tool, eliminating the need to switch over to the Voice Memos app. In addition, both Notes and Voice Memos could gain the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/ios-18-audio-transcriptions-rumor/">transcribe audio</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Safari:</strong> iOS 18 is likely to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-18-safari-browsing-assistant-rumor/">add a browsing assistant to Safari</a>, which could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/safari-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">summarize web pages and more</a>. A new "Web Eraser" feature that would allow users to remove certain elements from web pages has also been rumored.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Shortcuts:</strong> With iOS 18, users will reportedly be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">automate complex tasks more easily</a> with the Shortcuts app.</li></ul>While they are not dedicated apps, it has also been rumored that generative AI technology will allow the iPhone's virtual assistant Siri and built-in search tool Spotlight to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">respond to more complex questions and search queries</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-rumor-recap-ahead-of-wwdc/">iOS 18 Rumor Recap: Over 20 New Features to Expect as WWDC Nears</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-recap-over-20-new-features-to-expect-as-wwdc-nears.2427700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV App Likely Coming to Android Smartphones, Job Listing Shows</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-tv-app-for-android-job-listing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-app-likely-coming-to-android-smartphones-job-listing-shows.2427695/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:02:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-tv-app-for-android-job-listing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's TV app could be available on Android smartphones and tablets in the future, according to a <a href="https://jobs.apple.com/en-us/details/200551832/android-software-engineer-apple-tv-app">job listing</a> spotted by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-29/apple-signals-that-it-s-working-on-tv-app-for-android-phones"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-TV-Plus-Black-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952746" /><br/>
Apple is seeking a senior Android software engineer to join the Apple TV app team. The engineer would be tasked with leading the development of "an application used by millions to watch and discover tv and sports," which heavily suggests that Apple plans to make its TV app available on Android smartphones and tablets.<br/>
<br/>
With the Apple TV app, Android smartphone and tablet users would have a more convenient way to access the Apple TV+ streaming service, instead of having to rely on tv.apple.com on the web. The app also provides access to MLS Season Pass, includes a storefront for purchasing or renting movies and TV shows, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already offers the TV app on Android TV devices, including the Chromecast with Google TV, but not on the main Android platform. Apple only offers a <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/developer?id=Apple&hl=en_US">handful of apps</a> on Android phones, such as Apple Music, Move to iOS, and a Beats app.<br/>
<br/>
Android would join a long list of platforms where Apple's TV app is available, including the iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple TV, Apple Vision Pro, PS4, PS5, Xbox One, Xbox Series S, Xbox Series X, Roku and Amazon Fire TV streaming sticks, select smart TVs, and more. It is unclear when the app will be made available to the public, or if development has started.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-tv-app-for-android-job-listing/">Apple TV App Likely Coming to Android Smartphones, Job Listing Shows</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-app-likely-coming-to-android-smartphones-job-listing-shows.2427695/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;80 Off the M2 iPad Air With Amazon&#039;s New Discounts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/80-off-the-m2-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-80-off-the-m2-ipad-air-with-amazons-new-discounts.2427682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:57:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/80-off-the-m2-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's M2 iPad Air models are less than a month old, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5VFYQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon has up to &#36;80 off select models</a> this week. We're tracking deals across the entire Wi-Fi M2 iPad Air lineup, although the steepest discounts will be found on 13-inch models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m2-iPad-Air-Horizontal-Feature-Blue-and-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950735" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The cheapest model is the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5VFYQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;569.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.00. You'll also find deals on the 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB models below, all of which are in stock on Amazon with delivery dates as soon as the end of the week for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5VFYQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;569.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5D33G%2Fref%3Dtwister_B0D3KGR4NB%3F_encoding%3DUTF8%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;659.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6MNSG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (512GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;879.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6VB4J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;65 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (1TB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,034.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch M2 iPad Air models start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5XNCT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;754.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;799.00. Similar to the 11-inch devices, all Wi-Fi models are on sale this week, and for the larger display iPad Airs these discounts reach up to &#36;80 off original prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5XNCT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;45 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;754.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8W54H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7YQC1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;65 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (512GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,034.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J75PYR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (1TB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The iPad Air is Apple's middle-tier iPad model, equipped with an LCD Liquid Retina display, True Tone support, four unique color options, Touch ID, relocated front-facing camera, and two new size options with the 11-inch and 13-inch sizes.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/80-off-the-m2-ipad-air/">Get Up to &#36;80 Off the M2 iPad Air With Amazon&#039;s New Discounts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-80-off-the-m2-ipad-air-with-amazons-new-discounts.2427682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares WWDC 2024 Playlist With One Hour of &#039;Summer Sounds&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-shares-wwdc-2024-playlist/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-wwdc-2024-playlist-with-one-hour-of-summer-sounds.2427680/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:44:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-shares-wwdc-2024-playlist/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Excited for WWDC 2024? Get in the mood with the <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/wwdc24-hello/pl.6448801469e1477b8de649daa3def4b3">official Apple Music playlist</a> for the event, which features 20 songs from a variety of artists, including Billie Eilish, Sabrina Carpenter, Tommy Richman, Dominic Fike, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/wwdc-2024-main-image-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944281" /><br/>
"Check out this playlist of summer sounds to get ready for the biggest Apple developer event of the year," said Apple, in a <a href="https://x.com/AppleMusic/status/1795832553611678201">social media post</a> today.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; fullscreen *; clipboard-write" frameborder="0" height="450" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;border-radius:10px;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.music.apple.com/us/playlist/wwdc24-hello/pl.6448801469e1477b8de649daa3def4b3"></iframe></div><br/>
WWDC 2024 kicks off with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">Apple's keynote on June 10</a> at 10 a.m. Pacific Time, with the company expected to outline its AI strategy following the rise of services like ChatGPT. Apple will preview its latest software updates during the keynote, including iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS 15, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, visionOS 2, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shared the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">full schedule for WWDC 2024</a> this week, and the Apple Developer app should be updated for the event soon. In addition to being posted on Apple's website, WWDC sessions <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-developer-youtube-account-wwdc-2024/">will be available on YouTube</a> going forward.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-shares-wwdc-2024-playlist/">Apple Shares WWDC 2024 Playlist With One Hour of &#039;Summer Sounds&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-wwdc-2024-playlist-with-one-hour-of-summer-sounds.2427680/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Worlds Made on iPad: Apple&#039;s Latest Ad Showcases Animating With Apple Pencil Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-pencil-pro-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/worlds-made-on-ipad-apples-latest-ad-showcases-animating-with-apple-pencil-pro.2427678/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:31:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-pencil-pro-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a new ad called "<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aoimKc1CGh4">Worlds Made on iPad</a>" on its YouTube channel. The video features green-screen footage from actress Sofia Wylie overlaid on three different animated backdrops, which Apple says were created by illustrators using the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-announces-new-ipad-pro/">new iPad Pro with the M4 chip</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-pencil-pro-announced/">Apple Pencil Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aoimKc1CGh4?si=4GKvmlNY4WvKpYD4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
"One piece of green screen footage interpreted by different animators using iPad Pro powered by the M4 chip, and the new Apple Pencil Pro," says Apple's video description. The ad is set to the song "Concentrate" by Billy Lemos (featuring Dua Saleh).<br/>
<br/>
Apple also shared a behind-the-scenes YouTube Short:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/21Ci7d5ZZAk?si=KbWyZVUbgHrpRML5" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The new iPad Pro, iPad Air, and Apple Pencil Pro launched on May 15.<br/>
<br/>
Key new features of the Apple Pencil Pro include the ability to squeeze the accessory to bring up a tool palette, a gyroscope that allows users to roll the Apple Pencil Pro for precise control of shaped pen and brush tools, haptic feedback for certain actions, and the ability to find the Apple Pencil Pro in the Find My app if it is misplaced.<br/>
<br/>
Priced at &#36;129, the Apple Pencil Pro is only compatible with the new iPad Pro and iPad Air models.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-pencil-pro-ad/">Worlds Made on iPad: Apple&#039;s Latest Ad Showcases Animating With Apple Pencil Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/worlds-made-on-ipad-apples-latest-ad-showcases-animating-with-apple-pencil-pro.2427678/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18&#039;s Cloud-Based AI Features Will Have Strong Privacy Protections, Report Says</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-cloud-ai-features-privacy-protections/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-cloud-based-ai-features-will-have-strong-privacy-protections-report-says.2427670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 09:04:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-cloud-ai-features-privacy-protections/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 is widely expected to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/">new generative AI features</a> for the iPhone, with a mix of on-device and cloud-based processing, and a new report has outlined Apple's alleged privacy measures for the cloud-based features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
Apple's AI servers will supposedly be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/apple-building-m2-ultra-and-m4-servers/">powered by a combination of M2 Ultra and M4 chips</a> that it uses in Macs and iPads. According to <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apples-plan-to-protect-privacy-with-ai-putting-cloud-data-in-a-black-box"><em>The Information</em>'s Wayne Ma</a>, Apple plans to utilize the Secure Enclave in its chips "to help isolate the data being processed on its servers so that it can't be seen by the wider system or Apple." Technical details about the Secure Enclave are outlined <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/security/sec59b0b31ff/web">in Apple's Platform Security Guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The report said this "confidential-computing approach" will have strong privacy protections:<blockquote>With the confidential-computing approach, Apple will be able to handle processing of AI-related data in the cloud while making it extremely difficult for hackers to gain access to the data even in the event of a data breach. It would also reduce Apple's burden of having to hand over personal data from its servers in the event of a government or law enforcement request.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The report added that Apple has a longer-term goal of offloading the processing power of future wearable devices to servers powered by Apple silicon chips. This move could allow Apple to design a thinner and lighter Vision Pro headset, or future Apple Glasses.<br/>
<br/>
More details can be found in the full report <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apples-plan-to-protect-privacy-with-ai-putting-cloud-data-in-a-black-box">on <em>The Information</em>'s website</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-cloud-ai-features-privacy-protections/">iOS 18&#039;s Cloud-Based AI Features Will Have Strong Privacy Protections, Report Says</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-cloud-based-ai-features-will-have-strong-privacy-protections-report-says.2427670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pushes Back Against India&#039;s New Digital Market Regulations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-pushes-back-against-india-regulations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pushes-back-against-indias-new-digital-market-regulations.2427664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 08:22:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-pushes-back-against-india-regulations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>India</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple, Google, and Amazon are urging India to reconsider its proposed Digital Competition Bill, citing concerns over increased user costs and potential reductions in investment (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-amazon-apple-lobby-group-opposes-indias-eu-like-antitrust-proposal-2024-05-28/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/apple-india.jpg" alt="" width="2304" height="1296" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-756076" /><br/>
A U.S. lobby group representing major technology companies has asked the Indian government to rethink the proposed legislation that closely mirrors the European Union's Digital Markets Act. The request was made in a letter sent by the U.S.-India Business Council (USIBC), a part of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce, to India's Corporate Affairs Ministry. The proposed Digital Competition Bill aims to regulate the market power of large digital firms with global revenues exceeding &#36;30 billion and at least 10 million local users.<br/>
<br/>
The Digital Competition Bill seeks to introduce measures to prevent companies from exploiting non-public user data and from giving preferential treatment to their own services over those of rivals. The bill would also remove restrictions on sideloading apps. <br/>
<br/>
The USIBC has raised concerns that these regulations could lead to significant repercussions for targeted companies like Apple. According to the council, the draft Indian law is "much further in scope" than the EU's regulations, potentially resulting in reduced investment in India, higher prices for digital services, and a decreased range of services available to consumers.<br/>
<br/>
The Indian government argues that the new law is necessary to address the growing market power of a few large digital companies that "wield immense control over the market." The proposed legislation includes provisions for penalties of up to 10 percent of a company's annual global turnover for violations.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/india/">India</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/apple-pushes-back-against-india-regulations/">Apple Pushes Back Against India&#039;s New Digital Market Regulations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pushes-back-against-indias-new-digital-market-regulations.2427664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV: The Latest Rumors About a New Model and Possible &#36;99 Price</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/latest-apple-tv-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-the-latest-rumors-about-a-new-model-and-possible-99-price.2427662/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 08:06:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/latest-apple-tv-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It has been over a year and a half since the current Apple TV was released, so you may be wondering when a new model will be released. Below, we recap rumors about the next-generation Apple TV, including new features and lower pricing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-tv-4k-yellow-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870258" /><br/>
The current Apple TV 4K was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/apple-announces-apple-tv-with-a15-and-hdr10-for-129/">introduced in October 2022</a>. Key new features compared to the previous model from 2021 include a faster A15 Bionic chip, a larger 128GB storage option, a slightly thinner and lighter design, HDR10+ support, a USB-C port on the Siri Remote, a lower &#36;129 starting price vs. &#36;179, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/19/10-new-features-of-2022-apple-tv/">more</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In January 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reported that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">new Apple TV was on track for release in the first half of 2024</a>:<blockquote>Beyond the future smart displays and new speaker, Apple is working on revamping its TV box. A new version with the current design is in the works for the first half of next year with a faster processor, the people said.</blockquote>With only one month remaining in the first half of 2024, it is unclear if this timeframe remains accurate. A new Apple TV could be unveiled at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>, but no hardware announcements have been firmly rumored for the event.<br/>
<br/>
Here is when the previous five Apple TV models were announced:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>Second-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> April 2021</li><br/>
<li><strong>First-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> September 2017</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple TV HD:</strong> September 2015</li><br/>
<li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV:</strong> March 2012</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Regardless of when it is unveiled, the next Apple TV is rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">faster processor</a> than the current A15 Bionic chip, and even lower pricing. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo suggested that the next Apple TV <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">could have a sub-&#36;100 starting price</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Both the second-generation (2010) and third-generation (2012) versions of the Apple TV were priced at &#36;99 in the U.S. at launch, and Apple eventually lowered the price of the third-generation model to &#36;69, so there is precedent for a sub-&#36;100 Apple TV that would better compete with low-priced streaming devices sold by Google, Amazon, and Roku.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes have been rumored for the next Apple TV specifically, but Gurman said Apple has considered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/apple-tv-with-camera-again-rumored/">adding a built-in camera</a> to a future model. tvOS 17 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-iphone-facetime-camera-apple-tv/">added a FaceTime app to the Apple TV</a>, allowing for users to have video calls by using the rear camera on a connected iPhone or iPad. If the Apple TV gained a built-in camera, users would no longer need to rely on an external device for video calls on the TV.<br/>
<br/>
Should the WWDC keynote pass without any new Apple TV announcement, then there will no longer be any active rumor for when the next model might launch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/latest-apple-tv-rumors/">Apple TV: The Latest Rumors About a New Model and Possible &#36;99 Price</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-the-latest-rumors-about-a-new-model-and-possible-99-price.2427662/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From CarPlay on iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/what-to-expect-from-carplay-on-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-carplay-on-ios-18.2427659/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/what-to-expect-from-carplay-on-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will be unveiled at Apple's annual developers conference WWDC in less than two weeks, and the update will include some new features for CarPlay.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-CarPlay-Dash.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934995" /><br/>
Below, we recap new accessibility features that Apple recently previewed for CarPlay, and discuss the current status of the promised next-generation CarPlay.<br/>
<br/>
The first beta of iOS 18 will likely be made available to members of the Apple Developer Program immediately following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>, and a public beta is usually released in July, which will allow iPhone users to test out the new CarPlay features. As usual, the update should be widely released in September.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Accessibility Features</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/CarPlay-Sound-Recognition.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="718" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950848" /><em>Sound Recognition is coming to CarPlay</em></div><br/>
In a press release earlier this month, Apple highlighted <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-18-accessibility-features-for-carplay/">three new accessibility features</a> coming to CarPlay as part of iOS 18:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Voice Control:</strong> This feature will allow users to navigate CarPlay and control apps with just their voice.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Color Filters:</strong> This feature will make the CarPlay interface visually easier to use for individuals with color blindness.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Sound Recognition:</strong> This feature will enable drivers or passengers who are deaf or hard of hearing to receive notifications on CarPlay for driving-related sounds, such as car horns and sirens.</li></ul>All three of these features are already available on the iPhone and iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Next-Generation CarPlay</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><em>Porsche's next-generation CarPlay preview</em></div><br/>
It has been nearly two years since Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/06/apple-announces-multi-display-carplay/">first previewed next-generation CarPlay</a> at WWDC 2022, and it has still yet to become available in any vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/carplay/">Apple's website says</a> the first vehicle models with next-generation CarPlay will "arrive in 2024," but nothing has materialized yet. Aston Martin and Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed next-generation CarPlay designs</a> in December, but Aston Martin has been silent ever since and Porsche continues to <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/5/28/24166210/porsche-911-carrera-gts-hybrid-apple-carplay">release vehicles without next-generation CarPlay</a>. In addition, Mercedes-Benz has seemingly <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/4/29/24144356/mercedes-benz-ceo-apple-carplay-next-gen-decoder">reversed course on adopting next-generation CarPlay</a>, despite being on Apple's list of committed automakers shown at WWDC 2022.<br/>
<br/>
At this point, it is looking like next-generation CarPlay will debut with iOS 18, but it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">could be compatible with some iOS 17 versions</a> too.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said next-generation CarPlay will have deeper integration with a vehicle's instrument cluster, climate controls, FM radio, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/what-to-expect-from-carplay-on-ios-18/">What to Expect From CarPlay on iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-carplay-on-ios-18.2427659/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
