<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 21:03:00 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>2024 Apple TV: All the Rumors So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2024-apple-tv-all-the-rumors-so-far.2407485/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:19:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv&#038;post_date=1697242772/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2024 Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on a new version of the 4K <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and rumors suggest that it could launch as soon as 2024, two years after the launch of the current model. This guide includes details on everything that we expect to see in the 2024 &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-tv-4k-design-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796083" /><br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple has not notably changed the design of the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; in several years, and that's not going to change in 2024. We are not expecting any updates to the form factor, and it will continue to use the same slimmed-down black plastic body from the current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869858" /><br/>
<h2 id="a_new_chip">A New Chip</h2><br/>
The current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K has the same A15 Bionic chip that was in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> lineup, and we're expecting a new A-series chip for the 2024 &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;. Apple doesn't design chips exclusively for the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, so it's likely that the next-generation model will use the same A16 chip from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
There is also the possibility that the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K will have the A17 Pro chip used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, as that would give the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; the capability to play console-quality games, a rumor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/22/2021-apple-tv-rumors/">from years back</a>. The A17 Pro is Apple's first 3-nanometer chip, and it includes a 6-core GPU that's able to support hardware-accelerated ray tracing for the first time, enabling games with more realistic graphics. Several console games like Resident Evil 4 and Death Stranding will be coming to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; thanks to the A17 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
At the same time, it is worth noting that the A17 Pro chip may ultimately be too expensive for Apple to include in an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, especially as there are rumors that Apple is aiming for a lower price point.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="wi-fi_6e_or_wi-fi_7">Wi-Fi 6E or Wi-Fi 7</h2><br/>
It could make sense for Apple to bring new, more modern Wi-Fi protocols to the next-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, but we haven't heard rumors about this. The current &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models support Wi-Fi 6E and rumors suggest Apple will adopt Wi-Fi 7 for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as soon as next year.<br/>
<br/>
Current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K models support Wi-Fi 6, but upping that with at least Wi-Fi 6E would allow the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; to take advantage of the faster 6GHz band for improved streaming and content download speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_connectivity">Other Connectivity</h2><br/>
Apple offers both a Wi-Fi only &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K and a Wi-Fi + Ethernet model, and that could continue with the next-generation model. We could also see the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; adopt Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; is expected to continue to offer Thread integration and support for Matter when used as a home hub for smart home products.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="pricing">Pricing</h2><br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said last year that he expects the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; to be more affordable, and that a price under &#36;100 would be the "sweet spot." Pricing on the current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K starts at &#36;129 for 64GB storage and Wi-Fi only connectivity, so it is not hard to imagine that Apple could introduce a new model at a lower price point or, alternatively, keep the current model as a lower-cost option alongside a new model with updated capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
Apple is said to be planning to release the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; in the first half of 2024, which would perhaps see it debut at a spring event somewhere around March or April. In the past, Apple has introduced &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K models in September 2017, May 2021, and November 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="future_apple_tv_innovations">Future Apple TV Innovations</h2><br/>
Apple is rumored to be working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/18/apple-work-on-apple-tv-homepod-continues/">some sort of product</a> that would combine the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; functionality, a smart speaker, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> camera in one device, but it's been over a year since we last heard about it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/AppleTV-and-HomePod-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793543" /><br/>
There are also rumors of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-smart-home-display/">Apple smart home display</a> that would serve as a central hub for controlling smart home products, and there is a possibility that it could have &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; functionality. This product could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-smart-home-ipad-display/">launch as soon as 2024</a>, but it is distinct from the next-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K that is also in development.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="guide_feedback">Guide Feedback</h2><br/>
Have questions about the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K or want to offer feedback on this guide? <a href="mailto:guides@macrumors.com">Send us an email here</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv/">2024 Apple TV: All the Rumors So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2024-apple-tv-all-the-rumors-so-far.2407485/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 to Launch by October 24</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-to-launch-by-october-24.2407467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:30:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming iOS 17.1 update is set to be released to the public by October 24, according to <a href="https://www.anfr.fr/liste-actualites/actualite/iphone-12-informations-sur-la-mise-a-jour-preparee-par-apple">the French regulatory group ANFR</a> (via <em><a href="https://iphonesoft.fr/2023/10/13/anfr-revele-date-sortie-maximale-ios-17-1-iphone-12-das-eleve">iPhoneSoft</a></em>). The release date was shared on the ANFR's website in an update outlining Apple's plan to address radiation levels in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912333" /><br/>
"Apple has committed to deploy an update in France," reads a translation of the update, which is in French. "This fix will be available to all users no later than October 24."<br/>
<br/>
Apple earlier this week confirmed that iOS 17.1 will include a tweak that will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-iphone-12-radiation-fix/">lower iPhone 12 radiation levels</a>. Back in September, France ordered Apple to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/france-orders-end-to-iphone-12-sales-radiation/">stop selling the iPhone 12</a> and "fix" devices to bring them into compliance with European electromagnetic radiation standards. The order came after the ANFR found that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12's Specific Absorption Rate (SAR) came in at 5.74 watts per kilogram, above the limit set by the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the ANFR made an error in its radiation tests, using a testing protocol that did not account for the off-body detection mechanism in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. iPhones have a built-in feature that allows them to increase their transmit power when not held on the body for optimized cellular performance.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the off-body detection has been "thoroughly tested and verified internationally to be an effective mechanism to comply with SAR requirements," bur nevertheless, the company has agreed to disable this feature on iPhones in France.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 is safe to use "and always has been." After the iOS 17.1 update, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models in France will no longer increase their transmit power when the off-body state is detected, so coverage in areas where cellular signal is low may cause lower cellular performance in some use cases.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 17.1 update brings a number of other changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system, including an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> favorites system, support for AirDrop over the internet, new options to see bank and card balances in the Wallet app, changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Action Button and more, with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-1-beta-features/">full list available in our iOS 17.1 features guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/">iOS 17.1 to Launch by October 24</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-to-launch-by-october-24.2407467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iMac With M2 and M2 Pro Chips Could Arrive Soon, Says Latest Conflicting Rumor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imac-with-m2-and-m2-pro-chips-could-arrive-soon-says-latest-conflicting-rumor.2407466/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:21:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>Mac Otakara</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The next-generation 24-inch iMac will likely be available with M2 and M2 Pro chip options, Thunderbolt 4 ports, Wi-Fi 6E support, and Bluetooth 5.3 support, according to a report today from <a href="https://www.macotakara.jp/macintosh/entry-45460.html">Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Hello-Tim-Cook-iMac.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-885129" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has repeatedly claimed that the next 24-inch iMac <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/05/new-imac-advanced-development/">will be equipped with the M3 chip</a>, so it's unclear if the information reported today is accurate. It is possible that Apple's plans have changed, but no other sources have indicated that the iMac will be updated with M2 and M2 Pro chips as of yet.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Mac Otakara</em> notes that some custom 24-inch iMac configurations are facing up to one-month shipping delays on Apple's online store in the U.S., but this has been the case for a while now, and there is no guarantee that an iMac refresh is imminent.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/kuo-first-m3-macbooks-unlikely-2023/">unlikely that Apple would release any new MacBooks with the M3 chip this year</a>, but a new iMac has not been ruled out this year. Apple is not expected to hold an event this October, so if there were to be a new iMac this month, it would likely be announced in a press release on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, rumors about which chip the new iMac will have and when the computer will be released remain in a state of flux. The only certain thing is that October continues to roll along without any product announcements from Apple so far.<br/>
<br/>
The current 24-inch iMac with the M1 chip was released in May 2021.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/">iMac With M2 and M2 Pro Chips Could Arrive Soon, Says Latest Conflicting Rumor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imac-with-m2-and-m2-pro-chips-could-arrive-soon-says-latest-conflicting-rumor.2407466/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 14-Inch MacBook Pro and Accessories From Plugable</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-14-inch-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-14-inch-macbook-pro-and-accessories-from-plugable.2407464/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:00:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-14-inch-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		<category>Plugable</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://plugable.com/">Plugable</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 14-inch MacBook Pro and several accessories to go along with it, including the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/tbt4-udx1">Plugable Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station</a>, the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ams-5in1e">MagSafe-Compatible Plugable USB-C 5-in-1 Hub</a>, and the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ps-epr-140c1">Plugable 140W USB-C GaN Power Adapter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-docking-station-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916860" /><br/>
Plugable is a well-established company that is best known for its docking stations, but it makes all kinds of adapters, cables, hubs, chargers, and SSDs for Macs, PCs, and other devices. Just this month, Plugable released the aforementioned Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station as its latest dock product, and it has all of the latest technologies that you want for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://plugable.com/products/tbt4-udx1">Available for &#36;289.95</a>, the Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station is equipped with a total of 11 ports, including two Thunderbolt 4 ports, 4 10Gb/s USB-A ports (one of which can be used for charging accessories), an SD card slot, audio in/out, an HDMI 2.0 port, and a 2.5GB/s Ethernet port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-docking-station-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916859" /><br/>
There's also a Thunderbolt 4 host port that provides 96W charging, which is enough power even for Apple's 16-inch MacBook Pro. Dual 4K 60Hz displays are supported, or a single 8K 30Hz display (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>/<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro/Max chips). The Thunderbolt ports can be used to charge accessories like iPhones and iPads at 15W with power distribution, so if you have two devices charging at 15W, your Mac will get 66W.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-docking-station-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916861" /><br/>
If you just need a few extra ports at an affordable price, the &#36;33 <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ams-5in1e">USB-C 5-in-1 Hub Designed for MagSafe</a> delivers. You'll need two USB-C ports to plug in this accessory, but it a cutout for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> port lets you continue to charge with the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; port on Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; MacBook Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-hub-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916862" /><br/>
The 5-in-1 Hub adds two 5Gb/s USB-A ports, a 40Gb/s USB-C port with up to 100W pass-through charging, a combination audio port, and a Gigabit Ethernet port. Up to a 6K 60Hz display is supported.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-hub-2.jpg" alt="" width="3013" height="1695" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916864" /><br/>
For charging Apple devices like the MacBook Pro, Plugable has the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ps-epr-140c1">&#36;50 140W USB-C GaN Power Adapter</a>, which has the right output to fast charge all Apple devices up to the 16-inch MacBook Pro (note that you'll need Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Cable for the 16-inch model). Because it's using GaN technology and a flip-out plug, this is a compact charger that's ideal for travel, and it's smaller than the power adapter that comes with the 16-inch MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-power-adapter.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916865" /><br/>
We have one amazing Plugable prize pack to give away to a <em>MacRumors</em> reader. It includes a 14-inch &zwnj;M2&zwnj; MacBook Pro with 16GB RAM and 512GB storage, the Plugable Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station, the 5-in-1 USB-C Hub, and the 140W USB-C GaN Power Adapter. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/FtpQE/plugable-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Plugable Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (October 13) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on October 20. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after October 20 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/plugable/">Plugable</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-14-inch-macbook-pro/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 14-Inch MacBook Pro and Accessories From Plugable</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-14-inch-macbook-pro-and-accessories-from-plugable.2407464/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods, MacBook Air, Beats, and More at All-Time Low Prices in Wake of Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-13-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-macbook-air-beats-and-more-at-all-time-low-prices-in-wake-of-prime-day.2407459/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 09:33:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-13-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's October Prime Day happened this week, and although it's now over, we're tracking a few leftover discounts on popular Apple products. This weekend, you can still get Prime Day pricing on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, AirPods 2, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0012.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848002" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airpods-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916843" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;49 off the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C and AirPods 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-airpods-pro-2-usb-c/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C/MagSafe Case) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One of the biggest deals of the week came from Amazon, which is taking &#36;49 off the all-new AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case. It's available for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;249.00. Earlier in the week, the earbuds were priced at &#36;189.00, but that Prime Day deal has expired and the new sale is still a solid second-best price on the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/samsung-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916842" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;300 off Samsung monitors</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/samsung-viewfinity-s9-5k-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>Smart Monitor M80C for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>ViewFinity S9 Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Over at Samsung, the retailer introduced record low prices on a pair of its best monitors this week. The ViewFinity S9 5K Display is available for &#36;1,299.99 (&#36;300 off) and the Smart Monitor M8 is available for &#36;499.99 (&#36;200 off).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beats</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/beats-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916841" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;170 off Beats headphones</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us0%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/the-new-beats-studio-pro-half-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us0%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>Beats Studio Pro for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Cancelling-Earbuds-Built-Bluetooth-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB096SSCV5K%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1_sspa"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Beats Studio Buds for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09JL65GNM%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us2%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Beats Fit Pro for &#36;159.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Major Beats deals arrived at Amazon this week, headlined by nearly half off the brand new Beats Studio Pro. You can get these headphones for &#36;179.99, down from &#36;349.99, along with sales on Beats Studio Buds and Beats Fit Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916840" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker's best USB-C accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119398550">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/best-apple-deals-still-get-prime-day/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Although many of Anker's Prime Day deals have expired, there are still a few options available for anyone looking to purchase USB-C chargers and accessories for a new iPhone 15.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK6DDL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1697119464293">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119264712">67W 3-Port USB-C Wall Charger</a> - &#36;47.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C5QY4BL2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1697119578723">67W 6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;52.79 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSGH355C%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119264713">140W 6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;87.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119398550">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916839" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;80 off the 9th generation iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-ipad/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The week's best iPad deal centered on the 9th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad, which hit &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00. This is a match of the best price we've ever seen on this tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>15-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/15in-mba-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916838" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;250 off the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-15-inch-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-Inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best MacBook-related deal this week was on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, which was marked down by &#36;250 across every model on Amazon. You can still get these deals today, including the 256GB notebook for &#36;1,049.00 and the 512GB notebook for &#36;1,249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/13in-mba-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916837" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;200 off the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/ckFMqvF4y1f">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-best-apple-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckFMqvF4y1f"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>256GB for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckFMufbzGMu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>512GB for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon wasn't the only retailer providing all-time low discounts on Apple products this week, with Best Buy discounting the 256GB 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air to &#36;899.00, down from &#36;1,099.00. You can also get the 512GB notebook at a record low price of &#36;1,199.00.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-13-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods, MacBook Air, Beats, and More at All-Time Low Prices in Wake of Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-macbook-air-beats-and-more-at-all-time-low-prices-in-wake-of-prime-day.2407459/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Former Apple Executive Mike Bell Talks AirPort, CarPlay, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell-talks-airport-carplay-and-more.2407456/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 09:18:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Lucid Senior Vice President of Digital and former Apple Executive <a href="https://lucidmotors.com/company/leadership/michael-bell">Mike Bell</a> joins us on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/former-apple-executive-mike-bell-talks-airport-carplay/id1602394741?i=1000631231829">The MacRumors Show</a> to discuss the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, AirPort, Vision Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ixsvh_MAJVY?si=cXKfUDsIVhqnZS96" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Mike worked at Apple from 1991 to 2007 and played a significant role in development of hardware products like the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, AirPort, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, as well as software features like Boot Camp. After leaving Apple, he worked at Palm, Intel, and Rivian, and now leads digital at luxury electric automaker Lucid.<br/>
<br/>
We reflect on the success of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; since Mike's work to deliver the original model and where it stands today. We also look at Apple's Vision Pro headset and consider whether it will catch on. Mike discusses AirPort, a personal-favorite product that he led, how he feels about its discontinuation, and whether Apple is likely to return to the product line in the future.<br/>
<br/>
We talk through the process and importance of integrating Apple &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; in Lucid vehicles, as well as the challenges involved in bringing new digital features to EVs. We also discuss Mike's experience of working at Apple as a senior decision-maker in the 1990s and 2000s, how the company changed in the formative period in which he was there, similarities between Lucid and Apple, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player. Watch a video version of the show <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD8VmuL7qc7ii5uyjzSRk3UM7KI_c4qC5">on the <em>MacRumors</em> YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about some of our favorite Apple accessories with YouTuber and content creator Sara Dietschy.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is now on X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@macrumorsshow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast!<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for more episodes, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/09/iphone-14-event-reactions-with-luke-miani/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the show, and let us know what subjects you would like the podcast to cover in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">The MacRumors Show: Former Apple Executive Mike Bell Talks AirPort, CarPlay, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell-talks-airport-carplay-and-more.2407456/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>HomePod Mini Now Three Years Old: Here&#039;s What to Expect From the Next Generation</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old-heres-what-to-expect-from-the-next-generation.2407441/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 06:58:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple announced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> three years ago today at its "Hi, Speed" event alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 Pro, offering a small form-factor version of its smart speaker for the first time, with a price tag of just &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/homepod-mini-thumb-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-770560" /><br/>
Less than half a year after announcing the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/12/apple-discontinuing-homepod/">discontinued</a> the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, leaving the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; as the company's only smart speaker until earlier this year when Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-announces-new-homepod/">relaunched the full-size HomePod</a> form factor. The newly reintroduced &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; offers a large number of features that were previously exclusive to the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;, including an Apple Watch S-series chip, a U1 ultra wideband chip, Thread support, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/homepods-now-feature-temperature-humidity-sensor/">temperature and humidity sensor</a>, and a larger backlit touch surface that illuminates from edge to edge.<br/>
<br/>
Apple refreshed the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; with color in 2021, adding Blue, Yellow, and Orange options, but the device has remained otherwise unchanged since its introduction. It is now among the oldest devices that Apple still sells, surpassed only by the Pro Display XDR and second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>What Next for the HomePod mini?</h3><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> was first to highlight Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/07/new-homepod-mini-and-high-end-homepod/">work on a second-generation HomePod mini</a> in August 2022. Gurman has since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/22/gurman-apple-not-working-on-new-homepod-mini/">expressed skepticism</a> about what a new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could offer since "the latest &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; doesn't include any major new functions that aren't already in the &#36;99 mini." <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/f1602608757.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="445" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-763787" /><br/>
A second-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could conceivably introduce a lower-latency Handoff experience with the second-generation ultra wideband chip, improved sound and microphones, and the S7, S8, S9, or S10 chip. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> requests are now processed locally on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> thanks to the improved performance of the S9 chip, so bringing the same hardware to the next-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could considerably boost &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s responsiveness. A new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could also see specification upgrades, such as Wi-Fi 6E support.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; currently contains the S5 chip from the Apple Watch Series 5 and first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>. 2024 will likely see the introduction of the S10 chip in the next-generation Apple Watch, so that's the most advanced chip Apple could feasibly give the device if it launches before late 2025.<br/>
<br/>
The 2023 &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; contains the S7 chip, the same chip used in 2021's Apple Watch Series 7. Despite the introduction of the S8 chip in late 2022 in the Apple Watch Series 8, Apple Watch Ultra, and second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, Apple elected to use the S7 chip. This suggests it isn't certain that Apple will use its latest S-series chip in the second-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/s9-chip-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1501" height="844" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913379" /><br/>
The S6, S7, and S8 chips are all fundamentally the same and based on the A13 Bionic chip. The S9 chip, on the other hand, is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/apple-watch-series-9-updated-chip/">based on the A15 Bionic chip</a>, leading to major performance and efficiency improvements. The S6, S7, or S8 chip would still be a notable upgrade for the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;, but the S9 or S10 chip would offer even more substantial enhancements.<br/>
<br/>
It also seems highly likely that a new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; will come in a refreshed selection of color options. The current device is available in Space Gray, Blue, Yellow, White, and Orange. With the reintroduced full-size &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, Apple swapped Space Gray for Midnight, so a similar switch seems likely for the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; at a minimum.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Release Date</h3><br/>
In February, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that Apple will begin mass shipments of the second-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/03/homepod-mini-2-shipping-next-year/">in the second half of 2024</a>, which seems likely given the age of the current model and apparent active development on a new version for over a year.<br/>
<br/>
It is also possible that Apple could wait to introduce a new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; until the debut of a third-generation full-size &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, especially if it includes new features. Apple is developing an updated version of the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; that will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">7-inch display</a>, according to &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj;. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a 7-inch display is expected to come out <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/20/homepod-with-screen-delayed-next-year/">next year at the earliest</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old/">HomePod Mini Now Three Years Old: Here&#039;s What to Expect From the Next Generation</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old-heres-what-to-expect-from-the-next-generation.2407441/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Jelly Scrolling&#039; Rumored to Be Reduced on iPad Mini 7 Thanks to Rotated Screen Assembly</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/jelly-scrolling-rumored-to-be-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7-thanks-to-rotated-screen-assembly.2407432/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:46:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		<category>Setsuna Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>'s screen assembly will be rotated to reduce the effect of "jelly scrolling" that some users complain about with the current model, according to a Weibo leaker with an early track record for disclosing accurate information about Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/ipad-mini-9.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-818328" /><br/>
The account, known as "<a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/NnyGqvZHU#comment">Instant Digital</a>," claims that in addition to reduced jelly scrolling, the new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will also feature the A16 Bionic chip and front camera improvements.<br/>
<br/>
"Jelly scrolling" refers to screen tearing, which can cause text or images on one side of the screen to appear to be tilted downwards because of a mismatch in refresh rates. It can cause one side of the display to look as if it is responding faster than the other side in a visual disturbance that is hard to ignore once noticed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the phenomenon is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">normal behavior</a> for LCD iPads. Since LCD screens refresh line by line, there is a tiny delay between when the lines at the top and lines at the bottom are refreshed. But while this may be normal behavior for LCD screens, it can appear more obvious when observed on the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s smaller screen.<br/>
<br/>
Users have generally only complained about jelly scrolling when the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">in portrait orientation</a>. The issue is not reproducible in landscape orientation when scrolling, indicating this is a vertical refresh issue. According to the latest rumor, Apple plans to rotate the screen assembly to reduce the jelly scrolling effect in portrait orientation. Whether it will now become more prominent when the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is in landscape orientation is yet to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
The seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is among several devices that Apple could launch this month, the Weibo user goes on to claim. A modified first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> with a USB-C connector instead of Lightning and the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip are also apparently on the table for announcement toward the end of October. After evidence of a refreshed first-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with a USB-C connector was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/ios-17-1-apple-pencil-usb-c/">discovered in iOS 17.1 beta code</a>, Instant Digital said that "Apple has not given up on the original &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, and a USB-C version is expected to be coming soon."<br/>
<br/>
The "Instant Digital" account has shared accurate standalone rumors about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">Yellow iPhone 14 spring refresh</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted back glass</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/future-iphone-could-capture-spatial-photos-videos/">spatial video capture</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and more. That being said, questions remain about how much of the information shared by the user is original or accurate, but until a more long-term track record is established their rumors are worth highlighting.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/setsuna-digital/">Setsuna Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">&#039;Jelly Scrolling&#039; Rumored to Be Reduced on iPad Mini 7 Thanks to Rotated Screen Assembly</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/jelly-scrolling-rumored-to-be-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7-thanks-to-rotated-screen-assembly.2407432/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>California AirTag Lawsuit Widened to Include Dozens More Stalking Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/airtag-lawsuit-widened-stalking-cases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/california-airtag-lawsuit-widened-to-include-dozens-more-stalking-cases.2407426/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 04:45:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/airtag-lawsuit-widened-stalking-cases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTags</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is facing an expanded class action lawsuit in federal court in San Francisco by more than three dozen victims allegedly terrorized by stalkers using Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a>, reports <em><a href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2023/10/apple-airtags-triggered-explosion-of-stalking-reports-nationwide-lawsuit-says/">ArsTechnica</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/airtag-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-798036" /><br/>
The complaint targets Apple alleged negligence in allowing &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; to become "one of the most dangerous and frightening technologies employed by stalkers" since they can be easily used used to determine "real-time location information to track victims."<br/>
<br/>
The complaint is a revised version that was brought before a Californian judge in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/women-sue-apple-over-airtags/">December 2022</a> by two women, one of which claims her ex-boyfriend used an AirTag to track her without her consent. Since then, plaintiffs allege that there has been an "explosion of reporting" showing that &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; are often used for stalking.<br/>
<br/>
To evidence its claims, the complaint cites more than 150 police reports in the United States as of April 2022, as well as an upsurge in international stalking cases involving &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;. Plaintiffs argue that Apple has not done enough to reduce potential harms, which they claim can include financial ruin and in extreme cases murder. <br/>
<br/>
There have been multiple news stories about &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; being used for vehicle theft, stalking, and other nefarious purposes, which has led Apple to make several updates to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/10/airtag-updates-unwanted-tracking/">how AirTags work</a> to prevent criminals from taking advantage of them.<br/>
<br/>
When setting up an AirTag, for example, Apple shows warnings to thwart malicious use. The warning makes it clear that the AirTag is linked to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, that using it to track people is a crime, and that law enforcement can request identifying information about the owner of the AirTag, which Apple will readily provide.<br/>
<br/>
With an April 2022 software update, Apple made the AirTag sound louder, also to help cut down on stalking attempts. Apple also added safety features that include Precision Finding, improved display alerts, and louder sounds that are designed to make &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; more difficult to use for people-tracking purposes. Additionally, Apple released the "Tracker Detect" app that allows Android users to scan for &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; to make sure there are none around.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these updates, plaintiffs have alleged that &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; remain dangerous. For instance, one Georgia resident quoted by <em>ArsTechnica</em> reported that she and her daughter were being stalked by someone using &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; within the past two weeks "without knowing by whom or why." Although she cannot locate the &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;, she receives daily alerts from Apple and chimes from the &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; that confirm that the &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; are still there. These chimes only signal to the victim that she's being perpetually watched. "Every day, I am reminded that me and my daughter are not safe," added the victim in the complaint.<br/>
<br/>
The complaint alleges that Apple violated federal and state laws by negligently releasing a defective product, and has been unjustly enriched while invading the privacy of those victim unwittingly being tracked on its devices. Plaintiffs are seeking damages to all persons in the US who own iOS or Android devices, which includes classes of users who were stalked, as well as those who were allegedly at risk of stalking. <br/>
<br/>
The complaint also seeks a court order "enjoining Apple from further unlawful, unfair, and/or fraudulent practices with respect to the design, manufacture, and release into the market of its &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;."<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to move to dismiss the lawsuit by October 27, the deadline by which the company must respond to the amended complaint.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airtags.232">AirTags</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/airtag-lawsuit-widened-stalking-cases/">California AirTag Lawsuit Widened to Include Dozens More Stalking Cases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/california-airtag-lawsuit-widened-to-include-dozens-more-stalking-cases.2407426/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Series Chip Technology Moves to Volume Production</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/apple-obtains-orders-for-iphone-16-tsmc-chips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-series-chip-technology-moves-to-volume-production.2407417/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 03:17:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/apple-obtains-orders-for-iphone-16-tsmc-chips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has already given order commitments to chip supplier TSMC for its second-generation 3nm chip fabrication process known as N3E, which is expected to be used in all four models of next year's iPhone 16 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
TSMC's next 3nm node upgrade to N3E is less expensive and has improved yield compared to the Taiwanese foundry's first-generation 3nm process, N3B, which made its debut on the smartphone market with the A17 Pro chip that powers Apple's iPhone 15 Pro models. The N3E process also focuses on enhancing chip performance and power consumption. <br/>
<br/>
According to <em>DigiTimes</em>' sources, the foundry house has already moved N3E to volume production, and plans to have the upgraded version replace N3 starting 2024. Except for Samsung, all major chip vendors will embrace N3E, and TSMC has already obtained order commitments from its customers, the largest being Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is receiving all of TSMC's first-generation 3-nanometer process chips this year. As early as May, Apple was known to have booked nearly 90 percent of the foundry's 3nm production for its devices. Apple is now projected to take 100 percent of TSMC's capacity in 2023, due to delays in Intel's wafer needs owing to later modifications to the company's CPU platform design plans.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC is expected to see 4-6 percent of its overall sales in 2023 to come from 3nm manufacturing, thanks to huge orders from Apple for N3B chips for its iPhone 15 devices. Apple alone is expected to contribute as much as &#36;3.4 billion in sales for the foundry this year.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC also plans to move N3P to volume production in the second half of 2024, according to the report. N3P is said to offer an additional boost to N3E with 5 percent more speed at the same leakage, 5-10 percent power reduction at the same speed, and 1.04x more chip density.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 16 models will be equipped with A18-branded chips based on TSMC's N3E node, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">according to Jeff Pu</a>, an often-accurate analyst who covers companies within Apple's supply chain. The iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are equipped with the A16 Bionic chip, so a jump to the A18 chip for the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus would be significant.<br/>
<br/>
Given that the iPhone 16 lineup is around a year away from launching, Pu is probably making an educated guess about the marketing names, so it remains to be seen if Apple actually moves forward with A18 and A18 Pro branding.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/apple-obtains-orders-for-iphone-16-tsmc-chips/">iPhone 16 Series Chip Technology Moves to Volume Production</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-series-chip-technology-moves-to-volume-production.2407417/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps Redesign Expands to Denmark and Greece</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/apple-maps-redesign-expands-denmark-greece/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-redesign-expands-to-denmark-and-greece.2407415/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:23:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/apple-maps-redesign-expands-denmark-greece/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		<category>Greece</category>
		<category>Denmark</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/dk/newsroom/2023/10/apple-rolls-out-all-new-map-across-denmark/">announced</a> that its revamped Maps app is rolling out in Denmark and Greece.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Maps-update-denmark.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916766" /><br/>
The new experience provides more detail, improved navigation, custom-designed 3D models of popular landmarks, immersive turn-by-turn walking directions powered by augmented reality, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Look Around, which was first introduced in iOS 13, is also expanding to both countries starting today. Look Around provides 3D street-level imagery in cities where it is available, and it is similar to Google's Street View.<br/>
<br/>
Apple users in the above countries received notifications of the rollout this morning, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> expert Justin O'Beirne also <a href="https://www.justinobeirne.com/new-apple-maps-expansion-20-release">catalogued the expansion</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This is the twentieth time that Apple has expanded its new map data since its public launch in September 2018. It has since expanded to the U.K., Ireland, Canada, Spain, Portugal, Italy, Australia, New Zealand, Singapore, France, Germany, and select other countries and territories.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/greece/">Greece</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/denmark/">Denmark</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/apple-maps-redesign-expands-denmark-greece/">Apple Maps Redesign Expands to Denmark and Greece</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-redesign-expands-to-denmark-and-greece.2407415/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft&#039;s &#36;69 Billion Deal to Buy Activision Blizzard Cleared By UK</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/microsoft-to-buy-activision-blizzard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsofts-69-billion-deal-to-buy-activision-blizzard-cleared-by-uk.2407413/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:12:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/microsoft-to-buy-activision-blizzard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft's revised offer to buy Activision Blizzard has been approved by the Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) after its initial acquisition attempt was blocked by the UK antitrust regulator. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/microsoft-purchases-Activision.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833586" /><br/>
Under the revised deal, French video game publisher Ubisoft will be given the rights to distribute Activision's games on consoles and PCs over the cloud.  <br/>
<br/>
The CMA <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/microsoft-concession-a-gamechanger-that-will-promote-competition">said</a> the reworked deal would "preserve competitive prices" in the gaming industry and provide more choice and better services. "We've made sure Microsoft can't have a stranglehold over this important and rapidly developing market," the regulator added. <br/>
<br/>
The approval brings an end to Microsoft's nearly two-year battle to secure the takeover. The company entered into a &#36;68.7 billion deal to buy Activision Blizzard in January 2022, but the CMA <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/26/microsoft-activision-blizzard-merger-blocked/">blocked</a> it over concerns it would be anticompetitive in the cloud gaming market.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft was unable to finalize the deal globally until approval was granted.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard was approved by regulators in several other regions and territories including Brazil, Chile, Japan, Saudi Arabia, Serbia, South Africa, and most recently, the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
Activision is one of the most popular video games publishers in the world, and the deal represents one of the biggest shake-ups in the games industry in recent history. The studio is the maker of hit titles such as Call of Duty, Candy Crush, World of Warcraft, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft hopes the takeover will boost demand for its Xbox console and allow it to add more titles to its Xbox Game Pass streaming service, where members pay a subscription fee to access a catalog of titles via the cloud.<br/>
<br/>
Xbox Game Pass is available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> through Safari, but not the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. While Apple does allow all-in-one gaming subscription services to be on the platform, every game offered on the service must be submitted individually for approval through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; review process.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/microsoft-to-buy-activision-blizzard/">Microsoft&#039;s &#36;69 Billion Deal to Buy Activision Blizzard Cleared By UK</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsofts-69-billion-deal-to-buy-activision-blizzard-cleared-by-uk.2407413/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Astropad Slate iPad App Lets You Control Your Mac With Apple Pencil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/astropad-slate-ipad-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/astropad-slate-ipad-app-lets-you-control-your-mac-with-apple-pencil.2407381/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 16:36:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/astropad-slate-ipad-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Astropad today announced a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> app called <a href="https://astropad.com/slate/">Astropad Slate</a>, which can be used to control the Mac with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>. Astropad Slate is available as a public beta, and because it's still in testing, it is free for everyone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/astropad-slate-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="1999" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916747" /><br/>
There are several Mac functions that can be performed with the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;. It works as a cursor for controlling the desktop mouse, with a tap on the screen serving as a click. Handwriting done on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will be translated into typed text on the Mac. Astropad Slate supports the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover gestures on newer iPads, and there is a simulated hover option on older iPads, plus you can use two-finger touch gestures for actions like scrolling and zoom.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/872784238?h=548327e593" width="560" height="364" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
You can also use the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; as a pen tablet with Mac apps that support drawing, sketching, and other creative work. The Astropad Slate app basically turns the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; into a no-screen drawing tablet so you can focus on your work on the Mac. A Mac and an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; can be connected using Wi-Fi, Peer-to-Peer networking, or an appropriate USB cable. Requirements include iPadOS 15 or later and macOS 11 or later.<br/>
<br/>
The Astropad Slate app can be accessed by signing up for the beta <a href="https://astropad.com/slate/">on the Astropad website</a>. <br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/astropad-slate-ipad-app/">Astropad Slate iPad App Lets You Control Your Mac With Apple Pencil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/astropad-slate-ipad-app-lets-you-control-your-mac-with-apple-pencil.2407381/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nanoleaf Debuts HomeKit-Compatible Downlights, GU10 Bulbs and Lamps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/nanoleaf-downlights-lamps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-debuts-homekit-compatible-downlights-gu10-bulbs-and-lamps.2407378/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 15:37:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/nanoleaf-downlights-lamps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Lighting company <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/">Nanoleaf</a> today announced the launch of new Essentials lights that are aimed at replacing some of the standard bulbs that are installed in ceilings, plus it is introducing a new series of products in partnership with Umbra.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/nanoleaf-downlight.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916707" /><br/>
The <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/essentials/bulbs/?category=GU10&amp;standard=matter&amp;size=3">Essentials Matter GU10</a> and the Essentials Matter Recessed Downlight are compatible with smart home platforms that support Matter, which includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>. The lights can be added to a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; setup as long as a Matter hub like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> is available. The Essentials lights are also Thread enabled and will integrate with other Thread products for improved connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
Nanoleaf's Recessed Downlights are four inches in size and can replace standard downlights that you may have in your home, while the GU10 bulbs can replace light fixtures that use that bulb style. Like all Nanoleaf Essential lights, the Downlights and GU10 bulbs support 16 million colors as well as a range of different white temperatures.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/nanoleaf-gu10.jpg" alt="" width="3988" height="2243" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916708" /><br/>
The lights can be controlled through the Nanoleaf app or through the Home app when added to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;, and can be activated through automations to have lights turn on at specific times or work in tandem with other smart home devices. Multiple bulbs can be grouped together so you can change the lighting in entire rooms at one time.<br/>
<br/>
Nanoleaf today also announced that it is partnering with Umbra on two new Smart Lamps that are compatible with Matter. The Cono Portable Lamp and the Cup Lamp have unique designs created by Umbra with lighting technology supplied by Nanoleaf. The Cono and Cup Lamps work like other Nanoleaf lights, supporting millions of colors and working with scenes, automations, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/cono-lamp-nanoleaf.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916711" /><br/>
The Cono Portable Lamp has a built-in battery that lasts for up to five hours so it can be taken from room to room, while the Cup Lamp is a desktop lamp with a USB charging port and a cup base that is able to hold desk accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/nanoleaf-cup-lamp.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916712" /><br/>
Three of the GU10 bulbs <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/essentials/bulbs/?category=GU10&amp;standard=matter&amp;size=3">can be preordered</a> for &#36;50, while the downlights are <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/ceiling-lights/downlight/?size=each">priced at &#36;35 each</a>. The <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/smarter-partners/umbra-lamps/?category=cono-lamp&amp;color=grey">Cono Portable Lamp</a> is available for preorder now and is priced at &#36;95, and the &#36;130 Cup Lamp will be available in early 2024.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/nanoleaf-downlights-lamps/">Nanoleaf Debuts HomeKit-Compatible Downlights, GU10 Bulbs and Lamps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-debuts-homekit-compatible-downlights-gu10-bulbs-and-lamps.2407378/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Remember the Lower-Cost Apple Watch Series 1? It&#039;s Vintage Now</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-watch-series-1-vintage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/remember-the-lower-cost-apple-watch-series-1-its-vintage-now.2407358/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:21:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-watch-series-1-vintage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated the public-facing <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201624">vintage and obsolete products list</a> on its website. The page confirms that all first-generation Apple Watch models are now obsolete, as we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/original-apple-watch-now-obsolete/">reported earlier this month</a> based on an internal memo. Obsolete products are no longer eligible for repairs or service at Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Watch-Series-1-Vintage-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1966" height="1106" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916758" /><br/>
Another addition to the page is the Apple Watch Series 1, which is now classified as vintage. Introduced alongside the Apple Watch Series 2 in September 2016, the Series 1 was a more affordable model that lacked the Series 2's built-in GPS, brighter display, and improved water resistance. It was also only available with an aluminum case, whereas the Series 2 had aluminum, stainless steel, and ceramic case options. In the U.S., the Series 1 started at &#36;269, compared to &#36;369 for the Series 2.<br/>
<br/>
Apple considers a product to be vintage once five years have passed since it was last distributed for sale. Apple discontinued the Series 1 in September 2018 after introducing the Apple Watch Series 4, so that five-year mark has now been reached. Vintage products are no longer guaranteed to be eligible for repairs at Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers, with service subject to parts availability.<br/>
<br/>
Nowadays, the Apple Watch SE is the budget model, with pricing starting at &#36;249.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-watch-series-1-vintage/">Remember the Lower-Cost Apple Watch Series 1? It&#039;s Vintage Now</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/remember-the-lower-cost-apple-watch-series-1-its-vintage-now.2407358/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Settles 7-Year Wi-Fi Chip Patent Dispute With Caltech</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-caltech-wi-fi-lawsuit-settlement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-settles-7-year-wi-fi-chip-patent-dispute-with-caltech.2407352/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 12:45:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-caltech-wi-fi-lawsuit-settlement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Broadcom</category>
		<category>Caltech</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and its Wi-Fi chip supplier Broadcom have reached an agreement with the California Institute of Technology (Caltech), putting an end to a years-long legal battle over wireless communication patents, reports <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/apple-caltech-lawsuit-idCAKBN31C1S5">Reuters</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-Wi-Fi-Chip-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-883034" /><br/>
The terms of the settlement have not been shared, but Caltech will be dropping its lawsuit against Apple and Broadcom with prejudice, preventing Caltech from refiling in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Caltech sued Apple and Broadcom <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/05/30/caltech-vs-apple-broadcom-wifi-lawsuit/">way back in 2016</a>, accusing the two companies of infringing on a series of Wi-Fi patents covering encoding and decoding circuitry for improving data transmission and performance. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, and Apple Watch were all targeted in the suit for using Caltech technology.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/08/03/apple-countersues-caltech-settles-dot-23/">ended up countersuing</a> in an attempt to have the patents invalidated, a tactic that was unsuccessful. In 2020, a jury decided that Apple and Broadcom had indeed infringed on Caltech's patents, and Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/01/29/apple-caltech-patent-infringement/">ordered to pay &#36;838 million</a>, while Broadcom was told to pay &#36;270 million.<br/>
<br/>
The two companies combined were ordered to pay &#36;1.1 billion, which would have been one of the largest payouts in U.S. history for a patent dispute. Apple and Broadcom <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/04/apple-dispute-with-caltech-granted-new-trial/">appealed the decision</a>, and the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit ultimately decided that while the two companies had infringed on Caltech patents, the damages award was not justified. The prior court had used a two-tier system to award damages based on different royalty rates, which the appeals court said was "legally unsupportable."<br/>
<br/>
A new trial was ordered, which would recalculate the amount that Apple and Broadcom would need to pay to Caltech. Rather than undergoing a second trial, Apple, Broadcom, and Caltech back in August told the court that a potential settlement was in the works, and now the settlement is official.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/broadcom/">Broadcom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/caltech/">Caltech</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-caltech-wi-fi-lawsuit-settlement/">Apple Settles 7-Year Wi-Fi Chip Patent Dispute With Caltech</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-settles-7-year-wi-fi-chip-patent-dispute-with-caltech.2407352/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Expected to Support &#039;5G Advanced&#039; With Qualcomm&#039;s Snapdragon X75 Modem</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-expected-to-support-5g-advanced-with-qualcomms-snapdragon-x75-modem.2407339/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:13:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be equipped with Qualcomm's latest cellular modem, according to technology analyst Jeff Pu, enabling faster and more power efficient 5G connectivity for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
In a research note this week with investment firm Haitong International Securities, Pu said the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be equipped with <a href="https://www.qualcomm.com/products/technology/modems/snapdragon-x75-5g-modem-rf-system">Qualcomm's Snapdragon X75 modem</a>. However, he expects the standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus to retain the Snapdragon X70 modem used for the entire iPhone 15 lineup. Apple has typically used the same Qualcomm modem across all models for each generation of iPhones, excluding the low-end iPhone SE, so this would be a change in strategy for the company.<br/>
<br/>
Announced in February 2023, the Snapdragon X75 features improved carrier aggregation and other technology advancements for faster 5G download and upload speeds compared to the X70. The modem's combined mmWave and sub-6GHz 5G transceiver takes up 25% less circuit board space, and uses up to 20% less power, according <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/2/15/23600171/qualcomm-snapdragon-x75-5g-modem-rf">to <em>The Verge</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Snapdragon X75 also supports the latest "5G Advanced" standard, which is described as "the next phase of 5G" and an "evolution towards 6G." 5G Advanced will include artificial intelligence and machine learning enhancements for improved 5G performance, and it will also expand 5G to additional types of devices and use cases.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is likely to market the iPhone 16 Pro models as featuring "5G Advanced," much like the iPhone 6s gained support for "LTE Advanced" in 2015.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to have been working on its own 5G modem for iPhones since 2018, but the project has reportedly faced development challenges, and the modem is not expected to be announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/apple-modem-in-2025-kuo/">until 2025 or later</a> should it ever materialize. In the meantime, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/">extended its 5G modem agreement with Qualcomm</a> through 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Apple should announce the iPhone 16 lineup in September 2024, so there is still plenty of time remaining until the devices launch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">iPhone 16 Pro Expected to Support &#039;5G Advanced&#039; With Qualcomm&#039;s Snapdragon X75 Modem</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-expected-to-support-5g-advanced-with-qualcomms-snapdragon-x75-modem.2407339/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhones Won&#039;t Adopt RCC for Thinner Circuit Boards Until 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/rcc-thinner-circuit-boards-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphones-wont-adopt-rcc-for-thinner-circuit-boards-until-2025.2407338/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:24:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/rcc-thinner-circuit-boards-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhones will not adopt resin coated copper (RCC) foil for their printed circuit boards until 2025, <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/2025iphonercc-it-will-take-until-2025-at-the-earliest-for-the-iphone-mainboard-to-61abc0d30883">according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. Kuo says that Apple will not adopt this technology in 2024 because of its "fragile characteristics" and "inability to pass drop tests."<br/>
<br/>
<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-767478" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Apple-Silicon-Teal-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
If Apple and its supplier Ajinomoto can improve the RCC material before the third quarter of 2024, the high-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 models could use it. Resin coated copper does not sound exciting, but it has the potential to slim down the size of circuit boards, freeing up space inside of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that can be used for larger batteries or other technology. Kuo says that it also makes the drilling process easier for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; manufacturing because RCC is fiberglass-free.<br/>
<br/>
Late last month, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-looking-to-save-space-with-thinner-pcbs/">Weibo circuit expert</a> claimed that Apple would adopt RCC for circuit boards starting in 2024, but it appears that we might not see the shift until 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/rcc-thinner-circuit-boards-2025/">Kuo: iPhones Won&#039;t Adopt RCC for Thinner Circuit Boards Until 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphones-wont-adopt-rcc-for-thinner-circuit-boards-until-2025.2407338/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Apple Deals You Can Still Get From Amazon&#039;s October Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/best-apple-deals-still-get-prime-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-apple-deals-you-can-still-get-from-amazons-october-prime-day.2407337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:17:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/best-apple-deals-still-get-prime-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Now that Amazon's Prime Big Deal Days event has ended, many of the week's best sales have expired. However, we're tracking a few Apple products that remain at their best-ever prices even after the end of the sale, including the AirPods 2, 15-inch MacBook Air, and 9th generation iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/last-minute-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916640" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>15-Inch MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/15inch-macbook-air-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916649" /><br/>
<br/>
An overall highlight of Prime Day has been a &#36;250 discount across the entire 15-inch M2 MacBook Air lineup, and all of these sales are still around. The 256GB model is down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a> and the 512GB model is down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,249.00</strong></a>, and both are record low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-Inch MacBook Air for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airpods-purple-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916647" /><br/>
<br/>
There were quite a few AirPods deals earlier in the week, but the only notable deal that has stuck around is on the AirPods 2. You can get these earbuds for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;89.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00, which is one of the lowest prices of the year and an overall second-bet price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're still shopping for the newest model of the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C, there is a sale on this model, it's just not at its all-time low Prime Day price. You can pick up these earbuds for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00, which is still a good deal on the newest model of AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-purple-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916648" /><br/>
<br/>
The major iPad deal that has stuck around post-Prime Day is on the 9th generation iPad (64GB Wi-Fi), which is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;249.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. This is a match of the best price we've ever tracked on the tablet, and the 256GB Wi-Fi option is on sale too, just not at a record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for 249.00</div></a></div><h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-purple-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916646" /><br/>
<br/>
Anker deals remain abundant in the wake of Prime Day, with steep savings on USB-C wall chargers, portable batteries, and power strips. All of the discounts below require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the deal price at the checkout screen.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK6DDL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1697119464293">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119264712">67W 3-Port USB-C Wall Charger</a> - &#36;47.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C5QY4BL2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1697119578723">67W 6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;52.79 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSGH355C%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119264713">140W 6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;87.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119398550">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airtag-purple-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916645" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's Bluetooth tracker accessory hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;88.99</strong></a> during Prime Day, and that &#36;10 off discount is still available on Amazon today. This is for the 4-pack of the AirTag, and it's a solid second-best price on the device.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;88.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/best-apple-deals-still-get-prime-day/">The Best Apple Deals You Can Still Get From Amazon&#039;s October Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-apple-deals-you-can-still-get-from-amazons-october-prime-day.2407337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Checklist With Important Tips for Buying a Used iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-preowned-iphone-checklist/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-checklist-with-important-tips-for-buying-a-used-iphone.2407322/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 08:08:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-preowned-iphone-checklist/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week published a new <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213680">support document</a> with some valuable tips for buying a preowned iPhone online or in person.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/iphoneseblack.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1200" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-737527" /><br/>
Apple starts off by touting that the iPhone "lasts longer than other smartphones," making a preowned iPhone a "great way to own an iPhone." Apple says it provides "industry-leading device support for software updates," although Google <a href="https://blog.google/products/pixel/software-support-pixel-8-pixel-8-pro/">recently announced</a> that its latest Pixel 8 phones will receive full Android updates for seven years, whereas iOS 17 only supports iPhone models released up to five years ago.<br/>
<br/>
When buying a preowned iPhone online, it is very important to choose a trusted seller, as the device cannot be physically inspected at the time of purchase. If possible, make sure the iPhone is not Activation Locked, as this would prevent you from using the device unless you know the previous owner's Apple ID and password.<br/>
<br/>
For in-person purchases, Apple shared a helpful checklist for inspecting a preowned iPhone. Apple explains how to check for damage, how to find out if parts have been replaced, how to view the battery's health, how to find out if the iPhone is locked to a carrier, how to ensure hardware like the camera and microphone are functional, and more.<br/>
<br/>
While some of the tips are obvious, Apple's support document might be worth bookmarking if you plan to buy a used iPhone in the future.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/apple-preowned-iphone-checklist/">Apple Shares Checklist With Important Tips for Buying a Used iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-checklist-with-important-tips-for-buying-a-used-iphone.2407322/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
