<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 08:02:20 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next-Gen Apple Chip Technology on Track to Reach Production in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-gen-apple-chip-technology-on-track-to-reach-production-in-2025.2416379/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 07:26:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next-generation 2nm chip technology destined for future Apple devices is on schedule to begin production next year, <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240115PD215.html"><em>DigiTimes</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Apple-Silicon-Teal-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-767478" /><br/>
TSMC chip fabrication facilities will begin installing equipment designed for 2nm chip production in April at the earliest. Apple was the first company to utilize TSMC's initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> technology with the A17 Pro chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, and the company is likely to follow suit with the chipmaker's 2nm chips. With production set to begin in 2025, 2nm chips are likely to make their first appearance in Apple devices soon after.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, the <em>Financial Times</em> reported that TSMC had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/tsmc-demos-next-gen-chip-technology/">already demonstrated</a> prototype 2nm chips to Apple ahead of their expected introduction in 2025. Apple is said to be closely aligned with TSMC in the race to develop and implement 2nm chip technology, which will surpass their current &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; chips and associated nodes in terms of transistor density, performance, and efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
Today, <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></em> added that the chip supplier is also believed to be evaluating which of its plants will be the first to produce even <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/tsmc-mentions-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips/">more advanced 1.4nm chips</a> in 2027. The company began mass production of its enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; node, which is likely to appear in Apple devices for the first time later this year, in the fourth quarter of 2023.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/">Next-Gen Apple Chip Technology on Track to Reach Production in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-gen-apple-chip-technology-on-track-to-reach-production-in-2025.2416379/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max to Remain Best-Selling Model in Early 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/iphone-15-pro-max-best-seller-early-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-to-remain-best-selling-model-in-early-2024.2416372/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:11:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/iphone-15-pro-max-best-seller-early-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhone 15 Pro Max will continue to be the best-selling iPhone model in the first half of this year, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/大立光罕見正向看待淡季高階鏡頭需求之深度分析-玻塑混合鏡頭-華為歸來與鏡頭單價上漲-以及ai手機成為samsung-s24-高階手機新賣點-in-depth-analysis-of-8e71324d080b">latest industry note on Medium</a>, Kuo said the iPhone 15 Pro Max "will still account for 40–45% of all iPhone 15 shipments in 1H24," which will be "critical" to Taiwanese camera lens supplier Largan's buoyant off-season in the first half of the year.<br/>
<br/>
Apart from being the premium model with the largest display at 6.7-inches, the iPhone 15 Pro Max also features a 5x Telephoto zoom or "tetraprism" lens that is not found in other models. The tetraprism lens in the Pro Max model alone is expected to increase Largan's first half-year revenue by &#36;108.8 to &#36;121.6 million, according to Kuo. <br/>
<br/>
Kuo has repeatedly said he expects the tetraprism lens to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">expand</a> to both the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max later this year, enabling at least 5x optical zoom and 25x digital zoom on the Telephoto lens of both premium models. <br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro is expected to feature a larger 6.3-inch display, compared to the 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro. This change would increase the overall size of the device, which would provide additional internal space for a tetraprism lens.<br/>
<br/>
According to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/both-iphone-16-pro-models-tetraprism-zoom-lens/">report</a> by <em>The Elec</em>, Apple will add LG Innotek as another supplier of the folded zoom module used in the technology, in an attempt to secure production yields for the increased number of units required.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/iphone-15-pro-max-best-seller-early-2024/">Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max to Remain Best-Selling Model in Early 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-to-remain-best-selling-model-in-early-2024.2416372/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro M2 Chip Said to Have 10 GPU, 8 CPU Cores</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/vision-pro-m2-chip-10-gpu-8-cpu-cores/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-m2-chip-said-to-have-10-gpu-8-cpu-cores.2416370/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 04:28:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/vision-pro-m2-chip-10-gpu-8-cpu-cores/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Vision Pro runs on an M2 chip equipped with ten GPU cores and eight CPU cores – the same version used in Apple's higher-end MacBook Air models. That's according to a <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1746585308626612655?s=20">post on X</a> (formerly Twitter) by <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-vision-pro-setup.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923100" /><br/>
Apple revealed early on that its mixed reality headset uses an M2 processor, but it wasn't clear until now which variant of the chip Apple had chosen. <br/>
<br/>
Apple uses the M2 chip in both of its current 13.6- and 15.3-inch MacBook Air models, which launched in June 2022. Built on 5-nanometer technology, the M2 has an 8-core CPU, much like the M1, but it supports eight or ten GPU cores, up from seven or eight in the M1.<br/>
<br/>
As things stand, Apple's &#36;3,499 Vision Pro will launch on February 2 with what is officially a last-generation processor, given that Apple has since released 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models powered by M3 chips. <br/>
<br/>
The M2 chip in Vision Pro is responsible for processing content, running the visionOS operating system, executing computer vision algorithms, and providing graphical content. However, it does not work alone.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro offloads the processing of information coming from the cameras, sensors, and microphones to a dedicated custom-built R1 chip. Apple says that it can stream images to the displays within 12 milliseconds, providing a "virtually lag-free" view of the world.<br/>
<br/>
The entry-level Vision Pro is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-how-much-ram-and-storage/">equipped</a> 16GB of RAM and 256GB of storage space. Apple could offer models with up to 1TB of storage, but the existence of bigger capacities has not yet been confirmed.<br/>
<br/>
In the <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1746585308626612655?s=20">same post on X</a>, Gurman additionally confirmed that Apple customers will be able to purchase the Vision Pro online and at retail stores using Apple Card installments. Typically, Apple Card installments let customers spread the purchase over monthly payments with no interest. iPhone purchases can be made over 24 monthly payments, for example. Apple Vision Pro pre-orders open on Friday, January 19 at 5.00 a.m. PST in the United States.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/vision-pro-m2-chip-10-gpu-8-cpu-cores/">Apple Vision Pro M2 Chip Said to Have 10 GPU, 8 CPU Cores</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-m2-chip-said-to-have-10-gpu-8-cpu-cores.2416370/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Virtual Keyboard Blasted As &#039;Complete Write-Off&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-criticism/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-blasted-as-complete-write-off.2416369/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 03:25:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-criticism/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anyone paying attention to Apple's Vision Pro headset unveiling at WWDC 2023 will have seen its virtual keyboard demo. The keyboard floats in mid-air, allowing you to input text in your spatial computing environment while wearing the device. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1278" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930653" /><br/>
However, anyone planning to ditch their physical keyboard may want to hold onto it for a little while longer: According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, the virtual keyboard experience in visionOS 1.0 is "a complete write-off," and most people will want to use a Bluetooth keyboard instead.<br/>
<blockquote>"The Vision Pro virtual keyboard is a complete write-off at least in 1.0," wrote Gurman in an <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1745907431564063208?s=20">X post</a>. "You have to poke each key one finger at a time like you did before you learned how to type. There is no magical in-air typing. You can also look at a character and pinch. You'll want a Bluetooth keyboard."</blockquote><a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2023/10073/">According to Apple</a>, the buttons on the virtual keyboard are raised above the platter to mimic the affordance of pushing physical keys, and the keyboard even includes feedback via spatial sound effects to "compensate for the missing tactile information." <br/>
<br/>
Going on what Gurman said though, it doesn't sound like Apple has quite perfected the experience, which is probably always going to be degraded by the fatigue caused by having to hold your hands in the air to type, regardless of what Apple does to improve it in future software updates. Fortunately, Vision Pro can wirelessly connect to Mac accessories including the Magic Keyboard and the Magic Trackpad for more traditional tactile input. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Vision Pro virtual keyboard is a complete write-off at least in 1.0. You have to poke each key one finger at a time like you did before you learned how to type. There is no magical in-air typing. You can also look at a character and pinch. You’ll want a Bluetooth keyboard.</p>&mdash; Mark Gurman (@markgurman) <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1745907431564063208?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 12, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Starting at &#36;3,499, Apple Vision Pro pre-orders open on Friday, January 19 at 5.00 a.m. PST, and the device goes on sale in the U.S. on Friday, February 2, with availability in Canada and the United Kingdom expected to follow later in the year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-criticism/">Apple Vision Pro Virtual Keyboard Blasted As &#039;Complete Write-Off&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-blasted-as-complete-write-off.2416369/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Offers Rare iPhone Discounts in China to Counter Sales Slump</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-in-china-to-counter-sales-slump.2416368/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 02:41:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will launch a rare <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/shop/gifts/chinese-new-year/shopping-event">promotional discount</a> on its iPhones in China, offering customers as much as 500 yuan (&#36;70) off the price of its flagship devices ahead of the Lunar New Year in February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-discounts-lunar-new-year-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1294" height="840" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930648" /><br/>
The promotion, which runs from January 18 through January 21, applies to everything from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max, and also includes smaller discounts off other major Apple products like Macs, iPads, AirPods, and Apple Watch models. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's discounts are notable because the company does not typically offer promotions on its website around the Lunar New Year, usually leaving promotions to Apple authorized resellers instead. <br/>
<br/>
The move comes as Apple tries to stave off falling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China, with last year's double-digit decline projected by analysts to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/iphone-sales-down-huawei-resurgence-china/">deepen through 2024</a> owing to strong interest in Huawei's latest home-grown lineup, the Mate 60 series.<br/>
<br/>
Released in September just weeks before the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, Huawei's Mate 60 phones use a new China-made 7-nanometer processor tailored for the local market, showcasing the kind of advanced semiconductor manufacturing capabilities that US sanctions were originally designed to prevent.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the promotions, Apple's efforts to counter its sales slump are likely to be hampered by China's decision last year to ban iPhones from the offices of multiple government agencies and state companies. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">Apple Offers Rare iPhone Discounts in China to Counter Sales Slump</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-in-china-to-counter-sales-slump.2416368/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus Rumored to Feature Increased 8GB RAM and Wi-Fi 6E Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-iphone-16-plus-rumored-to-feature-increased-8gb-ram-and-wi-fi-6e-support.2416354/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 16:41:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus models will both feature 8GB of RAM, an increase over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-models-have-8gb-ram/">6GB of RAM in the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a>, according to information shared today by technology analyst Jeff Pu.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-Boxes-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920850" /><br/>
In a research note with investment firm Haitong International Securities, Pu reiterated his belief that all iPhone 16 models will be equipped with 8GB of RAM. Increased RAM can contribute to improved performance for multitasking on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 lineup:<ul><li><strong>iPhone 15:</strong> 6GB</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 15 Plus:</strong> 6GB</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro:</strong> 8GB</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max:</strong> 8GB</li></ul>iPhone 16 lineup, according to Pu:<ul><li><strong>iPhone 16:</strong> 8GB</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 16 Plus:</strong> 8GB</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro:</strong> 8GB</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max:</strong> 8GB</li></ul>Pu also expects the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus to support Wi-Fi 6E, which works with the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference with a compatible router. For the iPhone 15 lineup, Wi-Fi 6E is limited to the Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 lineup in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus Rumored to Feature Increased 8GB RAM and Wi-Fi 6E Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-iphone-16-plus-rumored-to-feature-increased-8gb-ram-and-wi-fi-6e-support.2416354/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16: Qualcomm&#039;s Latest 5G Modem May Be Limited to Pro Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-pro-qualcomm-x75-modem-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-qualcomms-latest-5g-modem-may-be-limited-to-pro-models.2416351/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 16:13:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-pro-qualcomm-x75-modem-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		<category>5G</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Qualcomm's latest cellular modem may be limited to the iPhone 16 Pro models this year, according to technology analyst Jeff Pu.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
In a research note today with investment firm Haitong International Securities, Pu reiterated his belief that the iPhone 16 Pro models will be equipped with <a href="https://www.qualcomm.com/products/technology/modems/snapdragon-x75-5g-modem-rf-system">Qualcomm's Snapdragon X75 modem</a>. However, he expects the standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus to retain the Snapdragon X70 modem found in all iPhone 15 models. This modem differentiation between the standard and Pro models would be a change in strategy for Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Announced in February 2023, the Snapdragon X75 features improved carrier aggregation and other technology advancements for faster 5G download and upload speeds compared to the X70. The modem's combined mmWave and sub-6GHz 5G transceiver takes up 25% less circuit board space, and uses up to 20% less power, according <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/2/15/23600171/qualcomm-snapdragon-x75-5g-modem-rf">to <em>The Verge</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Snapdragon X75 also supports the latest "5G Advanced" standard, which is described as "the next phase of 5G" and an "evolution towards 6G." 5G Advanced will include artificial intelligence and machine learning enhancements for improved 5G performance, and it will also expand 5G to additional device types and use cases.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is likely to advertise 5G Advanced support on the iPhone 16 Pro models, like it did with LTE Advanced on the iPhone 6s in 2015.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to have been working on its own 5G modem for iPhones since 2018, but the project has reportedly faced development challenges, and the modem is not expected to be announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/apple-modem-in-2025-kuo/">until 2025 or later</a> should it ever materialize. In the meantime, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/">extended its 5G modem agreement with Qualcomm</a> through 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 lineup in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/5g/">5G</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-pro-qualcomm-x75-modem-rumor/">iPhone 16: Qualcomm&#039;s Latest 5G Modem May Be Limited to Pro Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-qualcomms-latest-5g-modem-may-be-limited-to-pro-models.2416351/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s How Vision Pro Demos Will Work at Apple Stores Next Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-store-vision-pro-demos-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-vision-pro-demos-will-work-at-apple-stores-next-month.2416349/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:39:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-store-vision-pro-demos-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting on February 2 at 8 a.m. local time, Apple Stores in the U.S. will allow customers to sign up for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-demos-february-2/">demo of the Vision Pro headset</a>. In an email, Apple said it will be offering demos from February 2 through February 4 on a first‑come, first‑served basis.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Digital-Crown.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930595" /><br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-01-14/how-to-buy-apple-vision-pro-3-499-device-to-go-on-sale-feb-2-lrdjtdm7"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said each demo will last around 20 to 25 minutes. After a calibration process, he said the customer will view still photos, panoramas, spatial photos, and spatial videos in the Photos app. Next, he said customers will learn how to position multiple app windows and scroll through pages in Safari. Then, they will view immersive 3D content, including movie clips, sports, and a tightrope scene.<br/>
<br/>
Media personnel, YouTube creators, and some others invited to attend WWDC 2023 at Apple Park last June received a similar demo experience.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro demo units will also be preloaded with various third-party apps that will be available on the App Store at launch, according to the newsletter. Apple began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-releases-vision-pro-updates-testflight-xcode/">allowing developers to submit visionOS apps</a> for approval earlier this month.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will begin accepting Vision Pro pre-orders in the U.S. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">on January 19</a>, with pricing starting at &#36;3,499. The headset launches February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-store-vision-pro-demos-details/">Here&#039;s How Vision Pro Demos Will Work at Apple Stores Next Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-vision-pro-demos-will-work-at-apple-stores-next-month.2416349/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Belkin Expected to Sell Battery Pack Clip Accessory for Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/belkin-vision-pro-battery-pack-clip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/belkin-expected-to-sell-battery-pack-clip-accessory-for-apple-vision-pro.2416343/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 14:25:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/belkin-vision-pro-battery-pack-clip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Belkin</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro headset</a> is powered by an external battery pack that attaches with a cable. For customers who want to use the headset on the go without pockets or a backpack, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-01-14/how-to-buy-apple-vision-pro-3-499-device-to-go-on-sale-feb-2-lrdjtdm7"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman today said</a> that Belkin is planning to release a clip that allows the battery pack to be attached to clothing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Belkin will begin selling the clip when the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launches in the U.S. on February 2</a>, and Apple will also offer it, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
Belkin offers a range of Apple-endorsed accessories, including iPhone screen protectors, MagSafe charging stands, a Continuity Camera mount for Macs, and more. Many of its accessories are available on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the Vision Pro can provide up to two hours of battery life overall, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-battery-life-video-playback/">up to 2.5 hours for 2D video playback</a>, on a full charge.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/belkin/">Belkin</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/belkin-vision-pro-battery-pack-clip/">Belkin Expected to Sell Battery Pack Clip Accessory for Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/belkin-expected-to-sell-battery-pack-clip-accessory-for-apple-vision-pro.2416343/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Relocating Siri Evaluation Team in San Diego to Austin</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-moving-san-diego-siri-team-to-austin/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-relocating-siri-evaluation-team-in-san-diego-to-austin.2416340/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 13:33:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-moving-san-diego-siri-team-to-austin/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is relocating a team of around 120 people focused on improving Siri from San Diego to Austin later this year, according to multiple affected employees.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
The reorganization was confirmed by Apple today in a statement shared with <em>MacRumors</em>.<br/>
<br/>
"We're bringing our Data Operations Annotations teams in the US together at our campus in Austin, where a majority of the team is already based," an Apple spokesperson said. "Everyone currently employed will have the opportunity to continue their role with Apple in Austin. We are deeply committed to San Diego where we have grown significantly, and are continuing to hire as we expand our world-class engineering teams."<br/>
<br/>
The news was first reported <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-14/apple-to-shutter-121-person-san-diego-ai-team-in-reorganization">by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, who said employees in San Diego willing to relocate to Austin by June will be able to continue in their roles. The report said employees who do not relocate or find another role within Apple will receive severance pay, and outlines many other specific details.<br/>
<br/>
While some other large tech companies like Google, Microsoft, and Amazon have laid off thousands of employees over the past year, Apple has so far avoided this outcome. However, it is unlikely that all affected employees in San Diego are willing to relocate over a thousand miles away to Austin, so some may be facing termination.<br/>
<br/>
"Data Operations Annotations" employees are primarily tasked with evaluating Siri's responses to queries from customers who have opted in to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/28/apple-apologizes-over-siri-privacy-concerns/">Siri grading program</a>. In the U.S., this work will continue entirely in Austin going forward. Apple has similar teams in China, Ireland, Singapore, Spain, and other countries around the world.<br/>
<br/>
Apple had approximately 161,000 full-time employees as of September 30, according to a company filing last year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-moving-san-diego-siri-team-to-austin/">Apple Relocating Siri Evaluation Team in San Diego to Austin</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-relocating-siri-evaluation-team-in-san-diego-to-austin.2416340/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Vision Pro Release Date, iOS 17.3 Coming Soon, CES 2024 Recap</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/13/top-stories-vision-pro-release-date/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-release-date-ios-17-3-coming-soon-ces-2024-recap.2416222/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/13/top-stories-vision-pro-release-date/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset finally has a release date in the U.S., and it's coming up quickly! Alongside that announcement, we learned a bit more about the device and what to expect with the ordering process.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/top-stories-13jan2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930408" /><br/>
Other news this week included Apple starting to pay out claims for the high-profile class action lawsuit that claimed Apple was "secretly throttling" older iPhones with degraded batteries, an approaching release of iOS 17.3 and related updates, and the annual CES tech event in Las Vegas, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Launches February 2, Pre-Orders Start Next Week</h2><br/>
After being unveiled at WWDC 2023 last June, Apple's long-awaited Vision Pro mixed reality headset <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">now has a release date: Friday, February 2</a>. Pre-orders begin on Friday, January 19 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time. Availability is limited to the U.S., with more countries to follow later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Pricing starts at &#36;3,499 with 256GB of storage, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99/">ZEISS optical inserts will be available for &#36;99 to &#36;149</a>. If you're planning to order, make sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-vision-pro-preorder-tips/">check out Apple's tips</a> to make sure you're ready.<br/>
<br/>
Apple refers to the Vision Pro as a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/vision-pro-developers-asked-to-avoid-vr-branding/">spatial computer</a>," and it offers a combination of augmented reality and virtual reality features. The headset is powered by an all-new visionOS operating system, which can be controlled with a user's eyes, hands, and voice.<br/>
<br/>
Learn more in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro: Here's Everything You Get in the Box</h2><br/>
In its press release announcing the Vision Pro's launch date, Apple revealed the various <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-everything-included-in-box/">items that will be included with the headset</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Teal-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929939" /><br/>
Apple says the headset will ship with two types of head bands (a Solo Knit Band and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band/">Dual Loop Band</a>), a light seal, two light seal cushions, a cover for the front glass, a polishing cloth, an external battery pack, a USB-C power adapter, and a USB-C charging cable.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Features 16GB of RAM</h2><br/>
Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-how-much-ram-and-storage/">equipped with 16GB of unified memory</a>, according to files related to the device in Xcode 15.2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-chips.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898904" /><br/>
Our finding in Apple's app development tool confirms a June 2023 <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-02/apple-wwdc-2023-mixed-reality-headset-ios-17-and-other-products-to-expect">report from <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> that said the Vision Pro would be equipped with 16GB of RAM, and that is also the same amount of memory that was included in Vision Pro development kits.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Sends &#36;92 'Batterygate' Payments to iPhone Users</h2><br/>
Apple in 2020 agreed to pay up to &#36;500 million to settle a class action lawsuit in the U.S. that accused the company of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/12/18/geekbench-iphone-6s-slowdowns/">"secretly throttling" some iPhone models</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/06/apple-starts-iphone-batterygate-payouts/">payouts finally started going out this week</a> to individuals who submitted a claim.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-6s-MacRumors-YouTube.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929156" /><br/>
iPhone users have received &#36;92.17 per claim from Apple, according to multiple <em>MacRumors</em> readers. The deadline to submit a claim was in October 2020.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17.3 Coming Soon With These Two New Features for Your iPhone</h2><br/>
iOS 17.3 has been in beta testing since mid-December, and the upcoming software update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/10/ios-17-3-coming-soon/">includes two new features for the iPhone</a>, including Stolen Device Protection and collaborative Apple Music playlists.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" /><br/>
<strong>Related:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/10/when-will-ios-17-3-be-released/">When Will iOS 17.3 Be Released?</a><br/>
<br/>
Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-ios-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/">third beta of iOS 17.3</a> this week, and the update will likely be widely released later this month.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>CES 2024 Recap of Apple-Related Announcements</h2><br/>
The annual CES tech conference was held in Las Vegas this week, and there were a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">handful of Apple-related announcements</a> as usual.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CES-2024-Day-1-Thumbnail-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929609" /><br/>
Check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024 news hub</a> for a recap of new HomeKit accessories and more.<br/>
<br/>
Also be sure to watch our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-day-1-recap/">Day One</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-day-2-recap/">Day Two</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/ces-2024-day-3-recap/">Day Three</a> videos for more highlights.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jan-11-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/13/top-stories-vision-pro-release-date/">Top Stories: Apple Vision Pro Release Date, iOS 17.3 Coming Soon, CES 2024 Recap</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-release-date-ios-17-3-coming-soon-ces-2024-recap.2416222/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Tweaks iPhone 16 Pro Action Button Design as Early Development Continues</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-iphone-16-pro-action-button-tweaks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-iphone-16-pro-action-button-design-as-early-development-continues.2416183/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:47:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-iphone-16-pro-action-button-tweaks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Action Button</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> prototypes seen by <em>MacRumors</em> indicate that Apple has again tweaked the design of the Action button, and now it looks much like the Action button found on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>. Apple has been toying with the size and design of the Action button for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, but in the latest "Proto2" development stage, the company is sticking with a tried and true design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Left-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928696" /><br/>
During the different &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; development stages, Apple has tested four button configurations and two sizes for the Action button.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Unified volume button with small Action button</li><br/>
<li>Unified volume button with large Action button and new Capture button</li><br/>
<li>Separate volume buttons with large Action button and Capture button flush with frame</li><br/>
<li>Separate volume buttons with small Action button and Capture button flush with frame (current)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The earliest known prototypes of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; had a unified volume button and small multi-purpose Action button, both on the left side, with a power button on the right. This design was initially developed as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/">Project Bongo</a>, which was an attempt to bring haptic buttons the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. While the project was ultimately canceled due to unsatisfactory test results and high hardware failure rates, parts of the Bongo design, namely the unified volume button, found their way onto early designs of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The second prototype variant of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; also used a unified volume button, but it had a larger Action button that was close in size to the volume buttons. This prototype also had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">an additional "Capture button"</a> on the right side below the power button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
Later prototypes (pictured above) featured separate volume buttons rather than the unified button design. With these more recent units, Apple planned to include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">capacitive Action button</a> and Capture button, both of which were flush with the frame and featured force sensor technology.<br/>
<br/>
With the most recent "Proto2" design, Apple has once again changed the Action button. Apple has now adopted a smaller Action button that mirrors the Action button on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, doing away with the larger, flush look. While it is currently unclear how this affects the future of Apple's work on a capacitive Action button, a design change as significant as this indicates it has been canceled or postponed for future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> iterations.<br/>
<br/>
Although the information presented here accurately describes existing internal designs, it is important to note that additional design changes are always possible, and the information presented here may not reflect finalized design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
For additional information on what to expect from the 2024 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup, check out our dedicated rumor roundups for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/action-button/">Action Button</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-iphone-16-pro-action-button-tweaks/">Apple Tweaks iPhone 16 Pro Action Button Design as Early Development Continues</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-iphone-16-pro-action-button-design-as-early-development-continues.2416183/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Prices Hit AirPods Pro, Apple Watch, iPad, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-12-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-prices-hit-airpods-pro-apple-watch-ipad-and-more.2416167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:08:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-12-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals include record low prices on the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C, Apple Watch Series 9, iPad, and MacBook Air. Amazon is hosting every deal listed below, and some do require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the discount at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0009.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847999" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/airpods-pro-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930419" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;60 off AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/airpods-deals-60-in-savings/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon kicked off the New Year with an all-time low price on the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C, and this deal is still available to purchase this week. You can get the earbuds for &#36;189.00, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-watch-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930418" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;70 off Apple Watch models</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1RVMT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices-2/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1RVMT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;229.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7C4CL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple Watches have also seen solid discounts at the start of the year, and Series 9 models got even better deals this week. You can get both 41mm and 45mm GPS models of the Series 9 at all-time low prices on Amazon right now, while SE and Ultra 2 models are at solid second-best prices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ipad-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930417" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;99 off iPads</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/10/amazons-new-ipad-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
iPad deals reach up to &#36;99 off this week, starting at &#36;249.00 for the 9th gen iPad and rising to &#36;349.99 for the 10th gen iPad. We're also tracking a good iPad mini deal on Amazon at &#36;399.99 for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/macbook-air-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930416" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;249 off M1 13-inch MacBook Air and M2 15-inch MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/249-off-15-inch-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M1 13-inch MacBook Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C7686169%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M2 15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76B7QHC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M2 15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for a MacBook in early 2024, the MacBook Air is the way to go. Amazon has the previous generation M1 13-inch MacBook Air at just &#36;749.99, while the M2 15-inch MacBook Air is at a second-best price of &#36;1,049.99 with an on-page coupon.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-12-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Prices Hit AirPods Pro, Apple Watch, iPad, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-prices-hit-airpods-pro-apple-watch-ipad-and-more.2416167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024 Day 3: Clicks iPhone Keyboard, Qi2 Chargers, AR Glasses and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/ces-2024-day-3-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-day-3-clicks-iphone-keyboard-qi2-chargers-ar-glasses-and-more.2416160/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:07:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/ces-2024-day-3-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Hundreds of companies are at CES in Las Vegas this week showing off new products, and <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera has been spending time on the show floor to check out what's new, exciting, and worth taking note of.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZuzgBud-TPo" title="CES 2024 Day 3: Clicks iPhone Keyboard, Qi2 Chargers, AR Glasses and More" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
We wrote about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/clicks-iphone-keyboard/">the Clicks physical keyboard</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> last week, but Dan was able to test it out in person and he said that the keys feel great under the fingers and those who want a tactile typing experience will like it. The case is easy to put on and take off the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and there are handy shortcut keys for Spotlight search, webpage scrolling, and getting back to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Withings was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/07/ces-2024-withings-beamo/">demoing the BeamO</a>, an all-in-one device that can take your temperature, capture an ECG, monitor blood oxygen, and even serve as a digital stethoscope, and there were Qi2 chargers galore from brands like Hyper, Anker, and ESR. Qi2 is the latest charging technology, and it's bringing more affordable 15W wireless charging to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Targus was showing off an ambidextrous mouse that can be used by both right and left-handed people, and the company also had a dock that can connect two laptops together with three monitors, serving as a KVM.<br/>
<br/>
Sony and Honda had the Afeela electric car on the show floor with its dozens of sensors for driver safety, and Dan also took note of the Barsys 360, a smart cocktail machine that mixes and pours bartender-grade drinks.<br/>
<br/>
Unsurprisingly, there were a <em>ton</em> of AR/VR devices, some of which seemed to be inspired by the Vision Pro. One standout was the <a href="https://www.xreal.com">XREAL AR Glasses</a>, but they're only compatible with Samsung's latest smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
CES is just about wrapped up with the show coming to a close on Friday, but make sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">check out our CES 2024 hub</a> for anything that you might have missed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/ces-2024-day-3-recap/">CES 2024 Day 3: Clicks iPhone Keyboard, Qi2 Chargers, AR Glasses and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-day-3-clicks-iphone-keyboard-qi2-chargers-ar-glasses-and-more.2416160/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Withings Body Scan Review: High-End Health Monitoring at a High-End Price</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/withings-body-scan-smart-scale-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/withings-body-scan-review-high-end-health-monitoring-at-a-high-end-price.2416151/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:32:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/withings-body-scan-smart-scale-review&#038;post_date=1705084348/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Withings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When the holiday festivities are done with and January rolls around, people naturally look to improving their health and usually turn to smart devices to get their lifestyle back on track. Weight loss is typically part of that calculation, and while smart scales can help, there's little to distinguish between the majority of offerings on the market. <br/>
<br/>
Weight and body composition analysis have become <em>de rigueur</em> features these days, but Withings' <a href="https://www.withings.com/us/en/body-scan">Body Scan Connected Health Station</a> aims to go above and beyond the competition by offering an almost dizzying array of information about your physiological makeup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/withings-body-scan.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930339" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Features</h2><br/>
At &#36;400 in the U.S. and £350 in the U.K., the Withings Body Scan is definitely at the higher end of the market for a smart scale. But when you consider its comprehensive set of body measurements, the price is a little easier to swallow. Biometrics include:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Weight</li><br/>
  <li>Metabolic Age</li><br/>
<li>Basal Metabolic Rate</li><br/>
  <li>BMI</li><br/>
  <li>Segmental body composition analysis including:<br/>
    <ul><br/>
      <li>Muscle Mass (across five zones)</li><br/>
      <li>Fat Mass (across five zones)</li><br/>
      <li>Bone Mass</li><br/>
      <li>Visceral Fat Index</li><br/>
      <li>Lean Mass</li><br/>
      <li>Water Mass</li><br/>
    </ul><br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li>Nerve health</li><br/>
  <li>Pulse Wave Velocity</li><br/>
  <li>ECG</li><br/>
 <li>Vascular Age</li><br/>
  <li>Heart Rate</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Connecting via Wi-Fi and Bluetooth, the scale feeds all of this information into the Withings Health Mate app, which connects to Apple Health or Google Fit to provide a comprehensive hub for pretty much everything to do with your body (more on this later). <br/>
<br/>
While the scale measures weight to 0.11 pounds (50g) precision and provides several insightful metrics not seen on other scales, its standout feature is the segmental body composition analysis. This is made possible by a retractable handle that has a series of metal plates on it. When standing on the scale and with the handle held in both hands, the device sends an imperceptible electrical current through your body and analyzes the fat and muscle mass for your torso, arms, and legs independently. The idea here is to spot fat and muscle imbalances so that you can target your efforts on the specific areas of your body that need more work. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/withings-body-scan-packaging.jpg" alt="" width="3992" height="2887" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930389" /><br/>
A similar technique is also used to measure arterial stiffness, by tracking how long it takes for a wave created in the blood as the heart beats to arrive at the foot — a measure Withings calls Pulse Wave Velocity (PWV). The retractable handle also features a 6-lead ECG that, like Apple Watch, can detect AFib, the most common cardiac rhythm disturbance that can cause stroke and heart failure.  <br/>
<br/>
Due to differing clinical regulatory hurdles based on region, there are also a couple of differences between the Body Scan that's sold in the United States and models available in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. version includes an Electrodermal Activity (EDA) Score. This biomarker measures and assesses the activity of the sweat glands in the soles of your feet. According to Withings, the EDA score can provide care teams with insight into a patient's stress levels, diet, and overall health. Meanwhile, the EU version tracks nerve health by providing a Nerve Health Score, which can help to detect signs of peripheral autonomic neuropathies, a damage in small nerves, one of the most prevalent complications of diabetes, and other common chronic conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Design and Performance</h2><br/>
The Body Scan's design is robust and visually inoffensive, combining a sleek striped tempered glass surface with a durable plastic base. However, measuring approximately 12.5 x 14 inches, it's larger and quite a bit heavier than most smart scales. It also lacks non-slip feet on the base, so it's probably not suited to super-smooth flooring. The scale interface also includes a large, vibrant color display that's easy to read from standing height. <br/>
<br/>
The initial setup process of the Body Scan is user-friendly and intuitive enough. After charging the scale via the supplied USB-C cable and downloading the Withings Health Mate app to your phone, pairing the scale is generally straightforward, although this can be subject to the usual challenges of Wi-Fi connectivity, such as signal strength and interference, so make sure you have coverage in your bathroom or wherever you plan to keep it. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/withings-body-scan-scale.jpg" alt="" width="1336" height="852" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930373" /><br/>
To get a Body Scan, you need to stand on the scale barefoot and grip the handle with both hands. This allows the scale to conduct its comprehensive health check, but the duration for a complete scan is around one and a half minutes, so there's some waiting around. If you step off early, you'll still get your weight and some of the other standard biometrics, but things like Pulse Velocity and the segmental body composition analysis will usually fail. Fortunately, the app lets you customize which health metrics are recorded and displayed on the scale's screen, so you can tailor the experience to your own needs.<br/>
<br/>
The scale can support up to eight individual user profiles, making it suitable for family use. However, its user recognition system is not foolproof and may occasionally misidentify the user standing on it, especially if two people in your household have a similar weight. Fortunately, the scale includes a neat solution that usually works – if it's not sure who you are, it will show you each family member's profile as a list, which you can scroll through by balancing on the foot of the direction you wish to scroll.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/withings-body-scan-handle.jpg" alt="" width="1336" height="852" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930374" /><br/>
There are a few other notable features that may be appealing to different members of a household. An eyes-closed mode hides the numbers from the scale screen at weigh-ins, offering motivational messages instead, while a baby mode will give you an accurate weight of your child just by holding them in your arms and stepping on the scale. There's also a pregnancy mode and an athletic mode for tracking health with different measurement algorithms.<br/>
<br/>
All of this is customizable within the app, which is generally well designed and intuitive. It includes a visual 3D map of your segmented body composition (which tells you whether you are in or outside a normal range versus other users like you), trending graphs for several metrics like weight and BMI, and actionable health insights based on your weekly and monthly trends. It also allows you to export a health report PDF for a healthcare specialist or personal trainer. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/withings-mate-app.jpg" alt="" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930380" /><br/>
The app is definitely aiming to be more than just a scale accompaniment, and will also track your physical activity and sleep. It also suggests long-term goals, challenges, and reminders for continuing healthy habits. The optional Withings+ subscription (&#36;10/month) goes further by offering programs and workouts, but unless you are invested in the Withings ecosystem, many of these things can already be achieved with an Apple Watch and Fitness+.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Final Thoughts</h2><br/>
Priced significantly higher than many smart scales in the market, the Withings Body Scan represents a considerable investment over other smart devices. It costs almost double that of Withings' <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FWITHINGS-Body-Comp-Bluetooth-Compatible%2Fdp%2FB0C34ZWCXH%2Fref%3Dsr_1_2%3Fcrid%3D27QSIMMKKSU1C%26keywords%3Dwithings%2Bbody%2Bscan%2Bconnected%2Bhealth%2Bstation%26qid%3D1705069926%26sprefix%3Dwithings%2Bbody%2Bscan%252Caps%252C220%26sr%3D8-2">next most expensive model</a>, but that fairly reflects the depth and breadth of health data it provides. For those readings that I could compare on another smart scale, the Body Scan appeared accurate over time, although it's worth noting that occasionally the fat mass measurements on its body segmentation scan appeared to be unrealistically low, and I had to re-take the scan once or twice to get a correct reading.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, its ability to provide detailed insights into various health aspects should make it particularly appealing to health enthusiasts and anyone closely monitoring specific health conditions. That said, if all you want from a smart scale is something to track your weight and general body composition, there are plenty of other cheaper alternatives out there.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/withings-body-scan-connected-health.jpg" alt="" width="8192" height="4908" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930376" /><br/>
Available on both <a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/WITHINGS-Segmental-Composition-Analysis-Detection/dp/B0C5JP7HN7/ref=sr_1_3?crid=2K2R6ZF63LX1Z&keywords=withings+smart+scan&qid=1705072574&sprefix=withings+smart+scan%2Caps%2C199&sr=8-3&ufe=app_do%3Aamzn1.fos.d7e5a2de-8759-4da3-993c-d11b6e3d217f">Amazon (UK)</a> and the <a href="https://www.withings.com/us/en/body-scan">Withings website</a>, the FDA-cleared Withings Body Scan Connected Health Station is available in a white or black finish, and costs &#36;399.99 (£349.99).  <br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Withings provided MacRumors with a Body Scan scale for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/withings/">Withings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/withings-body-scan-smart-scale-review/">Withings Body Scan Review: High-End Health Monitoring at a High-End Price</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/withings-body-scan-review-high-end-health-monitoring-at-a-high-end-price.2416151/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 Drops to All-Time Low Prices on Amazon, Starting at &#36;329</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-drops-to-all-time-low-prices-on-amazon-starting-at-329.2416150/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:20:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 41mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1RVMT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;329.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;399.00. This is a match of the all-time low price on the wearable, and a deal we haven't tracked since the Black Friday shopping season.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-watch-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928995" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Colors on sale at this price include Pink Aluminum, Midnight Aluminum, Silver Aluminum, and Starlight Aluminum. For every color, you can get both the Sport Loop and Sport Band at this record low price, and some also have multiple band sizes available as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1RVMT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, the 45mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7R7Y7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;359.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;429.00. You'll find many of the same colors and band styles on sale in this larger size, but there are fewer options overall in stock right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7R7Y7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices-2/">Apple Watch Series 9 Drops to All-Time Low Prices on Amazon, Starting at &#36;329</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-drops-to-all-time-low-prices-on-amazon-starting-at-329.2416150/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains How to Get Ready for Vision Pro Pre-Orders Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-vision-pro-preorder-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-to-get-ready-for-vision-pro-pre-orders-next-week.2416146/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:57:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-vision-pro-preorder-tips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided customers in the U.S. with some tips for pre-ordering the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">starting next Friday, January 19</a> at 5 a.m. Pacific Time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
First, Apple says to have an iPhone or iPad with Face ID nearby.<br/>
<br/>
"When you order Apple Vision Pro, you'll need to scan your face with an iPhone or iPad with Face ID," wrote Apple, in an email. "This helps us determine the right size Light Seal and head bands, which work together to give you a precise fit."<br/>
<br/>
Second, make sure your Apple Store app is updated, as the latest version released on January 11 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/vision-pro-apple-store-app-face-scan/">supports Vision Pro face scanning</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Third, Apple says customers with vision correction needs will be required to upload a valid, unexpired prescription from a U.S. eye‑care professional after checkout.<br/>
<br/>
"Because Apple Vision Pro is designed to be worn without glasses, we've partnered with ZEISS to create <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99/">custom optical inserts</a> that accommodate most prescriptions," wrote Apple, with fine print noting that not all prescriptions are supported. "When you order, we'll ask a few quick questions to find out if you need optical inserts. If you do, you'll upload a valid, unexpired prescription from a U.S. eye‑care professional after checkout."<br/>
<br/>
You can <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213226">add and store your vision prescription in the Health app</a> on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
Following pre-orders, the Vision Pro will launch in the U.S. on Friday, February 2. Starting at 8 a.m. local time that day, customers are invited to sign up for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-demos-february-2/">demo of the headset</a> at their local Apple Store, with slots to be available through the weekend on a first-come, first-served basis, according to Apple's email.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro starts at &#36;3,499 in the U.S. with 256GB of storage. For more details about the headset, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-vision-pro-preorder-tips/">Apple Explains How to Get Ready for Vision Pro Pre-Orders Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-to-get-ready-for-vision-pro-pre-orders-next-week.2416146/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook Meets EU Antitrust Chief Ahead of iPhone App Sideloading Deadline</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/tim-cook-meets-eu-antitrust-chief/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-meets-eu-antitrust-chief-ahead-of-iphone-app-sideloading-deadline.2416141/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:10:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/tim-cook-meets-eu-antitrust-chief/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> yesterday met the European Union's antitrust chief, Margrethe Vestager, at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> amid a series of disputes between the organizations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/margrethe-vestager-and-tim-cook.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-930327" /><br/>
The meeting focused on European competition policy and digital regulation. On X (formerly Twitter), Vestager explained that she stressed Apple's impending obligation to allow users to install third-party app stores and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/app-sideloading-support-coming-ios-17/">sideload apps</a> under the Digital Markets Act (DMA). They also spoke about ongoing investigations involving Apple, such as a complaint raised by Spotify against <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, but Vestager declined to provide more specific detail of the discussion.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is facing a range of challenges in the EU, such as a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-could-pay-ireland-eu-tax-dispute/">&#36;14 billion tax dispute</a> and a potential deal to open up the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s NFC technology to payment services from rival companies. Most strikingly, new EU rules such as the DMA designate major tech companies as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/app-store-safari-and-ios-designated-gatekeepers/">gatekeepers</a>" and compel them to open up their various services and platforms to other companies and developers. The DMA is expected to force Apple to make significant changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> work in Europe. For example, Apple will be obliged to give developers the ability to promote their offers outside the ‌‌‌&zwnj;App Store&zwnj;‌‌‌ and use third-party payment systems.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/tim-cook-meets-eu-antitrust-chief/">Tim Cook Meets EU Antitrust Chief Ahead of iPhone App Sideloading Deadline</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-meets-eu-antitrust-chief-ahead-of-iphone-app-sideloading-deadline.2416141/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Clarifies How Many Items Can Be Tracked in Find My</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/apple-clarifies-find-my-items-limit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-clarifies-how-many-items-can-be-tracked-in-find-my.2416113/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:25:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/apple-clarifies-find-my-items-limit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Find My</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today confirmed that up to 32 items can be added to the Find My app on the iPhone and iPad, up from a previous limit of 16.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/Find-My-AirPods-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-811280" /><br/>
Apple revealed this information in a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211331">support document</a> updated today:<blockquote>You can add up to 32 items in Find My. In addition to AirTag and the third-party Find My network accessories in the Items tab, AirPods Max count as one item, AirPods and AirPods Pro (1st generation) count as two items, and AirPods Pro (2nd generation) count as three items.</blockquote>We confirmed that Apple increased the item limit starting with iOS 16 and iPadOS 16, but the change was not reflected on Apple's website until now.<br/>
<br/>
Items that count towards the limit include AirTags, AirPods, newer MagSafe Wallets, select Beats headphones, third-party accessories with Find My support, and more, according to Apple. Once the items are added to the app, users can track the location of each one on a map across the iPhone, iPad, and Mac.<br/>
<br/>
Some models of AirPods are considered multiple items due to each individual earbud and charging case being counted separately.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/nicolas09F9/status/1745554500562174110">Nicolás Álvarez</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/apple-clarifies-find-my-items-limit/">Apple Clarifies How Many Items Can Be Tracked in Find My</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-clarifies-how-many-items-can-be-tracked-in-find-my.2416113/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Satechi Debuts Thunderbolt 4 Hub, 145W USB-C Charger and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/ces-2024-satechi-thunderbolt-hub/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-satechi-debuts-thunderbolt-4-hub-145w-usb-c-charger-and-more.2416106/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:49:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/ces-2024-satechi-thunderbolt-hub/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Satechi</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-satechi-qi2-chargers/">Qi2 wireless charging stands</a>, Apple accessory maker Satechi this week unveiled new hubs and charger options for Apple's Mac lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/satechi-stand-and-hub-for-mac-studio.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930279" /><br/>
The upgraded Stand & Hub for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> fits under one of Apple's slim desktop machines, and it includes an NVMe SSD enclosure that supports NVMe and M.2 SATA SSDs. There are USB-C 3.1 and USB-A 3.1 ports for file transfers, with support for speeds up to 10Gb/s.<br/>
<br/>
An SSD added into the hub can be used for Time Machine backups, plus there are also two additional USB-A 3.0 ports, micro/SD card readers, and an audio jack for headphones.<br/>
<br/>
Satechi's Thunderbolt 4 Slim Hub Pro has three Thunderbolt 4 downstream ports that support data transfers at up to 40GB/s, plus it can deliver up to 15W of power to connected peripherals. It supports up to two 4K displays or one 8K display, and it offers 32Gb/s native PCIe support for external GPUs and Thunderbolt-based SSDs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/satechi-thunderbolt-4-slim-hub-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930280" /><br/>
The 145W USB-C 4-Port GaN Travel Charger has two USB-C 3.1 ports that can provide up to 140W and two USB-C 3.0 ports that can provide up to 45W. The 145W max power is split between devices when more than one device is plugged in, with the charger providing smart power distribution that automatically adjusts wattage for optimal charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/satechi-145w-travel-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930282" /><br/>
All three devices are available today from the Satechi website. The <a href="https://satechi.net/products/stand-hub-for-mac-mini-studio-with-nvme-ssd-enclosure">Stand & Hub for Mac mini/Mac Studio</a> is priced at &#36;100, the <a href="https://satechi.net/products/thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station">Thunderbolt 4 Slim Hub Pro</a> is &#36;200, and the <a href="https://satechi.net/products/145w-usb-c-4-port-gan-travel-charger">145W Travel Charger</a> is &#36;120. A 20 percent discount is available with the promo code CES20.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/satechi/">Satechi</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/ces-2024-satechi-thunderbolt-hub/">CES 2024: Satechi Debuts Thunderbolt 4 Hub, 145W USB-C Charger and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-satechi-debuts-thunderbolt-4-hub-145w-usb-c-charger-and-more.2416106/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
