<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 20:03:05 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Special AirPods Pro and More for Year of the Dragon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-pro-year-of-dragon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-special-airpods-pro-and-more-for-year-of-the-dragon.2416659/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 18:44:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-pro-year-of-dragon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In celebration of the upcoming Lunar New Year on February 10, Apple has released limited-edition second-generation AirPods Pro with a Year of the Dragon engraving on its online store in <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/shop/product/MW4F3CH/A">China</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/shop/product/MW4F3ZP/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Hong Kong</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/tw/shop/product/MW4F3TA/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Taiwan</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/sg/shop/product/MW4F3ZA/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Singapore</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/vn/shop/product/MW4F3ZP/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Vietnam</a>, and Macao. They are also available in <a href="https://www.apple.com/kr/shop/product/MW4F3KH/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">South Korea</a>, where it is the Year of the Blue Dragon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/AirPods-Pro-Year-of-the-Dragon.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931451" /><br/>
The special AirPods Pro have a dragon engraving on the USB-C charging case, and there is a red dragon printed on the box they come in. Otherwise, these AirPods Pro are unchanged in terms of features and pricing compared to the regular ones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has previously offered limited-edition AirPods Pro in some Asian countries for the Year of the Ox, Year of the Tiger, and Year of the Rabbit.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also shared a <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/store">Chinese New Year gift guide</a> in the countries and regions listed above, along with Malaysia. As we previously reported, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">offering limited-time savings</a> on a variety of products in China from January 18 through January 21.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Year-of-the-Dragon-Wallpaper.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931455" /><br/>
From January 18 through February 13, free <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/en/today/collection/create-new-year-magic/">Today at Apple sessions with a Lunar New Year theme</a> will be held in some countries, as spotted by Michael Steeber, who publishes the <a href="https://michaelsteeber.substack.com/">Apple retail newsletter Tabletops</a>. He also noted there are <a href="https://weibo.com/6045623381/4991142772875767">window decals</a> celebrating the Lunar New Year at select Apple Stores in Asia, along with a Year of the Dragon wallpaper available for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/store">on Apple's website in Hong Kong</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S. and many other countries, Apple is selling <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/accessories/all/new-arrivals?page=1&s=newest">Year of the Dragon accessories</a> from OtterBox and Mophie on its online store, including iPhone cases, an AirTag holder, and a battery pack, as spotted by <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/17/iphone-airtag-year-of-the-dragon/"><em>9to5Mac</em>'s Zac Hall</a>. Apple is also releasing <a href="https://twitter.com/beatsbydre/status/1747807917951373449">limited-edition Beats Solo3 Wireless headphones</a> with a red-and-gold color scheme.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently offered a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/">limited-edition AirTag</a> with a Year of the Dragon engraving in Japan, in celebration of the Japanese New Year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-pro-year-of-dragon/">Apple Releases Special AirPods Pro and More for Year of the Dragon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-special-airpods-pro-and-more-for-year-of-the-dragon.2416659/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Sell Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen Feature in U.S. Starting Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-sell-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches-without-blood-oxygen-feature-in-u-s-starting-tomorrow.2416657/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 18:12:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models will be sold without the Blood Oxygen feature in the U.S. starting on January 18, according to <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen-sensor/"><em>9to5Mac</em>'s Chance Miller</a>, allowing Apple to avoid a sales ban on these models. On its online store in the U.S., this change will occur starting at 6 a.m. Pacific Time tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-watch-series-6-blood-oxygen-monitoring-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-759072" /><br/>
The report says these Apple Watch models will still include the Blood Oxygen app, but when a user opens it, they will be presented with an alert saying that the app is no longer available, and directed to the Health app on the iPhone. Apple plans to share more details in a support document that will be published on its website.<br/>
<br/>
Apple confirmed that the Blood Oxygen app will remain functional on previously-sold Series 9 and Ultra 2 models. The feature will also remain available on Apple Watch models sold outside the U.S., as the sales ban does not apply internationally.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered an import and sales ban</a> on Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents with the feature, first introduced on the Series 6 model in 2020. Masimo has accused Apple of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/18/apple-masimo-legal-battle/">stealing trade secrets and poaching employees</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The sales ban first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">began last month</a>, but it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">quickly paused</a>, as Apple received an interim stay. Apple was denied a longer-term stay, however, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">ban is set to be reinstated</a> tomorrow starting at 2 p.m. Pacific Time. In a statement, Apple said it disabled the blood oxygen sensing feature on new U.S. models to comply with the ruling and ensure that customers have access to the Apple Watch with limited disruption.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's appeal is ongoing. The company said it strongly disagrees with the ITC's decision, and it feels the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit should reverse it. As a longer-term solution, Apple is reportedly working on changes to the Blood Oxygen app's algorithm in an attempt to avoid Masimo's patented technology. It's unclear when those changes will be ready, or if they will be enough for Apple to avoid patent infringement.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/">Apple to Sell Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen Feature in U.S. Starting Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-sell-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches-without-blood-oxygen-feature-in-u-s-starting-tomorrow.2416657/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Won&#039;t Offer Apple Vision Pro App at Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-wont-offer-apple-vision-pro-app-at-launch.2416642/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 14:19:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix has no plans to release an app for Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-17/watching-netflix-on-apple-vision-pro-you-ll-have-to-use-the-web"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Instead, the streaming service will be accessible through Safari and other web browsers on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Vision-Pro-Living-Room.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931385" /><br/>
"Our members will be able to enjoy Netflix on the web browser on the Vision Pro, similar to how our members can enjoy Netflix on Macs," a Netflix spokesperson told Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-07-23/apple-vision-pro-will-developers-sell-visionos-apps-for-the-3-499-device-lkfg5b1l">July 2023 edition</a> of his <em>Power On</em> newsletter, Gurman said Netflix would "still let its iPad app run on the headset unmodified," but he now says the streaming service will not offer an app of any kind on the Vision Pro at launch. Apple makes it easy for developers to port their iPadOS apps to visionOS, with over one million apps to be available on the Vision Pro's App Store at launch, but Netflix has evidently opted out.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-streaming-services-and-sports-apps/">various video and sports apps</a> that will be available on the Vision Pro at launch, including Disney+, Discovery+, Max, Amazon Prime Video, Paramount+, Peacock, ESPN, MLB, and more. There is also MLS Season Pass in the Apple TV app.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro pre-orders begin Friday in the U.S., and the headset launches February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/">Netflix Won&#039;t Offer Apple Vision Pro App at Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-wont-offer-apple-vision-pro-app-at-launch.2416642/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Sales Ban Reinstated in U.S. Effective Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated-in-u-s-effective-tomorrow.2416628/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 11:41:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's motion to stay an Apple Watch sales ban for the duration of its appeal was denied today by the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit, according to a <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/699619677/Federal-Circuit-Denies-Apple-Motion-to-Stay">court document</a> viewed by <em>MacRumors</em>. Apple's interim stay will be lifted as of January 18 at 2 p.m. Pacific Time, the filing indicates, meaning the sales ban will be reinstated tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
The order means that Apple will once again no longer be able to sell Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing in the U.S., including the Series 9 and Ultra 2. The ban <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">first began last month</a>, but it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">quickly paused</a> after Apple received an interim stay.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. International Trade Commission last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered the import and sales ban</a> after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents with the Apple Watch's blood oxygen sensing feature, first introduced on the Series 6 model in 2020. Masimo has accused Apple of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/18/apple-masimo-legal-battle/">stealing trade secrets and poaching employees</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely sell modified Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-app-removal/">without the Blood Oxygen app</a> in the U.S. to sidestep the sales ban, while it continues to appeal.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple's claim that its redesigned watch does not contain pulse oximetry is a positive step toward accountability," a Masimo spokesperson told <em>MacRumors</em>. "It is especially important that one of the world's largest and most powerful companies respects the intellectual property rights of smaller companies and complies with ITC orders when it is caught infringing."<br/>
<br/>
As a longer-term measure, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-15/apple-to-remove-watch-blood-oxygen-app-to-avoid-ban-masimo-says"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> recently reported that Apple is preparing a software update that would adjust the Blood Oxygen app's algorithms, in an attempt to avoid Masimo's patented technology. It's unclear if this effort will be successful, and the legal battle between Apple and Masimo is likely far from over.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> In a <a href="https://www.masimo.com/company/news/news-media/#Masimo_Announces_Reinstatement_of_Import_Ban_on_Infringing_Apple_Watches">press release</a>, Masimo CEO Joe Kiani shared the following statement in response to Apple's motion for stay being denied.<br/>
<br/>
"The Federal Circuit's decision to lift the temporary stay is a victory for the integrity of the American patent system and the safety of people relying on pulse oximetry," said Kiani. "It affirms that even the largest and most powerful companies must respect the intellectual rights of American inventors and must deal with the consequences when they are caught infringing others' patents."<br/>
<br/>
Masimo said it previously released a study showing that the Apple Watch's blood oxygen sensing feature "missed over 90% of potentially life-threatening events," while touting the effectiveness of its own Masimo W1 health watch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">Apple Watch Sales Ban Reinstated in U.S. Effective Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated-in-u-s-effective-tomorrow.2416628/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Updated Firmware for AirPods 3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-3-firmware-6a321/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-updated-firmware-for-airpods-3.2416625/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 11:24:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-3-firmware-6a321/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced a new firmware update for the third-generation AirPods. The new firmware is version 6A321, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/19/apple-airpods-3-firmware-update-december/">6A317 firmware</a> introduced in December.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airpods-3-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917911" /><br/>
Apple's AirPods firmware updates often do not come with details on new features, so it is unclear what might be included in the software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also does not offer instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌AirPods‌‌ or ‌‌‌‌‌‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>‌‌‌‌‌‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the AirPods firmware release, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-3-firmware-6a321/">Apple Releases Updated Firmware for AirPods 3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-updated-firmware-for-airpods-3.2416625/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Pay iPhone 7 Users in U.S. Who Experienced &#039;Loop Disease&#039; Audio Issues</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-settlement-iphone-7-audio-issues/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-pay-iphone-7-users-in-u-s-who-experienced-loop-disease-audio-issues.2416622/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 11:06:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-settlement-iphone-7-audio-issues/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last year agreed to pay &#36;35 million to settle a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/01/31/iphone-7-loop-disease-lawsuit-narrowed-proceeds/">U.S. class action lawsuit</a> alleging that the iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus were prone to audio issues due to a defective chip in the devices, and it has now started notifying eligible customers by email.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-7-Plus-Jet-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931342" /><br/>
You may be eligible for a payment from Apple if you are a U.S. resident who owned an iPhone 7 or iPhone 7 Plus between September 16, 2016 and January 3, 2023, and reported audio issues covered by the settlement to Apple, and/or paid Apple out of pocket to have your iPhone repaired or replaced as a result of the covered audio issues.<br/>
<br/>
Those who did not receive a notice, but believe they are eligible to submit a claim, are instructed to email info@smartphoneaudiosettlement.com.<br/>
<br/>
The deadline to select a payment method, object to the settlement, or opt out is June 3, with more details available on the <a href="https://smartphoneaudiosettlement.com/">settlement notice website</a>. Those who paid Apple out of pocket could receive up to &#36;349, while others could get up to &#36;125, according to the proposed settlement, which requires approval by a California court on July 18.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/05/07/apple-class-action-lawsuits-iphone-7-audio-issues/">sued over the issue</a> in multiple U.S. states in 2019, with the complaints alleging that the company violated consumer protection laws and breached warranties. Despite agreeing to a settlement, Apple has denied any wrongdoing, and the court hearing the class action has not ruled in favor of Apple or the plaintiffs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>"Loop Disease"</h2><br/>
In an internal document, obtained by <em>MacRumors</em> in May 2018, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/05/04/apple-aware-of-iphone-7-mic-issue-ios-11-3/">acknowledged a microphone issue affecting some iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus models</a>:<blockquote>Some customers might report that after they've updated to iOS 11.3, the microphone on their iPhone 7 or iPhone 7 Plus doesn't work and the speaker button is grayed out when they make or receive a call.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Symptoms:</strong><br/>
- The speaker button is grayed out during calls<br/>
- Other people are unable to hear the customer on cellular or FaceTime calls<br/>
- If a customer plays back a video or voice memo that they've made after installing iOS 11.3, there is no sound</blockquote>The alleged defect is informally known as "Loop Disease" online. Despite acknowledging the issue internally, Apple never posted a service program about the issue on its website, and it never responded to our repeated requests for comment.<br/>
<br/>
As far as an underlying cause, the class action lawsuit alleged that "the materials used in the ‌iPhone‌'s external casing are insufficient and inadequate to protect the internal parts," eventually resulting in the audio chip losing electrical contact with the logic board due to "flexion" of the device's external casing during regular use. It's unclear how many iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus units were affected in total.<br/>
<br/>
Apple initially said its service providers could request a "warranty exception" for affected iPhones, which resulted in free repairs for at least some customers, but that abruptly ended in July 2018 after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/07/17/apple-ends-free-oow-iphone-7-mic-repairs/">Apple deleted the document</a>. Afterwards, some customers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/12/17/iphone-7-microphone-defect/">had to pay an out-of-warranty fee of around &#36;300</a> in the U.S. for a fix.<br/>
<br/>
If the settlement is approved, those customers will finally be able to get at least some of their money back from Apple after years of silence.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/mbrkhrdt">Michael Burkhardt</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-settlement-iphone-7-audio-issues/">Apple to Pay iPhone 7 Users in U.S. Who Experienced &#039;Loop Disease&#039; Audio Issues</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-pay-iphone-7-users-in-u-s-who-experienced-loop-disease-audio-issues.2416622/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.3 Allows iPhones to Connect to Some Hotel Room TVs via AirPlay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-allows-iphones-to-connect-to-some-hotel-room-tvs-via-airplay.2416617/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:19:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-release-candidate/">full release notes for iOS 17.3</a>, which will be released to the public <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/">next week</a>. The notes reveal that iOS 17.3 allows the iPhone to connect to select hotel room TVs via AirPlay, but details remain slim for now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airplay-hotels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898340" /><br/>
"AirPlay hotel support lets you stream content directly to the TV in your room in select hotels," the notes say for the iOS 17.3 Release Candidate.<br/>
<br/>
The feature allows iPhone users to scan a QR code on a supported hotel room TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing them to wirelessly stream videos, photos, and music from their iPhone to the TV. Google already offers a similar feature on some hotel TVs, allowing guests to stream content from their smartphone via Chromecast.<br/>
<br/>
In June 2023, Apple said Holiday Inn parent company IHG Hotels & Resorts planned to adopt the feature, but exact availability is unknown. LG previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/22/lg-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">announced</a> that it would be one of the first hotel room TV manufacturers to support the feature.<br/>
<br/>
Apple originally said the feature would launch last year, but it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-delays-airplay-in-hotel-rooms/">delayed until 2024</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">iOS 17.3 Allows iPhones to Connect to Some Hotel Room TVs via AirPlay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-allows-iphones-to-connect-to-some-hotel-room-tvs-via-airplay.2416617/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 Release Candidates</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-release-candidates.2416607/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:05:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate versions of upcoming iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 updates to developers and public beta testers, with the updates available a week after the release of the third <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-ios-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/">iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3 introduces a Stolen Device Protection feature that limits access to your private information in case someone obtains both your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and your passcode. When activated, it requires <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> identity verification to do things like accessing passwords in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, turning off Lost Mode, making purchases through Safari with saved payment credentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
There are also features that require verification <em>and</em> have a one-hour delay to access, such as changing an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; passcode, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; passcode, turning off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, and turning off &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;. More details can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-stolen-device-protection-feature/">found in our article on Stolen Device Protection</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The update also adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-collaborative-playlists-2024/">collaborative Apple Music playlists</a>, a feature that lets <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers share playlists with others to build shared song lists. Collaborative playlists are simple to use, can be shared with a link, and support emoji reactions.<br/>
<br/>
Finally, the update adds a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">new Unity Bloom wallpaper</a> for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Release candidate builds of iOS 16.7.5, iPadOS 16.7.5, iOS 15.8.1, iPadOS 15.8.1 with security fixes for older devices are also available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple today said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/">iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 will be released next week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Full release notes for iOS 17.3 are below:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote><b>Stolen Device Protection</b><br/>
- Stolen Device Protection increases security of iPhone and Apple ID by requiring Face ID or Touch ID with no passcode fallback to perform certain actions<br/>
- Security Delay requires Face ID or Touch ID, an hour wait, and then an additional successful biometric authentication before sensitive operations like changing device passcode or Apple ID password can be performed<br/>
<br/>
<b>Lock Screen</b><br/>
- New Unity wallpaper honors Black history and culture in celebration of Black History Month<br/>
<br/>
<b>Music</b><br/>
- Collaborate on playlists allows you to invite friends to join your playlist and everyone can add, reorder, and remove songs<br/>
- Emoji reactions can be added to any track in a collaborative playlist<br/>
<br/>
<b>This update also includes the following improvements:</b><br/>
- AirPlay hotel support lets you stream content directly to the TV in your room in select hotels<br/>
- AppleCare & Warranty in Settings shows your coverage for all devices signed in with your Apple ID<br/>
- Crash detection optimizations (all iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 models)</blockquote><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 Release Candidates</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-release-candidates.2416607/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Release Candidate Version of macOS Sonoma 14.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/macos-sonoma-14-3-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-version-of-macos-sonoma-14-3.2416611/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:04:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/macos-sonoma-14-3-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded a release candidate version of the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3 update to developers and public beta testers, with the software coming a week after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-beta-3/">third macOS Sonoma 14.3 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
Release candidate versions of macOS 13.6.4 and macOS 12.7.3 with security fixes are also available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to release &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 to the public next week.<br/>
<br/>
Full release notes are below:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>macOS Sonoma 14.3 introduces enhancements to Apple Music, as well as other features, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
-  Collaborate on playlists in Apple Music allows you to invite friends to join your playlist and everyone can add, reorder, and remove songs<br/>
-  Emoji reactions can be added to any track in a collaborative playlist in Apple Music<br/>
-  AppleCare & Warranty in Settings shows your coverage for all devices signed in with your Apple ID</blockquote><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/macos-sonoma-14-3-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds Release Candidate Version of macOS Sonoma 14.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-version-of-macos-sonoma-14-3.2416611/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Release Candidate Version of watchOS 10.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/watchos-10-3-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-version-of-watchos-10-3.2416615/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:03:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/watchos-10-3-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of the upcoming watchOS 10.3 update to developers and public beta testers, with the beta coming a week after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-3-beta-3-to-developers/">third watchOS 10.3 beta</a>. The release candidate represents the final version of watchOS 10.3 that will be provided to the public next week when watchOS 10.3 launches. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.3‌ update, developers will need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.3 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
There's no word yet on the new features that might be included in watchOS 10.3 beyond a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">Unity Bloom watch face</a>, and no notable new features were found during the beta testing process.<br/>
<br/>
Full release notes are below:<blockquote>watchOS 10.3 includes new features, improvements, and bug fixes, including new Unity Bloom watch face to honor Black history and culture in celebration of Black History Month.</blockquote><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/watchos-10-3-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds Release Candidate Version of watchOS 10.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-version-of-watchos-10-3.2416615/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds tvOS 17.3 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/tvos-17-3-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-release-candidate.2416614/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:02:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/tvos-17-3-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of the upcoming tvOS 17.3 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/">third tvOS 17.3 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.3 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.3.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing. tvOS 17.3 is set to be released next week.<br/>
<br/>
A related <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> software version 17.3 release candidate has also been seeded with unspecified performance and stability improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS and &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/tvos-17-3-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds tvOS 17.3 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-release-candidate.2416614/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Launches New Galaxy S24 Smartphone Lineup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/samsung-launches-galaxy-s24-lineup/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-launches-new-galaxy-s24-smartphone-lineup.2416606/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/samsung-launches-galaxy-s24-lineup/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung today announced the launch of the <a href="https://howl.me/clq3B9tsWBC">Galaxy S24, Galaxy S24+,</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/clq3B9BlD1H">Galaxy S24 Ultra</a>, its new flagship smartphones that are designed to compete with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KnX97AFTMV4" title="Samsung Galaxy S24 First Impressions: SO MUCH AI" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Artificial intelligence is the focus of Samsung's new S24 devices, with all three offering Galaxy AI. Galaxy AI supports Live Translate for two-way real-time voice and text translation in phone calls, and an Interpreter function translates live conversations on a split-view so two people can converse in different languages.<br/>
<br/>
Chat Assist can help users perfect conversational tones, and AI built into the Samsung Keyboard can translate messages in real-time in 13 languages. Android Auto is able to summarize incoming messages and suggest relevant replies, Transcript Assist uses AI to transcribe, summarize, and translate recordings, and a Note Assist feature in Samsung Notes offers AI-generated summaries and templates. Samsung also partnered with Google to offer "Circle to Search," an option that lets S24 users circle, highlight, scribble on, or tap items on the S24 display to see search results.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-ultra-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931229" /><br/>
Samsung's high-end Galaxy S24 Ultra pairs AI with camera improvements. Samsung has done away with its 10x zoom lens, opting instead for a Quad Tele System with a 50-megapixel 5x optical zoom lens, which is the optical zoom level that Apple settled on.<br/>
<br/>
The S24 Ultra has a larger pixel size and an improved optical image stabilization system to cut down on hand-shake for reduced blur, plus the ProVisual Engine AI system allows for enhanced digital zoom, more light capture in dim conditions, and better noise reduction when recording video. Galaxy AI editing tools allow for edits like erase, recompose, and remaster, and Edit Suggestions suggests tweaks for each photo. Generative Edit can fill in parts of an image background with generative AI when removing an object or correcting a crooked image.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-ultra-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931230" /><br/>
The Galaxy S24 Ultra is equipped with Qualcomm's Snapdragon Gen 3 Mobile Platform, which Samsung says has been optimized for AI processing and requires enhanced thermal control. All three models support 1 to 120Hz adaptive refresh rates for the displays, with the Ultra offering the brightest Galaxy display to date at 2,600 nits peak brightness. Samsung is using Corning's Gorilla Armor for improved durability and scratch resistance on the Ultra, along with reduced reflection. Like Apple's A17 Pro, Samsung's latest chips support ray tracing for gaming.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung tweaked the design of the Ultra and it now offers a 6.8-inch flat display that's optimized for viewing, while the Galaxy S24 now measures in at 6.2 inches and the S24+ measures in at 6.7 inches. The screen size enhancements have been made through reductions in bezel size to keep the device size about the same.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-ultra-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931231" /><br/>
Samsung copied Apple's &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; lineup and the S24 Ultra is available with a titanium frame in gray, black, violet, yellow, green, blue, and orange.<br/>
<br/>
The Galaxy S24 Ultra is priced starting at &#36;1,300, the S24+ is priced starting at &#36;1,000, and the S24 is priced starting at &#36;800.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's Galaxy S24 lineup is available for pre-order as of today, and Samsung is offering several deals. For <a href="https://howl.me/clq3B9BlD1H">the S24 Ultra</a>, customers can get up to &#36;750 off with a trade-in, along with an exclusive &#36;50 Samsung credit, a free storage upgrade (doubling storage at no cost), and a &#36;100 eCertificate, plus students can get a 15 percent discount.<br/>
<br/>
For <a href="https://howl.me/clq3B9tsWBC">the S24+</a>, up to a &#36;650 trade-in credit is available with a &#36;50 Samsung credit, storage upgrade, &#36;75 eCertificate, and a 7.5 percent student discount. For <a href="https://howl.me/clq3B9tsWBC">the S24</a>, up to a &#36;550 trade-in credit is available, along with a &#36;50 Samsung credit, a storage upgrade, a &#36;25 eCertificate, and a five percent discount for students.<br/>
<br/>
Customers can also receive 20 percent off Samsung Care+ with Theft and Loss with the purchase of any Galaxy S24 series device.<br/>
<br/>
Best Buy is offering <a href="https://howl.me/clq3B9psIXM">up to &#36;870 off</a> the S24 series with trade-in and pre-order, with a storage upgrade and up to a &#36;150 Best Buy gift card.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung and Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/samsung-launches-galaxy-s24-lineup/">Samsung Launches New Galaxy S24 Smartphone Lineup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-launches-new-galaxy-s24-smartphone-lineup.2416606/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Again Leads in Smartphone Resale Value With iPhone 15</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-leads-in-smartphone-resale-value/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-again-leads-in-smartphone-resale-value-with-iphone-15.2416601/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:03:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-leads-in-smartphone-resale-value/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>SellCell</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup sets a new standard in value retention, outperforming its predecessors and leading the pack among 2023 flagship smartphones, a new report finds.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.sellcell.com/blog/smartphone-depreciation-report-2023/">New data from SellCell</a>, an aggregator of buyback prices from over 40 vendors, reveals that the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; range, particularly the 256GB Pro Max model, is depreciating at a notably slower rate compared to other flagship models released in 2023, including those from Samsung, Google, and OnePlus.<br/>
<br/>
Since its launch, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; series has shown strong market value resilience. Initially, the range experienced an average depreciation of 28.8% in the first month. Intriguingly, this figure improved to 27.1% in the second month, indicating a regained value before a slight rise to 27.9% in the third month. Currently, the series stands at a depreciation of 27.4%, underscoring a trend of consistent value retention.<br/>
<br/>
In comparison, Samsung's Galaxy S23 series was unable to match Apple's value retention. The S23 range saw a depreciation of 42.4% by the end of the first month, 43.5% in the second, and 44.5% by the third. This sequence highlights a much more significant drop in value than Apple's rival smartphone series, but it does represent a slight improvement over the company's previous S22 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
The OnePlus 11 series demonstrated a depreciation of 51.5% after two months, recovering to 48.5% in the third month. Google's Pixel 8 range struggled more significantly, with the flagship 1TB Pixel 8 Pro model losing 68.1% of its value in the first month and maintaining this level in the subsequent months.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; range is also noticeably stronger in value retention compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>. Apple's latest devices are depreciating up to 11% less across all models, averaging a 5% better value retention than the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; range in the same post-launch period. Specifically, the 256GB &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus model shows a remarkable depreciation of only 11.3% less than its &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; equivalent.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, the data reinforces the longstanding trend of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> being the best smartphone for value retention and there are indications that this may even be improving further generation-over-generation. Buyers continue to be better off buying an Apple device if resale or trade-in is an essential future prospect.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sellcell/">SellCell</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-leads-in-smartphone-resale-value/">Apple Again Leads in Smartphone Resale Value With iPhone 15</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-again-leads-in-smartphone-resale-value-with-iphone-15.2416601/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Silicon Security Flaw Discovered in iPhone 12 and M2 MacBook Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-silicon-security-flaw-discovered/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-silicon-security-flaw-discovered-in-iphone-12-and-m2-macbook-air.2416595/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:39:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-silicon-security-flaw-discovered/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A security vulnerability that could allow attackers to access sensitive data has been discovered in some Apple silicon GPUs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/a14-bionic-chip-video.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="875" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-764500" /><br/>
A <a href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2024/01/16/leftoverlocals-listening-to-llm-responses-through-leaked-gpu-local-memory/">recent investigation</a> by cybersecurity firm Trail of Bits discovered the security flaw, named "LeftoverLocals," which allows attackers with local access to a device to retrieve data processed in the GPU's local memory. The issue is particularly concerning because of the expanding use of GPUs in processing Large Language Models (LLMs) for AI applications.<br/>
<br/>
According to the firm, the vulnerability enables an attacker to eavesdrop on another user's interactive LLM session, potentially accessing sensitive information. Apple told <em><a href="https://www.wired.com/story/leftoverlocals-gpu-vulnerability-generative-ai/">Wired</a></em> that newer devices with the A17 Pro and M3 chips have received patches to address this flaw, and Trail of Bits found that the third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> had also received a fix.<br/>
<br/>
Most older models with vulnerable GPUs, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, are still vulnerable. While Apple has taken steps to patch certain devices, it remains unclear if and when all impacted models will receive security updates to directly address the problem. <br/>
<br/>
The nature of the LeftoverLocals vulnerability is such that it requires physical access to the device, making remote exploitation highly improbable. As always, Apple encourages users to install the latest available software update to ensure they receive security fixes.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-silicon-security-flaw-discovered/">Apple Silicon Security Flaw Discovered in iPhone 12 and M2 MacBook Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-silicon-security-flaw-discovered-in-iphone-12-and-m2-macbook-air.2416595/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Ultra 2 Model for &#36;749 (&#36;50 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/amazon-apple-watch-ultra-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-ultra-2-model-for-749-50-off.2416591/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:00:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/amazon-apple-watch-ultra-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon has nearly every model of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;749.00</strong></a> today, down from &#36;799.00. You'll find all band options on sale at this price, including Trail Loop, Ocean Band, and Alpine Loop.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9-and-Ultra-2-Deals-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913209" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can find the full list of Apple Watch Ultra 2 models on sale below, with the Alpine Loop and Trail Loop getting the most discounts this time around. Most of the wearables are in stock on Amazon and can be delivered between January 21 and January 22, although a few won't be delivered until later in the month.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Compared to past sales, this deal is a solid second-best price on the Apple Watch Ultra 2, and it continues to be the best deal we've tracked so far on the watch in 2024. Because we're unlikely to see those record low holiday discounts come back any time soon, we recommend purchasing now if you've been waiting.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Indigo Alpine Loop (Small)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Indigo Alpine Loop (Medium)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYVS23%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Indigo Alpine Loop (Large)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXC7YJ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Olive Alpine Loop (Small)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX779JN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Olive Alpine Loop (Medium)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9N594%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Blue Alpine Loop (Medium)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX6XK6V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">White Ocean Band</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXC3DTX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Orange Ocean Band</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9G1VB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Orange/Beige Trail Loop (M/L)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Green/Gray Trail Loop (S/M)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3VVKS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Green/Gray Trail Loop (M/L)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FRH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Blue/Black Trail Loop (S/M)</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7C4CL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Blue/Black Trail Loop (M/L)</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has a few extra Apple Watch deals worth noting, including the Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2F5NJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.00</strong></a> (&#36;50 off) and the Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1RVMT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;329.00</strong></a> (&#36;70 off). Both of these are all-time low prices on each wearable.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/amazon-apple-watch-ultra-2/">Amazon Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Ultra 2 Model for &#36;749 (&#36;50 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-ultra-2-model-for-749-50-off.2416591/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releasing iOS 17.3 Next Week With These New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week-with-these-new-features.2416586/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:21:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In its press release <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">unveiling a new Black Unity Sport Band</a> for the Apple Watch, Apple confirmed that iOS 17.3 will be released next week. The software update will likely be available on Monday, January 22 or Tuesday, January 23.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" /><br/>
Apple's confirmation that iOS 17.3 will be released next week:<blockquote>The new Unity Bloom iPhone and iPad wallpaper for the Lock Screen will be also be available next week, and requires iPhone Xs or later running iOS 17.3 and iPad (6th generation and later), iPad mini (5th generation and later), iPad Air (3rd generation and later), 12.9-inch iPad Pro (2nd generation and later), 10.5-inch iPad Pro, and 11-inch iPad Pro (1st generation and later) running iPadOS 17.3.</blockquote>New features and changes for the iPhone in iOS 17.3 include Stolen Device Protection, collaborative Apple Music playlists, and a Unity Bloom wallpaper for the Lock Screen. More details about these additions are outlined below.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ios-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926120" /><br/>
Earlier this year, <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> reported about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/19/apple-responds-to-iphone-theft-recovery-key-report/">thieves spying on an iPhone user's passcode</a> before stealing the device, often in public places like bars. With knowledge of the passcode, the thief can then change the victim's Apple ID password, turn off Find My, and more to gain full control of the device. The thief can also use the passcode to gain access to passwords stored in iCloud Keychain and other sensitive information.<br/>
<br/>
Stolen Device Protection is Apple's hopeful solution to the problem. Apple says the feature is designed to add an additional layer of security in the event someone has stolen your iPhone and also obtained the device's passcode.<br/>
<br/>
When the feature is turned on, Face ID or Touch ID authentication is strictly required for the following actions, with a passcode fallback no longer available:<ul><li>Accessing passwords or passkeys saved in iCloud Keychain</li><br/>
<li>Applying for a new Apple Card or viewing an Apple Card's virtual number</li><br/>
<li>Turning off Lost Mode</li><br/>
<li>Erasing all content and settings</li><br/>
<li>Taking certain Apple Cash and Apple Card Savings actions in the Wallet app</li><br/>
<li>Using payment methods saved in Safari</li><br/>
<li>Using your iPhone to set up a new device</li></ul>For especially sensitive actions, including changing the password of the Apple ID account associated with the iPhone, the feature adds a one-hour security delay on top of biometric authentication. In these cases, the user must authenticate with Face ID or Touch ID, wait one hour, and authenticate with Face ID or Touch ID again. However, Apple says there is no delay when the iPhone is in familiar locations, such as at home or work.<br/>
<br/>
Actions that require Face ID or Touch ID authentication, and have a one-hour security delay, when the feature is turned on:<ul><li>Changing your Apple ID password</li><br/>
<li>Updating select Apple ID security settings, including adding or removing a trusted device, trusted phone number, Recovery Key, or Recovery Contact</li><br/>
<li>Changing your iPhone passcode</li><br/>
<li>Adding or removing Face ID or Touch ID</li><br/>
<li>Turning off Find My</li><br/>
<li>Turning off Stolen Device Protection</li></ul>Stolen Device Protection is an opt-in feature that can be found in the Settings app under Face ID & Passcode, and it is available for all iPhones that are compatible with iOS 17.3.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music Collaborative Playlists</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-music-collaborative-playlist.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898803" /><br/>
A new Collaborative Playlists option for Apple Music subscribers allows multiple people to add, reorder, and remove songs in a shared playlist. Users are able to leave <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-17-3-collaborative-playlist-emoji/">animated emoji reactions</a> next to songs in the playlist.<br/>
<br/>
This feature was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">initially expected to launch with iOS 17.2</a>, but it was removed from that update towards the end of the beta testing period. The feature was re-added in iOS 17.3, and Apple's website confirmed that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-collaborative-playlists-2024/">would return in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Unity Bloom Wallpaper</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Unity-Bloom-Wallpaper-iPhone-iPad.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931156" /><br/>
iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 include Apple's new Unity Bloom wallpaper for the iPhone and iPad, in support of the Black community. The wallpaper includes an outline of flowers that fill with color when the display is active.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the "blooming flowers and vibrant colors represent Pan-Africanism and symbolize generations working together to address injustice and dismantle systemic barriers." There is also a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">Black Unity Sport Band for the Apple Watch</a>, and an accompanying Black Unity watch face available with watchOS 10.3, which will also be released next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/">Apple Releasing iOS 17.3 Next Week With These New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week-with-these-new-features.2416586/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Black Unity Band for Apple Watch Now Available to Order</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-black-unity-band-for-apple-watch-now-available-to-order.2416585/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:07:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Bands</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-unveils-2024-black-unity-collection-and-announces-six-reji-grantees/">announced</a> that a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW4U3AM/A/41mm-black-unity-sport-band-unity-bloom-s-m">new Black Unity Sport Band</a> for the Apple Watch is available to order on Apple.com and in the Apple Store app starting today for &#36;49. The band launches in select Apple Store locations on Tuesday, January 23.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Watch-Black-Unity-Band-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931139" /><br/>
Apple says the band's "blooming flowers and vibrant colors" represent "Pan-Africanism and symbolize generations working together to address injustice and dismantle systemic barriers." The band's pin is etched with "Truth, Power, Solidarity."<br/>
<br/>
An accompanying Black Unity watch face will be available for the Apple Watch with watchOS 10.3, which will be released next week, according to Apple. Users can choose between a single-bloom or full-bloom arrangement for the watch face, and when they raise their wrist, the "flowers begin to bloom with vibrant hues."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/2024-Apple-Watch-Black-Unity-Watch-Face-Combo.png" alt="" width="2612" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931168" /><br/>
Apple is also adding a new Unity Bloom wallpaper to the iPhone and iPad <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/">with iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3</a>, which will both be released next week. Apple says the wallpaper "presents an outline of flowers that fill with color when the display is active."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Unity-Bloom-Wallpaper-iPhone-iPad.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931156" /><br/>
More details about this Black Unity collection and Apple's Racial Equity and Justice Initiative can be found <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-unveils-2024-black-unity-collection-and-announces-six-reji-grantees/">in Apple's press release</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-bands/">Apple Watch Bands</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">New Black Unity Band for Apple Watch Now Available to Order</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-black-unity-band-for-apple-watch-now-available-to-order.2416585/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>1TB iPhone 16 Pro Models Could Face Performance Setback</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/1tb-iphone-16-pro-could-face-performance-setback/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/1tb-iphone-16-pro-models-could-face-performance-setback.2416578/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:06:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/1tb-iphone-16-pro-could-face-performance-setback/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models configured with 1TB of storage could feature slower read and write speeds to reduce costs, <em><a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240115PD231.html">DigiTimes</a></em> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-Updated-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922680" /><br/>
The change is part of Apple's potential switch to higher-density Quad-Level Cell (QLC) NAND flash memory for its 1TB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, which the company is said to currently be "actively evaluating." Apple currently uses costlier Triple-Level Cell (TLC) NAND.<br/>
<br/>
Using QLC NAND would allow Apple to cram more storage into a smaller space and comes at a lower price, but with the disadvantage of slower read and write speeds. QLC NAND can also be less durable and reliable than TLC NAND, handling constant write operations less effectively. Apple could, of course, seek to mitigate these issues with specific optimizations.<br/>
<br/>
The report adds that adopting QLC NAND could make offering iPhones with up to 2TB of storage viable for the first time. A 1TB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max is priced at &#36;1,599, &#36;200 more than the 512GB model, so a future 2TB model would need to be cost-effective, as well as contain flash storage that is sufficiently compact inside the device.<br/>
<br/>
New &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models with 128GB, 256GB, and 512GB of storage are highly likely to stick with TLC NAND for the foreseeable future. Although TLC NAND is still widespread in the industry, QLC NAND is expected to account for about 20% of all NAND shipments from the second half of 2023 to the first half of 2024, suggesting that its usage is growing despite its drawbacks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/1tb-iphone-16-pro-could-face-performance-setback/">1TB iPhone 16 Pro Models Could Face Performance Setback</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/1tb-iphone-16-pro-models-could-face-performance-setback.2416578/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Adjusts Trade-In Values for Select iPhones, Macs, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-iphone-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-for-select-iphones-macs-and-more.2416577/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 04:57:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-iphone-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today adjusted its <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">trade-in values</a> for select devices in the United States, with several reductions in value going into effect across the iPhone 14 series, Apple Watch models, select Macs, and some Android smartphones. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/apple-mac-ipad-watch-trade-in3.jpg" alt="" width="1472" height="850" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-844675" /><br/>
Most reductions were slight: iPhone trade-in values decreased by up to &#36;50, and most Android smartphones went down by &#36;5. Meanwhile, select Apple Watch and Mac models saw the largest downward adjustments. The latest trade-in values are listed below.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPhone 14</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>iPhone 14 Pro Max: Up to &#36;620 (vs. &#36;650)</li><br/>
    <li>iPhone 14 Pro: Up to &#36;520 (vs. &#36;570)</li><br/>
    <li>iPhone 14 Plus: Up to &#36;450 (vs. &#36;470)</li><br/>
    <li>iPhone 14: Up to &#36;400 (vs. &#36;430)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple Watch</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>Apple Watch Ultra: Up to &#36;390 (vs. &#36;425)</li><br/>
    <li>Apple Watch Series 8: Up to &#36;185 (vs. &#36;190)</li><br/>
    <li>Apple Watch SE (2nd generation): Up to &#36;125 (vs. &#36;120)</li><br/>
    <li>Apple Watch Series 7: Up to &#36;155 (vs. &#36;160)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Mac</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>MacBook Pro: Up to &#36;990 (vs. &#36;1070)</li><br/>
    <li>MacBook Air: Up to &#36;550 (vs. &#36;570)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac: Up to &#36;440 (vs. &#36;460)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Android</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>Samsung Galaxy S22 Ultra 5G: Up to &#36;345 (vs. &#36;340)</li><br/>
    <li>Samsung Galaxy S22 5G: Up to &#36;195 (vs. &#36;190)</li><br/>
    <li>Google Pixel 6 Pro: Up to &#36;145 (vs. &#36;140)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The full list of trade-in values, including those for iPads and Android smartphones, can be found on <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">Apple's trade-in website</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-iphone-mac/">Apple Adjusts Trade-In Values for Select iPhones, Macs, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-for-select-iphones-macs-and-more.2416577/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wants &#36;73.4 Million From Epic Games to Cover Its Legal Expenses</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-wants-epic-games-legal-expenses/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wants-73-4-million-from-epic-games-to-cover-its-legal-expenses.2416575/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 04:14:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-wants-epic-games-legal-expenses/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple wants <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> to pay &#36;73.4 million in legal fees after Apple won the antitrust case brought against it by the North Carolinian games maker. On Tuesday, the Supreme Court <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">declined</a> to hear separate requests from both Apple and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; in their long-standing lawsuit against each other regarding <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules, effectively closing a case that has run since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">August 2020</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
In multiple rounds of the dispute, Apple has won on every count with the exception of just one regarding Apple's "anti-steering" rule, which the company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">promptly addressed on Tuesday</a>. As a result of the Supreme Court's decision, the previous rulings stand and Apple is able to continue to disallow third-party payment processing within apps.<br/>
<br/>
Now though, Apple has asked the court to allow it to bill Epic for its litigation expenses, which amount to a whopping &#36;73,404,326. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/games_fray/status/1747504306532630858"><em>gamesfray</em>'s Florian Mueller</a>, Apple came up with the number by totaling up the &#36;82,971,401 in legal costs it spent on the case, and then adjusted that number down to &#36;81,560,362. Apple then deducted 10% since Epic prevailed on 1 of 10 counts (Apple's anti-steering rule).<br/>
<br/>
Apple bases the claim on Epic's original violation of its developer agreement, when out of the blue its Fortnite game offered an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/fornite-adds-direct-payment-option-on-ios/">in-app payment alternative</a> on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Epic previously accepted that it would owe damages if it lost its antitrust claims against Apple. Now that it has, Apple has issued the bill.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Apple?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Apple</a> wants <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/EpicGames?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#EpicGames</a> to reimburse &#36;73 MILLION AND COUNTING (the dispute isn&#39;t over yet) in litigation expenses. Apple says it&#39;s spent &#36;82,971,401 defending against that case, adjusts it to &#36;81,560,362, then deducts 10% as Epic prevailed on 1 of 10 counts &#x27a1;&#xfe0f; &#36;73,404,326.<br><br>&#x1f9f5;1/4 <a href="https://t.co/0Qwa3yA6es">pic.twitter.com/0Qwa3yA6es</a></p>&mdash; gamesfray (@games_fray) <a href="https://twitter.com/games_fray/status/1747504304695484810?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
For its Notice of Motion, the court has set a date of March 5, 2024 to hear Apple's claim about the fees owed, "plus additional amounts Apple is incurring during this ongoing litigation, under the indemnification provision of the Developer Program License Agreement."   <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-wants-epic-games-legal-expenses/">Apple Wants &#36;73.4 Million From Epic Games to Cover Its Legal Expenses</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wants-73-4-million-from-epic-games-to-cover-its-legal-expenses.2416575/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
