<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:03:44 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker&#039;s Qi2 Chargers Will Charge iPhones at 15W</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/anker-qi2-15w-charging/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-qi2-chargers-will-charge-iphones-at-15w.2413020/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:53:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/anker-qi2-15w-charging/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Anker</category>
		<category>Qi2</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next-generation Qi2 chargers from Anker will charge the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> at faster 15W speeds, Anker told <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/6/23990215/anker-qi2-15w-wireless-charging-iphone-13-14-15">The Verge</a></em>. Current Qi-based chargers from companies like Anker are limited to 7.5W when used with Apple's iPhones, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> chargers support 15W charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911511" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/magsafe-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
While Qi2 has the same magnetic alignment that &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; offers, Apple has not provided details on the Qi2 charging speeds that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will support. During the introduction of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, Apple said they support Qi2, but the technical specifications page for the devices says that Qi wireless charging is limited to 7.5W.<br/>
<blockquote>Anker spokesperson Mary Woodbury confirmed in an email to The Verge that, unlike older Qi products that were limited to half-speed 7.5W charging with iPhones, the new MagGo products can support 15W charging, the same maximum rate you get with Apple's MagSafe-branded gear.</blockquote><br/>
Apple has not confirmed 15W charging speeds with Qi2, nor have other manufacturers working on Qi2 provided specific charging speeds, but if Anker's upcoming Qi2 chargers work at 15W, other wireless chargers will likely have the same maximum speed.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models have had Qi2 support since they launched, and with the iOS 17.2 that's coming soon, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/ios-17-2-qi-iphone-13-14-models/">adding Qi2 support</a> to the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
If Qi2 does support actual 15W charging speeds on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; similar to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, the certification could help clear up some confusing with existing magnetic wireless chargers. Current Qi-based chargers that have magnets are still limited to 7.5W charging, but manufacturers often like to say that they support up to 15W because other non-iPhone smartphones are able to charge at those speeds.<br/>
<br/>
The first Qi2 chargers are expected in late 2023, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/31/belkin-qi2-wireless-chargers/">brands like Belkin</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/mophie-unveils-qi2-accessories/">Mophie</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/31/anker-usb-c-nano-accessories/">Anker</a> have already announced new Qi2 products.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anker/">Anker</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qi2/">Qi2</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/anker-qi2-15w-charging/">Anker&#039;s Qi2 Chargers Will Charge iPhones at 15W</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-qi2-chargers-will-charge-iphones-at-15w.2413020/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hulu on Disney+ Beta Launches for Bundle Subscribers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/hulu-disney-plus-merged-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hulu-on-disney-beta-launches-for-bundle-subscribers.2413014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/hulu-disney-plus-merged-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Disney</category>
		<category>Hulu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Disney <a href="https://thewaltdisneycompany.com/hulu-on-disney-beta-launch/">today announced</a> that customers who subscribe to its Hulu and Disney+ bundle can access Hulu content through a new "Hulu on Disney+" beta that aims to combine the two apps into a single app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Hulu on Disney+ Beta Now Streaming" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AgHZ7EeNaSg" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-thumb-size="hqdefault"></iframe></div><br/>
The beta is available to bundle subscribers as of now, with Disney planning to test the combined service before it rolls out in the spring. Bundle subscribers will see a Hulu title appear alongside Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars, and National Geographic tiles in the Disney+ interface.<br/>
<br/>
Clicking on the Hulu tile brings Bundle subscribers to the new Hulu Hub that has all of the Hulu content without the need to switch over to the Hulu app. The two-step launch process is meant to keep Hulu content separate from Disney+ content for parents who do not want the more adult content from Hulu accessible to children.<br/>
<br/>
Disney said that it wants to better understand consumer needs and wants for Hulu on Disney+ before it launches in March 2024. Disney does not plan to replace either the standalone Hulu or Disney+ subscriptions, both will continue be available.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney/">Disney</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/hulu/">Hulu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/hulu-disney-plus-merged-beta/">Hulu on Disney+ Beta Launches for Bundle Subscribers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hulu-on-disney-beta-launches-for-bundle-subscribers.2413014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 May Reuse Existing iPhone 14 Battery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-se-4-reuse-iphone-14-battery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-may-reuse-existing-iphone-14-battery.2413009/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:17:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-se-4-reuse-iphone-14-battery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>iPhone SE 4</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Recently, <em>MacRumors</em> has received details on the battery currently being tested on the upcoming fourth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, and the information corroborates previous findings in relation to the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/iphone-se-4-modified-flag-edges.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-886982" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, known by its device identifier D59, is expected to use the exact same battery found in the base model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>. Partially assembled prototypes of the next &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; have been seen equipped with lithium-ion batteries bearing the model number A2863, which Apple has already used in the past. Internal design documentation also corroborates this change. The battery itself features an improved capacity compared to the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>iPhone SE 3</strong>: 2018 mAh</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 14 (A2863)</strong>: 3279 mAh</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Compared to the battery used in the third-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;, the A2863 battery brings with it an increase of over 1250 mAh, potentially resulting in longer battery life for the end-user. <br/>
<br/>
As with most of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, Apple has chosen the A2863 battery as a carry-over from the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. While Apple has allegedly developed entirely <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">new batteries for the iPhone 16 Pro with enhanced thermal capabilities</a>, the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will continue to use existing parts as a cost-cutting measure.<br/>
<br/>
Developing new components for the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 would incur additional research and development costs for Apple, so the use of an existing battery would help maintain the relative affordability of the device compared to other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models Apple offers. This also lines up with Apple's previous decisions in regard to the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;, as the second-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; used the exact same battery as the older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of other relevant upgrades, the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/">new iPhone 14-based design</a>, and will be equipped with an Action button and USB-C port, which we've covered extensively in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/">previous reports</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It is important to remember, though, that the information provided here is pre-production information. While prototype units of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 use the A2863 battery, Apple's plans could change as the device is still far from release. <br/>
<br/>
For additional details on what to expect, check out our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">guide for the iPhone SE 4</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">iPhone SE 4</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-se-4-reuse-iphone-14-battery/">iPhone SE 4 May Reuse Existing iPhone 14 Battery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-may-reuse-existing-iphone-14-battery.2413009/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Nanoleaf&#039;s &#36;99 Matter-Enabled String Lights Are an Affordable Holiday Option</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-string-lights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-nanoleafs-99-matter-enabled-string-lights-are-an-affordable-holiday-option.2413008/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:04:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-string-lights&#038;post_date=1701907471/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nanoleaf is known for its smart lighting panels, but this year the company launched a set of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FNanoleaf-Essentials-Lightstrip-Smarter-Built%2Fdp%2FB0CKWLBQG5">&#36;99 Smart Holiday String Lights</a> that are compatible with Matter and thus <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>. Matter devices connect to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; in the same way that traditional &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; devices do, but you will need a Matter-compatible smart home hub. For the &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; ecosystem, this is anything that serves as a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; "home hub," such as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/nanoleaf-holiday-lights-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915782" /><br/>
Priced at &#36;99 for a 2-meter (65 ft) light strand with 250 LEDs, the Nanoleaf Holiday String Lights are priced competitively. They're more affordable than similar smart string lights from Philips Hue or Twinkly, though Twinkly is often around the same price if you find them on sale. A 65-foot light strand is about the right size for a 7-foot tree, though it won't be the most dense lighting. For a more even look, two light strands of this length are required for most trees around that size.<br/>
<br/>
There are two connected 10-meter strands with 125 LEDs each (which is also how Twinkly works). According to Nanoleaf, the dual strand design is ideal for use with trees. Starting at the middle of the tree, one strand can be wrapped up toward the top, while the second can be wrapped down toward the bottom. It is not possible to connect two sets of the string lights together, however, and each needs its own power supply if you're using multiples.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-string-lights-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925456" /><br/>
The Nanoleaf lights look a lot like the Twinkly lights in terms of design, with a flat-topped LED that has rounded sides. There's about three inches of space between each LED, and the cord is black with no other color options available. Black stands out more than green on a Christmas tree, so it would be nice to have a green cord option. Twinkly makes some clear cord string lights, and I think that's a good way to go because it's able to better blend into the surroundings.<br/>
<br/>
Unlike Twinkly lights, you cannot control each individual LED, and instead these are set to different color palettes and patterns like the Hue String Lights. The Nanoleaf lights actually feel like a cross between Hue and Twinkly because they're not quite as customizable as Twinkly, but offer more patterns than Hue. 16 million colors are supported on the Nanoleaf lights, as well as multiple shades of white. The Nanoleaf app has pre-designed color palettes that you can choose in addition to the tools to create your own.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-lights-multicolored.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925457" /><br/>
There's also a community feature with Nanoleaf so you can download lighting animations and color palettes created by others, giving you a lot of options for design without having to put in a lot of work. Nanoleaf's community feature has long been one of my favorite Nanoleaf features because it provides so many options with just a quick search.<br/>
<br/>
The Nanoleaf String Light's colors are vibrant and bright and remind me a lot of Twinkly in terms of saturation and lighting patterns. Compared to Hue, Nanoleaf is brighter, and I don't feel that Nanoleaf's lights do gradients quite as well. The Hue holiday lights have the best color fades and pre-made patterns, and Nanoleaf can't compete there.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-lights-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925458" /><br/>
The best way to control the lights is through the Nanoleaf app, but once you establish lighting scenes, you can activate them through the Home app or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands. The Home app can be used to control the Nanoleaf String Lights directly, but it's not really set up for individual LED control so it only works for turning the entire strand a single shade.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-string-lights-in-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925462" /><br/>
While these do connect to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; (and other Matter-enabled smart home platforms), you can use them with the Nanoleaf app alone over Wi-Fi or Bluetooth. With the included controller, the lights can be synced to music that is playing. There is a physical button on the light strand for turning them on and off and cycling through white shades, colors, and Scenes that have been set up.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-lights-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925459" /><br/>
According to Nanoleaf, the lights are 250 lumens, and the strand draws 18W of power. With the light strand on for 12 hours a day and an electricity cost of 13 cents per kilowatt hour, it would cost around &#36;10 a year to run these lights.<br/>
<br/>
These have an IP44 water/dust resistance rating, so they can be used indoors or outdoors and will be able to stand up to rain, but may not be able to hold up in particularly harsh weather like a downpour. Nanoleaf says they can be used in temperatures ranging from 5 degrees to 104 degrees.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-lights-white.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925460" /><br/>
As a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; device, automations and schedules can be used to turn the lights on and off at set times or to change patterns based on sensors, times, or with geofencing.<br/>
<br/>
During my time testing the lights, I did not run into issues with connectivity. Matter can be a little finicky right now, which is something to be aware of. In the past I have run into connectivity issues with non-Matter Nanoleaf products, but most of the time the solution has been removing and re-adding to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/nanoleaf-lights-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925461" /><br/>
Nanoleaf's Matter-enabled String Lights are the most affordable string lights that connect to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; that I'm aware of. At &#36;99, they're cheaper than the Hue or Twinkly versions that have the same 250-LED count.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
Nanoleaf's Matter-enabled Smart Holiday String Lights are a good deal comparatively, and they offer a lot of fun options for holiday decorating. These are quite not as customizable as Twinkly lights (which you can paint on using the app), but Nanoleaf has a better selection of pre-made scenes and color palettes to choose from.<br/>
<br/>
The Nanoleaf app is a lot more user friendly and intuitive than the Twinkly app, which is my least favorite smart home product app. If you're someone who wants to hop onto an app, find a set of cool colors, and be done in about 30 seconds, Nanoleaf's string lights will facilitate that.<br/>
<br/>
You can use these in tandem with other &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; products, but you won't have the integrations you'll have with say, the Hue String Lights and other Hue lights. If you're in the Hue ecosystem, I still think the Hue String Lights are the best holiday lights to get, but if you just need a general HomeKit-connected string light, Nanoleaf is a good option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Nanoleaf Downlights</h2><br/>
Though not related to the String Lights, Nanoleaf also came out with some <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FNanoleaf-Essentials-Lightstrip-Smarter-Built%2Fdp%2FB0CKWLBQG5">Matter 4-inch downlights</a>, a first for the company. I was able to test these out, and I think if you're looking for a smart downlight replacement that does not require a hub, these are a good bet.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/nanoleaf-downlight.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916707" /><br/>
I prefer my Hue downlights just because I am in the Hue ecosystem, but the Nanoleaf ones work just as well in terms of color options and brightness. Nanoleaf does not have 6-inch versions at this time, so that will be a barrier to those who have larger downlights or a mix.<br/>
<br/>
I have had some disconnects with these lights, but I don't want to blame Nanoleaf for that because I think it is a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; Matter issue where there are still bugs for Apple to work out.<br/>
<br/>
These are <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FNanoleaf-Essentials-Lightstrip-Smarter-Built%2Fdp%2FB0CKWLBQG5">only &#36;30 each</a>, which makes them half as expensive as the Hue version. If you're willing to do some troubleshooting every once in awhile until &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; is shored up for Matter, Nanoleaf's downlights are worth trying.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Nanoleaf String Lights can be <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FNanoleaf-Essentials-Lightstrip-Smarter-Built%2Fdp%2FB0CKWLBQG5">purchased from Amazon</a> or from the <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/seasonal/holiday-string-lights/">Nanoleaf website</a> for &#36;100.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Nanoleaf provided MacRumors with the Nanoleaf String Lights for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-string-lights/">Review: Nanoleaf&#039;s &#36;99 Matter-Enabled String Lights Are an Affordable Holiday Option</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-nanoleafs-99-matter-enabled-string-lights-are-an-affordable-holiday-option.2413008/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Eliminating iTunes Movies and TV Show Apps in tvOS 17.2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-itunes-movies-tv-show-apps-tvos-17-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-eliminating-itunes-movies-and-tv-show-apps-in-tvos-17-2.2412998/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:05:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-itunes-movies-tv-show-apps-tvos-17-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is doing away with the redundant iTunes Movies and iTunes TV Show apps on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> starting with the tvOS 17.2 update. As noted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/12/06/itunes-movies-and-tv-shows-app-discontinued-apple-tv/">9to5Mac</a></em>, in the release candidate version of tvOS 17.2, opening up those apps redirects users to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/apple-tv-itunes-purchases.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925449" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app supports both movie and TV show purchases, making the old iTunes Movies and iTunes TV Shows apps unnecessary and also confusing to some &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; users.<br/>
<br/>
"iTunes Movies and Your Purchases Have Moved," reads the text in the iOS 17.2 release candidate. "You can buy or rent movies and find your purchases in the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app."<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-tv-app-revamp/">in October said</a> that Apple planned to remove the standalone &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; apps available for renting and purchasing TV shows and movies, and he also said that the TV show and movie sections would be removed from the iTunes Store app on iPhones and iPads.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple has indeed started the process of eliminating its iTunes TV Shows and iTunes Movies apps on &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, the apps do still exist in the RC in order to provide customers with instructions on where to find their content going forward. Apple will likely remove the apps entirely in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, the iTunes Store app continues to offer TV show and movie purchases right alongside the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app, but the option to purchase that content may soon be removed from the iTunes Store app.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 17.2 also includes a sidebar that houses content from both Apple's services and streaming services that integrate with the tvOS Watch Now feature. The sidebar makes it easier to access a range of content, and there are dedicated sections for Search, Watch Now, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, Sports, Library, and the Store for purchases.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release tvOS 17.2 to the public next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-itunes-movies-tv-show-apps-tvos-17-2/">Apple Eliminating iTunes Movies and TV Show Apps in tvOS 17.2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-eliminating-itunes-movies-and-tv-show-apps-in-tvos-17-2.2412998/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: 2023 Genesis Electrified GV70 Offers Lots of Tech, but You&#039;ll Need a Cable for CarPlay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/2023-genesis-electrified-gv70-carplay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-2023-genesis-electrified-gv70-offers-lots-of-tech-but-youll-need-a-cable-for-carplay.2412995/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:34:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/2023-genesis-electrified-gv70-carplay&#038;post_date=1701902065/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>Genesis</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Hyundai's luxury brand <a href="https://www.genesis.com/us/en/home">Genesis</a> has been gaining increasing attention over the course of its relatively short lifetime, and I recently had a chance to try out a 2023 Electrified GV70 SUV to see how the infotainment experience stacks up for an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925005" /><br/>
My test vehicle was a high-end Prestige trim with a beautiful 14.5-inch widescreen center screen, complemented by a 12.3-inch all-digital driver display featuring autostereoscopic 3D technology, plus an additional head-up display for viewing key information without having to take your eyes off the road.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-sky.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925017" /><em>Infotainment display</em></div><br/>
The GV70's center display is mounted high on the dashboard and set back a decent amount, which puts it in a good spot for glancing at without having to look too far away from what's in front of you, but the positioning and widescreen dimensions make operating it via the touchscreen a bit of a reach. To address that, Genesis also includes a rotary controller and a number of buttons within easy reach of the driver on the center console.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-rotary-controller.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925012" /><em>Rotary controller located above a rotary shifter dial</em></div><br/>
The rotary controller includes a dial for navigating between user interface elements, and you can press the dial to register your selection, but the dial can also be rocked to move more quickly move between pages and sections in the system. The surface of the controller is also touch-sensitive, allowing you to draw out letters when trying to search for destinations or performing other tasks where text entry is needed. Voice commands are typically a much superior method for this, however.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the rotary controller, there are several buttons located directly above it on the console to quickly access specific functions in the infotainment system, including dedicated Home, Menu, and Back buttons. Scroll-style buttons also allow for easy volume and tuning adjustments.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-steering-wheel.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925013" /><em>Steering wheel controls</em></div><br/>
Steering wheel controls are another method for controlling some infotainment functions, and there's even another strip of buttons on the center stack below the climate controls with quick access to the map, navigation, radio, and media functions. This strip and the steering wheel each have a user-configurable "star" button that can be set to jump you straight into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>.<br/>
<br/>
And yes, climate controls have their own dedicated section separate from the main infotainment screen and they include a combination of physical and digital controls that works quite well. The driver and passenger each have a knob for adjusting the temperature for their respective sides of the cabin, and there additional commonly used controls to the outside of these dials.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-climate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925014" /><em>Dedicated climate controls</em></div><br/>
These climate controls are not individual buttons, but the small panels they're on do move when pressed, providing some tactile feedback. Other settings like heated and cooled seats, heated steering wheel, and manual fan speed adjustments are made on a digital screen, so they're harder to manage by feel, although they do provide some haptic and audio feedback when pressed.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-menu.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925348" /><em>Menu screen for native infotainment</em></div><br/>
For the most part, the native infotainment system has a sleek, modern look, with high-resolution graphics and a logical layout of screens and panels that's easy to navigate using the rotary controller or by touch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-nature-sounds.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925349" /><em>Nature sounds</em></div><br/>
A full array of functions are available, from SiriusXM to onboard navigation to EV data. There are even a variety of soothing nature sounds that can be piped throughout the cabin, and there's a weather app complete with a radar view.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-nav.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925350" /><em>Built-in navigation</em></div><br/>
The onboard navigation is functional and helpful with both overview and next-turn views available simultaneously while a route is in progress, but the look could stand some modernization to better match the rest of the infotainment system.<br/>
<br/>
In the driver's display, Genesis includes the neat Blind-Spot View Monitor system that Hyundai has offered for a number of years, which uses cameras on the side-view mirror to display a live video feed of your blind spot on a given side when you engage your turn signal. It's a handy feature that I wish was common in more brands.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-driver-display.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925015" /><em>Driver display with stereoscopic 3D view and Blind-Spot View Monitor</em></div><br/>
The other clever driver's display feature that comes as part of the Prestige package on the GV70 is the 3D aspect. It's something you really have to experience in person to fully grasp, but it takes advantage of parallax with offset images to turn gauges and other digital aspects of the instrument cluster into three-dimensional representations that give a sense of depth.<br/>
<br/>
A camera pointed at the driver tracks their position and gaze, adjusting the 3D effect accordingly. The whole thing is a bit gimmicky, but it's kind of neat and stands out as something different to help set the high-end Genesis trims apart.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-charging.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925010" /><em>USB ports and wireless charging pad in center console</em></div><br/>
The GV70 includes a pair of USB-A ports (one for charge and data and one for charging only) in a small cubby on the center console that also includes a wireless Qi charger. As with many car chargers, it can be difficult to get a reliable wireless charging connection, likely due to the slab-style charger design and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s camera bump and case lip interfering with positioning on the charger.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-rear-climate-usb-jpg.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925011" /><em>Rear climate controls and USB charging ports</em></div><br/>
On the rear of the center console are climate controls and a pair of USB-A charging ports for rear passengers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>CarPlay</h2><br/>
As you'd hope, the Electrified GV70 supports &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, but unfortunately only via a wired connection. Genesis is currently a victim of an odd split in Hyundai's infotainment systems wherein lower-tier systems support both wired and wireless &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; while higher-end systems with built-in navigation only support wired &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;. There have been rumors of Hyundai and Genesis adding wireless &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; to some of these higher-tier systems on select models via a software update in the relatively near future, but we'll have to see if that pans out.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-carplay-home.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925006" /><em>&zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; Home screen</em></div><br/>
So if you want to use &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, you're going to have plug your phone in, and it's unfortunate that more modern USB-C ports aren't included. The charging and USB compartment includes a spring-loaded cover to help hide things away, but if you've got a Pro Max-sized &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a cable sticking out the bottom for &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, you'll have a very difficult time getting that cover to close properly.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-carplay-maps.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925007" /><em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> in &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
&zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; looks great on the GV70's widescreen display, which even leaves enough room for a sidebar off to the right where you can view other functions from the native infotainment system. You can see your current radio station or audio track information, a compass, a dedicated clock, vehicle battery information, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-carplay-now-playing.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925008" /><em>Now Playing screen in &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
On the downside, &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; is a single-screen experience in the GV70, as it doesn't get the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/volvo-dual-screen-apple-maps-carplay/">dual-screen experience</a> rolling out recently to Volvo and a few other brands, and it doesn't even get the more basic &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; navigation prompts in the driver display or the head-up display that are available on many vehicles. Navigation prompts from the native navigation system do appear in the head-up display, so that's a plus for using the Hyundai/Genesis system. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/2023-gv70-carplay-dashboard.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925009" /><em>&zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; Dashboard view</em></div><br/>
<h2>Wrap-up</h2><br/>
The Genesis Electrified GV70 starts at a little over &#36;65,000, with the Prestige package on my test model, a paint upcharge, and destination fees bringing things to a little shy of &#36;75,000. It's not cheap, and its range clocks in at only 236 miles (and even a bit less than that in real-world review), but overall it's a fun drive with a boost mode that lets you go 0–60 in around four seconds.<br/>
<br/>
It's also packed with technology from the gorgeous center display to the 3D driver's display to a fingerprint authentication system. My main gripes on this front are the lack of wireless connectivity for &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, USB-A ports rather than USB-C, and an inconvenient phone storage/charging setup.<br/>
<br/>
Hopefully, those issues will be addressed in upcoming model years (or even via software updates to existing models such as for wireless &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;), but even now if the issues aren't deal-breakers and you're willing and able to spend that kind of cash, the Electrified GV70 is a pretty compelling package. A gasoline-powered version is also available for a still-premium but significantly lower price tag, but you'll be missing out on some of the fun EV features like zippy acceleration.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genesis/">Genesis</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/2023-genesis-electrified-gv70-carplay/">Review: 2023 Genesis Electrified GV70 Offers Lots of Tech, but You&#039;ll Need a Cable for CarPlay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-2023-genesis-electrified-gv70-offers-lots-of-tech-but-youll-need-a-cable-for-carplay.2412995/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New M3 MacBook Air Models Expected Around March 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/macbook-air-march-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-m3-macbook-air-models-expected-around-march-2024.2412990/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:36:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/macbook-air-march-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to refresh the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> around March 2024, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-06/apple-prepares-m3-macbook-air-and-revamped-ipad-pro-for-early-next-year">said today in a report</a> on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ipad-air-ipad-pro-2024-refresh/">Apple's future iPad</a> and Mac plans. Updated 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Pro models are in the works.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/15inch-macbook-air-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916649" /><br/>
As Apple overhauled the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;'s design in 2022 and then introduced a larger model in 2023, no design changes are planned for the 2024 models. The focus will instead be on new internal hardware, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m3/">the updated M3 chip</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Introduced earlier this year in the updated MacBook Pro models, the M3 chip is the first chip built on Apple's 3-nanometer process, bringing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-much-better-really-is-m3/">performance and efficiency improvements</a>. M3 chip benchmarks suggest that the CPU is up to 21 percent faster than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>, and the GPU is up to 15 percent faster.<br/>
<br/>
According to Gurman, Apple is developing the Macs alongside macOS 14.3, an update that is expected between the end of January and February, but new hardware may ship around the March timeframe. The new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models could be timed to launch alongside updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, which are coming around March.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word yet on when other Macs might be refreshed. The MacBook Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> models were updated in October 2023, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> was last updated in January 2023, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> updated in June 2023.<br/>
<br/>
In the fourth fiscal quarter of 2023, Apple saw a steep decline in Mac sales. Macs brought in &#36;7.6 billion, down 34 percent from the &#36;11.5 billion that Apple earned in Q4 2022. Apple expects Mac sales to go up following the launch of the October MacBook Pro models, and an early 2024 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; refresh will also help to drive growth.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/macbook-air-march-2024/">New M3 MacBook Air Models Expected Around March 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-m3-macbook-air-models-expected-around-march-2024.2412990/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Launch Two iPad Air and Two OLED iPad Pro Models Early Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ipad-air-ipad-pro-2024-refresh/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-two-ipad-air-and-two-oled-ipad-pro-models-early-next-year.2412987/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:53:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ipad-air-ipad-pro-2024-refresh/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[To boost falling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> sales, Apple has a major refresh planned for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lineup in early 2024, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-06/apple-prepares-m3-macbook-air-and-revamped-ipad-pro-for-early-next-year">Bloomberg</a></em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. Apple plans to debut new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models, both of which will feature notable changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/12.9-inch-ipad-pro-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875252" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will come in two sizes like the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; for the first time. The smaller model will continue to measure in at 10.9 inches, but the larger version will be 12.9 inches, like the larger &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. Apple is aiming to provide more variety between screen size and price, and the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be more affordable than the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's 2024 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will feature OLED displays, a first for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lineup. Apple has been using OLED technology for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the Apple Watch, but larger OLED screens are more expensive. Compared to LED or mini-LED, OLED brings deeper blacks and more vivid colors. OLED displays will be a Pro-only feature, with the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; to continue to use standard displays.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman says that the high-end version of the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will be equipped with the new M3 chip that Apple introduced earlier this year. The M3 is built on 3-nanometer technology, and it will bring notable graphics improvement over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip that is currently used in the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will refresh the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in 2024, but it is unclear if these tablets will be updated at the same time as the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
To go along with the updated iPads, Apple plans to introduce a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> and new Magic Keyboards. The updated Magic Keyboards are said to have a sturdier frame made from aluminum, which will allow the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to more closely resemble a laptop.<br/>
<br/>
There were no iPads released in 2023, which is the first time that Apple has not debuted a new tablet during a calendar year. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue came in at &#36;28.3 billion in 2023, down from &#36;29.3 billion in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models and their accompanying accessories are expected to launch around the end of March, which is also when Apple plans to release iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. Apple is likely to hold a March event to introduce the new devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ipad-air-ipad-pro-2024-refresh/">Apple to Launch Two iPad Air and Two OLED iPad Pro Models Early Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-two-ipad-air-and-two-oled-ipad-pro-models-early-next-year.2412987/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung&#039;s 27-Inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display Gets Massive &#36;555 Discount on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/viewfinity-s9-5k-display-massive-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-s9-5k-display-gets-massive-555-discount-on-amazon.2412975/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:48:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/viewfinity-s9-5k-display-massive-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung's 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K display has hit a new all-time low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,044.04</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. The display has an estimated delivery date of December 12 if ordered today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/samsung-viewfinity-s9.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903406" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This price is available directly from Amazon, so if you don't see it make sure you're looking at the right seller. Scroll down to the "new and used" option on the right side of the page and browse through the listings for new models of the display until you see Amazon's seller page and the correct price tag. Note that this sale has been fluctuating all day, so if you're interested, place your order soon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;555 OFF</div>Samsung 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display for &#36;1.044.04</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung itself is hosting a <a href="https://howl.me/ck9zilTUkVb">monitor sale</a> right now, offering up to 40 percent off select products. This does include the ViewFinity S9 5K display, but it's not quite as low as Amazon's discount. You can still find a few solid markdowns in this sale, with monitors starting at just &#36;349.99 and totaling up to &#36;600 off select models.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/viewfinity-s9-5k-display-massive-discount/">Samsung&#039;s 27-Inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display Gets Massive &#36;555 Discount on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-s9-5k-display-gets-massive-555-discount-on-amazon.2412975/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;200 Off 15-Inch MacBook Air, Available From &#36;1,099</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/amazon-200-off-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-200-off-15-inch-macbook-air-available-from-1-099.2412970/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 07:09:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/amazon-200-off-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has nearly every model of Apple's 15-inch M2 MacBook Air on sale. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,099.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model, and it's available in every color at this price, with a delivery estimate of December 12.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-gingerbread-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922720" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Compared to past sales, this is a solid second-best price on the 15-inch MacBook Air. Besides Amazon, you'll find matching prices in three colors <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1770940-REG/apple_mqkw3ll_a_15_macbook_air_midnight.html/kw/APMQKW3LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612">at B&H Photo</a>, which offers free two-day shipping to the contiguous United States.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For more storage, Amazon has the 512GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. This one is available in Space Gray and Midnight color options, and it's another second-best price on the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/amazon-200-off-macbook-air/">Amazon Takes &#36;200 Off 15-Inch MacBook Air, Available From &#36;1,099</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-200-off-15-inch-macbook-air-available-from-1-099.2412970/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iMessage May Dodge EU Regulatory Demand for Interoperability</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-imessage-dodge-eu-regulations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-imessage-may-dodge-eu-regulatory-demand-for-interoperability.2412963/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:36:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-imessage-dodge-eu-regulations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iMessage chat service may dodge EU regulatory demands for platform interoperability after all. <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-06/apple-imessage-set-to-avoid-eu-s-digital-dominance-crackdown">Bloomberg</a></em> reports that an investigation by the bloc's antitrust watchdog has tentatively concluded that the chat service is not popular enough with business users to warrant being subject to the new rules.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
The EU has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/01/dma-eu-law-could-force-major-changes-apple/">working on legislation</a> under the Digital Markets Act (DMA) that would have required Apple to make changes to iMessage to make it available on other platforms. The rules will apply to tech giants that meet its "gatekeeper" criteria, force them to open up their various services and platforms to other companies and developers.<br/>
<br/>
The interoperability rules theoretically mean that Meta apps like WhatsApp or Messenger could request to interoperate with Apple's iMessage framework, and Apple would be forced to comply within the EU. But today's report suggests iMessage may fall outside the legislation because it is not widely used by businesses.<br/>
<br/>
The report notes that the possible reprieve for Apple is part of a five-month market investigation by the European Commission, and Apple's exemption has not and will not be officially confirmed until the probe is completed in February.<br/>
<br/>
Regardless of the investigation's conclusions, the DMA will likely still force Apple to make major changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> work in Europe. For example, it is expected to allow users to install third-party app stores and side-load apps, and give developers the ability to promote their offers outside the ‌‌&zwnj;App Store&zwnj;‌‌ and use third-party payment systems.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-imessage-dodge-eu-regulations/">Apple&#039;s iMessage May Dodge EU Regulatory Demand for Interoperability</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-imessage-may-dodge-eu-regulatory-demand-for-interoperability.2412963/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Confirms Governments Using Push Notifications to Surveil Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-governments-surveil-push-notifications/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-governments-using-push-notifications-to-surveil-users.2412959/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:06:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-governments-surveil-push-notifications/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Privacy</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Unidentified governments are surveilling smartphone users by tracking push notifications that move through Google's and Apple's servers, a US senator warned on Wednesday (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/governments-spying-apple-google-users-through-push-notifications-us-senator-2023-12-06/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/iOS-16-4-Web-Push.jpeg" alt="" width="794" height="450" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-885967" /><br/>
In a letter to the Department of Justice, Senator Ron Wyden said foreign officials were demanding the data from the tech giants to track smartphones. The traffic flowing from apps that send push notifications put the companies "in a unique position to facilitate government surveillance of how users are using particular apps," Wyden said. He asked the Department of Justice to "repeal or modify any policies" that hindered public discussions of push notification spying.<br/>
<br/>
In a statement given to <em>Reuters</em>, Apple said that Wyden's letter gave them the opening they needed to share more details with the public about how governments monitored push notifications.<br/>
<blockquote>"In this case, the federal government prohibited us from sharing any information," the company said in a statement. "Now that this method has become public we are updating our transparency reporting to detail these kinds of requests."</blockquote>According to the report, Wyden's letter said a "tip" was the source of the information about the surveillance. A source familiar with the matter confirmed that both foreign and U.S. government agencies have been asking Apple and Google for metadata related to push notifications. The data is said to have been used to attempt to tie anonymous users of messaging apps to specific Apple or Google accounts.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Reuters</em>' source would not identify which governments were making the data requests but described them as "democracies allied to the United States." They did not know how long the requests had been going on for. <br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/usernotifications/setting_up_a_remote_notification_server/generating_a_remote_notification">advises developers</a> not to include sensitive data in notifications and to encrypt any data before adding it to a notification payload. However, this requires action on the developers' part. Likewise, metadata (like which apps are sending notifications and how often) is not encrypted, potentially giving anyone with access to the information insight into users' app usage.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/privacy/">Privacy</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-governments-surveil-push-notifications/">Apple Confirms Governments Using Push Notifications to Surveil Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-governments-using-push-notifications-to-surveil-users.2412959/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Make iPhone 16 Batteries in India, Apple Tells Component Suppliers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/make-iphone-16-batteries-in-india-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-iphone-16-batteries-in-india-apple-tells-component-suppliers.2412953/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:08:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/make-iphone-16-batteries-in-india-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>India</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has told component suppliers it wants iPhone 16 batteries to be made in India, as part of the company's efforts to diversify its global supply chain and reduce its reliance on Chinese manufacturing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-battery-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1333" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923492" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Leaked image of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">alleged iPhone 16 Pro battery</a> with new design, updated connector, and 3355mAh capacity.</em></div><br/>
The <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1eee7956-a5be-4df0-a9a9-139c573c4f8f">Financial Times</a></em> reports that Apple has informed battery suppliers including China's Desay and Taiwan's Simplo Technology of its preference to have batteries for next year's iPhone made in India, and has encouraged the manufacturers to establish new factories there or scale up production at existing sites for future orders.<br/>
<br/>
"If all goes well with iPhone 16 battery supply, Apple plans to move more iPhone battery production to India," said one of the people close to Apple who spoke to <em>FT</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already works with Foxconn, Pegatron, and Tata (new owner of Wistron) to manufacture iPhones in India, with Foxconn handling 75 to 80 percent of the device assembly. Foxconn has invested more than &#36;500 million in India to ramp up its manufacturing capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/iphone-17-assembly-india/">believes</a> that 12 to 14 percent of global ‌iPhone‌ shipments are made in India, with that proportion to increase to 20 to 25 percent by 2024. Introductory production on the standard iPhone 17 will start in India in the second half of 2025, according to Kuo, marking the first time that Apple begins development of a new ‌iPhone‌ outside of China.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to allowing Apple to move manufacturing away from China, increasing production in India provides Apple with an opportunity to strengthen its relationship with the Indian government. India is a key market for Apple due to growing demand for Apple products in the country.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/india/">India</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/make-iphone-16-batteries-in-india-apple/">Make iPhone 16 Batteries in India, Apple Tells Component Suppliers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-iphone-16-batteries-in-india-apple-tells-component-suppliers.2412953/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>UK&#039;s EE TV Platform Launches With Customized Apple TV 4K</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/uk-ee-tv-platform-custom-apple-tv-4k/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uks-ee-tv-platform-launches-with-customized-apple-tv-4k.2412950/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:16:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/uk-ee-tv-platform-custom-apple-tv-4k/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://ee.co.uk/tv/apple-tv-4k">EE TV</a>, a new broadband TV platform from EE, today launched as a BT TV replacement service in the UK, offering subscribers the option of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K with customized remote control.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ee-tv-apple-tv-4k.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925395" /><br/>
EE TV offers access to more than 70 Freeview channels, a Netflix subscription, as well as premium channels from Sky, Discovery, Eurosport, TNT Sports, and more.<br/>
<br/>
To access the platform, subscribers can opt to receive one of three set-top boxes: A standard EE TV "mini" box, a "pro" EE TV box that includes a hard drive for recording live TV, or – in what EE is calling a "UK-first" – a bespoke &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K set up for EE TV content consumption.<br/>
<br/>
Made in partnership with Apple, the custom &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K features a streamlined setup process and the EE TV app preinstalled, featuring live streaming and on-demand content, with quick access to live channels and third-party apps such as BBC iPlayer, as well as a unified search to find content across multiple platforms. The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; also comes with a custom EE-branded remote including a special TV guide button and channel rockers.<br/>
<br/>
The EE TV boxes offer a similar hub that combines live broadcast TV, access to UK catch-up and on demand apps, and the ability to buy and rent content, but they lack access to the other services that &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; typically provides. Those new to EE TV are also eligible to six months of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> for free. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ee-apple-tv-remote.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925396" /><br/>
All 24-month contracts come with live free-to-air channels and catchup. The platform also offers a range of additional services and premium channel packages, priced between £4.99 and £76, with customers able to flexibly add or remove packages from month to month. EE also offers subscribers a bonus EE TV Box Mini for "free multi-room TV." For more information, see the <a href="https://ee.co.uk/tv/apple-tv-4k">EE website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Ross!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/uk-ee-tv-platform-custom-apple-tv-4k/">UK&#039;s EE TV Platform Launches With Customized Apple TV 4K</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uks-ee-tv-platform-launches-with-customized-apple-tv-4k.2412950/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;All-Screen&#039; iPhone Under-Display Camera Enters Development</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-screen-iphone-under-display-camera-enters-development.2412943/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 02:03:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Korean suppliers have begun developing smartphone under-display cameras (UDC), paving the way for the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with a true "all-screen" appearance.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/Beyond-iPhone-13-Better-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793995" /><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=24568">The Elec</a></em>, LG Innotek has entered the preliminary development of the UDC, which sits under the display and does not result in a visible hole in the panel when the camera is not in use.<br/>
<br/>
A UPC differs from a typical front camera module, since it delivers less light to the image sensor. This is because light loss occurs as it passes through the display area before it reaches the camera lens, which can result in a deterioration in image quality and brightness.<br/>
<br/>
To compensate for this, LG Innotek is developing a special "freeform optic" multiple lens system that can reduce optical aberrations and increase the light intensity ratio around the optical module to improve peripheral image quality. LG Innotek has been publishing patents for the technology since December last year, and more are expected now that development has begun.<br/>
<br/>
LG Display, an affiliate of LG Innotek's LG Group, has also started UPC development, according to the report. LG Display aims to increase the UPC's light transmittance to 20% by 2023 and 40% after 2024, bringing it closer to the standard that Apple expects. Apple reportedly already received a UPC sample from an unnamed vendor, but rated it as unsatisfactory in performance.<br/>
<br/>
Before Apple uses the perfected under-screen camera technology, it is expected to adopt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/under-display-face-id-to-debut-on-iphone-17-pro/">under-panel Face ID technology in 2025's iPhone 17 Pro</a>. This is expected to be Apple's last premium model to include a circular cutout for the front-facing camera. Apple will then adopt the UPC in 2027's "Pro" &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, according to respected analyst Ross Young of research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/">&#039;All-Screen&#039; iPhone Under-Display Camera Enters Development</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-screen-iphone-under-display-camera-enters-development.2412943/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade Gains Disney Dreamlight Valley, Puzzle &amp; Dragons Story, and Sonic Dream Team</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-arcade-game-additions-december-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-gains-disney-dreamlight-valley-puzzle-dragons-story-and-sonic-dream-team.2412925/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:55:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-arcade-game-additions-december-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> gaming service with several new titles, including <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/disney-dreamlight-valley/id6456945575">Disney Dreamlight Valley</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sonic-dream-team/id1609094795">Sonic Dream Team</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/puzzle-dragons-story/id1636844853">Puzzle & Dragons Story</a>, and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/turmoil/id6446276883">Turmoil+</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/apple-arcade-orange-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-748620" /><br/>
Disney Dreamlight Valley is a life simulation game starring Disney characters, and it has previously been available on console platforms. The &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; version of the game includes the base version and the A Rift in Time expansion that is a paid option on other platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to other versions of the game, the &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; version does not have in-app purchases and thus does not include Star Path seasons or the Premium Shop.<br/>
<br/>
Sonic Dream Team is a racing game that stars popular Sonic characters, while Puzzle &amp; Dragons Story is an RPG adventure match-3 game. Turmoil+ is an oil rush simulation game that tasks players with digging oil to make money and grow the nearby town.<br/>
<br/>
Many of these games were <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/8-new-games-and-more-than-50-updates-coming-to-apple-arcade-this-holiday-season/">announced back in November</a> following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">October price increase</a> to the &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; service. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; now costs &#36;6.99 per month in the United States, up from &#36;4.99 per month. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games are free from all in-app purchases and ads.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-arcade-game-additions-december-2023/">Apple Arcade Gains Disney Dreamlight Valley, Puzzle &amp; Dragons Story, and Sonic Dream Team</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-gains-disney-dreamlight-valley-puzzle-dragons-story-and-sonic-dream-team.2412925/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Popular Adventure Game &#039;Stray&#039; Now Available for Apple Silicon Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/stray-apple-silicon-macs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-adventure-game-stray-now-available-for-apple-silicon-macs.2412922/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:12:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/stray-apple-silicon-macs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Adventure game "Stray," which is designed to let players take on the role of a daring orange cat, is available for download on the Mac as of today.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="STRAY Launch Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4uP2MyUL49s" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Though the game was first released in 2022, it has been limited to Windows machines and PlayStation and Xbox consoles until today.<br/>
<br/>
In this third-person adventure title, a stray cat's curiosity causes him to get stuck in a walled city filled with robots and mutant bacteria, and the aim in the game is to get back up to the surface using B-12, the cat's drone companion.<br/>
<br/>
Stray asks players to solve puzzles, bypass obstacles, and complete quests while avoiding security bots and evil bacteria. The game is platform-based, so players will need to climb up various obstacles and interact with the environment to open up new pathways.<br/>
<br/>
Since the main character is a cat, players can sneak, sleep, meow at robots, and nuzzle up to NPCs. Stray is limited to Apple silicon Macs, and it uses Metal Upscaling for accelerated graphics performance and high-quality visuals.<br/>
<br/>
Stray can be <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stray/id6451498949?mt=12">downloaded from the Mac App Store</a> for &#36;30.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/stray-apple-silicon-macs/">Popular Adventure Game &#039;Stray&#039; Now Available for Apple Silicon Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-adventure-game-stray-now-available-for-apple-silicon-macs.2412922/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s First iPhone SE Now Considered Vintage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-original-iphone-se-vintage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-iphone-se-now-considered-vintage.2412918/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-original-iphone-se-vintage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> to its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201624">vintage and obsolete products list</a>. The first version of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; came out in March 2016, which means it has been seven years since it launched.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iphone-se-2016.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925333" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; was sold until September 2018, so it has been five years since it was last available for sale, making it eligible for Apple's vintage designation. Products are marked as vintage five years after the device was last sold by Apple, while products are marked as obsolete at the seven year point.<br/>
<br/>
Vintage devices are not guaranteed to be eligible for repairs through Apple or Apple Authorized Service Providers, though Apple will offer repairs if the parts are available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has continued on with the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; line, and today, it continues to be the only <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> fingerprint sensor. There have been three generations released to date, with the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3 introduced in March 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Apple today has also marked the second-generation 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> as vintage, as well as the special edition Mickey Solo3 Wireless headphones. The Powerbeats 2 and Solo2 Wireless headphones are now considered obsolete.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-original-iphone-se-vintage/">Apple&#039;s First iPhone SE Now Considered Vintage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-iphone-se-now-considered-vintage.2412918/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Fixes Bug Preventing Wireless Charging From Working in Some Vehicles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/ios-17-2-wireless-charging-bug-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-fixes-bug-preventing-wireless-charging-from-working-in-some-vehicles.2412907/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:26:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/ios-17-2-wireless-charging-bug-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 17.2 addresses a bug that was preventing some iPhones from wirelessly charging on the wireless charging pads included in some vehicles, according to Apple's release notes for the iOS 17.2 RC <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-rc-to-developers/">that came out today</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/pacifica-2021-wireless-charging.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1005" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-788160" /><br/>
There <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-15-gm-charging-issue/">have been multiple complaints</a> from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> owners who have had charging issues in their Chevrolet, Cadillac, and Buick vehicles. In some of these cars, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> placed on the wireless charging pad would either not charge at all or start to charge and then stop.<br/>
<br/>
Most of the complaints were from &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; owners, and came after the iOS 17.1 update. General Motors said in November that it was aware of an issue and investigating the problem.<br/>
<br/>
This is the second charging-related bug fix that Apple has implemented in recent weeks. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/">iOS 17.1.1 update</a> that came out in early November addressed an issue that caused some &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models charged in BMW vehicles to lose NFC functionality.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 is expected to see a public release next week. The update also adds the Journal app, a Translate Action button option for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, new features in Messages, Weather and Clock widgets, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-rc-to-developers/">and more</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/ios-17-2-wireless-charging-bug-fix/">iOS 17.2 Fixes Bug Preventing Wireless Charging From Working in Some Vehicles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-fixes-bug-preventing-wireless-charging-from-working-in-some-vehicles.2412907/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b34/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware.2412901/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:28:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b34/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware update for both the Lightning and USB-C versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2. The new firmware is version 6B34, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b32/">6B32 firmware</a> introduced in November.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not provide details on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware beyond "bug fixes and other improvements," so it is unclear what's new in the update, but prior software releases have been refining functionality introduced in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> such as Adaptive Audio.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not give customers instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌AirPods‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the firmware release, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b34/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware.2412901/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
