<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 09:03:40 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Woot Discounts Apple Pencil Pro to New Record Low &#36;79.99 Price, USB-C Apple Pencil to &#36;49.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/29/woot-apple-pencil-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/woot-discounts-apple-pencil-pro-to-new-record-low-79-99-price-usb-c-apple-pencil-to-49-99.2454268/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 07:21:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/29/woot-apple-pencil-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot today has introduced a pair of solid discounts on the <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142085?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcomputers.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-pencil">Apple Pencil Pro and USB-C Apple Pencil</a> in New (Open Box) condition, providing new all-time low discounts on each model. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-pencil-pro-dark-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970551" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the Apple Pencil Pro for <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142085?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcomputers.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-pencil-pro%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00, and the USB-C Apple Pencil for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142085?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcomputers.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-pencil-usb-c-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"><strong>&#36;49.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;79.00. Both of these beat Amazon's current discount prices by about &#36;20, and they represent new record low prices on each model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142085?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcomputers.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-pencil-pro%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142085?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcomputers.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-pencil-usb-c-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>Apple Pencil (USB-C) for &#36;49.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Both accessories come in New (Open Box) condition, meaning they are expected to be in excellent condition, but are not guaranteed to come in the traditional retail packaging from Apple. They also include at least 120 days remaining of the original Apple warranty.<br/>
<br/>
You can find out which iPad is compatible with each Apple Pencil by <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/108937">visiting Apple's website</a>. The Apple Pencil Pro is compatible with the 11-inch M4 iPad Pro, 13-inch M4 iPad Pro, 11-inch M2/M3 iPad Air, 13-inch M2/M3 iPad Air, and iPad mini 7.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/29/woot-apple-pencil-pro/">Woot Discounts Apple Pencil Pro to New Record Low &#36;79.99 Price, USB-C Apple Pencil to &#36;49.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/woot-discounts-apple-pencil-pro-to-new-record-low-79-99-price-usb-c-apple-pencil-to-49-99.2454268/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: WWDC 2025 Announced, iPhone 17 Pro and iOS 19 Rumors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/29/top-stories-wwdc-2025-announced/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-wwdc-2025-announced-iphone-17-pro-and-ios-19-rumors-and-more.2454266/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/29/top-stories-wwdc-2025-announced/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's big developer event is a little over two months away, and rumors about what we can expect to see in Apple's next major operating system updates are becoming increasingly frequent.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/top-stories-2025-03-29.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997023" /><br/>
A public release of iOS 18.4 is also imminent with a number of updates and improvements, although we won't be getting the major Apple Intelligence Siri upgrades that had reportedly been planned for this update. This week also saw updated rumors about the iPhone 17 Pro models coming later this year and the first foldable iPhone likely coming as soon as next year, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces WWDC 2025 Event for June 9 to 13</h2><br/>
Apple this week announced that its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">36th annual Worldwide Developers Conference will begin on Monday, June 9, and run through on Friday, June 13</a>. As with WWDC events since 2020, WWDC 2025 will primarily be an online event that is open to all developers at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-WWDC25-event-branding_big.jpg.large_2x.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996564" /><br/>
WWDC 2025 will kick off with the traditional keynote on June 9, where Apple will unveil iOS 19, iPadOS 19, macOS 16, tvOS 19, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Pro Launching Later This Year With These 10 New Features</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max are not expected to launch until September, there are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/23/iphone-17-pro-10-rumored-features/">already plenty of rumors about the devices</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iPhone-17-Pro-34ths-Perspective.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996702" /><br/>
The most immediately obvious design change will be a large rectangular camera bump across the top of the device's rear, and it looks like the rear shell will be a combination of aluminum and glass. Other rumored features include camera improvements, an A19 Pro chip, a larger battery, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Top 5 New Features Coming in iOS 18.4</h2><br/>
Apple this week seeded <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-rc-2/">release candidate versions of iOS 18.4 and related updates</a>, signaling that a public release is likely to happen sometime next week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988289" /><br/>
While some of the Apple Intelligence updates we were expecting for iOS 18.4 have been delayed, there are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/ios-18-4-top-5-features/">still a number of improvements coming with the release</a>, including Priority Notifications, expanded device support for visual intelligence, new emoji, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Here's What Apple's iOS 19 Messages App Might Look Like</h2><br/>
Leaker Jon Prosser has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/ios-19-messages-app-mockup/">teased a glimpse of what the Messages app might look like in iOS 19</a> when it arrives later this year, and he's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/ios-19-visionos-like-design-rumors/">followed it up with a full video</a> outlining what he says he has seen with some additional design changes for the update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-19-messages-app.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996605" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has warned, however, that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/gurman-ios-19-mockups-not-accurate/">at least some of the images "aren't representative"</a> of what's actually coming in iOS 19, with Prosser's information perhaps based on "very old builds" or "vague descriptions."<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that design changes in iOS 19 may include adoption of some of the "glassy" elements found in visionOS and Apple's recent app releases such as Apple Sports and Apple Invites, an idea that has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/wwdc-2025-logo-hints-at-ios-19-design/">reinforced by the official WWDC 2025 logo</a> unveiled this week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max to Gain Lossless Audio and Low-Latency Audio in iOS 18.4</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 and a related firmware update will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/airpods-max-lossless-audio-coming-april/">bring some new capabilities to Apple's AirPods Max headphones with USB-C</a>, including support for lossless audio and ultra-low latency audio. As part of the update, wired connectivity for AirPods Max that was dropped with the launch of the USB-C models will return, and Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-selling-usb-c-to-3-5mm-audio-cable/">now selling a USB-C to 3.5mm audio cable</a> to help enable that feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18.4-airpods-max-2024-colors-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996305" /><br/>
While the addition of lossless audio may not mean much to many users <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/airpods-max-lossless-audio-overhyped/">given Apple's previous claims about compressed AAC audio from Apple Music being "virtually indistinguishable" from lossless audio</a>, some demanding users like musicians and sound mixers will be able to benefit from the upgrades.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Foldable iPhone Expected to Launch Next Year, Costing Around &#36;2,000</h2><br/>
Rumors about Apple's foldable iPhone are continuing to mount, and they're lining up behind a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/foldable-iphone-to-launch-next-year/">launch as soon as late next year with a price tag of around &#36;2,000 if not more</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Iridescent-Search.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995557" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman notes that Apple will leverage many of the advancements coming in this year's "iPhone 17 Air," including display, chip, battery, and modem updates that will all help Apple fit everything into a super-slim chassis for the foldable model.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/mar-27-2025">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/29/top-stories-wwdc-2025-announced/">Top Stories: WWDC 2025 Announced, iPhone 17 Pro and iOS 19 Rumors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-wwdc-2025-announced-iphone-17-pro-and-ios-19-rumors-and-more.2454266/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Six Things to Know About Apple&#039;s Upcoming Foldable iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-foldable-iphone-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-things-to-know-about-apples-upcoming-foldable-iphone.2454254/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:54:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-foldable-iphone-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We've been hearing rumors about a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> for almost a decade now, but it looks like we might finally see the device come to fruition in 2026. We're going to be waiting many more months for the foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but so far we're hearing good things.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Homescreen.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995585" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li><strong>Apple wants to make it creaseless</strong>. It's taken Apple multiple years to design a foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that it's satisfied with because Apple wants to get away from the pesky crease that impacts most foldable smartphones on the market. Apple is aiming for an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-2026-foldable-phone-has-no-crease/">entirely creaseless</a> look so you won't be distracted by a visible line going through the middle of the display.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>It'll open like a book</strong>. Based on the myriad rumors we've heard, Apple experimented with multiple designs. There was talk last year that Apple would go with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/23/foldable-iphone-2026-report/">a clamshell design</a> that opens top to bottom, like the Galaxy Z Flip. That's possibly something we'll see in the future, but now it's sounding like Apple's first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will have the book-like design we've seen in foldables like the Galaxy Z Fold. iOS isn't designed for a horizontal orientation, so this is going to require some major software updates. Apple <em>is</em> rumored to be working to redesign <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>, iPadOS 19, and macOS 16 to be more consistent cross-platform, and that kind of design would work well when you need an operating system that works seamlessly in both vertical and horizontal orientations.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>For size, imagine the iPad mini</strong>. When it's closed, Apple's foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is rumored to have a 5.5-inch outer display, which is smaller than current &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models that start at 6.1 inches. When opened, though, it will be 7.8 inches, which isn't too far off from the old 7.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>. Picture the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; in horizontal orientation, or put two 6.1-inch iPhones side by side to get an idea of how big the display might be.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>It's going to be thick and thin</strong>. Apple is going to use some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a> tech for the foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and it could be as thin as 4.8mm when it's opened up. That's even thinner than the 5.1-inch 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, which is Apple's thinnest device to date. When closed, though, it'll be somewhere around 9mm to 9.5mm, which is chunky.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>It might have Touch ID.</strong> This is a weird one, but Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> says Apple might use a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> power button instead of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>. If Apple can't slim down that front-facing TrueDepth camera module enough to get the screen to an acceptable thinness, &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; could work instead.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>It's going to cost you</strong>. Foldable smartphones are far from cheap, even from Android manufacturers. Apple's version is going to be expensive, with rumors suggesting it will be priced somewhere around &#36;2,000 to &#36;2,500.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
These are just the current rumors, and in the years before a device actually launches, information can be all over the place due to Apple's experimentation. The details we're hearing are starting to firm up, but there could be changes before it comes out. And given Apple's track record lately, it might never be released.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, it looks like we could get the first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; right around late 2026, so we might be hearing more in the coming months as we get into the 2026 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; rumor cycle.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-foldable-iphone-features/">Six Things to Know About Apple&#039;s Upcoming Foldable iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-things-to-know-about-apples-upcoming-foldable-iphone.2454254/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Expected Next Week - Here Are the Release Notes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/ios-18-4-coming-next-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-expected-next-week-here-are-the-release-notes.2454251/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:01:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/ios-18-4-coming-next-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the second release candidate of iOS 18.4 that Apple seeded out today, the company finally provided us with release notes that give a full rundown on what to expect.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988289" /><br/>
There's an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> app, new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features for notifications and additional language support, plus an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a> Food feature for &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers, and several updates that should improve the functionality of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app. Apple's release notes are below.<br/>
<blockquote><strong>Apple Intelligence (All iPhone 16 models, iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max)</strong><br/>
- Priority notifications appear at the top of your notifications, highlighting important notifications that may require your immediate attention<br/>
- Sketch is now available as an additional style option in Image Playground, allowing you to create gorgeous sketch drawings<br/>
- Apple Intelligence features support 8 additional languages and 2 additional English locales, including English (India, Singapore), French (France, Canada), German (Germany), Italian (Italy), Japanese (Japan), Korean (South Korea), Portuguese (Brazil), Simplified Chinese, and Spanish (Spain, Latin America, US)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Apple Vision Pro App</strong><br/>
- The new Apple Vision Pro app, automatically installed for users with Apple Vision Pro, helps you discover new content, spatial experiences, and quickly access information about your device<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Apple News+</strong><br/>
- Recipes from some of the world's best recipe publishers are now available on Apple News+<br/>
- Recipe Catalog allows you to browse or search to find the perfect dish and save it to your Saved Recipes<br/>
- Cooking mode lets you easily follow step-by-step directions<br/>
- The Food section also includes stories about restaurants, kitchen tips, healthy eating, and more<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Photos</strong><br/>
- New filters to show or hide items that are not contained in an album, or synced from a Mac or PC, in the Library view in Photos<br/>
- Reorder items in the Media Types and Utilities collections in Photos<br/>
- Consistent filtering options in all collections, including the ability to sort by oldest or newest first in Photos<br/>
- Option to sort albums by Date Modified in Photos<br/>
- Ability to disable "Recently Viewed" and "Recently Shared" collections in Photos Settings<br/>
- Hidden photos are no longer included for import to Mac or a PC if Use Face ID is enabled in Photos settings<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update also includes the following enhancements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Safari recent search suggestions help you quickly get back to previous search topics when starting a new query<br/>
- Setup Assistant streamlines steps parents need to take to create a Child Account for a kid in their family, and enables child-appropriate default settings if parents prefer to complete setting up a Child Account later<br/>
- Screen Time App Limits persist even after a child uninstalls and reinstalls an app<br/>
- App Store includes summaries for user reviews so you can get helpful insights from other users at a glance<br/>
- Pause and resume of an app download or update on App Store without losing progress<br/>
- New widgets for Podcasts including a Followed Shows widget to track your favorite shows and a Library widget to get to your most used sections, such as Latest Episodes, Saved, and Downloaded<br/>
- Ambient Music offers the ability to instantly play music from Control Center, giving access to a set of hand-curated playlists that offer soundtracks for daily life<br/>
- Apple Fitness+ Collections can now be added to Library<br/>
- Matter-compatible robot vacuum cleaners can be controlled in the Home app as well as be added to scenes and automations<br/>
- Support for 10 new system languages including Bangla, Gujarati, Kannada, Malayalam, Marathi, Odia, Punjabi, Tamil, Telugu, and Urdu<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit:<br/>
https://support.apple.com/100100</blockquote><br/>
Apple's release notes don't actually include all of the new features that were found in the update during the beta testing period, including some new Control Center options and a handful of new emoji characters.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.4 is expected in early April, which is actually next week. It's looking like Apple could release the update on Tuesday, April 1, given that we got two release candidates this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/ios-18-4-coming-next-week/">iOS 18.4 Expected Next Week - Here Are the Release Notes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-expected-next-week-here-are-the-release-notes.2454251/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 Release Candidate With Priority Notifications, Ambient Music and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-rc-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-ios-18-4-and-ipados-18-4-release-candidate-with-priority-notifications-ambient-music-and-more.2454238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:12:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-rc-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second release candidate versions of upcoming iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-beta-4/">coming a week</a> a few days after Apple released the first RC.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984205" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Generic-iOS-18.4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 can be downloaded from the Settings app on a compatible device by going to General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 18.4, Apple is adding the Priority Notifications <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> feature, which is designed to determine which of your notifications are the most important, highlighting them in an easy-to-see dedicated section on the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
The update includes a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ Food section for &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers, plus it adds the Sketch style to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> so you can generate images that look hand drawn. &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; is also available in more languages, including French, German, Italian, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish, Japanese, Korean, and Chinese (simplified), along with localized English for Singapore and India.<br/>
<br/>
There are new emoji characters, and a dedicated Vision Pro app that allows Vision Pro owners to find and download content, manage the headset, control guest experiences, and more, right from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Mail Categorization has expanded to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and there's a new Ambient Music feature for playing relaxing music from Control Center. There are a number of other smaller features too, with details <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features/">available in our iOS 18.4 features guide</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to release iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 in early April, potentially as soon as next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-rc-2/">Apple Seeds Second iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 Release Candidate With Priority Notifications, Ambient Music and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-ios-18-4-and-ipados-18-4-release-candidate-with-priority-notifications-ambient-music-and-more.2454238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Save Time Resizing Images on Mac With a Quick Action</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/save-time-resizing-images-on-mac-quick-action/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/save-time-resizing-images-on-mac-with-a-quick-action.2454231/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:33:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/save-time-resizing-images-on-mac-quick-action&#038;post_date=1743186790/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Automator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Resizing images in macOS is easily done in the Preview app, but if your daily workflow requires you to scale images to a specific size – for uploading to a blog, for example – then using an image resize Quick Action is a much faster way of getting the job done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/finder-images-folder.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995683" /><br/>
In this article, we'll show you how to use the Automator app to create a simple Quick Action that, once saved, will have you resizing images in just a couple of clicks, without even going near an image editing app. Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<!--more--><br/>
<h2>Create a Resize Image Quick Action</h2><ol><br/>
<li>Launch Automator from the <strong>Applications</strong> folder.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/finder-automator.jpg" alt="" width="2846" height="1404" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995685" /><br/>
<li>Click <strong>New Document</strong>, then choose <strong>Quick Action</strong> as the type of your document.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/new-quick-action.jpg" alt="automator" width="2204" height="1576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996995" /><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Files and Folders</strong> in the Actions sidebar, then drag <strong>Get Specified Finder Items</strong> to the workflow area.</li><br/>
<li>Click the <strong>Workflow received current</strong> dropdown at the top and select <strong>image files</strong> from the menu.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/files-and-folders-automator.jpg" alt="automator" width="2408" height="1622" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996998" /><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Photos</strong> in the Actions sidebar, then drag <strong>Scale Images</strong> to the workflow area.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/scale-images-automator.jpg" alt="automator" width="2408" height="1622" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996999" /><br/>
<li>Automator will prompt you to add a Copy Finder Items Action to save the original files in a separate folder. We're sticking to a simple workflow of resizing images here, so we click <strong>Don't Add</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/do-not-add-copy-files-folder.jpg" alt="automator" width="1637" height="841" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997000" /><br/>
<li>In the Scale Images action panel, type the width that you want to resize your images to. We're going to use 1200 pixels.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/scale-images-width.jpg" alt="automator" width="1630" height="202" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997001" /><br/>
<li>In the Automator menu bar, select <strong>File ➝ Save...</strong>, call your new Quick Action "Resize Image", then click <strong>Save</strong>.</li></ol><h2>Use Your New Quick Action</h2><br/>
Next time you want to resize an image, simply right-click (or Ctrl-click) the item in Finder and select <strong>Quick Actions ➝ Resize Image</strong> from the contextual dropdown menu. You can also drag a selection box over several images and resize them all in one go using the Quick Action.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/quick-action-context-menu.jpg" alt="automator" width="2568" height="1522" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997002" /><br/>
<h2>Add a Keyboard Shortcut</h2><br/>
Why not assign a key shortcut to your image resize Quick Action to speed up the process? To do so, launch System Settings, select <strong>Keyboard</strong> in the sidebar, then click the <strong>Keyboard Shortcuts...</strong> button. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/settings-keyboard-shortcuts.jpg" alt="automator" width="1570" height="1328" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997005" /><br/>
Select <strong>Services</strong> from the sidebar, expand the "Pictures" checklist, and you should find <strong>Resize Image</strong> near the bottom of the list. Double-click the line item where it says "none", then enter your custom key combination. Click <strong>Done</strong> when you're finished.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/resize-image-shortcut.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="1434" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997008" /><br/>
By integrating this Quick Action into your macOS workflow, you should be able to efficiently resize images with just a few clicks, saving you time and enhancing your productivity. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/automator/">Automator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/save-time-resizing-images-on-mac-quick-action/">Save Time Resizing Images on Mac With a Quick Action</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/save-time-resizing-images-on-mac-with-a-quick-action.2454231/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods, iPad, and More in Amazon&#039;s Big Spring Sale, Plus Save on Samsung&#039;s New Monitors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-3-28-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-ipad-and-more-in-amazons-big-spring-sale-plus-save-on-samsungs-new-monitors.2454228/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 07:40:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-3-28-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Most of the best Apple deals of this week can be found in Amazon's ongoing <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fevents%2Fbigspringsale">Big Spring Sale</a>, including record low prices on AirPods, iPad Air, Apple Pencil, AirTag, and more. You can find more details about the Big Spring Sale in our dedicated posts on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Apple product deals</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/26/amazon-big-spring-sale-accessory-deals/">Accessory discounts</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-new-purple-hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960078" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>OtterBox MagSafe Charging Stand</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/woot-otterbox-charger.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996987" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take 85% off OtterBox 15W MagSafe Charging Stand</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fnew-otterbox-15w-magsafe-wireless-charging-stand-bundle">Woot</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fnew-otterbox-15w-magsafe-wireless-charging-stand-bundle"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">85% OFF</div>OtterBox MagSafe Charging Stand for &#36;14.95</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot today introduced a huge discount on OtterBox's 15W MagSafe Charging Stand for iPhone, available for &#36;14.95, down from &#36;99.95. This accessory is in new condition and comes with a 90 day Woot limited warranty, 20W wall charger, and a 2m USB-C cable in the box.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/airpods-4-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996973" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;79 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJJDFPR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;479.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
AirPods 4 dropped to &#36;99.99 this week on Amazon, and they are still available at this all-time low price. If you want the model with ANC, they're on sale for &#36;148.99, down from &#36;179.00. There are also solid discounts on AirPods Pro 2 and AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/samsung-odyssey-g9.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996974" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off pre-orders for Samsung's new monitors</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/xbdl4r39kwqy9">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/26/samsung-announces-new-monitors/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/xbdl4r39kwqy9"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Samsung's New Gaming Monitors</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung this week <a href="https://news.samsung.com/us/samsung-launches-next-gen-odyssey-gaming-monitors-showcase-immersive-3d-oled-excellence-now-available-to-reserve/">announced</a> the launch of a few next-generation Odyssey gaming monitors, and you can <a href="https://howl.link/xbdl4r39kwqy9">get a &#36;50 discount</a> right now if you make a reservation for pre-orders. The new lineup includes the Odyssey 3D, Odyssey OLED G8, Ultrawide Odyssey G9, and the new ViewFinity S8.<br/>
<br/>
We're also still tracking a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/samsung-spring-sale-connected-health/">few deals on Samsung's connected health products</a> like the Galaxy Watch and Galaxy Ring, as well as savings on Samsung TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/apple-watch-series-10-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996975" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;100 off Apple Watch Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week has <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">numerous all-time low prices</a> on Apple Watch Series 10, including both GPS and cellular models. You'll find &#36;100 off both 42mm and 46mm GPS Series 10 models in multiple case colors and band styles, and this time the deals do not require any coupon codes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m3-ipad-air-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996976" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;70 off new iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76QBLQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;61 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;738.08</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Last week Apple launched the new M3 iPad Air, and Amazon has been providing solid launch window discounts on numerous models this week. You can find up to &#36;70 off these tablets on Amazon, with prices starting at &#36;549.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m4-macbook-air-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996977" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off M4 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC3WW5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC3WW5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD96R5S%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9XBK7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9VLQ4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;55 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,344.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCDJ21%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon introduced multiple discounts on the M4 MacBook Air this week, offering up to &#36;100 off numerous models of the computer. For some of these, you'll need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/apple-pencil-pro-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996978" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;30 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Another all-time low price available on Amazon this week was on the Apple Pencil Pro, and it's still available for &#36;99.00 today, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/airtag-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996979" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;29 off AirTag 4-pack</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/amazon-big-spring-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;69.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirTag 4-Pack on sale for &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.00. This is a solid second-best price, and you can find the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">1-Pack on sale</a> as well on Amazon, available for &#36;24.00, down from &#36;29.00.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-3-28-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods, iPad, and More in Amazon&#039;s Big Spring Sale, Plus Save on Samsung&#039;s New Monitors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-ipad-and-more-in-amazons-big-spring-sale-plus-save-on-samsungs-new-monitors.2454228/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ &#039;Friday Night Baseball&#039; Returns With New Documentary Series</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-tv-friday-night-baseball-returns/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-friday-night-baseball-returns-with-new-documentary-series.2454227/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 06:36:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-tv-friday-night-baseball-returns/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's "Friday Night Baseball" weekly doubleheader returns to Apple TV+ on Friday evening, and the company's streaming service is marking the occasion by premiering a new "<a href="https://tv.apple.com/show/fight-for-glory-2024-world-series/umc.cmc.6x620ggn8n2yamemiuk7ys8yt">Fight for Glory: 2024 World Series</a>" docuseries. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/baseball-fight-for-glory.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996968" /><br/>
The three-episode run follows the Dodgers and the Yankees through the postseason, providing viewers with behind-the-scenes access to superstar players, managers, and their families, as they attempt to claim Major League Baseball's throne in the playoffs. All three one-hour episodes are available today.<br/>
<br/>
"Friday Night Baseball" comes bundled with an Apple TV+ subscription at no extra charge. In the U.S., Apple TV+ is priced at &#36;9.99 per month or &#36;99 annually, and it's also part of every Apple One bundle alongside other Apple services.<br/>
<br/>
A schedule of games for the first half of the season is available in <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/03/friday-night-baseball-returns-to-apple-tv-plus-on-march-28/">Apple's press release</a> from earlier this month. <br/>
<br/>
Next month, Apple is also releasing a new, free immersive video called "VIP: Yankee Stadium" for Apple Vision Pro users that will feature "an all-access pass to one of the world's most iconic sports venues." The video covers the June 2024 match between the New York Yankees and Los Angeles Dodgers, and will not require an Apple TV+ subscription to watch. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/apple-tv-friday-night-baseball-returns/">Apple TV+ &#039;Friday Night Baseball&#039; Returns With New Documentary Series</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-friday-night-baseball-returns-with-new-documentary-series.2454227/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All-Glass Apple Watch – A First Step Toward Jony Ive&#039;s Dream iPhone?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/all-glass-apple-watch-before-glass-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-glass-apple-watch-–-a-first-step-toward-jony-ives-dream-iphone.2454225/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 05:28:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/all-glass-apple-watch-before-glass-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An iPhone sculpted from a single seamless sheet of glass... It's a vision that was once pursued by former Apple design chief Jony Ive. While the dream was never realized, Apple could take its first tangible step toward it with an all-glass Apple Watch. Or at least that's what one leaker has today suggested. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Watch-Series-10-Jet-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965089" /><br/>
According to the Weibo account <a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/PkEqB8dkU">Instant Digital</a>, before an all-glass iPhone ever hits the market, we could see an Apple Watch with a touch-interactive, fully-glass frame that blurs the boundaries between screen and enclosure. <br/>
<br/>
The Chinese leaker provided no evidence to back their claim. However, the concept appears in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/11/18/apple-researching-all-glass-designs/">existing Apple patents</a> that describe wearable devices with glass enclosures and integrated touch zones, pointing to a future where gesture control and minimalism converge in a typically Apple design.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's 2021 patent filings don't appear to indicate the concept is in the company's immediate plans, but they do show some of Apple's specific areas of research and development. That said, making an all-glass Apple Watch would be a major design and engineering leap for Apple that would not be without its challenges. <br/>
<br/>
The most obvious hurdle is durability. Glass may look sleek and futuristic, but it's also more fragile than the titanium, metal, and ceramic used in existing and previous Apple Watch models. Watches are constantly bumped, scraped, and dropped in daily wear, so Apple would need to develop a type of glass that's much stronger than what we're used to. For example, ultra-strong composites or laminated structures could potentially reinforce a new kind of glass that can withstand drops, scratches, and flexing over time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-glass-enclosures-patent-other-devices.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826171" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple patent envisions an all-glass Apple Watch, amongst other products</em></div><br/>
Touch interaction is another tricky area. If the entire frame was made of glass and responded to touch, Apple would have to make sure it could accurately tell the difference between a deliberate tap and an accidental brush against your sleeve. And because the Apple Watch is so small, the placement of those touch zones would have to be incredibly precise. <br/>
<br/>
Then there are questions about where key components like buttons, sensors, and antennas would go if the whole case was a single piece of glass. Making something like that at scale while ensuring it was flawless would also require some serious breakthroughs in how the device was manufactured.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple can solve these kinds of challenges, an all-glass Apple Watch could be a first step toward the seamless, futuristic devices long imagined by designers like Ive. But don't hold your breath just yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/all-glass-apple-watch-before-glass-iphone/">All-Glass Apple Watch – A First Step Toward Jony Ive&#039;s Dream iPhone?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-glass-apple-watch-–-a-first-step-toward-jony-ives-dream-iphone.2454225/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram&#039;s New Fast-Forward Feature Lets You Skip Ahead in Reels</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/instagram-new-fast-forward-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagrams-new-fast-forward-feature-lets-you-skip-ahead-in-reels.2454223/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 04:12:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/instagram-new-fast-forward-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram has introduced a new fast-forward feature for Reels that allows users to speed through videos by holding down on either edge of the screen. The action plays content at double speed, similar to a feature already available on TikTok.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Instagram-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786417" /><br/>
The Meta-owned platform initially limited Reels to 15-second clips but has since expanded the maximum duration to three minutes, making playback controls increasingly necessary for users who want to quickly navigate through longer content.<br/>
<br/>
To use the new feature, simply press and hold on the right or left side of their screen while watching a Reel. The video will then play at 2x speed, enabling you to skip to the parts that interest you most.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram users have become accustomed to consuming quick, bite-sized content, so the ability to fast-forward increases the likelihood that they will watch Reels through to completion rather than scrolling past longer videos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/2x-Speed_Still_2.jpeg" alt="" width="1440" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996956" /><br/>
It's the latest in a series of TikTok-inspired features that Instagram has added in its ongoing effort to compete in the short-form video market. Previously, Instagram introduced Remix, a direct copy of TikTok's Duet functionality, which allows users to create content alongside existing videos.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/03/27/instagram-now-lets-you-speed-up-videos-just-like-on-tiktok">TechCrunch</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/instagram-new-fast-forward-feature/">Instagram&#039;s New Fast-Forward Feature Lets You Skip Ahead in Reels</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagrams-new-fast-forward-feature-lets-you-skip-ahead-in-reels.2454223/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Foldable Display Said to Feature iPad-Style 4:3 Aspect Ratio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/iphone-foldable-display-ipad-style-aspect-ratio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-foldable-display-said-to-feature-ipad-style-4-3-aspect-ratio.2454219/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 03:44:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/iphone-foldable-display-ipad-style-aspect-ratio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming "iPhone Fold" will feature a foldable screen with a 4:3 aspect ratio, according to a Chinese leaker who previously leaked the book-style device's display dimensions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Homescreen.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995585" /><br/>
The Weibo-based account <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PkBXPoR6V">Digital Chat Station</a> claims that Apple will adopt a "roughly" 4:3 aspect ratio on the inner display in order to achieve consistency between the outer display, as well as to ensure parity with existing iPad software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's iPad and iPad Pro models have maintained a 4:3 aspect ratio across generations. The ratio offers a balanced experience in both portrait and landscape orientation, making it particularly versatile for reading/browsing and split-screen multitasking. Only the 8.3-inch iPad mini has deviated from the traditional ratio, instead using an approximate 3:2 ratio due to its slightly taller and narrower dimensions.<br/>
<br/>
Digital Chat Station previously revealed the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/alleged-display-sizes-apple-foldable-iphone/">alleged dimensions</a> of the iPhone Fold, claiming the device has a 5.5-inch outer screen and an inner folding 7.8-inch screen. Reputable Apple industry analyst Ming-Chi Kuo has since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/kuo-apple-foldable-iphone-book-style-2000/">corroborated</a> the dimensions, additionally describing the inner screen as "crease-free."<br/>
<br/>
Kuo says the device will feature a titanium alloy casing with a hinge made of metallic glass, and it will have a dual-lens rear camera with a front-facing camera for both folded and unfolded states.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, Kuo says that the phone will forgo Face ID authentication, instead using a Touch ID side button as a means to save precious internal space. It will also be positioned as a "true AI-driven phone," with the larger screens allowing for a better multi-tasking AI experience.<br/>
<br/>
Most estimates put the selling price of the iPhone Fold at around &#36;2,000-&#36;2,500 in the United States. <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman expects Apple's first foldable device to arrive as soon as next year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/iphone-foldable-display-ipad-style-aspect-ratio/">iPhone Foldable Display Said to Feature iPad-Style 4:3 Aspect Ratio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-foldable-display-said-to-feature-ipad-style-4-3-aspect-ratio.2454219/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Facebook&#039;s New iPhone App Feature Turns the Clock Back to 2007</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/facebook-app-friends-tab/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/facebooks-new-iphone-app-feature-turns-the-clock-back-to-2007.2454189/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:59:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/facebook-app-friends-tab/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Facebook</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the mid-to-late 2000s, Facebook was all about staying connected with friends and family. However, as the social media platform added new features and grew over time, that core experience began to get drowned out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Facebook-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786419" /><br/>
That changes starting now, according to Meta, which today <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2025/03/bringing-magic-of-friends-back-to-facebook/">introduced</a> a new feature that will "bring back the joy" of classic Facebook.<br/>
<br/>
Specifically, Meta has redesigned the Friends tab on Facebook to focus on the "magic of friends." The page now shows content from only your Facebook friends, with no recommended content or other distractions. The tab will show your friends' posts, reels, birthdays, and more, and it will continue to show your friend requests too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Facebook-Friends-Tab.jpg" alt="" width="960" height="836" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996943" /><br/>
Until now, the Friends tab only showed your friends requests and people you may know.<br/>
<br/>
The updated Friends tab is rolling out starting today in the U.S. and Canada, so you might not see it right away. The redesigned page appears to be a server-side change, with no update required, but installing the latest version of the app doesn't hurt. To access the tab, tap on your profile picture in the bottom-right corner, and select Friends.<br/>
<br/>
You can pin the Friends tab, so that it is easily accessible from the bottom navigation bar. To do so, tap on your profile picture in the bottom-right corner, and then select Settings & Privacy → Settings → Tab bar → Customize the bar.<br/>
<br/>
Meta promises to introduce other classic Facebook features throughout the year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facebook/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/facebook-app-friends-tab/">Facebook&#039;s New iPhone App Feature Turns the Clock Back to 2007</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/facebooks-new-iphone-app-feature-turns-the-clock-back-to-2007.2454189/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Are You a Nintendo Fan? There&#039;s an iPhone App For That Now</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/nintendo-today-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/are-you-a-nintendo-fan-theres-an-iphone-app-for-that-now.2454184/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:32:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/nintendo-today-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Nintendo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nintendo today released a <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nintendo-today/id6736725704">new iPhone app</a> that can provide you with daily updates about company news, upcoming game releases, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Nintendo-Today-iPhone-App.jpg" alt="" width="1874" height="1050" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996917" /><br/>
Nintendo Today! is available <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nintendo-today/id6736725704">in the App Store</a> for the iPhone for free, and it is also available in the Google Play Store for Android. <br/>
<br/>
After signing into your Nintendo Account, you can scroll through a news feed with video clips, images, and other fun content. There is also a calendar tab that lists upcoming Nintendo Direct presentations, game releases, in-game events, and more. The app offers a Home Screen widget that lets you view the calendar at a glance.<br/>
<br/>
The app will also keep customers informed about Nintendo's upcoming Switch 2 launch.<br/>
<br/>
You can personalize the news feed by selecting your favorite Nintendo games, and you can theme the app's design based on popular Nintendo game franchises, like Super Mario, Animal Crossing, The Legend of Zelda, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Let's-a go!</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nintendo/">Nintendo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/nintendo-today-app/">Are You a Nintendo Fan? There&#039;s an iPhone App For That Now</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/are-you-a-nintendo-fan-theres-an-iphone-app-for-that-now.2454184/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Final Cut Pro for Mac Gains Adjustment Clips, Image Playground Integration and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/final-cut-pro-mac-image-playground/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/final-cut-pro-for-mac-gains-adjustment-clips-image-playground-integration-and-more.2454176/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 10:55:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/final-cut-pro-mac-image-playground/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Final Cut Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated Final Cut Pro, its professional video editing software that runs on the Mac. Version 11.1 of Final Cut Pro includes several new features that improve video editing on the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Final-Cut-Pro-11-Thumb-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-977649" /><br/>
With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>, video editors can use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> to create stylized images, and Magnetic Mask workflows have been streamlined with a new keyboard shortcut to show or hide the Magnetic Mask Organizer. There are also new features for moving markets and naming audio effects, with Apple's release notes listed below.<br/>
<blockquote>- Add color corrections and effects to an adjustment clip above the timeline to apply them to a range of clips at once.<br/>
- Get inspired with Image Playground and use Apple Intelligence to quickly create stylized images based on a description, suggested concepts, or people from your Photos library. (Requires macOS 15.2 or later on Mac models with M1 or later.)<br/>
- Speed up your Magnetic Mask workflows with important bug fixes, performance improvements, and a new keyboard shortcut to show or hide the Magnetic Mask Editor.<br/>
- Use the Quantec QRS (Quantec Room Simulator) effect to create natural and transparent audio reverbs that simulate real acoustic spaces.<br/>
- Stay organized by renaming audio effects in the inspector.<br/>
- Reveal the source of a multicam angle or synced clip in the browser.<br/>
- Move markers in the timeline by dragging them in a clip, or remove markers by dragging them out of a clip.</blockquote><br/>
Apple has also updated its Motion and Compressor software that accompanies Final Cut Pro. Motion has &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; integration, and Compressor offers machine learning-powered frame rate retiming.<br/>
<br/>
Final Cut Pro for the Mac can be <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/final-cut-pro/id424389933?mt=12">downloaded from the Mac App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/final-cut-pro-mac-image-playground/">Final Cut Pro for Mac Gains Adjustment Clips, Image Playground Integration and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/final-cut-pro-for-mac-gains-adjustment-clips-image-playground-integration-and-more.2454176/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates Final Cut Pro for iPad and Final Cut Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/final-cut-pro-ipad-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-final-cut-pro-for-ipad-and-final-cut-camera.2454173/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 10:33:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/final-cut-pro-ipad-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Final Cut Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated both Final Cut Pro for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Final Cut Camera, introducing a handful of useful new features that improve video editing and recording on Apple's mobile devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/final-cut-pro-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-977355" /><br/>
Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; gains support for editing video in portrait orientation, and it includes new keyboard shortcuts. There's also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> integration, and an option to capture video in 50fps.<br/>
<blockquote>- Expand your editing workflows with support for portrait orientation on your iPad.<br/>
- Speed up your editing with keyboard shortcuts to nudge a selection, replace with gap, and lift or overwrite to the primary storyline.<br/>
- Get inspired with Image Playground and use Apple Intelligence to quickly create stylized images based on a description, suggested concepts, or people from your Photos library. (Requires iPad with A17 Pro or M1 and later and iPadOS 18.2 or later.)<br/>
- Capture in 50 fps for additional editing flexibility and delivery options.</blockquote><br/>
The updated version of Final Cut Camera includes support for quickly swapping over to the Telephoto lens on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 14 Pro and later, recording in Spatial Audio on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and later, and recording in 50fps video.<br/>
<blockquote>- Quickly switch to the 48 mm telephoto lens to capture the perfect shot. (Requires iPhone 14 Pro or later.)<br/>
- Play back your Log videos in SDR or HDR with the vibrancy of the original scene by applying the Apple Log LUT. (Requires iPhone 15 Pro or later.)<br/>
- Record videos in Spatial Audio for even more realistic and immersive sound. (Requires iPhone 16.)<br/>
- Capture in 50 fps for additional editing flexibility and delivery options.</blockquote><br/>
Final Cut Camera is software that is designed to let users record from up to four devices with footage imported into Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; <a href="https://www.apple.com/final-cut-pro-for-ipad/">is available</a> for &#36;49 per year or &#36;4.99 per month, while <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/final-cut-camera/id6469552837">Final Cut Camera</a> is free.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/final-cut-pro-ipad-update/">Apple Updates Final Cut Pro for iPad and Final Cut Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-final-cut-pro-for-ipad-and-final-cut-camera.2454173/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second macOS Sequoia 15.4 Release Candidate With Mail Categorization</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-4-rc-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-macos-sequoia-15-4-release-candidate-with-mail-categorization.2454168/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 10:09:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-4-rc-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with a second release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 update for testing purposes. The new RC is available a few days after Apple released the initial RC earlier this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4 brings Mail Categorization to the Mac for the first time, reorganizing the Mail app into dedicated categories like transactions, updates, promotions, and primary, a category that surfaces the most important emails first. The update brings a range of new emoji characters to the Mac. <br/>
<br/>
For <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ subscribers, there is a dedicated News+ Food section with recipes, articles about restaurants, and other related content. There's a new Sketch style in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>, the option to create Memory Movies in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> is expanding to new languages.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to release &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4 in early April, and the RC represents the finalized version of the software that will be launched to the public as long as no issues are found.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-4-rc-2/">Apple Seeds Second macOS Sequoia 15.4 Release Candidate With Mail Categorization</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-macos-sequoia-15-4-release-candidate-with-mail-categorization.2454168/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Starts Notifying WWDC 2025 Swift Student Challenge Winners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/apple-swift-student-challenge-winners-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-starts-notifying-wwdc-2025-swift-student-challenge-winners.2454167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 10:02:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/apple-swift-student-challenge-winners-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today started notifying students who won the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a> Swift Student Challenge, which took place from February 3 to February 23. Students who entered can sign in to Apple's Swift Student Challenge website to see their status.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/2025-Swift-Student-Challenge.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969979" /><br/>
A total of 350 winners have been selected, and the winners are eligible to attend the &zwnj;WWDC 2025&zwnj; special event that will take place at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> on Monday, June 9.<br/>
<br/>
Of the 350, 50 will be named Distinguished Winners, and will be invited to Cupertino, California for a multi-day &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; event that will include the keynote meetup and additional opportunities to meet with Apple engineers and employees.<br/>
<br/>
Those who are not chosen as Distinguished Winners can enter Apple's lottery for a chance to attend the &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; event. Apple is inviting students and developers to apply, but since space is limited, attendees will be selected through a lottery process. Winners will be notified on Thursday, April 3.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I really can&#39;t believe it... I&#39;m a Swift Student Challenge winner!! This was my first time submitting too! Huge congratulations to all the other winners!!<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SwiftStudentChallenge?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SwiftStudentChallenge</a> <a href="https://t.co/Hy2WHs1bob">pic.twitter.com/Hy2WHs1bob</a></p>&mdash; Dylan (@DylanMcD8) <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanMcD8/status/1905304766940426418?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 27, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Swift Student Challenge winners who are not able to attend the &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; event will be able to follow along with Apple's WWDC announcements through the Apple Developer website and the Apple Developer app. Winners will also be able to enter to attend future WWDC events for the next two years.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Swift Student Challenge takes place annually and tasks students with developing an innovative coding project using Xcode or Swift Playground. Projects are judged based on technical accomplishment, creativity of ideas, and the content of the written responses explaining the project.<br/>
<br/>
Swift Student Challenge winners also receive a one year membership in the Apple Developer Program and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> headphones.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;WWDC 2025&zwnj; will take place from Monday, June 9 to Friday, June 13.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/apple-swift-student-challenge-winners-2025/">Apple Starts Notifying WWDC 2025 Swift Student Challenge Winners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-starts-notifying-wwdc-2025-swift-student-challenge-winners.2454167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Made in America&#039; Apple Silicon to Lag Behind Taiwan&#039;s Output</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/made-in-america-apple-chips-to-lag-behind-taiwan/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/made-in-america-apple-silicon-to-lag-behind-taiwans-output.2454163/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 09:12:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/made-in-america-apple-chips-to-lag-behind-taiwan/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		<category>Nikkei</category>
		<category>Taiwan</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>United States</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's custom silicon chips will begin to be manufactured in the United States at an accelerated pace as TSMC adjusts its timelines, although the chips produced domestically will be limited to older models for the foreseeable future, <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/Tech-Asia/TSMC-s-165bn-U.S.-expansion-push-Inevitable-but-risky"><em>Nikkei Asia</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-silicon-feature-joeblue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945652" /><br/>
Exclusive Apple chip supplier TSMC has confirmed that future fabrication facilities in the United States will be brought online more quickly than its first Arizona-based plant, which was beset by delays. TSMC now expects new U.S. plants to take no more than two years to complete, a significant improvement over the five-year timeline required for its initial facility. Despite the expedited pace, the chips produced in these new plants will not power Apple's latest models, as the most advanced fabrication processes will remain exclusive to TSMC's operations in Taiwan.<br/>
<br/>
The company's first U.S. plant, located in Phoenix, Arizona, began construction in 2020 and is expected to begin production in 2025. This facility is configured to produce chips using TSMC's N4 process, which is part of the broader 5-nanometer node family. This generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/08/apple-watch-chips-now-being-made-in-the-u-s/">includes the A16 Bionic chip</a>, originally introduced in 2022 with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 14 Pro and later used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, and the latest entry-level <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. The S9 chip used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> is also an N4 chip. These chips are no longer at the top of Apple's product line technologically and their production today simply supports continued manufacturing of the company's older or lower-end models.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC has announced plans for a second Arizona plant that will support production of 3-nanometer chips, currently the most advanced node in mass production and used for chips like the A17 Pro, M3, A18, and M4. However, this second facility will not begin operations until 2028, at which point Apple's mainstream devices will likely have moved to 2-nanometer or more advanced silicon.<br/>
<br/>
A third facility, expected to produce chips with the 2-nanometer process, is planned for completion before the end of the decade, though TSMC has not committed to a specific timeline beyond "before 2030." Analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/22/kuo-a20-chip-2nm/">Ming-Chi Kuo expects</a> the first 2nm Apple chip to be the "A20," debuting in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 lineup next year, again suggesting that the U.S. chips will lag well behind the technological requirements of future high-end Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
The disparity between US and Taiwanese chip production timelines is partially a result of TSMC's longstanding technical and organizational infrastructure in Taiwan, where all research and development continues to take place. The company's semiconductor dominance is also considered by some analysts to act as a "silicon shield," deterring potential military aggression from China by making Taiwan's stability a matter of international economic importance. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nikkei-com/">Nikkei</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/taiwan/">Taiwan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-states/">United States</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/made-in-america-apple-chips-to-lag-behind-taiwan/">&#039;Made in America&#039; Apple Silicon to Lag Behind Taiwan&#039;s Output</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/made-in-america-apple-silicon-to-lag-behind-taiwans-output.2454163/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Can Now Be Your Default Call and Messaging App on iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/whatsapp-ios-default-calling-messaging-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-can-now-be-your-default-call-and-messaging-app-on-iphone.2454161/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 08:42:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/whatsapp-ios-default-calling-messaging-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp can now be selected as the default calling and messaging app on iPhone, if users so wish (via <em><a href="https://x.com/wabetainfo/status/1905229604966609030?s=46">WABetaInfo</a></em>). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/whatsapp-default-app-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996881" /><br/>
A change in the latest version of WhatsApp available on the App Store (v25.8.74) causes the Meta-owned encrypted chat platform to now show up in the Messaging and Calling options list in iOS Settings ➝ Apps ➝ Default Apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced a way for users to select their preferred default apps for iPhone in iOS 18.2. Apple initially said that the feature would be coming to the European Union, but it turned out to be available worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
If you select WhatsApp for Messaging and/or Calling, your iPhone will automatically open the app when called upon instead of Apple's built-in options, Messages and Phone/FaceTime. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/set-default-iphone-apps/">How to Set Your Default iPhone Apps</a></li></ul><br/>
For example, in Apple's Contacts app, if you tap the buttons to message or call someone from their contacts card, iOS will immediately open WhatsApp. <br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/whatsapp-ios-default-calling-messaging-app/">WhatsApp Can Now Be Your Default Call and Messaging App on iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-can-now-be-your-default-call-and-messaging-app-on-iphone.2454161/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>China&#039;s &#039;Vivo Vision&#039; Overtly Copies Apple Vision Pro Design</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/vivo-vision-copies-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chinas-vivo-vision-overtly-copies-apple-vision-pro-design.2454160/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 08:26:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/vivo-vision-copies-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Vivo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The design of Apple's Vision Pro has been overtly replicated by a new headset from Chinese smartphone maker Vivo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Vivo-Vision.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="955" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-996876" /><br/>
In the months following Apple's announcement of the Vision Pro, several companies revealed or teased similar devices, including Samsung, which announced in 2024 that it was working on an Android-based XR headset in collaboration with Google and Qualcomm. Now, at the 2025 Boao Forum for Asia, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/vivo-announces-robotics-lab-and-showcases-its-first-mixed-reality-headset-at-the-boao-forum-2025-302410473.html">Vivo unveiled</a> its first mixed reality headset, called the "Vivo Vision." <br/>
<br/>
Observers were <a href="https://www.uploadvr.com/vivo-vision-looks-like-blatant-chinese-apple-vision-pro-clone/">quick to notice</a> that the device's design closely mirrors that of Apple's Vision Pro, including a gray fabric facial interface, a curved glass front visor, two downward-pointing cameras, a knitted rear tension strap, and an external battery in an aluminum casing connected via a braided cable.<br/>
<br/>
The "Vivo Vision" name is also a clear take on "Vision Pro." The company even adopted Apple's terminology, using the phrase "spatial computing" in promotional materials to describe the capabilities of its headset. <br/>
<br/>
Vivo positioned its announcement as part of a broader push into AI and robotics. The company simultaneously revealed the establishment of the Vivo Robotics Lab, which it claims will use technologies developed for Vivo Vision in the development of consumer robotics. According to Vivo Executive Vice President Hu Baishan, the lab will focus on the "brain" and "eyes" of robotics.<br/>
<br/>
Although Vivo did not disclose any hardware specifications, pricing, or technical capabilities, it is expected to launch in "mid-2025." No details have been provided regarding its availability outside of China. <br/>
<br/>
The Vivo Vision joins a series of consumer electronic device designs that have been very strongly influenced by Apple, particularly in Asia where the company's products often serve as reference points for domestic hardware development. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vivo/">Vivo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/vivo-vision-copies-vision-pro/">China&#039;s &#039;Vivo Vision&#039; Overtly Copies Apple Vision Pro Design</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chinas-vivo-vision-overtly-copies-apple-vision-pro-design.2454160/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
