<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 02:03:51 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: New HomePod With Smart Home Display Arriving in Late 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/04/kuo-homepod-display-coming-late-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-new-homepod-with-smart-home-display-arriving-in-late-2025.2444583/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 01:57:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/04/kuo-homepod-display-coming-late-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's long-rumored HomePod with a display has been delayed again and is now expected to launch after WWDC 2025, likely in the third quarter of the year, according to <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/smart-home-market-becomes-apples-next-strategic-target-new-homepod-with-display-set-to-be-key-c92f44760a7c">analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. This timeline is a shift from Kuo's earlier prediction of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">2024 release</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Second-Generation-HomePod-With-Top-LCD-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931490" /><br/>
The new smart speaker is expected to feature Apple's A18 processor and a 6-7 inch display, with support for Apple Intelligence, says the analyst. According to Kuo, the delay is primarily attributed to software development challenges, rather than hardware issues.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors about a ‌HomePod with a display since 2021, and Apple actually seems to have several products in the works. Kuo's latest report harks back to previous predictions from <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, who suggested Apple was developing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/homepod-with-ipad-like-screen-2025-rumor/">several HomePod variants with screens</a>, including one with an iPad-like display and another featuring a screen mounted on a robotic arm. Gurman had indicated these devices were unlikely to launch before 2025.<br/>
<br/>
The new HomePod will reportedly emphasize smart home functionality more than current models, suggesting a strategic repositioning of the product line. The idea that Apple is targeting the smart home market follows a recent report by Gurman about Apple developing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-command-center/">all-in-one home management hub</a> with a square-shaped display, thick bezels, and a hemispherical base similar to the iMac G4.<br/>
<br/>
Initial shipment expectations for the new HomePod are relatively modest, with Kuo forecasting approximately 500,000 units in the second half of 2025. He also maintains his previous prediction that Apple will launch a compatible smart home IP camera in 2026 that is designed to work wirelessly with the display-equipped HomePod.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/04/kuo-homepod-display-coming-late-2025/">Kuo: New HomePod With Smart Home Display Arriving in Late 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-new-homepod-with-smart-home-display-arriving-in-late-2025.2444583/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Miss the MacBook Pro&#039;s Touch Bar? Check Out the Flexbar</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/flexbar-touch-bar-replacement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/miss-the-macbook-pros-touch-bar-check-out-the-flexbar.2444565/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:52:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/flexbar-touch-bar-replacement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/10/27/apple-unveils-new-macbook-pros/">the 2016 MacBook Pro models</a>, Apple introduced the Touch Bar, a small multi-touch display available above the keyboard. The Touch Bar replaced the function row of keys and added dynamic buttons that changed for each app, but it was a polarizing feature that many Mac users disliked.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Flexbar -- Your Next Touch-Bar Solution" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4fF_qUs6h1U?list=TLGG4NGpxHcFFKIwMzEyMjAyNA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Apple started phasing out the Touch Bar with the launch of the 2021 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> models, and the last Mac with a Touch Bar was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/touch-bar-discontinued/">discontinued in 2023</a>. If you're one of the &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; users who misses the Touch Bar, you'll want to take a look at <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1735591421/flexbar-a-versatile-and-fully-customizable-touch-bar-solution">the Flexbar</a>, which is designed to be a Touch Bar replacement.<br/>
<br/>
The Flexbar is a standalone touch-based hardware device that attaches to a Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, or PC over USB-C. It has a customizable, adaptive interface that's modeled after the Touch Bar, and in terms of functionality, it's similar to multi-button PC and Mac add-ons like the Stream Deck.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/flexbar.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1036" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980657" /><br/>
Flexbar features a 10-inch 2K OLED display and it comes equipped with preloaded shortcut combinations and controls tailored for popular apps. It supports third-party APIs and can allegedly offer "advanced, native-like controls" for YouTube, Microsoft apps, Adobe apps, AutoCAD, and more. Flexbar's creators say that a plugin system and marketplace are in development and slated to launch in the second quarter of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Like the Touch Bar, the Flexbar is designed to automatically switch controls based on your current task window, but users can create their preferred layouts using a "Workspace" recording function. While the Touch Bar was limited to more basic controls, the Flexbar supports multi-step macros and sequences for repetitive tasks.<br/>
<br/>
The Flexbar is a Kickstarter project from a Hong Kong-based company called <a href="https://eniacelec.com">ENIAC</a>, so first and foremost, <em>MacRumors</em> readers should know that ENIAC has not previously created a hardware product. Taking hardware from prototyping to mass production is a difficult task that can lead to delays and even insurmountable issues, plus there are also software integration requirements, so we recommend waiting until the product launches to make a purchase.<br/>
<br/>
It is &#36;120 to back the Flexbar now (shipping not included), and the product has been funded. The Kickstarter page lists an estimated delivery date of February 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/flexbar-touch-bar-replacement/">Miss the MacBook Pro&#039;s Touch Bar? Check Out the Flexbar</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/miss-the-macbook-pros-touch-bar-check-out-the-flexbar.2444565/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown Launches on Mac App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/mac-app-store-prince-of-persia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prince-of-persia-the-lost-crown-launches-on-mac-app-store.2444563/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:24:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/mac-app-store-prince-of-persia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		<category>Mac App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular Ubisoft game Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown is available for download from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a> as of today, allowing Mac users to play the title for the first time since its January 2024 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown - Launch Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/n4vaxKwZ5rQ" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown is an action adventure game that joins a long list of other Prince of Persia titles that are based on Persian mythology. Players take on the role of Sargon, a warrior journeying to Mount Qaf to free a captured prince. Gameplay consists of fighting enemies, solving puzzles, seeking out treasure, and completing quests.<br/>
<br/>
The game has been available on Windows machines, the Nintendo Switch, PlayStation consoles, and Xbox consoles, and it received largely positive reviews.<br/>
<br/>
The Mac version of Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown uses Metal3 for a smooth gameplay experience on Mac machines, with a Mac that has an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip or later required.<br/>
<br/>
Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for &#36;19.99. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/prince-of-persia-lost-crown/id6498547840">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/mac-app-store-prince-of-persia/">Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown Launches on Mac App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prince-of-persia-the-lost-crown-launches-on-mac-app-store.2444563/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Firmware Update for Beats Solo Buds</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/beats-solo-buds-firmware-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-firmware-update-for-beats-solo-buds.2444554/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 12:31:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/beats-solo-buds-firmware-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Beats Solo Buds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a firmware update for the Beats Solo Buds, marking the first new software the earbuds have received since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/beats-solo-buds-launch-date/">their June 2024 launch</a>. The firmware has a build number of 3A130, up from the 3A112 firmware the Solo Buds shipped with.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948605" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/beats-solo-buds-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
We don't know what's included in the new firmware, and Apple does not typically provide information about Beats firmware updates.<br/>
<br/>
The Beats Solo Buds are priced at &#36;80 and are Apple's smallest and most affordable Beats-branded earbuds. While the earbuds offer a custom-built acoustic architecture and ergonomic design, active noise cancellation is not available.<br/>
<br/>
Firmware updates for Beats headphones are delivered over-the-air. Firmware will be installed while the Beats headphones are charging and are in Bluetooth range of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac that's connected to Wi-Fi. On Android devices, users need to download the Beats app for Android and connect the Android device to a power outlet to initiate a firmware update.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats-solo-buds/">Beats Solo Buds</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/beats-solo-buds-firmware-update/">Apple Releases First Firmware Update for Beats Solo Buds</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-firmware-update-for-beats-solo-buds.2444554/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Uses Amazon&#039;s Custom AI Chips for Search Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-amazon-ai-chips-search/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-uses-amazons-custom-ai-chips-for-search-services.2444550/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:41:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-amazon-ai-chips-search/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple uses custom Inferentia and Graviton artificial intelligence chips from Amazon Web Services for search services, Apple machine learning and AI director Benoit Dupin said today at the AWS re:Invent conference (via <em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/03/apple-says-it-uses-amazons-custom-ai-chips-.html">CNBC</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/aws-trainium.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980645" /><br/>
Dupin said that Amazon's AI chips are "reliable, definite, and able to serve [Apple] customers worldwide." AWS and Amazon have a "strong relationship," and Apple plans to test whether Amazon's Trainium2 chip can be used for pre-training <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> and other AI models. Amazon announced rental opportunities for the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Faws.amazon.com%2Fai%2Fmachine-learning%2Ftrainium%2F">Trainium2 chip</a> today.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has used AWS for more than 10 years for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>. With Amazon's Inferentia and Graviton chips, Apple has seen a 40 percent efficiency gain, and with Trainium2, Dupin said Apple expects up to a 50 percent improvement in efficiency with pre-training.<br/>
<br/>
Nvidia is the market leader when it comes to GPUs for AI training, but companies like Amazon are aiming to compete with lower-cost options.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-amazon-ai-chips-search/">Apple Uses Amazon&#039;s Custom AI Chips for Search Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-uses-amazons-custom-ai-chips-for-search-services.2444550/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Cyber Week Sale Includes Big Savings on Earbuds, Headphones, and Speakers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/beats-cyber-week-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-cyber-week-sale-includes-big-savings-on-earbuds-headphones-and-speakers.2444546/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 11:11:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/beats-cyber-week-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday and Cyber Monday deals have disappeared for many products, but you can still find multiple Beats headphones and speakers at up to 52 percent off on Amazon. You'll find many of the same prices at other retailers like <a href="https://howl.link/0qewd5sw944dw">Best Buy</a> as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/beats-snow.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923214" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale includes major discounts on products like the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Solo-Buds-Compatibility-Built%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB14QS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Beats Solo Buds</a>, which have hit &#36;49.99, down from &#36;79.99. These are a solid entry-level option and feature up to 18 hours of playback, USB-C, and Spatial Audio.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F03667DF9-C068-4DFF-B1F2-A822918F9ABA%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 52%  OFF</div>Beats Cyber Week Deals</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For an upgraded model, Amazon has the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Cancelling-Earbuds-Built-Bluetooth-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB096SV8SJG%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Buds</a> for &#36;79.99, down from &#36;149.95. These have up to 9 hours of playback (up to 36 hours with charging case), USB-C, active noise cancellation, transparency mode, and an IPX4 rating for sweat and water resistance.<br/>
<br/>
For speakers, there's also &#36;50 off the 2024 model of the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Pill-2024-release-Compatible%2Fdp%2FB0D4SX9RC6%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Pill</a>, now down to &#36;99.95 in multiple colors. You'll also find a few steep discounts on over-ear headphones, like the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Pro-Personalized-Compatibility%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Pro</a> at &#36;199.99, down from &#36;349.99.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Solo-Buds-Compatibility-Built%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB14QS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Beats Solo Buds</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Cancelling-Earbuds-Built-Bluetooth-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB096SV8SJG%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Buds</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;149.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Pill-2024-release-Compatible%2Fdp%2FB0D4SX9RC6%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Pill</a> - &#36;99.95, down from &#36;149.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Solo-Ear-Headphones-Compatible%2Fdp%2FB0CZPGX972%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Beats Solo 4</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;199.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Cancelling-Compatibility-Microphone-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB0C2W1KLSS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Buds +</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;169.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Pro-Personalized-Compatibility%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Pro</a> - &#36;199.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/beats-cyber-week-sale/">Beats Cyber Week Sale Includes Big Savings on Earbuds, Headphones, and Speakers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-cyber-week-sale-includes-big-savings-on-earbuds-headphones-and-speakers.2444546/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of visionOS 2.2 to Developers With Ultrawide Mac Virtual Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-seeds-visionos-2-2-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-visionos-2-2-to-developers-with-ultrawide-mac-virtual-display.2444540/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 10:19:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-seeds-visionos-2-2-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming visionOS 2.2 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/apple-releases-visionos-2-2-beta-3/">third visionOS 2.2 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955607" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
visionOS 2.2 can be installed by going to the Software Update section of the Settings app on the Vision Pro and opting into Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
The visionOS 2.2 update adds a new feature for the Mac Virtual Display option, allowing it to be set to Wide and Ultrawide. The Ultrawide setting is equivalent to two 4K displays side-by-side, and it is a notable improvement over the current Mac Virtual Display that's available in visionOS 2.1.<br/>
<br/>
The Mac Virtual Display allows the Vision Pro to be connected to a Mac with the Vision Pro serving as the display for the machine. The virtual Mac desktop works just like a standard desktop with an external display, but Vision Pro does not support multiple displays. As a solution, Apple has added the option for a wider display to maximize space.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-seeds-visionos-2-2-beta-4/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of visionOS 2.2 to Developers With Ultrawide Mac Virtual Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-visionos-2-2-to-developers-with-ultrawide-mac-virtual-display.2444540/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Cyber Week Sale Has Year&#039;s Best Prices on Monitors, TVs, Fridges, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/samsung-cyber-week-sale-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-cyber-week-sale-has-years-best-prices-on-monitors-tvs-fridges-and-more.2444531/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 08:11:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/samsung-cyber-week-sale-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung kicked off its <a href="https://howl.link/0ufxm5ick33dz">Cyber Week sale</a> a few days ago, offering discounts across smartphones, smartwatches, tablets, computers, and home appliances. Many of the deals in this sale are the same prices we tracked during Samsung's Black Friday sale, making Samsung one of the few retailers to keep these best-ever prices around all week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-best-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923404" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Right now, Amazon has the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display at an all-time low price, beating Samsung's Cyber Week deal. You can get this monitor for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;767.99</strong></a> (&#36;832 off). Another notable Samsung monitor deal is on the 32-inch Smart Monitor M8, available for <a href="https://howl.link/m79zwydm8axba"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> on Samsung's own website (&#36;300 off).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/0ufxm5ick33dz"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Samsung Cyber Week Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
During this sale, if you purchase a <a href="https://howl.link/ekxaws4sul7id">select Samsung gaming monitor</a>, you'll also get the 27-inch Odyssey G3 Gaming Monitor for free (&#36;229.99 value). One of the best monitors to purchase with this offer is the 57-inch Odssey Neo G9 Curved Gaming Monitor for <a href="https://howl.link/ezd2zzv2k1wyv"><strong>&#36;1,599.99</strong></a> (&#36;1,129.99 off).<br/>
<br/>
Other than monitors and TVs, we're also now tracking quite a few deals on refrigerators, tablets, and computers below. These sale prices will be live for this week only, so be sure to check out Samsung's event before the best prices of the year disappear.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/p7y8pcx52jg1k">Monitors and Storage</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smart-monitor-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923411" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVMG7DfcK">990 EVO 5.0 NVMe SSD 2TB</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVLMVgenn">2TB Portable SSD</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;284.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/m79zwydm8axba">Smart Monitor M80D</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKayx1Nx">34-inch Odyssey OLED G8 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKXc8UKH">32-inch Odyssey Quantum Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26psc%3D1">27-inch ViewFinity S9 Smart Monitor</a> - &#36;767.99 at Amazon, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZtLQWw9">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,078.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmSCTMeMf1L">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,799.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/5tcobps7xvxh4">Refrigerators</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/fridge-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923409" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/rj0skwxvkajxt">Large Capacity Side-by-Side Fridge</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,666.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/wvh01oaq72v2w">4-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;1,499.00, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ozmz1x8zug5xn">Mega Capacity 3-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;2,399.00, down from &#36;3,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/2ywoezhcm8c5r">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;2,599.00, down from &#36;4,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ot6h8iqi1q361">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;3,299.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/gmsd1fl5cpubb">TVs</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/the-frame-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923410" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/basyw1q0kj7hr">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX0OsAHAg">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ykww20f4u23u4">65-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,699.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/btdmfxv0poeju">65-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,699.99, down from &#36;2,699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVRaSFAOn">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,679.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVQujFbtE">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;2,299.99, down from &#36;3,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/5tyldrblhkwko">Galaxy Products</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smartphone-samsung.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923408" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbV7Ybcky">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,575 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbXJFsJWi">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> - Save up to &#36;945 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbYxetDfM">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;460</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbZknUAIi">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;190</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/samsung-cyber-week-sale-2024/">Samsung Cyber Week Sale Has Year&#039;s Best Prices on Monitors, TVs, Fridges, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-cyber-week-sale-has-years-best-prices-on-monitors-tvs-fridges-and-more.2444531/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE Now Over 1,000 Days Old as New Model Edges Closer</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/iphone-se-now-over-1000-days-old/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-now-over-1-000-days-old-as-new-model-edges-closer.2444529/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 07:52:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/iphone-se-now-over-1000-days-old/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, introduced on March 8, 2022, has now reached the milestone of being <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#ios">over 1,000 days old</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/iphone-se-3-stage.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="893" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-838833" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; debuted in 2016 as Apple's answer to customers who wanted a more affordable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> without sacrificing key features. The first SE model was based on the design of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5s but packed the then-flagship A9 chip and latest camera technology. Subsequent iterations followed a similar formula: the second-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; in 2020 adopted the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8's design and added the A13 Bionic chip, while the third generation launched in 2022 with another leap in processing power thanks to the A15 Bionic chip. Over the years, the SE line has become synonymous with classic design paired with modern internals.<br/>
<br/>
When the third-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; was unveiled, it brought significant upgrades over its predecessor, including the A15 Bionic chip—the same processor used in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 lineup—longer battery life, and 5G connectivity, which extended high-speed wireless access to Apple's budget-conscious customers. However, the exterior design was starting to show its age even upon the device's unveiling in 2022. The third-generation SE retained the 4.7-inch Retina HD display and thick bezels of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8, a design that effectively first debuted in 2014 on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6. Likewise, its LCD screen felt out of step with Apple's more modern OLED displays. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> was also noticeably absent.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/iphone-se-2.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-841335" /><br/>
As the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3 crosses the 1,000-day threshold, there are a vast array of corroborated rumors about its successor. Expected to launch in the spring of 2025, the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is shaping up to be a significant upgrade. Unlike its two predecessors, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is rumored to abandon the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8's design entirely in favor of a modern aesthetic inspired by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The new model is expected to feature a larger 6.1-inch OLED display to provide deeper blacks, better contrast, and improved energy efficiency. &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; is also set to replace <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, marking the end of the physical Home button on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and embracing the all-screen design that has become a hallmark of contemporary iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
Under the hood, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is anticipated to be powered by the A18 Bionic chip, the same processor from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, along with 8GB of RAM to support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>. Another major change will be the adoption of USB-C, following Apple's broader transition away from the Lightning connector. Camera upgrades are also on the horizon, with the SE 4 likely to feature a single 48-megapixel rear camera, a dramatic improvement over the 12-megapixel sensor in the SE 3. Despite these substantial upgrades, Apple is reportedly committed to keeping the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 priced below &#36;500, maintaining its appeal as an affordable entry point into the Apple ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
For those considering the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3 today, the advice is clear: wait. While the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3 remains a capable device, it is difficult to justify its purchase when a redesigned, feature-packed successor is on the horizon. The dated design and hardware limitations of the current model make it markedly less future-proof compared to Apple's other offerings. With the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 expected to deliver a more modern design with a larger display, OLED technology, &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;, faster performance, and other improved features at a similar price point, holding out for its release in 2025 is by far the smartest choice.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/iphone-se-now-over-1000-days-old/">iPhone SE Now Over 1,000 Days Old as New Model Edges Closer</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-now-over-1-000-days-old-as-new-model-edges-closer.2444529/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Podcasts Reveals 2024 Show of the Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-podcasts-2024-show-of-the-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-podcasts-reveals-2024-show-of-the-year.2444522/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 06:20:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-podcasts-2024-show-of-the-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/12/apple-podcasts-names-hysterical-the-2024-show-of-the-year/">announced</a> that the true crime podcast "Hysterical" by Dan Taberski has received an Apple Podcasts Award for 2024 Show of the Year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-Podcasts-Award.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925206" /><em>Apple Podcasts Award</em></div><br/>
The podcast investigates a mysterious illness that spreads among a group of high school girls in upstate New York. The seven-part series debuted in July, and it reached the number-one spot in the Top Shows chart, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been revealing several year-end charts and awards over the past few weeks, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/most-popular-podcasts-of-2024/">most popular podcasts of the year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; fullscreen *; clipboard-write" frameborder="0" height="450" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;border-radius:10px;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hysterical/id1753789609"></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-podcasts-2024-show-of-the-year/">Apple Podcasts Reveals 2024 Show of the Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-podcasts-reveals-2024-show-of-the-year.2444522/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Raises Indonesia Investment Offer to &#36;1B Amid iPhone Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-iphone-ban/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-to-1b-amid-iphone-ban.2444516/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 05:22:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-iphone-ban/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Indonesia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has significantly hiked its investment proposal to Indonesia and is now offering &#36;1 billion in a bid to resolve the ongoing iPhone 16 sales ban in the country, according to the country's investment minister Rosan Roeslani (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/indonesia-expects-1-bln-investment-commitment-apple-a-week-minister-says-2024-12-03/">Reuters</a></em>). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-16-Apple-Store.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-976828" /><br/>
Speaking to lawmakers on Tuesday, Roeslani said the government expects to receive a written commitment from Apple within a week. "Whoever benefits from the sales must invest here, create jobs here," he added. The investment is described as a "first phase" of Apple's potential involvement in the country. The offer marks a tenfold increase from Apple's previous proposal earlier this month.<br/>
<br/>
The negotiation stems from Indonesia's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/indonesia-bans-iphone-16-sales/">October ban on iPhone 16 sales</a> after authorities determined Apple had not met the country's requirement for 40% domestic content in smartphones. The government previously rejected Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-10m-investment/">initial &#36;10 million offer</a>, followed by a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ups-invest-offer-indonesia-iphone-16-ban/">&#36;100 million proposal</a> that included plans for research and development facilities and developer academies.<br/>
<br/>
The government is particularly interested in having Apple establish local manufacturing partnerships and source components domestically. Apple has maintained developer academies in Indonesia since 2018, but the country currently hosts no Apple manufacturing facilities. Apple has not responded to requests for comment regarding the latest investment proposal.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/indonesia/">Indonesia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-iphone-ban/">Apple Raises Indonesia Investment Offer to &#36;1B Amid iPhone Ban</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-to-1b-amid-iphone-ban.2444516/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Fails to Block &#36;995M UK App Store Commission Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-fails-block-uk-app-store-lawsuit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fails-to-block-995m-uk-app-store-commission-lawsuit.2444515/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 04:57:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-fails-block-uk-app-store-lawsuit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A UK class action lawsuit against Apple over App Store commission fees will proceed after judges dismissed the company's attempt to block the case, <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-12-03/apple-faces-uk-class-action-over-app-store-commission-charges">Bloomberg</a></em> reports. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/app-store-blue-banner-uk-fixed.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-804521" /><br/>
Led by competition policy professor Sean Ennis, the suit alleges Apple's 15-30% commission on App Store sales creates an anti-competitive tax on the UK technology industry. The lawsuit seeks £785 million (&#36;995 million) in damages on behalf of UK app developers. The case could potentially benefit up to 13,000 developers who have sold apps or in-app subscriptions to iOS users since July 2017.<br/>
<br/>
The lawsuit follows similar challenges worldwide over Apple's App Store policies. Apple in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/apple-eu-app-ecosystem-tidbits/">January</a> announced changes to its App Store terms in response to European Union regulations, but these modifications have also faced criticism from EU watchdogs for potentially making conditions worse for developers.<br/>
<br/>
This latest legal challenge expands on a previous suit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/25/apple-uk-antitrust-lawsuit-app-store-fees/">filed last year</a>, which initially represented around 1,500 UK developers. Professor Ennis, who previously worked at the U.S. Department of Justice and European Commission, secured funding for the case through Harbour Litigation Funding.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has consistently defended its App Store practices, maintaining that most developers pay no commission and that the platform provides valuable security and development resources. The company also emphasizes that developers can reach users through web browsers, where Apple's rules don't apply.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-fails-block-uk-app-store-lawsuit/">Apple Fails to Block &#36;995M UK App Store Commission Lawsuit</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fails-to-block-995m-uk-app-store-commission-lawsuit.2444515/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Stop Live Activities Taking Over Your Apple Watch Face</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/stop-live-activities-apple-watch-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/stop-live-activities-taking-over-your-apple-watch-face.2444513/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 04:33:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/stop-live-activities-apple-watch-display&#038;post_date=1733240029/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In watchOS, the Smart Stack for your Apple Watch is pretty clever. The collection of widgets can be pulled up with a scroll of the Digital Crown, and shows you relevant information throughout your day. But sometimes, its eagerness to help can be a bit much, especially when it comes to Live Activities.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/live-activities-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980591" /><br/>
You're probably familiar with this scenario: You raise your wrist expecting to see your carefully customized watch face, but it's been replaced by media playback controls because someone's watching your Apple TV, or there's a delivery tracking screen showing that you aren't currently interested in. Live Activities in the Smart Stack can clearly be useful, but having them automatically take over your display isn't always ideal. Here's how to take back control:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open Settings on your Apple Watch.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Smart Stack</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Select <strong>Live Activities</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Toggle off the switch next to <strong>Auto-Launch Live Activities</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/watchos-live-activities.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980580" /><br/>
<br/>
After disabling auto-launch, Live Activities will still be available in your Smart Stack when you want them – you'll just need to manually scroll to see them instead of having them pop up automatically.<br/>
<br/>
If you want more granular control, you're in luck. From the same settings screen you can control which Apple apps display Live Activities. Using the Watch app on your iPhone, you can also manage Live Activities settings for third-party apps. This lets you keep the notifications you find useful while preventing the less important ones from interrupting your watch face.<br/>
<br/>
Pro Tip: If it's just those persistent media controls that bug you, head to <strong>Media Apps</strong> in the same settings menu and turn off <strong>Live Activities</strong> completely, or alternatively under "Auto-Launch," select <strong>Off</strong> or <strong>Smart Stack</strong> for a more focused watch face experience.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/stop-live-activities-apple-watch-display/">Stop Live Activities Taking Over Your Apple Watch Face</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/stop-live-activities-taking-over-your-apple-watch-face.2444513/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music&#039;s Full Replay 2024 Experience and Year-End Charts Now Out</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-music-replay-2024-experience-now-live/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-musics-full-replay-2024-experience-and-year-end-charts-now-out.2444510/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 02:56:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-music-replay-2024-experience-now-live/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has launched Apple Music Replay for 2024, giving subscribers early access to their personalized music listening statistics and trends for the year. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-music-replay.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980565" /><br/>
iPhone users on iOS 18.1 or later can now access the Replay 2024 experience directly in the Apple Music app, from the Home, New, and Search tabs. Users with previous iOS versions can still access the experience at <a href="http://replay.music.apple.com">replay.music.apple.com</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Apple already offered monthly replays since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-music-launches-monthly-replay-experience/">February</a>, but now users can view their stats for the full year.<br/>
<br/>
Expanded listening insights in Replay 2024 include: <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Top 100, 500, 1000 Listeners:</strong> Expanding the Top 100 listener insight from previous years, listeners can now also discover whether they've made it in to the Top 500 or Top 1000 listeners of any of their favorite artists or genres.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Listening Streaks:</strong> Now users can learn the longest consecutive number of days they’ve played from Apple Music.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Replay By Month:</strong> Relive your year through the months, with your #1 songs, artists, and albums from each month of 2024.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Top Artist Streak:</strong> Based on their most-played music of each month, users can now discover if they're a loyal fan with the top artist streak - available to users if they've had an artist as their #1 artist of the month for multiple consecutive months.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Date of First Play:</strong> Fans can find out the date they first listened to their top song, artist, and album this year.</ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple Music Replay generates a Highlight Reel featuring animated cards showcasing your top artists, songs, albums, and genres for 2024 so far. You can also discover if they rank among an artist's top fans with percentage-based "super-fan" designations, providing insight into how you compare to other listeners globally. The cards are accompanied by background music relevant to each statistical highlight.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Music Replay shows precise timestamps for when users reached significant listening milestones throughout the year. The service also provides year-over-year comparisons, allowing subscribers to see how their music preferences have evolved since 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Starting this year, the Replay experience is also available in the Apple Music for Artists app and dashboard. All qualifying artists with an Apple Music for Artists account can access their Replay insights, including the total number of minutes Apple Music subscribers have listened to their music in 2024, the cities that listen to their music the most, their song discovered the most via Shazam this year, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-Music-Replay-for-Artists.jpg" alt="" width="3228" height="1640" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980630" /><br/>
Apple Music has also shared year-end charts, including the <a href="http://apple.co/topsongs-global24">Top Songs of 2024: Global</a>, the <a href="http://apple.co/top100-shazam24">Top 100: Shazam</a>, the <a href="http://apple.co/top100-mrl24">Most-Read Lyrics</a>, <a href="http://apple.co/top100-sing24">Top 100: Sing</a> and the first-ever <a href="http://apple.co/radiochart-global24">Shazam Global Radio Spins</a> chart.<br/>
<br/>
Kendrick Lamar's "Not Like Us" was the top song on Apple Music worldwide this year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-music-replay-2024-experience-now-live/">Apple Music&#039;s Full Replay 2024 Experience and Year-End Charts Now Out</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-musics-full-replay-2024-experience-and-year-end-charts-now-out.2444510/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Launching in Taiwan on December 17</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-vision-pro-taiwan-december-17/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-launching-in-taiwan-on-december-17.2444492/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 19:33:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-vision-pro-taiwan-december-17/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/tw/newsroom/2024/12/apple-vision-pro-arrives-in-taiwan-beginning-tuesday-december-17/">announced</a> that its Vision Pro headset will be launching in Taiwan on Tuesday, December 17, with pre-orders beginning this Thursday, December 5, at 9:00 a.m.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944159" /><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/tw/apple-vision-pro/">localized Vision Pro page for Taiwan</a> highlights the pre-order and launch dates and provides all of the usual details about the high-end headset. The <a href="https://www.apple.com/tw/shop/buy-vision/apple-vision-pro">online Apple Store for Taiwan</a> has a purchasing page already live where potential customers can check out pricing and options such as storage capacities and ZEISS optical inserts.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has two retail stores in the Taiwanese capital of Taipei, and the stores will be offering 30-minute demo sessions of the Vision Pro headset. More details on the demo sessions will be announced once pre-orders begin.<br/>
<br/>
Taiwan will mark the thirteenth country or region with Vision Pro availability. After <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-launch-day/">launching in the United States in February</a>, availability expanded to Australia, Canada, France, Germany, the U.K., China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore in June and July. The most recent additions prior to today's announcement were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/vision-pro-launches-in-two-more-countries/">South Korea and the United Arab Emirates</a> just a few weeks ago.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-vision-pro-taiwan-december-17/">Apple Vision Pro Launching in Taiwan on December 17</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-launching-in-taiwan-on-december-17.2444492/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2026 Foldable iPhone Could Reinvigorate Stalling Market</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-2026-foldable-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2026-foldable-iphone-could-reinvigorate-stalling-market.2444487/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 16:04:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-2026-foldable-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The foldable smartphone market has stalled with customer interest in foldables waning, but that could change when <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/press-release/foldable-smartphone-market-stalls-in-2024-and-2025">Apple debuts a foldable iPhone</a>, according to display analyst Ross Young.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Flip-iPhone-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960019" /><br/>
In a report on the current foldable smartphone market, Young says that Apple is expected to "enter the foldable market" in the second half of 2026. Apple's "dominant position in flagship smartphones" could potentially lead to significant growth for the foldable market in 2026, ultimately leading to a record year for foldables.<br/>
<br/>
Young expects more than 30 percent growth in the foldable market in 2026, followed by continued 20 percent growth in 2027 and 2028.<br/>
<br/>
There have long been rumors suggesting that Apple is developing a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and some analysts believe that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">will finally debut a foldable iPhone</a> around September of 2026.<br/>
<br/>
The first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; could be between 7.9 and 8.3 inches in size, and it may have a "clamshell" design like Samsung's Galaxy Z Flip. A clamshell &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; would fold in half vertically rather than horizontally, allowing for a full-size &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; when unfolded, and a smaller, pocketable device when folded.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-2026-foldable-iphone/">Apple&#039;s 2026 Foldable iPhone Could Reinvigorate Stalling Market</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2026-foldable-iphone-could-reinvigorate-stalling-market.2444487/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sued for &#039;All-Seeing Eye&#039; Employee Device Monitoring Policy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-sued-employee-monitoring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sued-for-all-seeing-eye-employee-device-monitoring-policy.2444483/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 15:23:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-sued-employee-monitoring/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[California Apple employee Amar Bhakta has filed a lawsuit against Apple for alleged labor violations, accusing the Cupertino company of suppressing employee speech, invading employee privacy though surveillance and inspecting personal data, and clawing back earned wages (via <a href="https://www.semafor.com/article/12/02/2024/employee-lawsuit-accuses-apple-of-spying-on-its-workers"><em>Semafor</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/Apple-Park-View.jpeg" alt="" width="1440" height="790" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-854420" /><br/>
Bhakta sued Apple after Apple prohibited him from speaking about his work experience on podcasts and also instructed him to remove information about his "working conditions and work experiences" from his LinkedIn profile. He says that Apple's policies prevent employees from adequately describing their job responsibilities, accomplishments, and professional growth on sites like LinkedIn, hindering their ability to find employment.<br/>
<br/>
Further, Bhakta claims that Apple employees are prohibited from disclosing the skills, knowledge, and experience they gained at Apple when working for a subsequent employer, plus they are not allowed to speak with each other or outsiders about problems at work like harassment, discrimination, or unfair treatment.<br/>
<br/>
Apple employees are required to use Apple devices, software, and services, and the devices "collect and use the valuable personal data" of employees during non-work periods. The lawsuit states that employees have to agree to physical, video, and electronic surveillance by Apple, with Apple able to search Apple and non-Apple devices and other property when an employee is on "company premises," including in a home office. The Apple ecosystem is described as a "prison yard" for employees, with workers subject to "Apple's all-seeing eye" both on and off duty.<br/>
<br/>
The lawsuit takes issue with Apple's requirement that employees use Apple collaboration tools with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> account, often a personal &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; account. Bhakta says Apple allowed him to choose to use an Apple-owned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or a personal &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; for work, and when he chose his personal phone, Apple installed an eSIM and VPN, and required him to use his personal &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; account to collaborate with colleagues. He claims that Apple has forced him to remain an Apple consumer, and that he is required to continue to patronize Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Bhakta was hired at Apple in July 2020 as a Digital Ad Tech/Operations Manager, and he was required to sign documents listing the Apple policies that are cited in the lawsuit.<br/>
<br/>
The lawsuit seeks damages for violations of the California Labor Code as well as "appropriate injunctive relief" to protect California Apple employees from future violations.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/apple-sued-employee-monitoring/">Apple Sued for &#039;All-Seeing Eye&#039; Employee Device Monitoring Policy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sued-for-all-seeing-eye-employee-device-monitoring-policy.2444483/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Paid Version of Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp Now Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/paid-version-of-animal-crossing-pocket-camp-now-available.2444480/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 14:40:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nintendo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nintendo today debuted <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-c/id6547834967"><em>Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp Complete</em></a>, a paid offline version of Pocket Camp that lets customers continue to play now that the freemium version of the game <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/nintendo-shutting-down-animal-crossing-pocket-camp/">has been shut down</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-973075" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Animal-Crossing-Pocket-Camp-Complete.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The original Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp game was shuttered last week on November 29, almost exactly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/11/21/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-launches/">seven years after it launched</a>. Because it was a freemium game, there are players who invested a lot of money in various items in the game, so Pocket Camp Complete allows those players to continue to play the base version of the game.<br/>
<br/>
Nintendo has stopped all events and updates now that the online version of Pocket Camp has been discontinued. Pocket Camp saves can be transferred to Pocket Camp Complete and the game has many of the same features, but there is no support for visiting and interacting with other players or receiving gifts. It does not have in-app purchases, nor is there an online connection.<br/>
<br/>
Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp Complete is available from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for &#36;9.99. Saves can be transferred until June 2, 2025, and transferring a save requires a Nintendo Account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nintendo/">Nintendo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-complete/">Paid Version of Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp Now Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/paid-version-of-animal-crossing-pocket-camp-now-available.2444480/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Debuts (PRODUCT)RED Solo 4 Headphones, But You Won&#039;t Be Able to Buy Them</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/beats-productred-solo-4-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-debuts-product-red-solo-4-headphones-but-you-wont-be-able-to-buy-them.2444477/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 13:01:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/beats-productred-solo-4-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-pay-world-aids-day-donation-campaign/">annual Apple Pay donation campaign</a> supporting The Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria that's currently underway around World AIDS Day, the company has historically offered a selection of its products under the related (RED) brand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/beats-solo-4-red.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1200" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980532" /><br/>
While we recently noted that Apple has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-has-scaled-back-productred/">scaling back its (PRODUCT)RED portfolio</a> over the past few years, the company's Beats brand yesterday announced a collaboration with British Nigerian designer Yinka Ilori for (BEATS)RED Beats Solo 4 headphones with a limited-edition packaging design.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, there's a catch, which is that these new (BEATS)RED headphones aren't available for sale as they are a custom product to help create awareness around World AIDS Day and the (RED) campaign.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">To mark our long partnership with (RED) and continue supporting their mission, we created these custom Beats Solo 4 headphones. <br><br>As part of the collaboration, artist and designer <a href="https://twitter.com/YinkaIlori_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@YinkaIlori_</a> brings his bold and kaleidoscopic approach to exclusive special-edition packaging. <a href="https://t.co/dhJnqTNgai">pic.twitter.com/dhJnqTNgai</a></p>&mdash; Beats by Dre (@beatsbydre) <a href="https://twitter.com/beatsbydre/status/1863266928741220568?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 1, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<a href="https://www.yahoo.com/tech/exclusive-beats-teams-designer-yinka-153312495.html">According to <em>Women's Wear Daily</em></a>, Beats notes that the packaging design is a tribute to "resilience, community and hope," that "blend[s] traditional African aesthetics with contemporary design." Ilori says his design celebrates "the collective effort of nurturing" and was inspired by "the metaphorical sense of planting seeds and watching them grow into something beautiful."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/beats-productred-solo-4-headphones/">Beats Debuts (PRODUCT)RED Solo 4 Headphones, But You Won&#039;t Be Able to Buy Them</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-debuts-product-red-solo-4-headphones-but-you-wont-be-able-to-buy-them.2444477/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Onramp Now Supports Buying Crypto With Apple Pay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/coinbase-onramp-apple-pay-crypto/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/coinbase-onramp-now-supports-buying-crypto-with-apple-pay.2444471/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 11:34:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/coinbase-onramp-apple-pay-crypto/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency platform Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/Fiat-to-crypto-in-seconds-with-Apple-Pay">today announced</a> the launch of a new feature designed to let people buy cryptocurrency using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/coinbase-apple-pay.jpg" alt="" width="1800" height="1013" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980524" /><br/>
&zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; is available for all fiat-to-crypto purchases (aka paper currencies like the U.S. dollar) in Coinbase Onramp, a tool that developers and websites can use to accept crypto payments from customers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Fiat-to-crypto in seconds with Apple Pay" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tpYS2i3A8mU" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
With &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; integration in Coinbase Onramp, a customer can use &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; to buy an item or a service, paying in dollars that are converted to cryptocurrency for the merchant. Coinbase promises a straightforward verification process and free offramping.<br/>
<br/>
Coinbase says that Coinbase Onramp users can expect a faster end-to-end experience with fiat-to-crypto conversion that takes seconds, access to the most popular payment methods, and easier onramping for U.S. customers that use &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Developers who already use Coinbase Onramp don't need to do anything, and their customers will see &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; available as an option when making an eligible purchase.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/02/coinbase-onramp-apple-pay-crypto/">Coinbase Onramp Now Supports Buying Crypto With Apple Pay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/coinbase-onramp-now-supports-buying-crypto-with-apple-pay.2444471/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
