<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:03:51 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Twelve South Launches New BookArc Flex</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/twelve-south-bookarc-flex/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/twelve-south-launches-new-bookarc-flex.2416548/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:37:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/twelve-south-bookarc-flex/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Twelve South</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Twelve South today announced the launch of <a href="https://www.twelvesouth.com/products/bookarc-flex">the BookArc Flex</a>, a new stand designed for MacBooks that are used in clamshell mode while connected to a display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/twelve-south-bookarc-flex.jpg" alt="" width="1067" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931061" /><br/>
The BookArc Flex has a unique build that features a two legs connected by a flexible interior piece. A laptop is placed in the middle on the flexible part, which pulls the legs together to secure it upright using the weight of the laptop.<br/>
<br/>
Twelve South says that the design <a href="https://www.northcharleston.org/government/projects/noisette-creek-pedestrian-bridge/">was inspired by</a> the Noisette Creek Pedestrian Bridge in Charleston, South Carolina. The bridge has two steel arches that are indeed similar to the design of the BookArc Flex.<br/>
<br/>
We were able to test the BookArc Flex ahead of its launch, and while the design works well, it is important to ensure the laptop goes directly in the center of the stand. It's not difficult to do, and placing the laptop correctly ensures that it remains secure. If it's not placed in the center, however, it can shift out of place, though a misalignment is quickly noticeable.<br/>
<br/>
The construction of the BookArc Flex allows it to work with laptops of multiple sizes without different inserts, and it is compatible with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> and MacBook Pro from Apple. The slim size of the BookArc Flex ensures that it does not take up too much room on a desk, and it tucks a MacBook out of the way when used in clamshell mode.<br/>
<br/>
Twelve South's BookArc Flex is priced starting at &#36;50 it is available today <a href="https://www.twelvesouth.com/products/bookarc-flex">from the Twelve South website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twelve-south/">Twelve South</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/twelve-south-bookarc-flex/">Twelve South Launches New BookArc Flex</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/twelve-south-launches-new-bookarc-flex.2416548/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Developers Can Now Offer Non-App Store Purchasing Option, But Apple Will Still Collect Commissions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/u-s-developers-can-now-offer-non-app-store-purchasing-option-but-apple-will-still-collect-commissions.2416540/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:24:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is making major changes to its U.S. iOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> policies, and developers are now able to direct customers to a non-App Store purchasing option for digital goods. Apple is allowing apps to feature a single link to a developer website that leads to an in-app purchase alternative, but Apple plans to continue to collect a 12 to 27 percent commission on content bought this way.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
Apple's update and the backstory that led to it are a bit complicated, but what <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users need to know is that some apps in the U.S. storefront will soon feature a link to their website where subscriptions and other content can be purchased outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in-app purchase system, likely with a discounted price.<br/>
<br/>
Developers who want to offer this option will need to apply for a StoreKit External Purchase Link Entitlement, as Apple has outlined in both updated &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Review Guidelines and the statement of compliance submitted to the Northern California U.S. District Court. With a Link Entitlement, a developer is able to direct a user to an out-of-app purchasing mechanism using an external purchase link. From Apple's modified &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules:<br/>
<blockquote>Developers may apply for an entitlement to provide a link in their app to a website the developer owns or maintains responsibility for in order to purchase such items. Learn more about the entitlement. In accordance with the entitlement agreement, the link may inform users about where and how to purchase those in-app purchase items, and the fact that such items may be available for a comparatively lower price. The entitlement is limited to use only in the iOS or iPadOS App Store on the United States storefront. In all other storefronts, apps and their metadata may not include buttons, external links, or other calls to action that direct customers to purchasing mechanisms other than in-app purchase.<br/>
<br/>
If your app engages in misleading marketing practices, scams, or fraud in relation to the entitlement, your app will be removed from the App Store and you may be removed from the Apple Developer Program.</blockquote><br/>
There are several requirements that developers need to adhere to maintain the privacy and security of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; ecosystem, and notably, Apple will collect a commission on purchases made using these Entitlement Links. Rather than 30 percent, Apple will collect a 27 percent fee on user purchases or year-one subscriptions made through the link. On the second year of a subscription, the commission fee drops to 12 percent, which is three percentage points lower than the 15 percent fee that Apple collects from second-year or longer subscriptions made through the in-app purchase system. Apps that participate in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Small Business Program will be charged a 12 percent commission rate.<br/>
<br/>
The commission will apply to transactions for digital goods and services that take place on a developers website within seven days after a user taps through an External Purchase Link to an external website. <br/>
<br/>
Several key points about Entitlement Links are listed below.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>All links to outside purchasing methods must use the Entitlement Link system, and developers must apply and get Apple's approval.</li><br/>
 	<li>Developers are permitted to have a single plain link on <strong>one</strong> screen of an app. The link can be at a sign-in screen, in user settings, or elsewhere, but it can only be in one place. The single location may not be an interstitial, modal, or pop-up.</li><br/>
 	<li>The link can mention the specific price of content on a website, or that content is discounted on the website from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; price. Comparisons are allowed.</li><br/>
 	<li>Links cannot be placed directly on an in-app purchase screen or in the in-app purchase flow.</li><br/>
 	<li>Developers need to certify that the third-party payment service provider they are using for out-of-app purchasing meets industry standards for payment processors, and that they will offer users processes for managing subscriptions, requesting refunds, and disputing unauthorized transactions.</li><br/>
 	<li>Apps that participate in Apple's Video Partner Program or News Partner Program are not eligible for Link Entitlement.</li><br/>
 	<li>Apps that use the StoreKit External Purchase Link must continue to offer in-app purchases as an option.</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;App Store&zwnj; pages are not able to include information about purchasing on a website or a link to a website.</li><br/>
<li>Digital purchases that are sold on an app's website through the Entitlement Link must be available for use in that app.</li><br/>
 	<li>The StoreKit External Purchase Link cannot discourage users from making in-app purchases or mimic an in-app purchase.</li><br/>
 	<li>Links must open a new window in the default browser of the device, and are not able to open a web view.</li><br/>
 	<li>No redirecting, intermediate links, or URL tracking parameters are allowed.</li><br/>
<li>Developers are required to provide a periodic accounting of qualifying out-of-app purchases, and Apple has a right to audit developers' accounting to ensure compliance with their commission obligations and to charge interest and offset payments.</li><br/>
<br/>
</ul><br/>
The Link Entitlement process and the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes are applicable only in the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Apps for all other storefronts are not able to include buttons, external links, or calls to action that direct customers to alternative purchasing options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-external-link-examples.jpg" alt="" width="1635" height="920" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931057" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Examples of how Entitlement Links can be used in apps</div></em><br/>
Apple will provide an in-app warning to customers to let them know that they are leaving the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; ecosystem to make a purchase on an external website and that &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; protections will not be available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-external-app-store-warning.jpg" alt="" width="2030" height="1142" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931056" /><br/>
According to Apple's statement filed with the court, the requirements surrounding links are aimed at minimizing "fraud, scams, and confusion," while also providing developers with an opportunity to "entice users to other platforms" and give customers a choice between non-App Store purchasing and in-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
The changes today stem from Apple's 2021 legal battle with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>. Apple won the dispute and the court did not find that Apple had violated U.S. antitrust law, but Apple was at the time ordered to remove "anti-steering" rules preventing developers from informing customers about alternatives to in-app purchases. That order has been on hold <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/app-store-rule-change-epic-games-delayed/">during the appeals process</a>, but the appeals process ended today.<br/>
<br/>
Both Apple and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/">had appealed</a> to the United States Supreme Court, but the Supreme Court <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">declined to hear the case</a>. That means the initial ruling and the appeals court ruling that agreed with it are permanent, and Apple now has to comply with the part of that order that required it to change the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules.<br/>
<br/>
The anti-steering rule was two-pronged, requiring Apple to allow for links to in-app purchase alternatives and to allow developers to communicate with customers outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; through email and other contact information collected in the app. The outside communication part of the order was already satisfied with a change that Apple made to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules in 2021 to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/26/app-store-changes-developer-lawsuit-settlement/">settle a class-action developer lawsuit</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has already been allowing developers to use communication methods like email to inform customers about payment methods available outside of iOS apps, and Apple makes it clear in its messaging today that there are no limits on developers' out-of-app communications with users. The full statements that Apple provided to the court have been obtained by <em>MacRumors</em> and can be read below. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><p  style=" margin: 12px auto 6px auto; font-family: Helvetica,Arial,Sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 14px; line-height: normal; font-size-adjust: none; font-stretch: normal; -x-system-font: none; display: block;">   <a title="View App Store VP Matthew Fischer on Apple&#x27;s Injunction Compliance on Scribd" href="https://www.scribd.com/document/699388059/App-Store-VP-Matthew-Fischer-on-Apple-s-Injunction-Compliance#from_embed"  style="text-decoration: underline;" >App Store VP Matthew Fischer on Apple&#x27;s Injunction Compliance</a> by <a title="View MacRumors's profile on Scribd" href="https://www.scribd.com/user/212523051/MacRumors#from_embed"  style="text-decoration: underline;" >MacRumors</a> on Scribd</p><iframe class="scribd_iframe_embed" title="App Store VP Matthew Fischer on Apple's Injunction Compliance" src="https://www.scribd.com/embeds/699388059/content?start_page=1&view_mode=scroll&access_key=key-ED7bSkujN7wotXWkq7vD" data-auto-height="false" data-aspect-ratio="0.7729220222793488" scrolling="no" id="doc_43188" width="100%" height="600" frameborder="0"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><p  style=" margin: 12px auto 6px auto; font-family: Helvetica,Arial,Sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant: normal; font-weight: normal; font-size: 14px; line-height: normal; font-size-adjust: none; font-stretch: normal; -x-system-font: none; display: block;">   <a title="View Apple Notice of Compliance With UCL Injunction on Scribd" href="https://www.scribd.com/document/699388061/Apple-Notice-of-Compliance-With-UCL-Injunction#from_embed"  style="text-decoration: underline;" >Apple Notice of Compliance With UCL Injunction</a> by <a title="View MacRumors's profile on Scribd" href="https://www.scribd.com/user/212523051/MacRumors#from_embed"  style="text-decoration: underline;" >MacRumors</a> on Scribd</p><iframe class="scribd_iframe_embed" title="Apple Notice of Compliance With UCL Injunction" src="https://www.scribd.com/embeds/699388061/content?start_page=1&view_mode=scroll&access_key=key-Iyzh1bk6eAMlp68Mgo6E" data-auto-height="false" data-aspect-ratio="0.7729220222793488" scrolling="no" id="doc_50176" width="100%" height="600" frameborder="0"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; CEO Tim Sweeney criticized Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes and said that Epic plans to contest Apple's "bad-faith compliance plan" in District Court. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A quick summary of glaring problems we&#39;ve found so far:<br><br>1) Apple has introduced an anticompetitive new 27% tax on web purchases. Apple has never done this before, and it kills price competition. Developers can&#39;t offer digital items more cheaply on the web after paying a… <a href="https://t.co/YkHuapG7xa">pic.twitter.com/YkHuapG7xa</a></p>&mdash; Tim Sweeney (@TimSweeneyEpic) <a href="https://twitter.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1747408148799881390?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 16, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">U.S. Developers Can Now Offer Non-App Store Purchasing Option, But Apple Will Still Collect Commissions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/u-s-developers-can-now-offer-non-app-store-purchasing-option-but-apple-will-still-collect-commissions.2416540/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Lacks Wi-Fi 6E Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-lacks-wi-fi-6e-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-lacks-wi-fi-6e-support.2416525/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 11:48:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-lacks-wi-fi-6e-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-fcc-approval/">received FCC approval</a> for the Vision Pro today in the U.S., and the filing confirms that the headset does not support Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-vision-pro-setup.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923100" /><br/>
Wi-Fi 6E extends the capabilities of the regular Wi-Fi 6 standard to the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference with a compatible device and router. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-wi-fi-6e-iphone-mac/">Apple devices with Wi-Fi 6E support</a> include the latest iPad Pro models, iPhone 15 Pro models, and most Mac models released in 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The FCC filing shows that the Vision Pro does not have any approved operating frequencies in the 6 GHz range, confirming that the headset lacks Wi-Fi 6E support. Instead, one of Apple's documents in the application confirms that the Vision Pro supports regular Wi-Fi 6, which operates on the 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz frequency bands.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to share full tech specs for the Vision Pro, so only limited details are available. Apple has so far said the headset is equipped with its M2 chip, an all-new R1 chip that processes camera and microphone input, and 256GB of base storage. <em>MacRumors</em> discovered that the headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-how-much-ram-and-storage/">equipped with 16GB of RAM</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Vision Pro pre-orders begin this Friday, January 19 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time, with pricing starting at &#36;3,499. The headset <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launches on Friday, February 2</a>, and Apple previously said that availability would expand to more countries later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> Vision Pro also appears to lack Ultra Wideband support, according to <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-uwb-wifi-6e-7/"><em>9to5Mac</em>'s Zac Hall</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-lacks-wi-fi-6e-support/">Apple Vision Pro Lacks Wi-Fi 6E Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-lacks-wi-fi-6e-support.2416525/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Vision Pro Hands-On: Reviewers Comment on Weight, Disney+ Experience, Virtual Keyboard and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-hands-on-pre-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-hands-on-reviewers-comment-on-weight-disney-experience-virtual-keyboard-and-more.2416519/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 10:38:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-hands-on-pre-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week invited members of the media to New York City for another round of testing the Vision Pro ahead of its launch, and sites that were able to try out the device are now sharing their impressions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Purple-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929938" /><br/>
As a recap, Apple first allowed media to use the Vision Pro following its debut at the Worldwide Developers Conference, but it was still under development at the time and features were limited. Now the headset is nearing release, so testers are able to experience the Vision Pro as consumers will.<br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://www.engadget.com/apple-vision-pro-hands-on-redux-immersive-video-disney-app-floating-keyboard-and-a-little-screaming-180006222.html?src=rss">Engadget</a></em>'s Cherlynn Low wore the headset for just 20 minutes with the standard strap and "was in pain" due to the weight of the device. Apple swapped her over to the Dual Loop Band, which "felt much better for weight distribution."<br/>
<br/>
Dana Wollman from <em>Engadget</em> had to experiment with Light Seals in order to get the right fit against the face, and when it was too loose, the headset's lettering did not look sharp. Both testers preferred the Dual Loop version of the band, which was more comfortable, and they said there were a lot of options for fit. Joanna Stern from <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em> said that the Dual Loop, which she was able to try for the first time, was much more comfortable than the single band option.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Had my 4th demo of the Vision Pro this AM and Apple finally let us take a photo with it on.<br><br>My first three demos (1 in June, 1 in November, 1 in December) were all with the Solo Knit Band and I really felt the weight of the face computer on my face. <br><br>Today I tried the Dual… <a href="https://t.co/DjyYknyme3">pic.twitter.com/DjyYknyme3</a></p>&mdash; Joanna Stern (@JoannaStern) <a href="https://twitter.com/JoannaStern/status/1747331779285991649?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 16, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/24040075/apple-vision-pro-hands-on-virtual-reality">The Verge</a></em>'s Victoria Song didn't comment in detail on the weight, but said that you can feel it sitting on your head "wrecking your hairdo," and that those with long hair can feel it bunch up at the back.<br/>
<br/>
Immersive video was part of the demonstration, which Low said showed impressive levels of texture. Wollman felt immersed in the scene, but "also excluded" because it's lifelike, but no one in the immersive videos "sees you or interacts with you." Disney+ for Vision Pro was described as "like playing a video game" because you can select a Disney-esque background for watching content. Wollman described it as a "Disney-themed drive-in." From Low:<br/>
<blockquote>As a big Marvel fangirl, I really geeked out when the Avengers Tower environment came on. I looked around and saw all kinds of easter eggs, including a takeout container from Shawarma Grill on the table next to me. It feels a little silly to gush about the realism of the images, but I saw no pixels. Instead, I looked at a little handwritten note that Tony Stark had clearly left behind and felt like I was almost able to pick it up. When we switched over to the Tattooine environment, I was placed in the cockpit of Luke Skywalker's landspeeder, and when I reached out to grab the steering controls, I was able to see my own hands in front of me.</blockquote><br/>
Song described the experience of watching spatial videos shot on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and she felt "some familiar VR motion queasiness" from the camera shake.<br/>
<br/>
While the floating keyboard has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-criticism/">described by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> as a "complete write-off," Low said that it worked "fairly well," while Wollman said that it was "one of the more frustrating" parts of the demo because none of the typing options worked for extended use. Song said it worked, but it was clunky. "You look at a letter and pinch your fingers to select it," she described. <br/>
<br/>
Reviewers were also able to test out the meditation feature and the Encounter Dinosaurs app, and their full thoughts on the device can be read over at <em><a href="https://www.engadget.com/apple-vision-pro-hands-on-redux-immersive-video-disney-app-floating-keyboard-and-a-little-screaming-180006222.html">Engadget</a></em> and <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/24040075/apple-vision-pro-hands-on-virtual-reality">The Verge</a></em>. Additional accounts of in-person experiences will be coming out later this week, and Apple is giving some of the media that visit New York this week headsets to test out for full reviews. More in-depth reviews will be available ahead of when the Vision Pro launches on February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-hands-on-pre-launch/">Vision Pro Hands-On: Reviewers Comment on Weight, Disney+ Experience, Virtual Keyboard and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-hands-on-reviewers-comment-on-weight-disney-experience-virtual-keyboard-and-more.2416519/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Introduces New Sale With Big Savings on Computer Monitors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/samsung-introduces-new-sale-monitors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-introduces-new-sale-with-big-savings-on-computer-monitors.2416517/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 10:32:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/samsung-introduces-new-sale-monitors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has kicked off a <a href="https://howl.me/clq2oxlzaSU">new sale on computer monitors</a>, which is set to end on January 21. During this event you'll find discounts on 4K and 5K Samsung monitors, including the popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and Smart Monitor M8.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/samsung-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916842" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"><strong>&#36;1,199.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. At &#36;400 off this is a solid second-best price on the 2023 display, which has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;400 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;1,199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also being discounted during this sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clq2b1RAXhG"><strong>&#36;479.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;649.99. This is a 4K smart monitor with a design that looks similar to the new iMac line.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq2b1RAXhG"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;479.99</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2hIAozaO">27-inch Odyssey HDR10 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;269.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gYG78Q9">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gbHK6cQ">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2e77z0lE">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2iqJk4s6">55-inch Odyssey Ark 4K UHD Mini-LED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;2,199.99, down from &#36;2,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/samsung-introduces-new-sale-monitors/">Samsung Introduces New Sale With Big Savings on Computer Monitors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-introduces-new-sale-with-big-savings-on-computer-monitors.2416517/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro App Store Launches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-app-store-launches/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-app-store-launches.2416510/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:47:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-app-store-launches/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of the Vision Pro launch that's coming on February 2, Apple has officially debuted the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. With the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; live for the device, apps on the iOS &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will soon list Vision Pro compatibility.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/visionos-home-screen-mt-hood.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900011" /><br/>
Developers are now able to release apps for the Vision Pro and have those apps appear in the Vision Pro &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Consumers don't yet have access to the Vision Pro headset, but reviewers who have the device on hand will be able to try out third-party apps created for the headset.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will house both apps designed specifically to take advantage of the capabilities of the Vision Pro as well as iOS apps that are able to run on the device in a 2D mode. Existing apps are able to be ported to the Vision Pro with no action needed on the part of the developer, which means that most apps should be available in some capacity. Developers can choose to opt out of having their apps appear, however.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Looks like Apple has just released the visionOS App Store! <a href="https://t.co/zSdiY04JzF">pic.twitter.com/zSdiY04JzF</a></p>&mdash;  (@DylanMcD8) <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanMcD8/status/1747307110847680611?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 16, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple is meeting with select members of the media <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-reviews-multiple-meetings/">starting today</a> to provide review units. Reviews are expected to go live at the end of January, so reviewers should have ample time to test out apps.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders for the Vision Pro will begin this Friday at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time, and it is likely that available units will sell out quickly. The headset is set to launch on Friday, February 2, two weeks after when pre-orders happen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-app-store-launches/">Apple Vision Pro App Store Launches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-app-store-launches.2416510/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Receives FCC Approval Ahead of Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-fcc-approval/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-receives-fcc-approval-ahead-of-launch.2416508/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:33:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-fcc-approval/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today received FCC approval for the upcoming Vision Pro headset, just days ahead of when pre-orders are set to go live for the device. FCC approval comes a little over two weeks before when the Vision Pro will be in the hands of consumers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
It is not unusual for new Apple devices to lack FCC approval until close to their launch date as it can take quite a bit of time for Apple to get products cleared. Apple devices undergo rigorous FCC testing in the United States prior to being able to be sold to the public.<br/>
<br/>
For the last several months, Apple has been required to provide a warning message letting consumers know that the Vision Pro did not yet have FCC approval, but the wording will now be able to be removed from the website, advertising, and other places where it is printed.<br/>
<blockquote>Apple Vision Pro has not been authorized as required by the rules of the Federal Communications Commission. This device is not, and may not be, offered for sale or lease, or sold or leased, until authorization is obtained.</blockquote><br/>
The Vision Pro is set to go up for pre-order on Friday, January 19 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time. It is priced starting at &#36;3,500.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-fcc-approval/">Apple Vision Pro Receives FCC Approval Ahead of Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-receives-fcc-approval-ahead-of-launch.2416508/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights Guest and Travel Modes on Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-guest-user-and-travel-modes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-guest-and-travel-modes-on-vision-pro.2416502/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:01:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-guest-user-and-travel-modes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a press release outlining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-streaming-services-and-sports-apps/">entertainment options on the Vision Pro</a>, Apple also briefly highlighted Guest User and Travel Mode features on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Guest.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930974" /><br/>
With the Guest User mode, you can let family and friends use your Vision Pro with limited access to certain apps, such as Photos and Safari. Apple says the primary user's Apple ID account settings, Optic ID, passcode, passwords, Apple Pay, Persona, and health data will be restricted while the Guest User mode is active.<br/>
<br/>
Guest User mode was discovered last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/22/visionos-hands-on/">in the visionOS simulator</a>, part of Apple's app development tool Xcode. Once the mode is turned on, it will automatically shut off if the headset is not worn within five minutes, the simulator showed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Travel-Mode.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930973" /><br/>
When turned on via Control Center, Apple says Travel Mode stabilizes visuals on the Vision Pro for users wearing the headset on an airplane. Travel Mode was first discovered by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Steve Moser last year in visionOS beta code, with more details about this  feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/22/apple-vision-pro-travel-mode/">outlined in our coverage at the time</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In fine print related to Travel Mode, Apple warns that the Vision Pro should obviously not be used while operating a moving vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro can be pre-ordered in the U.S. starting Friday, January 19 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launches on Friday, February 2</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-guest-user-and-travel-modes/">Apple Highlights Guest and Travel Modes on Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-guest-and-travel-modes-on-vision-pro.2416502/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Pro Gets All-Time Low Prices on Amazon, Starting at &#36;1,399</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apples-m3-macbook-pro-low-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m3-macbook-pro-gets-all-time-low-prices-on-amazon-starting-at-1-399.2416492/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 07:17:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apples-m3-macbook-pro-low-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a collection of discounts on Apple's M3 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro, all of which can be found on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919851" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>14-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
Amazon has the 8-Core, 512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,399.00</strong></a> in Space Gray, down from &#36;1,599.00. This is a match of the all-time low price on this notebook, and right now it's the only 14-inch model that is at a record low price on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch M3 MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for more storage, Amazon has the 8-Core, 1TB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LZWJ1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,649.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,799.00. This is a second-best price on the notebook, and Amazon has it available in Silver and Space Gray.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>16-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
For the larger display, Amazon is discounting a few of the higher-end models to all-time low prices. You can get the 14-Core, 36GB RAM, 1TB M3 Max 16-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5MF262%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;3,249.99</strong></a> with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;3,499.00. Thanks to the on-page coupon, this is a new record low price for this model, and it's only available in Space Black.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5MF262%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (36GB RAM, 1TB, M3 Max) for &#36;3,249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the 16-Core, 48GB RAM, 1TB M3 Max 16-inch MacBook Pro has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5K7BCR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;3,799.00</strong></a> in Silver, down from &#36;3,999.00. This is another best-ever price on the 16-inch MacBook Pro, but stock has been dwindling on the notebook, so if you're interested be sure to place your order soon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5K7BCR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (48GB RAM, 1TB, M3 Max) for &#36;3,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apples-m3-macbook-pro-low-prices/">Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Pro Gets All-Time Low Prices on Amazon, Starting at &#36;1,399</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m3-macbook-pro-gets-all-time-low-prices-on-amazon-starting-at-1-399.2416492/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>US Supreme Court Declines to Hear Apple vs. Epic Games Case</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/us-supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-games-case.2416489/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 06:52:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Supreme Court today <a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/orders/courtorders/011624zor_e1pf.pdf">declined to hear</a> separate requests from both Apple and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> in their long-standing lawsuit against each other with regards to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
Apple made the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/">request</a> in September 2023, asking the Supreme Court to hear its appeal about the portion of its legal dispute that was ruled in Epic's favor. This was Apple's so-called "anti-steering" rule that bars developers of many iOS apps from directing users to methods of purchase available outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, circumventing Apple's revenue cut.<br/>
<br/>
The Supreme Court also declined to hear a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/">request from Epic Games</a> to make a ruling on the case. The Supreme Court was the last stop for &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; after it lost an appeal earlier this year. The Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals in April 2023 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/24/epic-games-loses-appeal-app-store-battle/">sided with the lower court</a> and ruled that Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules do not violate antitrust law by not allowing for third-party marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
The dispute between Apple and Epic <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">dates back to 2020</a> with Epic seeking to overturn Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules requiring content purchases within iOS apps to go through Apple, which takes a 15% to 30% cut of the revenue.<br/>
<br/>
In multiple rounds of the dispute, Apple has won on every count with the exception of just one regarding Apple's "anti-steering" rule. In July 2023, a judge ruled that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/app-store-rule-change-epic-games-delayed/">did not have to make changes to its policies</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As a result of the Supreme Court's decision today, the previous rulings stand and Apple is able to continue to disallow third-party payment processing within apps, but will have to allow developers to inform users about other purchasing options outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">US Supreme Court Declines to Hear Apple vs. Epic Games Case</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/us-supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-games-case.2416489/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces Streaming Services and Sports Apps Available on Vision Pro at Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-streaming-services-and-sports-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-streaming-services-and-sports-apps-available-on-vision-pro-at-launch.2416486/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 06:12:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-streaming-services-and-sports-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-previews-new-entertainment-experiences-launching-with-apple-vision-pro/">listed</a> some streaming, video, and sports apps that will be available on the Vision Pro when the headset <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launches on February 2</a>, including Disney+, ESPN, MLB, PGA Tour, Max, Discovery+, Amazon Prime Video, Paramount+, Peacock, Pluto TV, Tubi, Fubo, Crunchyroll, Red Bull TV, IMAX, TikTok, and MUBI. Major League Soccer fans can also access MLS Season Pass through the Apple TV app on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Disney-Plus-Vision-Pro-1.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930910" /><br/>
In addition to apps, users will be able to access many other streaming services using Safari and other web browsers on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro supports both 2D and 3D movies. Apple said Disney+ and several other streaming apps will offer select movies in 3D on the Vision Pro at launch, and will debut 3D versions of new movies alongside or shortly after 2D releases.<br/>
<br/>
At launch, more than 150 3D movies will be available to buy or rent through the Apple TV app on the Vision Pro, such as <em>Avatar: The Way of Water</em>, <em>Dune</em>, <em>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</em>, and <em>The Super Mario Bros. Movie</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Dune-Vision-Pro.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930942" /><br/>
In addition, the Apple TV app will offer a <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/01/apple-tv-unveils-groundbreaking-immersive-originals-from-todays-biggest-storytellers-set-to-debut-on-apple-vision-pro/">selection of content</a> recorded in the new Apple Immersive Video format at no additional cost. Apple says the format consists of 180-degree 3D 8K recordings captured with spatial audio. <br/>
<br/>
That immersive content includes:<blockquote>- <strong>Alicia Keys: Rehearsal Room</strong> offers a rare glimpse into the Grammy winner's creative process with this intimate rehearsal session featuring renditions of her hits "No One," "If I Ain't Got You," and "You Don't Know My Name." Users can also access these performances as a special EP exclusively on Apple Music when it debuts.<br/>
<br/>
- <strong>Adventure</strong> follows pioneering athletes as they take on awe-inspiring challenges in some of the world's most sensational locations. In the first episode, Highlining, viewers step into thin air with highliner Faith Dickey as she takes on her biggest challenge yet: a daring traverse 3,000 feet above Norway's breathtaking fjords.<br/>
<br/>
- <strong>Wild Life</strong> takes viewers up close and personal with some of the most charismatic creatures on the planet to uncover what makes them unique, featuring the experts who know them best. The first episode brings viewers into the world's largest rhinoceros sanctuary where a former police captain has dedicated her life to rescuing, raising, and rewilding these gentle giants.<br/>
<br/>
- <strong>Prehistoric Planet Immersive:</strong> The award-winning Apple Original docuseries from Jon Favreau and the producers of Planet Earth returns with an immersive film that transports viewers into the daily lives of dinosaurs, and follows the struggles and triumphs of these majestic animals amid spectacular scenery. Prehistoric Planet Immersive whisks viewers along a rugged ocean coast where a pterosaur colony settles in for an afternoon nap, which proves to be anything but restful.</blockquote>Vision Pro starts at &#36;3,499 in the U.S., and it will be available to pre-order starting this Friday, January 19. The headset is launching in the U.S. only for now, with availability expected to expand to additional countries <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">later this year</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-streaming-services-and-sports-apps/">Apple Announces Streaming Services and Sports Apps Available on Vision Pro at Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-streaming-services-and-sports-apps-available-on-vision-pro-at-launch.2416486/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Vision Pro to Launch Internationally Before WWDC 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc-2024.2416482/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:42:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is likely to launch its Vision Pro headset outside the United States before WWDC 2024, analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> today reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Teal-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-929939" /><br/>
In a new <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple-is-likely-to-release-vision-pro-outside-the-u-s-d8d2ed8f5f01">post on Medium</a>, Kuo said that Apple plans to share new details about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> with developers from around the globe at its 2024 Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC). To make this push toward global developers worthwhile, Apple needs to make the Vision Pro available in non-U.S. markets before the event. Making the headset available internationally before WWDC would apparently enable Apple to promote a "global development ecosystem" for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo explained that Apple's reasoning for keeping sales of the Vision Pro exclusive to the United States at first is due to limited supply, a wish to ensure that the sales process goes smoothly before expanding it, and to provide time to modify its software to be suitable for other countries. Once these issues have been resolved, Kuo believes the Vision Pro will go on sale in more countries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has hosted WWDC in early June every year since 2007, so it is highly likely to fall at the same time again this year. Earlier this month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that the launch of Vision Pro in other countries around the world <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/07/gurman-vision-pro-launch-imminent/">will not "actually be that much later"</a> than its release in the United States. Apple is said to be considering the United Kingdom, Canada, and China as the next markets to receive the product.<br/>
<br/>
It is not clear how much supply will be available in the rest of the world by the time the Vision Pro goes on sale outside the United States. With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/kuo-vision-pro-sellout-likely/">only 80,000 units</a> expected to be available upon launch in the U.S., the headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/kuo-apple-vision-pro-may-sell-out-fast/">expected to sell out quickly</a> and thereafter be subject to long shipping delays.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">Kuo: Apple Vision Pro to Launch Internationally Before WWDC 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc-2024.2416482/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are All the New M3 Apple Macs Expected This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/here-are-all-the-new-m3-apple-macs-expected-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-new-m3-apple-macs-expected-this-year.2416465/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 02:26:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/here-are-all-the-new-m3-apple-macs-expected-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>M3</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in 2023 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">launched</a> an M3-powered 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, as well as new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3 series chips. But the rest of Apple's Mac lineup is still to be updated to the latest M3 processors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/When-Will-Apple-Launch-More-M3-Macs-Feature-Sans-13inch-MBP.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920524" /><br/>
Now that 2023 is over, attention naturally turns to the other Macs in the company's lineup and where they fit into Apple's M3 roadmap for the year ahead. Here's what the latest rumors say.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Apple sells three versions of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>: A cheaper previous-generation 13-inch model with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip, and 13-inch and 15-inch models equipped with the newer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip. The question is, when will Apple discontinue the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and replace its top-of-the-line 13-inch and 15-inch machines with M3 equivalents?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-MacBook-Air-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920517" /><br/>
<br/>
The existing 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; arrived in June 2023, which is not that long ago in terms of Mac update cycles. However, Apple released the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; 13-inch ‌&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; back in June 2022. It is now the oldest Mac in Apple's current crop, having not been updated in over 550 days.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, Apple has new M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models in development that are scheduled for release in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/macbook-air-march-2024/">March this year</a>. In October it was reported that both models had passed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024/">engineering verification testing (EVT)</a>, an early production testing phase on prototype devices. The M3 chip used in the Airs is expected to have similar CPU and GPU core counts as the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip in the current models.<br/>
<br/>
According to Gurman, Apple is developing the Macs alongside macOS 14.3, an update that is expected between the end of January and February, but new hardware may ship around the March timeframe. The new ‌&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;‌ models could be timed to launch alongside updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, which are coming around March.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac Mini</h2><br/>
Apple announced &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> models in January, which at the time of writing is just over 360 days ago, but Apple could be already testing an M3 &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Mac-Mini-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920522" /><br/>
<br/>
In August, signs of an unknown "15,12" Mac machine were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/07/apple-testing-mac-mini-m3/">found in developer code</a>, with the Mac featuring an 8-core CPU (consisting of four efficiency cores and four performance cores), 10-core GPU, and 24GB RAM. Based on the similar specifications to the base &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; (bar the existing model's 8GB RAM as standard), Gurman believes it represents a next-generation &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/23/new-macbook-pro-and-mac-mini-with-m3-2024-launch/">previously said</a> he was not expecting an M3 version of the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; to launch until late 2024, but as it is already in testing, it could potentially be unveiled sooner.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac Studio, Mac Pro</h2><br/>
Apple updated the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> with &zwnj;M2&zwnj; series chips in June 2023. &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; models come with either the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max or &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chip, while the &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; has adopted the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Mac-Pro-and-Studio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920519" /><br/>
<br/>
Both Macs are considered to be in the middle of their product cycles, and Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/07/apple-working-on-new-mac-studio-and-mac-pro/">believes</a> Apple is working on a new &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; that is likely to launch in the second half of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
The next ‌&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;‌ is likely to be offered with the as-yet-unannounced fourth variant of the M3 chip. Like previous generations, this will double the components of the "Max" version, meaning that it will feature up to 32 CPU cores and 80 GPU cores. Gurman says that Apple is also likely to refresh the &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; with this new high-end chip. <br/>
<br/>
Taiwanese research firm TrendForce claims that Apple will launch a new ‌&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;‌ featuring the M3 Ultra chip at WWDC in June, so we could well see the new &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; alongside of it. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-discontinues-13-inch-macbook-pro/">discontinued</a> the 13-inch &zwnj;M2&zwnj; MacBook Pro – and along with it the Touch Bar – replacing it with a 14-inch model that's equipped with a next-generation M3 chip. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/No-M3-MacBook-Pro-13-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920518" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro is up to 60 percent faster than the 13-inch MacBook Pro with &zwnj;M1&zwnj;. The M3 14-inch MacBook Pro also comes with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-macbook-pro-comparison/">number of other benefits</a> that make it worth the upgrade for anyone with the original 13-inch machine. So do not expect to see an M3-powered 13-inch MacBook Pro anytime soon, if ever.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 Chip Speed and Performance Gains</h2><br/>
The M3 series of chips are built on TSMC's 3-nanometer process, bringing performance and efficiency improvements over Apple's previous &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chips, which are based on the earlier-generation 5-nanometer process. Since its transition to Intel chips, Apple's strategy has been as follows. <br/>
<br/>
In the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; series of Apple silicon, each generation has a baseline version, then a "Pro" chip with more cores for its central processing unit and graphics. Next is an even more powerful "Max" version that doubles the number of graphics cores. Lastly, an "Ultra" model doubles the number of main processing cores and graphics cores found in the "Max." Things are slightly different with the M3 series, as explained below.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of the actual real-world gains, this of course depends on the M3 processor version, coupled with the particular Mac model and other component factors like RAM and thermal dissipation. Nevertheless, all of Apple's M3 chips also boast GPU improvements not found in the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; series, including Dynamic Caching, hardware-accelerated ray tracing, and hardware-accelerated mesh shading.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>M3</h3><br/>
Apple's base M3 chip will likely feature in future &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, as well as an updated lower-end version of the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;. At least in the MacBook Airs, the M3 chip is expected to have similar CPU and GPU core counts as the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip in the current models, but that could be true for the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Chip-Apple-Event-Slide.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920110" /><br/>
Based on Geekbench benchmarks, the M3 chip has single-core and multi-core scores of around 3,000 and 11,700, respectively. The standard &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip has single-core and multi-core scores of around 2,600 and 9,700, respectively, so the M3 chip is up to 20% faster than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, which is what Apple claimed during its "Scary Fast" event in October.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>M3 Pro</h3><br/>
Going on what we know from the recently released 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro M3 models, the M3 Pro chip outperforms the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ Pro, but not by a lot. Based on Geekbench benchmarks, single-core speed is up around 16.7 percent, while multi-core speed is up approximately 6.7 percent. For context, the M3 Pro has 150GB/s memory bandwidth, while the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro had 200GB/s. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-pro-chip.jpg" alt="" width="5104" height="2868" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919649" /><br/>
<br/>
The M3 Pro and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chips in the 16-inch MacBook Pro have 12 CPU cores, but the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro actually featured one additional GPU core over the M3 Pro. Despite that, Apple claims it is 10 percent faster than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro GPU and 40 percent faster than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-pro/">M1 Pro</a> GPU. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>M3 Max</h3><br/>
With the M3 series, Apple deviated slightly from the doubling strategy it followed with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max by adding several more CPU cores to the M3 Max compared to the M3 Pro. Benchmarks indicate that Apple's M3 Max chip in the 16-inch MacBook Pro is around as fast as the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chip used in the current-generation &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; and the higher-end &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;. In other words, the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; is outperformed by what is on paper a lower-end machine, just four months after it was released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Max-Chip.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920348" /><br/>
Note that the M3-powered 16-inch MacBook Pro starts at &#36;3,499 in the U.S. when configured with the M3 Max chip, while the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chip starts at &#36;3,999, so you can effectively get the same performance for &#36;500 less by buying a 16-inch MacBook Pro, which also includes display, keyboard, and trackpad. <br/>
<br/>
Will this performance imbalance alone encourage Apple to bring forward the launch of M3-powered &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; and &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; models? Unlikely. But we can always hope. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>M3 Ultra</h3><br/>
Having not yet been announced, the M3 Ultra chip is something of an unknown quantity. The existing &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra encompasses two &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips for double overall CPU and GPU performance, as well as twice the memory bandwidth (800GB/s), so it would seem safe to expect Apple to follow the same strategy as it did with the M3 Ultra, with similar performance gains over the M3 Max from Apple's next-generation high-end M3 Ultra chip.<br/>
<br/>
In a small deviation, Apple did add several more CPU cores to the M3 Max compared to the M3 Pro. However, if Apple continues to double both the CPU and graphics configurations with the Ultra, the M3 Ultra could end up having 32 CPU cores and 80 graphics cores. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m3/">M3</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/here-are-all-the-new-m3-apple-macs-expected-in-2024/">Here Are All the New M3 Apple Macs Expected This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-new-m3-apple-macs-expected-this-year.2416465/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ships More Smartphones Annually Than Samsung for First Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-top-spot-global-smartphone-shipments/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ships-more-smartphones-annually-than-samsung-for-first-time.2416460/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:48:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-top-spot-global-smartphone-shipments/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>IDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple overtook Samsung as the top global smartphone manufacturer in 2023, according to preliminary data from <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prUS51776424">market research firm IDC</a>. If the data is accurate, it is the first time Samsung has lost the top spot to another company in 13 years. In 2013, Nokia held the number one spot, Samsung was second, and Apple didn't even feature in the top five.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/iphone-14-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875270" /><br/>
IDC bases its analyses on market share of global smartphone shipments across the year. According to the report, Apple took a 20.1% market share, while Samsung took 19.4% of the share. <br/>
<br/>
Apple was also the only company in the top three to achieve positive growth year-on-year, increasing shipments from 226.3 million units to 234.6 million units.<br/>
<blockquote>"While we saw some strong growth from low-end Android players like Transsion and Xiaomi in the second half of 2023, stemming from rapid growth in emerging markets, the biggest winner is clearly Apple," said Nabila Popal, research director with IDC's Worldwide Tracker team. "Not only is Apple the only player in the Top 3 to show positive growth annually, but also bags the number 1 spot annually for the first time ever. All this despite facing increased regulatory challenges and renewed competition from Huawei in China, its largest market."</blockquote>Samsung's drop in rank is interpreted as only partly down to strong sales of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models and the company's debut of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> series, while diversification in the Android market is also said to be a factor. Other impacting variables are said to include Huawei's resurgence in China, and brands like OnePlus, Honor, Google, and others launching competitive devices in the lower price range of the high-end market. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/idc-global-smartphone-shipments-2023.jpg" alt="" width="1828" height="870" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930866" /><br/>
Overall, the smartphone market declined by 3.2% to 1.17 billion units shipped across the year, driven largely by macroeconomic challenges and elevated inventory early in the year. However, a growth spurt in the latter stages of 2023 suggests the market could see a recovery this year, with foldable devices and increased interest in AI capabilities also said to be gaining traction.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/idc/">IDC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-top-spot-global-smartphone-shipments/">Apple Ships More Smartphones Annually Than Samsung for First Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ships-more-smartphones-annually-than-samsung-for-first-time.2416460/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED iPad Pro Displays Now in Production, Devices to Ship in April</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/oled-ipad-displays-enter-production/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pro-displays-now-in-production-devices-to-ship-in-april.2416456/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:01:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/oled-ipad-displays-enter-production/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OLED displays for both of Apple's next-generation iPad Pro models will have entered the production phase by this week in time for device shipments to begin in April, claims a new report by <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=25343">The Elec</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/iPad-Pro-OLED-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853666" /><br/>
According to the Korean-language outlet, LG Display recently began manufacturing the thin film transistor (TFT) for the new 13-inch iPad Pro displays, while Samsung will this week similarly kickstart its own TFT production for the new 11-inch iPad Pro. The TFT essentially acts as a switch to turn off and turn on individual OLED pixels.<br/>
<br/>
Finished 11-inch and 13-inch OLED iPad Pro models are expected to go into mass production around March, in time for a scheduled release in April, according to today's report. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo has said he expects the new ‌iPad Pro‌ models to launch in the second quarter of 2024, which runs from April to June. <br/>
<br/>
The timeframe given by <em>The Elec</em> also dovetails with an earlier <em>Bloomberg</em> report that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ipad-air-ipad-pro-2024-refresh/">claimed</a> the new iPad Pro models could be announced at a March event, along with a new iPad Air that will be available in two sizes for the first time. Apple usually opens pre-orders during an event or a week or two after it, and then begins delivering the devices to customers the following week.<br/>
<br/>
OLED displays are a first for the ‌iPad‌ lineup. Apple has been using OLED technology for the iPhone and the Apple Watch, but larger OLED screens are more expensive. Compared to LED or mini-LED, OLED brings deeper blacks and more vivid colors. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's OLED iPad Pro shipments forecast for the year have reportedly decreased to 8 million units, down from the 10 million units that were projected for 2024 last year. The reduction is said to be a reflection of broadly sluggish performance across Apple's product lineup. Apple did not release any new iPad models last year, so it will be interesting to see if pent-up demand can offset poor sales.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/oled-ipad-prices-to-start-1500-dollars/">OLED iPad Pros Could Start From &#36;1,500, Rising to as Much as &#36;2,000</a></li></ul><br/>
Along with new displays, the ‌iPad Pro‌ models are expected to be powered by Apple's latest M3 chip, which debuted in new MacBook Pro models last year. The M3 is built on 3-nanometer technology, and should bring a notable graphics improvement over the M2 chip that is currently used in the ‌iPad Pro‌.<br/>
<br/>
The displays are expected to be three times the price of those used in iPhones, which could translate to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/oled-ipad-prices-to-start-1500-dollars/">much higher prices for customers</a>. Apple is also rumored to be releasing a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">redesigned Magic Keyboard accessory</a> for the devices, since the screens will be slightly larger and the tablets themselves could be slightly thinner.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/oled-ipad-displays-enter-production/">OLED iPad Pro Displays Now in Production, Devices to Ship in April</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pro-displays-now-in-production-devices-to-ship-in-april.2416456/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple May Sell Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen App in U.S. Amid Patent Dispute</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-app-removal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-may-sell-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches-without-blood-oxygen-app-in-u-s-amid-patent-dispute.2416413/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 11:27:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-app-removal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has readied modified Apple Watch models that "do not contain pulse oximetry functionality," medical technology company Masimo said in a <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/699113770/Apple-Masimo-Notice-of-Supplemental-Authority">document filed today</a> with the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-watch-series-6-blood-oxygen-monitoring-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-759072" /><br/>
The filing, viewed by <em>MacRumors</em>, suggests that Apple will be removing the Blood Oxygen app from new Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models sold in the U.S., at least temporarily. This change would allow Apple to sidestep an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">import and sales ban on Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing</a>, which the U.S. International Trade Commission <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered last year</a> after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents. The ban was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">already temporarily paused</a> shortly after it began last month, but it could have resumed as early as this month, which likely spurred Apple to take this measure.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has started shipping modified Apple Watch models to retail stores in the U.S., according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-15/apple-to-remove-watch-blood-oxygen-app-to-avoid-ban-masimo-says"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, but it's unclear when they will go on sale. Apple has yet to respond to our request for comment.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's website still advertises the Blood Oxygen app as an available feature on the Series 9 and Ultra 2 order pages in the U.S. as of writing. The feature can measure and display your body's blood oxygen percentage, and is intended for "wellness purposes only." Existing owners of the Series 9 and Ultra 2 will likely retain access to the feature, and it is not expected to be removed on models sold in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
The feature's removal is likely a stopgap, as Gurman reported that Apple is preparing a software update that would adjust the Blood Oxygen app's algorithms, in an attempt to avoid Masimo's patented technology. It's unclear if this effort will be successful, and the legal battle between Apple and Masimo is likely far from over.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple's claim that its redesigned watch does not contain pulse oximetry is a positive step toward accountability," a Masimo spokesperson told <em>MacRumors</em>. "It is especially important that one of the world's largest and most powerful companies respects the intellectual property rights of smaller companies and complies with ITC orders when it is caught infringing."<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-app-removal/">Apple May Sell Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen App in U.S. Amid Patent Dispute</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-may-sell-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches-without-blood-oxygen-app-in-u-s-amid-patent-dispute.2416413/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>App Store to Be &#039;Split in Two&#039; Ahead of EU iPhone Sideloading Deadline</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/app-store-to-be-split-in-two/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-to-be-split-in-two-ahead-of-eu-iphone-sideloading-deadline.2416395/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 08:57:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/app-store-to-be-split-in-two/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing to split the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> "in two" in the coming weeks ahead of European Union requirements that will force Apple to enable app sideloading in the region, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Desaturated.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833991" /><br/>
In the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-01-14/how-to-buy-apple-vision-pro-3-499-device-to-go-on-sale-feb-2-lrdjtdm7">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that Apple is gearing up to make changes to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the EU to comply with the region's impending Digital Markets Act (DMA). Apple is apparently planning to roll out adjustments to comply with the new legal requirements in the coming weeks, including splitting off the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the EU from the rest of the world. The deadline for Apple to comply with the DMA is March 7, so the company has just over seven weeks to enact the changes.<br/>
<br/>
Last week, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> met the European Union's antitrust chief, Margrethe Vestager, at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a>. Vestager <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/tim-cook-meets-eu-antitrust-chief/">reminded Cook</a> of Apple's impending obligation to allow users to install third-party app stores and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/app-sideloading-support-coming-ios-17/">sideload apps</a> under the DMA. Apple will also be obliged to give developers the ability to promote their offers outside the ‌‌‌&zwnj;App Store&zwnj;‌‌‌ and use third-party payment systems. The DMA is expected to force Apple to make a range of significant changes to the way the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> work in Europe.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/app-store-to-be-split-in-two/">App Store to Be &#039;Split in Two&#039; Ahead of EU iPhone Sideloading Deadline</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-to-be-split-in-two-ahead-of-eu-iphone-sideloading-deadline.2416395/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>HBO&#039;s Max Streaming Service to Natively Support Vision Pro at Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/hbo-max-apple-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hbos-max-streaming-service-to-natively-support-vision-pro-at-launch.2416387/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 08:30:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/hbo-max-apple-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[You'll soon be able to watch your favorite HBO shows on the Vision Pro, as streaming service Max will be available on Apple's mixed reality headset at launch. Formerly known as HBO Max, the service also offers content from CNN, the DC Universe, the Discovery Channel, the Food Network, HGTV, TBS, TLC, TNT, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Max-Formerly-HBO-Max.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="563" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930755" /><br/>
Apple last week confirmed that Max would be one of the entertainment options available on the Vision Pro, along with Apple TV+ and Disney+.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple Vision Pro features ultra-high-resolution displays that deliver more pixels than a 4K TV for each eye, enabling users to watch movies and TV shows from Apple TV+, Disney+, Max, and other services on a screen that feels 100 feet wide with support for HDR content,"  said Apple, in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-vision-pro-available-in-the-us-on-february-2/">press release</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Max will natively support the visionOS operating system, allowing it to take full advantage of the Vision Pro's immersive capabilities. However, the exact design and functionality of the app remains to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Disney-Plus-Vision-Pro.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930759" /><br/>
Disney CEO Bob Iger last year said Disney+ would also be available on the Vision Pro at launch, promising "deeply personal experiences." Its app will also natively support visionOS, and it will be prominently featured in the App Store on the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Some other streaming services will likely be available on the Vision Pro at launch, but not all will natively support visionOS. For example, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-07-23/apple-vision-pro-will-developers-sell-visionos-apps-for-the-3-499-device-lkfg5b1l"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said</a> Netflix will simply offer its iPadOS app on visionOS without any modifications, at least to start. Apple said the Vision Pro is compatible with over one million iOS and iPadOS apps.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro pre-orders begin in the U.S. this Friday, January 19 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time, and the headset <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launches on Friday, February 2</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/hbo-max-apple-vision-pro/">HBO&#039;s Max Streaming Service to Natively Support Vision Pro at Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hbos-max-streaming-service-to-natively-support-vision-pro-at-launch.2416387/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next-Gen Apple Chip Technology on Track to Reach Production in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-gen-apple-chip-technology-on-track-to-reach-production-in-2025.2416379/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 07:26:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next-generation 2nm chip technology destined for future Apple devices is on schedule to begin production next year, <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240115PD215.html"><em>DigiTimes</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Apple-Silicon-Teal-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-767478" /><br/>
TSMC chip fabrication facilities will begin installing equipment designed for 2nm chip production in April at the earliest. Apple was the first company to utilize TSMC's initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> technology with the A17 Pro chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, and the company is likely to follow suit with the chipmaker's 2nm chips. With production set to begin in 2025, 2nm chips are likely to make their first appearance in Apple devices soon after.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, the <em>Financial Times</em> reported that TSMC had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/tsmc-demos-next-gen-chip-technology/">already demonstrated</a> prototype 2nm chips to Apple ahead of their expected introduction in 2025. Apple is said to be closely aligned with TSMC in the race to develop and implement 2nm chip technology, which will surpass their current &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; chips and associated nodes in terms of transistor density, performance, and efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
Today, <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></em> added that the chip supplier is also believed to be evaluating which of its plants will be the first to produce even <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/tsmc-mentions-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips/">more advanced 1.4nm chips</a> in 2027. The company began mass production of its enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; node, which is likely to appear in Apple devices for the first time later this year, in the fourth quarter of 2023.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/">Next-Gen Apple Chip Technology on Track to Reach Production in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-gen-apple-chip-technology-on-track-to-reach-production-in-2025.2416379/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max to Remain Best-Selling Model in Early 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/iphone-15-pro-max-best-seller-early-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-to-remain-best-selling-model-in-early-2024.2416372/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:11:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/iphone-15-pro-max-best-seller-early-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhone 15 Pro Max will continue to be the best-selling iPhone model in the first half of this year, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/大立光罕見正向看待淡季高階鏡頭需求之深度分析-玻塑混合鏡頭-華為歸來與鏡頭單價上漲-以及ai手機成為samsung-s24-高階手機新賣點-in-depth-analysis-of-8e71324d080b">latest industry note on Medium</a>, Kuo said the iPhone 15 Pro Max "will still account for 40–45% of all iPhone 15 shipments in 1H24," which will be "critical" to Taiwanese camera lens supplier Largan's buoyant off-season in the first half of the year.<br/>
<br/>
Apart from being the premium model with the largest display at 6.7-inches, the iPhone 15 Pro Max also features a 5x Telephoto zoom or "tetraprism" lens that is not found in other models. The tetraprism lens in the Pro Max model alone is expected to increase Largan's first half-year revenue by &#36;108.8 to &#36;121.6 million, according to Kuo. <br/>
<br/>
Kuo has repeatedly said he expects the tetraprism lens to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">expand</a> to both the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max later this year, enabling at least 5x optical zoom and 25x digital zoom on the Telephoto lens of both premium models. <br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro is expected to feature a larger 6.3-inch display, compared to the 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro. This change would increase the overall size of the device, which would provide additional internal space for a tetraprism lens.<br/>
<br/>
According to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/both-iphone-16-pro-models-tetraprism-zoom-lens/">report</a> by <em>The Elec</em>, Apple will add LG Innotek as another supplier of the folded zoom module used in the technology, in an attempt to secure production yields for the increased number of units required.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/iphone-15-pro-max-best-seller-early-2024/">Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max to Remain Best-Selling Model in Early 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-to-remain-best-selling-model-in-early-2024.2416372/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
