<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:03:00 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Hold Q1 2025 Earnings Call on January 30</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/apple-q1-2025-earnings-january-30/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-hold-q1-2025-earnings-call-on-january-30.2446664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:46:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/apple-q1-2025-earnings-january-30/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to hold its first earnings call of 2025 on Thursday, January 30, according to the company's <a href="https://investor.apple.com/investor-relations/default.aspx">Investor Relations website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834994" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/Apple-Logo-Cash-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2676" height="1504" /><br/>
During the call, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and new chief financial officer Kevan Parekh will provide insight into Apple's performance during the 2024 holiday quarter spanning from October to December. Apple's Q4 2024 earnings call was the last for former Apple CFO Luca Maestri, who has now transitioned to a new role as vice president of corporate services.<br/>
<br/>
In the fourth quarter of 2024, Apple released new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> models, so we will get our first look at how these devices performed, as well as some insight into Apple device sales during the holiday period.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in Q1 2024 posted revenue of &#36;119.6 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;33.9 billion. Apple said last quarter that revenue is expected to grow low to mid single digits year-over-year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's earnings call will take place at 2:00 p.m. Pacific Time on the 30th, just after the company's Q1 2025 earnings release.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/apple-q1-2025-earnings-january-30/">Apple to Hold Q1 2025 Earnings Call on January 30</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-hold-q1-2025-earnings-call-on-january-30.2446664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s What&#039;s Changing With Siri in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/siri-2025-updates/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-whats-changing-with-siri-in-2025.2446662/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:52:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/siri-2025-updates/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple started making <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> more capable with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features in iOS 18.1 and iOS 18.2, but there are additional &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; updates that are set to come in 2025 with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>. By this time next year, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; should be much smarter, if Apple's planned changes live up to what the company says is coming.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Features Coming in iOS 18</h2><br/>
The best new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features haven't been added yet, but Apple previewed them at WWDC when &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; was first announced. We're expecting these changes to come in iOS 18.4 in the spring.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Personal Context</h3><br/>
With personal context, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will keep track of your emails, messages, files, photos, and more. If it's on your device, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will know where it is and where it came from.<br/>
<br/>
Using this information, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be be able to help you better find something that you're looking for, whether it's a flight number in an email you received, a file you downloaded, or a photo that someone sent you.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will use personal context to learn more about you too, which means &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to better help you complete tasks and keep track of everything on your device.<br/>
<br/>
Some examples Apple has provided:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Play that podcast that Jamie recommended.</li><br/>
 	<li>When is mom's flight landing?</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3>Onscreen Awareness</h3><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will know what's on your screen, so when you make a request, you can reference what you're looking at. If someone sends you an address via text, for example, you'll be able to tell &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to add "this" to your contacts, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will know what you're talking about.<br/>
<br/>
Onscreen awareness will essentially allow &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to perform actions related to whatever information is on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>'s display.<br/>
<br/>
In iOS 18.2, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is able to send a screenshot of your display to ChatGPT and ChatGPT can perform some of this same functionality, but Apple has clarified that the ChatGPT integration is not the same thing as the future onscreen awareness feature coming to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>App Integration</h3><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is gaining deeper integration with apps, and it's going to allow the personal assistant to perform hundreds of new actions in and across both Apple apps and third-party apps. This feature is so wide-ranging that it's going to cover a lot of new functions, but Apple has provided examples like using &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to bring up articles from the Safari Reading List, or sending photos from a specific location to someone, e.g. "send the photos from the party on Friday to Eric."<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to complete multi-step tasks too, such as editing a photo that you take and then sending it to someone all with one command.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Features Rumored for iOS 19</h2><br/>
All of the features above are part of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and are going to come in an &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update, but rumors suggest that Apple has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/21/apple-llm-siri-2026/">next-generation version of Siri</a> in development for &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; in &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; will rely on large language models, or LLMs. LLMs are what power ChatGPT, Google Gemini, Claude, and other AI chatbot services. An LLM version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to hold ongoing conversations, and it will be more like speaking with a human. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to perform more complex tasks, and will be able to better compete with ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to replace the current version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; with LLM &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; in the future. So far, it sounds like it's going to be announced in &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, but the actual functionality might not come until an &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; update that Apple releases in 2026, much like how &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features have been spread over &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; updates.<br/>
<br/>
We'll hear about &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; features in June at WWDC, and it's possible we could get at least some new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality when &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; launches in September 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>When to Expect the New Siri Features</h2><br/>
The features that Apple has planned for &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; are expected in iOS 18.4, and it looks like that's an update that will come out in April. Apple will release iOS 18.3 in late January, and then we'll get the iOS 18.4 beta. iOS 18.4 will be beta tested for a couple months before it is released to the public.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; features will be introduced in June and the update will launch in September, but we may not get everything at once and some features could come as updates to &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; later in 2025 and in 2026.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More on Siri's Capabilities in iOS 18 and Beyond</h2><br/>
We have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri-apple-intelligence/">full Apple Intelligence Siri guide</a> on all of the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features that have been introduced in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, iOS 18.1, and iOS 18.2, as well as a look at what to expect in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/siri-2025-updates/">Here&#039;s What&#039;s Changing With Siri in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-whats-changing-with-siri-in-2025.2446662/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook Donating &#36;1 Million to Trump&#039;s Inaugural Fund</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/tim-cook-trump-inauguration-donation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-donating-1-million-to-trumps-inaugural-fund.2446658/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 13:27:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/tim-cook-trump-inauguration-donation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> plans to donate &#36;1 million to Donald Trump's inauguration fund, reports <em><a href="https://www.axios.com/2025/01/03/tim-cook-apple-donate-1-million-trump-inauguration">Axios</a></em>. The donation will be a personal donation directly from Cook rather than a donation from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Tim-Cook-MacBook-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-894618" /><br/>
Following Trump's win, Cook <a href="https://x.com/tim_cook/status/1854225875002396860?lang=en">congratulated him</a> on social media site X, and in December, Cook had dinner with Trump at Mar-a-Lago. Cook aimed to maintain a relationship with Trump during Trump's first term as president, and it appears Cook plans to continue on with that plan going forward.<br/>
<br/>
Sources that spoke to <em>Axios</em> said that Cook is donating to the inauguration "in the spirit of unity." Apple is not expected to make a donation.<br/>
<br/>
Trump is taking office as Apple faces regulatory pressure both in the United States and in other countries. In March 2024, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/">Apple was sued</a> by the United States Department of Justice <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">for allegedly violating antitrust law</a> in multiple ways with its platforms. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">Apple vs. DoJ</a> legal battle will play out during Trump's term.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon, Meta, Uber, OpenAI's Sam Altman, Goldman Sachs, Bank of America, Coinbase, Toyota, Ford, GM, AT&amp;T, Black &amp; Decker, and Charter Communications are also making donations to Trump's inauguration fund.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/tim-cook-trump-inauguration-donation/">Apple CEO Tim Cook Donating &#36;1 Million to Trump&#039;s Inaugural Fund</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-donating-1-million-to-trumps-inaugural-fund.2446658/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Reminder: You Can Watch Apple TV+ Shows and Movies for Free This Weekend</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/apple-tv-plus-free-weekend/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/reminder-you-can-watch-apple-tv-shows-and-movies-for-free-this-weekend.2446654/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 12:01:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/apple-tv-plus-free-weekend/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ will be available to stream for free starting on Friday, January 3, with the promotion set to last through Sunday, January 5. For the first time, Apple is providing unlimited access to its catalog of TV shows and movies with no subscription fee.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-TV-Plus-Feature-2-Green-and-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959288" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ streaming service can be accessed <a href="https://tv.apple.com">from any web browser</a> and on any device that has an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app. The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app is available on all iOS and macOS devices and also Android devices, select smart TVs, consoles, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's free viewing event will begin on Friday evening, starting at 5:00 p.m. local time in countries where &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ is available. In Europe, the UK, and countries in Asia, the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ promotion has already started. <br/>
<br/>
To watch &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ for free, all that's needed is an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> to log in. Viewers will not need to subscribe to a free trial or worry about canceling a subscription after the free weekend ends.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple TV+ is Now FREE Watch These Shows ASAP!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yD6Ho0N7AXc" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Apple is offering the free &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ viewing event ahead of the release of the second season of hit thriller Severance. For those new to &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+, Severance is a good choice for a show to check out. Other recommendations include Silo, Shrinking, Ted Lasso, Slow Horses, The Morning Show, Dickinson, For All Mankind, Black Bird, and Bad Sisters.<br/>
<br/>
There are also several movies to watch, like Coda, Killers of the Flower Moon, Fly Me to the Moon, and more.<br/>
<br/>
‌&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;‌+ is priced at &#36;9.99 per month, and up to six members of a Family Sharing group are able to watch content at that price point. It is also available in the various <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription bundles, starting at &#36;19.95 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/apple-tv-plus-free-weekend/">Reminder: You Can Watch Apple TV+ Shows and Movies for Free This Weekend</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/reminder-you-can-watch-apple-tv-shows-and-movies-for-free-this-weekend.2446654/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Apple&#039;s M4 Mac Mini is the Best Desktop Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/m4-mac-mini-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-apples-m4-mac-mini-is-the-best-desktop-mac.2446648/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 10:47:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/m4-mac-mini-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple refreshed the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> back in November, adding M4 chips and increasing the base memory. We did a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/08/m4-mac-mini-hands-on/">hands-on impressions video</a> at the time, but we thought we'd follow that up with a more in-depth review now that we've had more time to spend with Apple's cheapest desktop machine.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/b0_gx6EVk74" title="M4 Mac Mini Review: Apple&#39;s Best Mac for Everyone" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Priced starting at &#36;599, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; offers the most affordable way to get access to Apple's new M4 chip, plus the machine got a design overhaul with the 2024 refresh. The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; now measures in at 5 inches by 5 inches, and it's more than two inches smaller than the prior-generation model. It takes up much less space on a desk, and while it isn't quite as small as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, it offers impressive performance in a super compact package.<br/>
<br/>
With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> and the M4 chip, Apple stopped using 8GB as the base amount of memory that Macs ship with, and upped it to 16GB. The &#36;599 &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; has an M4 chip and 16GB of RAM as a result, and it is an excellent deal for a desktop machine. Of course, you're going to need to supply your own display, keyboard, and mouse, but it's so small that you can easily move it between desktop setups at home and work.<br/>
<br/>
The base &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; comes with an M4 chip, but there is an option to upgrade to the faster M4 Pro for those who need more power. The M4 models have three Thunderbolt 4 ports, but choosing the M4 Pro nets you three Thunderbolt 5 ports with faster transfer speeds. There are also two USB-C ports with 10Gb/s transfer speeds at the front of each machine. Compared to the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, the M4 models are up to 55 percent faster in terms of CPU speed.<br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for a desktop Mac, the base &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; is the best deal that you're going to get. The performance is more than enough for day to day tasks and even gaming, photo editing, and video editing, and that &#36;599 price tag really can't be beat.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/m4-mac-mini-review/">Review: Apple&#039;s M4 Mac Mini is the Best Desktop Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-apples-m4-mac-mini-is-the-best-desktop-mac.2446648/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Limited Edition AirPods 4 for Year of the Snake</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/year-of-the-snake-airpods-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-limited-edition-airpods-4-for-year-of-the-snake.2446641/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 09:30:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/year-of-the-snake-airpods-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[To celebrate the Lunar New Year that starts on January 29, Apple is releasing limited edition <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a> that are engraved with a special Year of the Snake icon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/year-of-the-snake-airpods.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984069" /><br/>
Apple's Year of the Snake &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; are available for purchase in <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/shop/product/MDF24CH/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/shop/product/MDF24ZP/A/special-edition-airpods-4">Hong Kong</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/tw/shop/product/MDF24TA/A/airpods-4-蛇年特別款">Taiwan</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/sg/shop/product/MDF24ZA/A/special-edition-airpods-4">Singapore</a> at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
The AirPods are identical to the standard &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; with Active Noise Cancellation and are available for the same price, but there is a unique engraving on the USB-C case of the device. Released earlier this year, the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; are Apple's first earbuds that offer Active Noise Cancellation without silicone ear tips. The &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; feature adaptive audio, transparency mode, support for spatial audio, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Customers can place orders for the special edition &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; as of today, with deliveries set to begin on January 8. Apple is limiting each customer to two of the Year of the Snake AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
Creating special edition AirPods is a tradition for Apple, though in past years, Apple has customized <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> rather than standard AirPods. There have been limited edition AirPods to celebrate the Year of the Dragon, Year of the Ox, Year of the Tiger, and Year of the Rabbit.<br/>
<br/>
Along with special edition AirPods, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-discounts-products-in-china/">holding a New Year sale in China</a>, dropping the price of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models by 500 yuan, and discounting other devices like the AirPods, Macs, iPads, and accessories. Apple is also offering Year of the Snake themed Today at Apple sessions from January 4 to February 14.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/year-of-the-snake-airpods-4/">Apple Releases Limited Edition AirPods 4 for Year of the Snake</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-limited-edition-airpods-4-for-year-of-the-snake.2446641/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Stick to Your New Year&#039;s Resolutions With Sales on Apple Watch and AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-3-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-stick-to-your-new-years-resolutions-with-sales-on-apple-watch-and-airpods-pro-2.2446636/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:41:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-3-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's the first week of 2025, and if you're trying to stay on track with any fitness-related New Year's resolutions there are a few deals you might be interested in this week. This includes a &#36;70 discount on Apple Watch Series 10, as well as &#36;59 off the AirPods Pro 2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0000.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847990" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/apple-watch-series-10-new-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984049" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;70 off Apple Watch Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-10-new-years-2/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is hosting a big New Year's sale across the Apple Watch Series 10 lineup, with &#36;70 off numerous models of the 42mm and 46mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/airpods-pro-2-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984050" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;59 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0DGJ7HYG1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has a few AirPods discounts available to kick off 2025, and the best one is on the AirPods Pro 2 at &#36;189.99, down from &#36;249.00. Of course, there was a better deal on this model during Black Friday last year, but if you missed out on those holiday deals and want the AirPods Pro 2 in the new year, this is the best discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/airtag-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984051" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;26 off AirTag 4-Pack</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;26 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;72.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has Apple's AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;72.99 this week, down from &#36;99.00. While this is a second-best price, it's only &#36;3 higher when compared to the all-time low price on the accessory, and still a great deal if you need an AirTag for any upcoming 2025 travel plans.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ipad-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984052" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;70 off 10th gen iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;279.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has three models of the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;279.00 this week, down from &#36;349.00. Although this was cheaper around the Black Friday season last year, this &#36;279.00 price point has been a more common deal since and it's still a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMac</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/imac-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984053" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;105 off M4 iMac</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL76BQ5N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL76BQ5N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;105 OFF</div>M4 iMac (16GB RAM, 256GB) for &#36;1,194.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, this week at Amazon you can get the M4 iMac (16GB RAM, 256GB) for &#36;1,194.00, down from &#36;1,299.00, which is a new record low price on the desktop.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-3-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Stick to Your New Year&#039;s Resolutions With Sales on Apple Watch and AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-stick-to-your-new-years-resolutions-with-sales-on-apple-watch-and-airpods-pro-2.2446636/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Air&#039;s Thickness and Price Range Revealed in New Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/iphone-17-air-thickness-and-price-range-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-airs-thickness-and-price-range-revealed-in-new-report.2446631/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 07:16:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/iphone-17-air-thickness-and-price-range-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is widely rumored to be planning an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/#iphone_17_air">ultra-thin iPhone 17 model</a> for release later this year, and a new report offers a few purported details.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iPhone-17-Slim-Feature-Single-Camera-1-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-974628" /><br/>
South Korea's <a href="https://www.sisajournal-e.com/news/articleView.html?idxno=408493"><em>Sisa Journal</em> today reported</a> that Apple is aiming for the so-called "iPhone 17 Air" to be 6.25mm thick. If that measurement ends up being accurate, the device would become the thinnest iPhone ever, topping the current 6.9mm record set by the iPhone 6. It also means the device would be around 20% thinner than the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus, and around 25% thinner than the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
Most rumors seem to agree that the "iPhone 17 Air" will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/iphone-17-air-could-be-thinnest-iphone-ever/">somewhere in the 6mm thickness range</a>, with one rumor going <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">as low as 5mm</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The report said the ultra-thin iPhone 17's price will be similar to that of the iPhone 16 Plus, which starts at &#36;899 in the United States. Apple is not expected to release an iPhone 17 Plus, and the "iPhone 17 Air" will effectively be its replacement.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung is also planning to release a substantially thinner smartphone this year, according to the report. Similar to the "iPhone 17 Air," the so-called "Galaxy S25 Slim" will apparently have a thickness in the mid-6mm range.<br/>
<br/>
There have been conflicting rumors about "iPhone 17 Air" design details and specifications, but most sources have agreed that the device will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">around a 6.6-inch display</a>. Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">said</a> he expects the device to have a standard A19 chip, a Dynamic Island, a single rear camera, and an Apple-designed 5G modem. The device is expected to be equipped with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence support</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, the device would have some compromises compared to the Pro models in order to achieve a much thinner and lighter design.<br/>
<br/>
Apple should release all iPhone 17 models in September, and additional rumors will likely surface about the "iPhone 17 Air" between now and then.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/iphone-17-air-thickness-and-price-range-report/">iPhone 17 Air&#039;s Thickness and Price Range Revealed in New Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-airs-thickness-and-price-range-revealed-in-new-report.2446631/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Fitness+ Announces New Programs, Strava Integration, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/fitness-plus-new-programs-strava-integration/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fitness-announces-new-programs-strava-integration-and-more.2446623/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 04:31:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/fitness-plus-new-programs-strava-integration/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Apple Fitness Plus</category>
		<category>Strava</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/01/apple-fitness-plus-unveils-an-exciting-lineup-of-new-ways-to-stay-active-in-2025/?1735905582">announced</a> that Apple Fitness+ is set to gain new workout programs, breath meditation, Strava integration, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Fitness-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-955996" /><br/>
Strava users will be able to share a Fitness+ workout directly to the Strava app, which will display rich details such as episode image and number, trainer name, and metrics to show to their Strava community. Celebrated Strava athletes will also join the Fitness+ trainer team as special guests in workouts throughout 2025. New and existing Strava subscribers can now redeem up to three months of Fitness+ at no additional cost.<br/>
<br/>
An all-new progressive strength training program will help guide users through the process of building and maintaining strength. The program is three weeks in duration and targets every major muscle group with 12 30-minute workouts, and it is designed for repeatability so users can add weight as they grow stronger. Week one focuses on progressive load, week two focuses on time under tension, and week three focuses on dynamic power.<br/>
<br/>
A new pickleball program is designed to improve strength, endurance, and agility with a mix of exercises. It features pickleball champion Catherine Parenteau, who has been ranked No. 1 in the world in both singles and doubles.<br/>
<br/>
Yoga Peak Poses are new workshop-style sessions that spotlight a single pose to help users build confidence and skill, featuring a 10-minute prep flow and a corresponding 10 minute practice session.<br/>
<br/>
A new Introduction to Breath Meditation program teaches users how to use simple meditation techniques to enhance focus, increase energy, and reduce stress. There are five 10-minute meditations to choose from. Breath is also now a meditation theme in Fitness+, joining Calm, Sleep, and Sound.<br/>
<br/>
The new Apple Fitness+ content will be available starting Monday, January 6. A new limited-edition Apple Watch award is available for users who close all three activity rings for seven days in a row in January.<br/>
<br/>
New episodes of Time to Walk are set to debut on January 13 with Adam Scott, Steve Aoki, Lana Condor, Tiffany Haddish, Rita Ora, Daddy Yankee, and Maddie Ziegler. Artist Spotlights also continue with new workout playlists dedicated to individual artists, including Janet Jackson, Coldplay, Bruno Mars, and Kendrick Lamar.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-fitness-plus/">Apple Fitness Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/strava/">Strava</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/fitness-plus-new-programs-strava-integration/">Apple Fitness+ Announces New Programs, Strava Integration, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fitness-announces-new-programs-strava-integration-and-more.2446623/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Telegram Adds New Verification Option to Cut Down on Scams</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/telegram-third-party-verification/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/telegram-adds-new-verification-option-to-cut-down-on-scams.2446598/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:17:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/telegram-third-party-verification/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Telegram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Telegram <a href="https://telegram.org/blog/collectible-gifts-and-more">today announced</a> the launch of a new feature that will allow official third-party services to <a href="https://telegram.org/verify#third-party-verification">assign extra verification icons</a> to user accounts and chats. The added verification is meant to cut down on scams and reduce misinformation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/telegram-extra-verification.jpg" alt="" width="1772" height="997" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984015" /><br/>
While Telegram already has a verification process for public figures and organizations, trusted third-party services will be able to provide additional verification options. A chat or account that has a third-party verification will be marked with a small logo before their name, and opening the associated profile will show a more detailed explanation of the account's status and what it means.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party verification is separate from the verified checkmarks that Telegram provides to public figures and organizations. A service that wants to provide third-party verification to others must first be verified by Telegram and must complete an application.<br/>
<br/>
According to Telegram, third-party verification will make it easier for users to independently confirm the people they contact and services they interact with.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the new verification option, Telegram added support for collectible gifts, reactions for service messages, extra message search filters, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Telegram says that its first major update of 2025 was actually supposed to come in on the last day of 2024, but it was "sadly delayed by a lack of attention from Apple's review team."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/telegram/">Telegram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/telegram-third-party-verification/">Telegram Adds New Verification Option to Cut Down on Scams</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/telegram-adds-new-verification-option-to-cut-down-on-scams.2446598/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Shell Out &#36;95 Million to Settle Siri Spying Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-settles-siri-spying-lawsuit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-shell-out-95-million-to-settle-siri-spying-lawsuit.2446588/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 11:17:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-settles-siri-spying-lawsuit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will pay &#36;95 million to settle a proposed class action lawsuit involving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> spying accusations, reports <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/apple-pay-95-million-settle-siri-privacy-lawsuit-2025-01-02/">Reuters</a></em>. The lawsuit alleges that Apple recorded conversations captured with accidental &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; activations, and then shared information from those conversations with third-party advertisers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/siri-glow.png" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-809517" /><br/>
Two plaintiffs claimed that after speaking about products like Air Jordan shoes and Olive Garden, their devices showed ads for those products, while another said he received ads for a surgical treatment after discussing it privately with his doctor.<br/>
<br/>
The lawsuit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/07/apple-lawsuit-siri-recordings/">dates back to 2019</a>, after a report outed the private conversations <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/26/siri-human-analysis-voice-recordings/">that contractors were privy to</a> when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; was accidentally activated. Apple was using contractors to evaluate &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings to make improvements to the service, and employees claimed to have heard confidential medical information, drug deals, intimate moments, and other private data.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was never secretive about the fact that some &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings were analyzed by humans, but the company's privacy terms at the time did not explicitly state that there was human oversight of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;. The customers that filed the lawsuit said that Apple did not inform consumers that they are "regularly being recorded without consent," and they claimed they would not have purchased Apple devices had they known about the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings.<br/>
<br/>
While the lawsuit initially focused on Apple's lack of disclosure, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/10/apple-siri-recording-lawsuit-dismissed/">first filing was dismissed</a> in February 2021 because it did not include enough concrete data about the recordings that Apple allegedly collected. An amended complaint that focused on &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings used for "targeted advertising" was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/02/apple-must-face-siri-privacy-lawsuit/">refiled in September 2021</a>, and that was allowed to move forward.<br/>
<br/>
There has been no evidence that Apple ever provided &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings or information from &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings to advertisers, and Apple's privacy policies have long made it clear that any data collected from &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; for the purpose of improving the feature is anonymized and not associated with a specific user.<br/>
<br/>
In the settlement filing, Apple says that it "continues to deny any and all alleged wrongdoing and liability, specifically denies each of the Plaintiffs' contentions and claims, and continues to deny that the Plaintiffs' claims and allegations would be suitable for class action status." Apple is settling to avoid further costs of litigation.<br/>
<br/>
The settlement has received preliminary approval from the court. According to the filing, all current or former owners or purchasers of a &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; device in the United States whose confidential or private communications were obtained by Apple between September 17, 2014 and December 31, 2024 are considered class members and could be eligible for a payment.<br/>
<br/>
A settlement website will be set up to identify those eligible to participate within 45 days, with Apple required to share contact information for customers who purchased a device with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; capabilities. Claim information will be collected until May 15, 2025, after which time the settlement will be finalized and payments will go out to eligible customers. Each class member will be able to submit claims for up to five &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; devices, receiving up to &#36;20 for each one. The actual settlement payment will depend on the total number of valid claims that are submitted.<br/>
<br/>
After the 2019 scandal about contractors listening to accidental &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/02/apple-suspending-siri-grading-program/">temporarily suspended</a> its &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; evaluation program, stopped using contractors, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/10/10/siri-privacy-options-ios-13-2/">implemented options</a> that allow users to delete &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; recordings and block them from being listened to. In later updates, Apple moved some &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; processing on-device, reducing the content that's uploaded to its servers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-settles-siri-spying-lawsuit/">Apple to Shell Out &#36;95 Million to Settle Siri Spying Lawsuit</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-shell-out-95-million-to-settle-siri-spying-lawsuit.2446588/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 10 Hits Record Low Prices on Amazon for All Your New Year&#039;s Resolution Fitness Needs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-10-new-years-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-hits-record-low-prices-on-amazon-for-all-your-new-years-resolution-fitness-needs.2446583/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 10:29:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-10-new-years-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is kicking off the year with <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">numerous all-time low prices</a> on Apple Watch Series 10, perfect timing for anyone looking for a smartwatch to help fulfill any New Year's health and fitness resolutions. You'll find &#36;70 off both 42mm and 46mm GPS Series 10 models in multiple case colors and band styles, and this time the deals do not require any coupon codes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-watch-series-10-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968482" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Every price listed below is a match of the record low prices on the Apple Watch Series 10, and in some cases delivery is slipping into February. If you've been eyeing an Apple Watch Series 10 as a way to help keep up with your New Year's resolutions, and didn't get one for the holidays, now is the time to purchase one at these best-ever prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><h2>42mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHLCYJ7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Black Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Black Sport Band (S/M)</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJBRKHV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Ink Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ1YMC1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Rose Gold Aluminum Case with Light Blush Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHV8NLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Rose Gold Aluminum Case with Plum Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ2C3YR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Blue Cloud Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHHJ1PJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Denim Sport Band (S/M)</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>46mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Black Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ4QLYH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Black Sport Band (S/M)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHNXP5Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Ink Sport Loop</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3WKR6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Rose Gold Aluminum Case with Light Blush Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHVB7QS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Blue Cloud Sport Loop</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ1F2BG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Denim Sport Band (S/M)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ745J6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Denim Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-10-new-years-2/">Apple Watch Series 10 Hits Record Low Prices on Amazon for All Your New Year&#039;s Resolution Fitness Needs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-hits-record-low-prices-on-amazon-for-all-your-new-years-resolution-fitness-needs.2446583/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Made a Change to the AirTag That You Probably Didn&#039;t Notice</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/airtag-battery-warning-labels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-made-a-change-to-the-airtag-that-you-probably-didnt-notice.2446582/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 10:12:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/airtag-battery-warning-labels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC) today <a href="https://www.cpsc.gov/Newsroom/News-Releases/2025/CPSC-Secures-Agreement-with-Apple-for-Enhanced-Warnings-to-Protect-Children-from-Hazards-of-Battery-Ingestion-Apple-Takes-Action-to-Address-Labeling-Violations-on-AirTags">announced</a> that Apple has added a warning label to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a>'s box that says to keep its coin-cell battery out of reach of children due to the severe risk of injury or death if the battery is ingested. Apple added a corresponding warning symbol inside the AirTag's battery compartment too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/airtag-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849630" /><br/>
Apple made these changes at some point after "Reese's Law" went into effect in March 2024, according to the announcement. The CPSC did not indicate if the warnings were added to the AirTag in the U.S. only or worldwide. <br/>
<br/>
"Reese's Law" aims to prevent injuries and deaths caused by the tiny, circular coin-cell batteries. The law was named after Reese Hamsmith, a baby who died in 2020 after swallowing a coin-cell battery that was inside of a remote control.<br/>
<br/>
Given that many AirTags without these warnings had already been sold, the CPSC said Apple now displays a warning about the hazards of coin-cell batteries in the Find My app each time a user is prompted to change the AirTag's battery.<br/>
<br/>
The announcement was <a href="https://macreports.com/apple-updates-airtag-warnings-to-comply-with-safety-standards-after-cpsc-violation-notice/">first reported by <em>macReports</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/what-to-expect-from-airtag-2/">expected to release an AirTag 2 this year</a> with longer range for item tracking. It is also rumored that the AirTag 2's built-in speaker will be more difficult to remove compared to the original AirTag, as an anti-stalking measure.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/airtag-battery-warning-labels/">Apple Made a Change to the AirTag That You Probably Didn&#039;t Notice</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-made-a-change-to-the-airtag-that-you-probably-didnt-notice.2446582/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>RIP, Apple Watch Series 4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-4-now-vintage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rip-apple-watch-series-4.2446579/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:09:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-4-now-vintage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's nearly the end of the road for the Apple Watch Series 4, which was added to Apple's public-facing <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage products list</a> today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Watch-Series-4-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1800" height="1012" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983960" /><br/>
All aluminum and stainless steel 40mm and 44mm models of the Apple Watch Series 4 are now considered vintage worldwide. Apple considers a device to be vintage once five years have passed since the company stopped distributing it for sale. Apple and Apple Authorized Service Providers may offer repairs for vintage devices if parts remain available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch Series 4 models launched in 2018, ushering in a major new design with a thinner case and a 30% larger display than before.<br/>
<br/>
The latest watchOS 11 update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/">dropped support for the Apple Watch Series 4</a>, as well as the Apple Watch Series 5 and the original Apple Watch SE.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also added the final 15-inch MacBook Pro model to the vintage products list today. This particular model launched in May 2019, and it was pretty quickly succeeded by the first 16-inch MacBook Pro in November of that year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-watch-series-4-now-vintage/">RIP, Apple Watch Series 4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rip-apple-watch-series-4.2446579/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discounts Products in China Amid Fierce Competition</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-discounts-products-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discounts-products-in-china-amid-fierce-competition.2446576/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 06:54:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-discounts-products-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has announced rare direct discounts on its flagship <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models and other products in China, signaling an effort to counter mounting competition and fluctuating consumer demand in one of its largest markets.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iPhone-16-Pro-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-964606" /><br/>
Between January 4 and January 7, Apple will provide discounts of up to 500 yuan (approximately &#36;68) on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max models through its website and Apple Stores in mainland China. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus models will be discounted by 400 yuan, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models will receive markdowns of up to 300 yuan. Other products, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Apple Watch, AirPods, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, will also see price reductions, with the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; eligible for a discount of up to 800 yuan. The promotional items are available in limited quantities, with only 29,300 iPhones included in the sale. The promotion is tied to specific payment methods, such as WeChat Pay and Alipay.<br/>
<br/>
Apple rarely offers direct discounts on its latest products, particularly its flagship &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. Such promotions are usually handled by third-party retailers in China, especially during major shopping events like Singles Day, when platforms like Alibaba's Tmall and Pinduoduo slash prices to drive sales. For instance, during the last Singles Day shopping festival in November, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models were discounted by as much as 1,600 yuan on Tmall. The timing of the latest promotion comes as Apple faces heightened competition from Huawei and other Chinese brands, although the company did offer a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">similar promotion last year</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/apple-discounts-products-in-china/">Apple Discounts Products in China Amid Fierce Competition</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discounts-products-in-china-amid-fierce-competition.2446576/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Plans to Expand iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses to These 7 U.S. States</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/iphone-drivers-licenses-states-in-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-plans-to-expand-iphone-drivers-licenses-to-these-7-u-s-states.2446574/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 06:45:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/iphone-drivers-licenses-states-in-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In select U.S. states, residents can <a href="https://learn.wallet.apple/id">add their driver's license or state ID to the Wallet app</a> on the iPhone and Apple Watch, providing a convenient and contactless way to display proof of identity or age at select airports and businesses, and in select apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-wallet-drivers-license-feature-iPhone-15-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947140" /><br/>
Below, we outline which U.S. states and territories offer the feature, and additional states that have committed to rolling it out in the future. 2025 just began, and many of the states listed below will likely roll out the feature throughout the year.<br/>
<h2>Supported States</h2><br/>
<ul><li>Arizona (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/23/apple-launches-ids-in-wallet-arizona/">March 2022</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Maryland (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/25/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-maryland/">May 2022</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Colorado (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/colorado-ids-wallet-app-support/">November 2022</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Georgia (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/18/iphone-drivers-license-georgia/">May 2023</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Ohio (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/iphone-drivers-licenses-ohio/">July 2024</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Hawaii (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-wallet-app-ids-seventh-state/">August 2024</a>)</li><br/>
<li>California (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-california/">September 2024</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Iowa (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/iowa-wallet-iphone-drivers-license-support/">October 2024</a>)</li><br/>
<li>New Mexico (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/05/iphone-drivers-license-support-new-mexico/">December 2024</a>)</li></ul>The feature is also available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/12/apple-wallet-ids-expand-to-10th-location/">Puerto Rico</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Future States</h2><br/>
Apple said the following states have "signed on" to adopt the feature in the future:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Montana</li><br/>
<li>West Virginia</li><br/>
<li>Connecticut</li><br/>
<li>Kentucky</li><br/>
<li>Mississippi</li><br/>
<li>Oklahoma</li><br/>
<li>Utah</li></ul>The feature will also work with Japan's My Number Card in the future, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Participating Airports</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-Wallet-ID-TSA.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-868295" /><br/>
Apple Wallet app IDs can be used at select TSA checkpoints within select U.S. airports:<ul><li>Baltimore/Washington International Thurgood Marshall Airport (BWI)</li><br/>
<li>Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA)</li><br/>
<li>Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX)</li><br/>
<li>Denver International Airport (DEN)</li><br/>
<li>Hartsfield–Jackson Atlanta International Airport (ATL)</li><br/>
<li>Cincinnati/Northern Kentucky Airport (CVG)</li><br/>
<li>John Glenn Columbus International Airport (CMH)</li><br/>
<li>San Francisco International Airport (SFO)</li><br/>
<li>San Jose Mineta International Airport (SJC)</li><br/>
<li>Los Angeles International (LAX)</li><br/>
<li>Daniel K. Inouye International Airport (HNL)</li><br/>
<li>Des Moines International Airport (DSM)</li><br/>
<li>Eastern Iowa Airport (CID)</li><br/>
<li>Albuquerque International Sunport (ABQ)</li><br/>
<li>Lea County Regional Airport (HOB)</li><br/>
<li>Luis Munoz Marin International Airport (SJU)</li></ul>Apple says travelers should refer to TSA checkpoint signage to confirm availability of the feature, and the <a href="https://www.tsa.gov/travel/digital-id/map">TSA's website offers more details</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to participating TSA checkpoints, Apple in September announced that users would soon be able to present an Apple Wallet ID for CLEAR member enrollment at airports. Apple Wallet IDs can also be used to show proof of age or identity at select businesses and venues in the U.S., although Apple does not maintain a list of specific locations for this.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/iphone-drivers-licenses-states-in-2025/">Apple Plans to Expand iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses to These 7 U.S. States</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-plans-to-expand-iphone-drivers-licenses-to-these-7-u-s-states.2446574/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New MacBook Air Models Coming Soon With These Rumored Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/what-to-expect-from-2025-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-models-coming-soon-with-these-rumored-features.2446573/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 06:42:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/what-to-expect-from-2025-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of Apple's first product announcements of 2025 will likely be updated 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models with the M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898576" /><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about the next MacBook Air models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Expected</h3><br/>
<br/>
The new MacBook Air models are expected to be equipped with Apple's already-released <strong>M4 chip</strong>, which has a 10-core CPU and a 10-core GPU.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already updated the MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini with M4 chips a few months ago. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-chip-benchmarks/">Geekbench 6 results</a> showed that the M4 chip is <strong>up to 25% faster than the M3 chip</strong> in terms of multi-core CPU performance, while the chip's power efficiency improvements should contribute to the MacBook Air getting <strong>longer battery life</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/30/macbook-air-now-starts-with-16gb-ram/">increased the minimum RAM</a> included in all MacBook Air models from 8GB to 16GB, so expect <strong>16GB of RAM</strong> for base 2025 configurations.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last redesigned the MacBook Air in 2022. <strong>No major external design changes</strong> have been rumored for the next MacBook Air models.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Likely</h3><br/>
<br/>
Following in the footsteps of the MacBook Pro, the next MacBook Air models will likely have an upgraded <strong>12-megapixel camera with support for Center Stage</strong>, a feature that automatically keeps you centered on video as you move around. The camera will likely also support <strong>Desk View</strong>, which shows an overhead view of your desk.<br/>
<br/>
Center Stage is available in video calling apps like FaceTime and Zoom. The feature was previously limited to newer iPad models and Macs connected to Apple's external Studio Display. The new MacBook Pro and iMac models were the first Macs to support Center Stage without needing to rely on a Studio Display.<br/>
<br/>
The new MacBook Air models will likely be equipped with <strong>three Thunderbolt 4 ports</strong>, whereas the current models have two Thunderbolt 3 ports. The new models will likely support <strong>up to two external displays</strong>, even when the lid is open. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Possible</h3><br/>
<br/>
The latest MacBook Pro and iMac models can be configured with a <strong>nano-texture display</strong>, which has a special coating that better scatters light to further minimize glare on the screen. It is possible that Apple will extend this option to the new MacBook Air models, unless it opts to keep the option exclusive to the MacBook Pro among its laptops.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Timing</h2><br/>
<br/>
Last month, Apple released macOS Sequoia 15.2, and in doing so it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/macos-sequoia-15-2-m4-macbook-air-leak/">accidentally confirmed new MacBook Air models</a> are coming this year.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman recently said the new MacBook Air models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/">will be announced "earlier" than some other devices</a> rumored to launch this spring, such as a new iPhone SE. This likely means the new MacBook Air models will be announced in a press release on the Apple Newsroom website at some point from <strong>January through March</strong>, whereas the other devices might be announced at Apple's usual spring event in March or April. Apple would be getting the minor MacBook Air update out of the way early.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/02/what-to-expect-from-2025-macbook-air/">New MacBook Air Models Coming Soon With These Rumored Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-models-coming-soon-with-these-rumored-features.2446573/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What Do You Want to See From Apple in 2025?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-2025-wishlist/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-in-2025.2446527/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 09:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-2025-wishlist&#038;post_date=1735761600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Based on rumors and historical product release information, 2025 is going to be an exciting year for Apple. As we outlined in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-from-apple-2025/">annual What to Expect Guide</a>, Apple is redesigning the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, jumping into new smart home tech, and preparing to launch new Apple-designed chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-2025-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983757" /><br/>
Early in the year, we're expecting to get the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 4, a low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models, and a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, then later, we'll get a new smart home "Command Center," a whole new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup, new Apple Watch models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, plus a bunch more.<br/>
<br/>
While we know what's likely to launch based on rumors and past release information, we want to hear from the MacRumors community. What are you hoping to see Apple release this year?<br/>
<br/>
Are you looking forward to a new version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>? New &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; features? A more cohesive smart home strategy? What do you want to see in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> and macOS 16?<br/>
<br/>
Let us know your thoughts in the comments, and take a look at our What to Expect guide for an overview of the current rumors. We'll be hearing a lot more about Apple's 2025 plans in the coming months, and as always, we'll have in-depth coverage at MacRumors.com.<br/>
<br/>
If you want to discuss Apple's upcoming products, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/">our MacRumors forums</a> are an excellent resource, plus they're a great place to get help on current Apple products, software, and just to find like-minded folks in the Apple community.<br/>
<br/>
A big thank you to our readers and our forum members for continuing to make MacRumors the number one source for Apple news, rumors, and advice. MacRumors celebrated its 24th birthday this year, thanks to our dedicated supporters. We're looking forward to another year of rumors and product launches in 2025. Happy New Year!<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-2025-wishlist/">What Do You Want to See From Apple in 2025?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-in-2025.2446527/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Special Wallpaper and Watch Face to Celebrate New Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/apple-store-mixc-hefei/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-special-wallpaper-and-watch-face-to-celebrate-new-store.2446532/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 08:59:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/apple-store-mixc-hefei/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/retail/mixchefei/">announced</a> it will be opening a new retail store at the MixC Hefei shopping mall in Hefei, China on January 18 at 10 a.m. local time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple_Hefei_Wallpaper_Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983873" /><br/>
To celebrate the store's upcoming grand opening, Apple has shared both a special wallpaper and <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/nso/hefei/images/wallpaper/Apple_Hefei_Wallpaper_Watch.watchface">Apple Watch face</a> featuring a custom-designed Apple logo.<br/>
<br/>
The wallpaper is available for the <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/nso/hefei/images/wallpaper/Apple_Hefei_Wallpaper_iPhone.jpg">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/nso/hefei/images/wallpaper/Apple_Hefei_Wallpaper_iPad.jpg">iPad</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/nso/hefei/images/wallpaper/Apple_Hefei_Wallpaper_Mac.jpg">Mac</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Ahead of the Chinese New Year later this month, Apple will be running a promotion in China that offers savings on select products. The promotion runs from January 4 through January 7, and details are available <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/store">on Apple's online store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/26/apple-japan-new-year-promotion/">annual Japanese New Year promotion</a> is <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/shop/gifts/new-year">now underway</a>, with customers in Japan able to receive savings and/or a special AirTag with select purchases.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/storetellee">Filip Chudzinski</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/apple-store-mixc-hefei/">Apple Shares Special Wallpaper and Watch Face to Celebrate New Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-special-wallpaper-and-watch-face-to-celebrate-new-store.2446532/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;iPhone SE 4&#039; Rumored to Be Named &#039;iPhone 16E&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e.2446525/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 08:31:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Fixed Focus Digital</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/iphone-se-4-expected-to-launch-in-march/">release a fourth-generation iPhone SE in March</a>, but it has been rumored that the device will have a different name.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
The device succeeding the third-generation iPhone SE will be named the iPhone 16E, according to a <a href="https://weibo.com/5821279480/P4GTgeTRj">December 13 post from Fixed Focus Digital</a>, an account with over two million followers on Chinese social media platform Weibo. On December 31, another leaker known as <a href="https://x.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1874078173802942732">Majin Bu on X also cited a source</a> who said the device's name will be iPhone 16E.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if the name would use a capital E, or if the name would end up being iPhone 16e, or iPhone 16 with an <a href="https://www.compart.com/en/unicode/U+1F134#:~:text=%E2%80%9C%F0%9F%84%B4%E2%80%9D%20U%2B1F134%20Squared%20Latin%20Capital%20Letter%20E%20Unicode%20Character">E inside a square</a>. Or perhaps iPhone 16 SE? Or, this rumor is simply wrong and Apple sticks with iPhone SE branding.<br/>
<br/>
"Fixed Focus Digital" doesn't have a very established <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fixed-focus-digital/">track record with Apple rumors</a> yet. The account accurately claimed the iPhone 16 Pro models would be available in a new bronze finish, which ended up being Desert Titanium, but the color had already been rumored at the time. On the other hand, the account was wrong about the number of iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus color options that would be available. The account's make-or-break moment will mostly come down to whether its claims about the iPhone SE's successor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/">using the same chassis as the iPhone 16</a> and being named iPhone 16E prove to be accurate.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, the device is said to have a similar design as the base iPhone 14, which is similar to the base iPhone 16. Rumored features include a 6.1-inch OLED display, Face ID, a USB-C port, a single 48-megapixel rear camera, a newer A-series chip and 8GB of RAM <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/">for Apple Intelligence</a>, and the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apple-5g-modem-plans-report/">Apple-designed 5G modem</a>. It is not clear if the device will have an Action button, which debuted on the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced the current iPhone SE during an online event <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/08/apple-announces-new-iphone-se/">in March 2022</a>. The device looks similar to the iPhone 8, with outdated features such as a Touch ID button, Lightning port, and thick bezels around the display. In the U.S., the iPhone SE currently starts at &#36;429, but at least a slight price increase seems likely for the next model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fixed-focus-digital/">Fixed Focus Digital</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e/">&#039;iPhone SE 4&#039; Rumored to Be Named &#039;iPhone 16E&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e.2446525/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
