<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 01:03:30 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Adobe Premiere Pro Gains AI Tools to Add and Remove Objects From Videos, Extend Clips and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/adobe-premiere-pro-ai-tools/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-premiere-pro-gains-ai-tools-to-add-and-remove-objects-from-videos-extend-clips-and-more.2424261/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:28:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/adobe-premiere-pro-ai-tools/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Adobe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Adobe <a href="https://news.adobe.com/news/news-details/2024/Adobe-previews-breakthrough-AI-innovations-to-advance-professional-video-workflows-within-Adobe-Premiere-Pro/">today debuted</a> several new AI features for Premiere Pro, software designed for professional video editing. Adobe's Premiere Pro is set to gain useful editing functions powered by generative AI, which will let video editors do more with less work.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Generative AI in Premiere Pro powered by Adobe Firefly Adobe Video" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6de4akFiNYM" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
With a Generative Extend feature, Premiere Pro will be able to add frames to make video clips longer, allowing for properly timed edits and smooth transitions by extending a scene.<br/>
<br/>
Objects in videos will also be able to be added or removed through smart selection and tracking tools. Adobe says that video editors can do things like remove an unwanted item, change an actor's wardrobe, or add set dressings like paintings on the wall or plants on a desk.<br/>
<br/>
Perhaps the most interesting new feature is an option to create new video footage directly within Premiere Pro using a text to video feature. Users will be able to type text into a prompt or upload images to create video, and the resulting clips can be used for B-roll, creating storyboards, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Adobe plans to introduce these generative AI tools later in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has its own professional video editing software, Final Cut Pro. Final Cut Pro is a Premiere Pro competitor, and as of now, it is lacking in the AI department. Apple has not announced any AI features for Final Cut Pro, but with AI capabilities rumored to be coming to multiple apps in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>, we could perhaps see some new AI feature additions for Final Cut Pro.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/adobe/">Adobe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/adobe-premiere-pro-ai-tools/">Adobe Premiere Pro Gains AI Tools to Add and Remove Objects From Videos, Extend Clips and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-premiere-pro-gains-ai-tools-to-add-and-remove-objects-from-videos-extend-clips-and-more.2424261/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>X May Charge New Users a &#039;Small Fee&#039; to Post, Like and Reply</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/x-small-fee-new-users/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-may-charge-new-users-a-small-fee-to-post-like-and-reply.2424255/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:46:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/x-small-fee-new-users/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Social media platform X (formerly Twitter) will soon begin charging new users "a small fee" for posting content and liking, replying, and bookmarking tweets, according to Elon Musk.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
<a href="https://twitter.com/xDaily/status/1779927679493411209">X Daily News</a>, a feed that posts X updates, today noticed that text strings on the website have been updated to mention a small annual fee that new users will need to pay in order to access the social network.<br/>
<br/>
Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1779930065469383166">said in response</a> that the fee for new users is "the only way to curb the relentless onslaught of bots."<br/>
<br/>
The fee has previously been tested in New Zealand and the Philippines, and Musk says that it is applicable only to those who are new to Twitter. When a new user signs up, the user will need to pay the fee, or wait for three months to be able to engage on the network. The updated language on the Twitter site:<br/>
<blockquote>New accounts are required to pay a small annual fee before you're able to post, like, bookmark, and reply. This is to reduce spam and create a better experience for everyone. You can still follow accounts and browse X for free.</blockquote><br/>
The text does not mention being able to post for free after three months, but <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1779939517278957714">Musk confirmed</a> that "write actions" would be free after that time period.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear how the policy will stop spam accounts and bots, as spammers will be able to pay the fee or simply create multiple accounts and wait to be able to post. Regular users, meanwhile, could be discouraged from using X due to the extra step and the fact that other social networks are free.<br/>
<br/>
The fee appears to be around &#36;1, as it costs &#36;1.75 NZD in New Zealand. The pay-for-access policy has not yet been implemented outside of New Zealand and the Philippines.<br/>
<br/>
Musk said that fake accounts also use up "the available namespace" limiting the "good handles." X has freed up over a million usernames so far, and will "free up tens of millions in the coming weeks."<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/x-small-fee-new-users/">X May Charge New Users a &#039;Small Fee&#039; to Post, Like and Reply</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-may-charge-new-users-a-small-fee-to-post-like-and-reply.2424255/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: iVANKY&#039;s FusionDock Max 1 Delivers Extreme Versatility With Dual Thunderbolt Connectivity</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ivankys-fusiondock-max-1-delivers-extreme-versatility-with-dual-thunderbolt-connectivity.2424251/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:27:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1&#038;post_date=1713223670/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>iVANKY</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Dock accessory company <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=2178566&u=63177&m=132800&urllink=&afftrack=">iVANKY</a> recently launched its most powerful Thunderbolt dock yet, the <a href="https://shrsl.com/4hpkr">FusionDock Max 1</a>, which takes advantage of dual Thunderbolt chips and connections to offer the greatest amount of versatility I've seen in a Mac-focused dock. I've spent some time testing out the FusionDock Max 1 in my daily workflow, and I think I've found my new daily driver.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1-installed.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946576" /><br/>
What sets the FusionDock Max 1 apart from other Thunderbolt docks on the market is the inclusion of dual Thunderbolt 4 chips, which essentially doubles the capacity of the dock, allowing you to run all sorts of displays and other peripherals at maximum speed. We'll dig into what that means for connectivity in just a minute, but let's start with an overview of the design and setup. Note that the FusionDock Max 1 is only compatible with Apple silicon Macs, so it won't work with older Intel Macs, Windows PCs, or Chromebooks.<br/>
<br/>
The FusionDock Max 1 offers an eye-catching design in something of a midnight-colored aluminum housing. Rather than just featuring a simple brick shape, the FusionDock Max 1 has a unique "floating" design with a thin metal frame on the left side and bottom of the dock and the main body of the dock elevated on small legs. The design might help ensure some airflow around the dock, though I'm not sure just how much it actually assists in that regard. The dock can definitely get fairly warm during use, but I've never found it to get so hot that it's uncomfortable to leave a hand on it.<br/>
<br/>
Similar to the Satechi USB-C Dual Dock Stand that I <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/satechi-usb-c-dual-dock-stand/">recently reviewed</a>, the FusionDock Max 1 uses a dual-cable connection to your Mac, but this is Thunderbolt rather than the slower USB, so the greater bandwidth opens up a lot more possibilities for connectivity. The custom cable includes rather bulky housing on each end with a fixed arrangement of the two Thunderbolt connectors to match the port spacing on the dock and Apple's laptops. This makes it super easy to plug in and unplug the cable in one motion with very little fiddling required to get the connectors lined up properly.<br/>
<br/>
The dock measures in at around 6.7 inches (17 cm) wide, 3.7 inches (9.4 cm) deep, and a little under 2 inches (5 cm) high, and there's a separate 180-watt power brick. The brick does have a fairly bright green light on it that could be distracting in dark rooms, but most users should be able to tuck it away on the floor or elsewhere where it won't be bothersome.<br/>
<br/>
The dock itself has smooth surfaces on all sides, and it can tend to slide around on surfaces if it's bumped or even just under any sort of tension from the attached cables. Fortunately, iVANKY includes some sticky rubber pads you can install for either horizontal or vertical orientation of your dock, and those go a long way toward making sure the dock stays where you want it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="553" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946578" /><br/>
The dock's 20 ports are clearly labeled, which is great simply because there are so many that it's tricky to keep track of all of them. Aside from the DC-in barrel plug connection for power, everything is driven through a pair of 40 Gbps Thunderbolt USB-C ports stacked vertically on the rear on panel of the dock. iVANKY provides a custom cable with a vertically arranged dual connector on one end to fit these ports and a horizontally arranged dual connector on the other end to fit the exact spacing of adjacent Thunderbolt ports on your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
Once you've hooked the dock up to power and your computer, your Mac will recognize the dock and you'll need to grant a couple privacy-related permissions, and then you'll be ready to go. The dock can deliver up to 96 watts of power to a connected computer, so you won't need a separate power connection for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the DC-in and upstream Thunderbolt ports, the rear of the dock features two additional 40 Gbps USB-C ports that can drive up to 6K displays at 60Hz, and they can each provide up to 15 watts of power. For other types of displays, there are two HDMI ports supporting up to 4K displays at 60Hz, and while the ports officially support HDMI 2.1, iVANKY is only advertising them as supporting HDMI 2.0 due to Apple's limitations on docking stations connecting over USB-C/Thunderbolt.  There are also three 10 Gbps USB-A ports delivering up to 7.5 watts of power each, a 2.5 Gb Ethernet port, a 3.5 mm audio out port, and a Toslink optical audio out port. A Kensington lock slot is also included to help physically secure the dock if desired.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1-front.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946579" /><br/>
On the front of the dock, you'll find another pair of 40 Gbps Thunderbolt USB-C ports capable of driving up to 6K displays at 60Hz, a pair of 10 Gbps USB-C ports (one with 20-watt Power Delivery capabilities and one offering 7.5 watts), another pair of 10 Gbps USB-A ports with 7.5 watts of power, plus a 3.5 mm combo headphone/mic audio port and SD and TF/microSD slots supporting the UHS-II standard. There is a white LED on the front to indicate whether the dock has power, but it's dim enough that it's not bothersome in a dark room.<br/>
<br/>
With this array of ports, the FusionDock Max 1 can support up to four external displays, but it depends on which Mac you have, as that's where the graphics horsepower is ultimately coming from. If you've got a Mac with the base <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip such as a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, or entry-level MacBook Pro, you can only drive a single external display at up to 6K resolution. M3-based machines like the latest &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and entry-level MacBook Pro models should be able to drive a pair of displays as long as your Mac is in clamshell mode with the display off.<br/>
<br/>
If you've got a Mac with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-pro/">M1 Pro</a>, &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro, or M3 Pro chip such as a higher-end &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; or a mid-level MacBook Pro, you'll be able to drive dual displays at up to 6K via the dock in additional to an internal display for the MacBook Pro, and if you've got a Max or Ultra chip from any of those families, you can drive a total of four external displays at up to 6K resolution.<br/>
<br/>
It's important to keep in mind that only the USB-C ports support 6K resolution, but there are four downstream ones available for display connections, two on the front and two on the back. The HDMI ports on the back can only support a maximum of 4K resolution.<br/>
<br/>
I don't have any machines in my possession equipped with Max-level chips, so I wasn't able to push the FusionDock Max 1 to its limit when it comes to displays, but it had no trouble driving a pair of 5K displays from my 16-inch MacBook Pro with an &zwnj;M1 Pro&zwnj; chip. I tried several other combinations of displays over Thunderbolt/USB and HDMI, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-max-touch-display/">Alogic's 32-inch 4K display with touchscreen support</a>, and everything worked without a hitch.<br/>
<br/>
Other peripherals also worked well with the dock, from my USB-A Stream Deck to a fast external SSD that was able to achieve speeds of up to 2,800 MB/s read and 1,950 MB/s write when connected to one of the 40 Gbps USB-C ports. Connecting that drive directly to my MacBook Pro yields read speeds of around 3,000 MB/s and write speeds of around 3,100 MB/s, so there's only a small penalty to read speeds for going through the dock, while write speeds take a bit bigger hit but remain speedy. Read and write speeds will ultimately depend on what else is connected to the dock and thus what that SSD is sharing its connection with.<br/>
<br/>
SD card speeds came in at around 90 MB/s read and 90–160 MB/s write depending on file size for the reasonably fast card I had available for testing, which is below both the theoretical specs of the card and the up to ~200 MB/s speeds I see in some testing when inserting it directly into my MacBook Pro, but still satisfactory in my opinion.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wrap-up</h2><br/>
I've been a loyal CalDigit TS3 Plus user for many years, but the iVANKY FusionDock Max 1 is likely to take its place in my permanent desk setup. With a single-cable connection (yes, it has dual connectors, but just one thing to plug and unplug), it's the most convenient way to quickly and easily convert my MacBook Pro from a large desk setup to a convenient on-the-go machine.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1-parts.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="706" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946577" /><br/>
With the FusionDock Max 1's vast array of ports, everything from my dual 5K displays to external drives, a Stream Deck, and more can all be connected and disconnected with almost no effort, and there's essentially no compromise in performance or speed.<br/>
<br/>
All of this convenience and technology packed into the FusionDock Max 1 doesn't come cheap, however, as it carries a normal price of &#36;549.99, so this dock definitely won't be everyone, but for power users this may be well worth the price tag. Fortunately, iVANKY is <a href="https://shrsl.com/4hpkr">currently offering &#36;150 off</a> when you use our exclusive promo code MACRUMOURS on iVANKY's site, bringing the price to &#36;399.99.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: iVANKY provided MacRumors with the FusionDock Max 1 for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with iVANKY and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ivanky/">iVANKY</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/ivanky-fusiondock-max-1/">Review: iVANKY&#039;s FusionDock Max 1 Delivers Extreme Versatility With Dual Thunderbolt Connectivity</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ivankys-fusiondock-max-1-delivers-extreme-versatility-with-dual-thunderbolt-connectivity.2424251/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 30 Rumored Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-30-rumored-upgrades-compared.2419268/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:42:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro&#038;post_date=1713206520/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After over a year of rumors, there are now 30 changes and improvements expected to be offered by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models later this year. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fVetwQ82vRA" title="iPhone 16 Pro Max: Should You Upgrade?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their direct forerunners are listed below, using information from reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">previously covered</a>. We will update this article as more rumors emerge in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="displays">Displays</h3><br/>
Both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature larger displays than their predecessors, pushing the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max to be the biggest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> ever offered. There are also reportedly improvements to the underlying OLED technology in store.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6.1- or 6.7-inch display</td><br/>
 <td>6.3- or 6.9-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thinner borders around the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_thermals_and_connectivity">Chip, Thermals, and Connectivity</h3><br/>
Under the hood, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to bring notable improvements in processing power, thermal management, and connectivity. From a more powerful "A18 Pro" chip to advanced thermal designs and enhanced connectivity options including the latest Wi-Fi standards, these changes promise to further update the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s basic specifications.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A17 Pro chip (TSMC's "N3B" <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 Pro chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Thermal design with copper heatsink and black foil battery casing</td><br/>
 <td>New thermal design with graphene heatsink and metal battery casing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X70 5G modem</td><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X75 5G modem</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 7 connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="cameras">Cameras</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are slated to receive a range of substantial camera enhancements, such as a larger main camera sensor, a 48-megapixel sensor on the ultra wide camera, and a dedicated hardware button for photography and videography on the side of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>"Capture Button" to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1/1.28-inch main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max</strong>: 1/1.14-inch main camera sensor (12% larger)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Sony IMX-803 main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: Sony IMX-903 main camera sensor with stacked design for better performance, a 14-bit Analog-to-Digital Converter (ADC) for high-quality image data conversion, and Digital Gain Control (DCG) for better dynamic range and noise control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7P main camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>8P main camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: Telephoto camera with second-generation sensor-shift optical image stabilization<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: Telephoto camera with larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, optical image stabilization, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module</td><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, optical image stabilization, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 77mm maximum focal length<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 120mm maximum focal length</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 120mm maximum focal length<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: "Super" telephoto camera with focal length above 300mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 3x optical zoom<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 0.5x, 1x, 2x, 3x, and 5x optical zoom (5x on Pro Max only)</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 5x optical zoom </td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>5P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel ultra wide camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel ultra wide camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>6P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting bigger, denser batteries and faster charging capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 3,274 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 4,422 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 3,355 mAh mAh battery (+2.5%)<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 4,676 mAh battery (+5%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 27W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h3><br/>
While many of Apple's devices are rumored to receive a series of new AI-based features via software updates later this year, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to take these further with exclusive capabilities and an upgraded microphone.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Support for new AI features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></td><br/>
 <td>Support for new AI features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, plus a suite of device-exclusive AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance, designed to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 2TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Black Titanium, White Titanium, Blue Titanium, and Natural Titanium color options</td><br/>
 <td>Black Titanium/Space Black, White Titanium, Desert Titanium, Titanium Gray, and potentially Rose Gold color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Brushed titanium frame</td><br/>
 <td>Glossy titanium frame</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="dimensions">Dimensions</h3><br/>
To accommodate the devices' larger displays, both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to grow in height and width, but no changes to the depth are anticipated.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 146.6mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 159.9mm height</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 149.6mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 163.0mm height</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 70.60mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 76.70mm width</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 71.45mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 77.58mm width</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 187g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 221g weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 194g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 225g weight</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="release_date">Release Date</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max are expected to launch in the fall. Apple usually hosts an event every September to unveil new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, with launch following just over a week later. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; was a fairly significant upgrade over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro in 2023, introducing a new design with a titanium frame, slimmer bezels, the Action button, a USB-C port, and more. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s upgrades will likely not be as substantial as those offered by its predecessor. As a result, most &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; users will have little reason to upgrade, but some who would appreciate a larger display, better cameras, and a dedicated button for photography and videography features may find it worthwhile.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 30 Rumored Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-30-rumored-upgrades-compared.2419268/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Save on Anker&#039;s Best Portable Batteries and USB-C Accessories, Plus Jackery&#039;s Power Stations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/anker-portable-batteries-jackery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/save-on-ankers-best-portable-batteries-and-usb-c-accessories-plus-jackerys-power-stations.2424233/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:03:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/anker-portable-batteries-jackery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a few deals offered by <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056">Anker</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Jackery</a>, including a wide array of wall chargers and other USB-C accessories. All of the products in this sale can be found on Amazon, and some will require you to clip an on-page coupon then head to the checkout screen before you see the final sale price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/new-anker-jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946517" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Highlights of Jackery's deals include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a>, available for just &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00. This is a miniature-sized portable power station that can fit in the palm of your hand and weighs just 2.13 lbs, while featuring a 31,000 mAh capacity and 128W output.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Switching to the Anker deals, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056">20,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> for &#36;104.99 with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;129.99. If you need a bigger battery, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> for &#36;109.99 with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99. Additionally, below you'll find more Anker accessories including speakers and USB-C products.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;25 OFF</div>20,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for &#36;104.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;37 OFF</div>Anker 3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube for &#36;112.46</div></a></div><h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2D47DQD1FRWW3%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2D47DQD1FRWW3_1710770158851">Solar Generator 300 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;449.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IF0PS8UT4GJ7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IF0PS8UT4GJ7_1710770002372">Expansion Battery Pack for 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;509.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S52LG1288F1D%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S52LG1288F1D_1710770092703">Explorer 2000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU_1710770037246">Expansion Battery Pack for 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;63.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CQ53RVTW%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.25RMP5XMPEBDM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.25RMP5XMPEBDM_1713191835036">Soundcore Boom 2 Outdoor Speaker</a> - &#36;109.99 with code INFBOOM2, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725913103">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;34.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;159.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;112.46 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1770-Powerhouse%2Fdp%2FB099Z2RDS5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F1200 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;749.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,098.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,399.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;11.19 for Prime members, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;53.95, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;44.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;75.00, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/anker-portable-batteries-jackery/">Save on Anker&#039;s Best Portable Batteries and USB-C Accessories, Plus Jackery&#039;s Power Stations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/save-on-ankers-best-portable-batteries-and-usb-c-accessories-plus-jackerys-power-stations.2424233/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sports App Updated for NBA and NHL Playoffs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-sports-app-updated-for-nba-and-nhl-playoffs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-updated-for-nba-and-nhl-playoffs.2424229/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:36:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-sports-app-updated-for-nba-and-nhl-playoffs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-announced/">recently-launched Sports app</a> for the iPhone was updated today ahead of the NBA and NHL playoffs, which both begin this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Sports-App-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1961" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937385" /><br/>
Apple says fans will be able to "follow every matchup with added details on each series and more," but we have not noticed any immediate changes in the app after updating to the new version. The first NBA and NHL playoff series begin on Saturday, April 20, so the extra details will presumably become visible then. Some info like playoff matchups and conference standings was already available in the previous version of the app.<br/>
<br/>
Released in February, the Apple Sports app shows scores, schedules, stats, and more for a variety of leagues, such as the NBA, NHL, MLB, MLS, and Premier League. The app also displays real-time play-by-play information for ongoing games.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports is available for free <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-sports/id6446788829">on the App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-sports-app-updated-for-nba-and-nhl-playoffs/">Apple Sports App Updated for NBA and NHL Playoffs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-updated-for-nba-and-nhl-playoffs.2424229/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Regains Top Spot as Apple&#039;s iPhone Shipments Fall in Q1 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-iphone-shipments-fall-globally-1q2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-regains-top-spot-as-apples-iphone-shipments-fall-in-q1-2024.2424224/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 05:05:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-iphone-shipments-fall-globally-1q2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>IDC</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> shipments decreased by nearly 10% globally in the first quarter of 2024, hit by rapid growth in shipments by rival Chinese vendors, based on data provided by the International Data Corporation (IDC). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-15-china.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943595" /><br/>
According to the <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prUS52032524">IDC report</a>, Apple's shipments fell 9.6% to 50.1 million units in the first quarter, down from 55.4 million units in the same quarter the previous year. Apple experienced the most significant annual decline among the top five smartphone brands covered in the report.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung reclaimed its position as the market leader, which it had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-top-spot-global-smartphone-shipments/">lost to Apple the previous year</a>, by capturing a 20.8% market share with shipments of about 60.1 million units, roughly the same as last year. In 2023, its market share was 22.5% during the same period.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/IDC-global-phone-shipments-1q2024.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946467" /><br/>
In contrast, after having last year overtaken Samsung to become the top smartphone manufacturer for the first time, Apple experienced a decline in market share from 20.7% to 17.3%.<br/>
<blockquote>"While IDC expects these two companies to maintain their hold on the high end of the market, the resurgence of Huawei in China, as well as notable gains from Xiaomi, Transsion, OPPO/OnePlus, and vivo will likely have both OEMs looking for areas to expand and diversify," said Ryan Reith, group vice president at IDC Worldwide Mobility and Consumer Device Trackers.</blockquote>Apple has struggled to sustain interest in its flagship smartphone lineup in China since the company released its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> series in September, which came just weeks after Huawei debuted its highly popular Mate 60 series. Interest in iPhones has also been impacted by a Beijing-backed ban from the offices of a huge number of state-owned enterprises in power generation, seaport construction, mining, manufacturing, education, and investment markets.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/IDC-global-smartphone-shipments-1q20242.jpg" alt="" width="1452" height="654" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946466" /><br/>
Apple's drop in shipments came during a time when global first-quarter smartphone shipments actually rose 7.8% year-on-year to 289.4 million units. It was the third consecutive quarter of shipment growth across the worldwide market, according to IDC.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/idc/">IDC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-iphone-shipments-fall-globally-1q2024/">Samsung Regains Top Spot as Apple&#039;s iPhone Shipments Fall in Q1 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-regains-top-spot-as-apples-iphone-shipments-fall-in-q1-2024.2424224/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Camera May Be Less Prone to Lens Flare and Ghosting</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/iphone-16-pro-camera-reduced-lens-flare/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-camera-may-be-less-prone-to-lens-flare-and-ghosting.2424218/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 03:43:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/iphone-16-pro-camera-reduced-lens-flare/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Naver</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is testing a new anti-reflective optical coating technology for future iPhone cameras that could improve the quality of photos by reducing artifacts like lens flare and ghosting, claims a rumor out of Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Perspective-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928694" /><br/>
According to the news aggregator account <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223414985445&navType=by">"yeux1122" on the Naver blog</a>, citing a company source within Apple's supply chain, Apple is looking at introducing new atomic layer deposition (ALD) equipment into the iPhone camera lens manufacturing process.<br/>
<br/>
ALD involves depositing materials one atomic layer at a time onto a substrate, allowing for extremely precise control over thickness and composition. Its use allows manufacturers to apply very thin layers of materials onto semiconductor devices, including camera components.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of camera lenses, ALD can be used to apply anti-reflective coatings, which can help to reduce photographic artifacts like streaks of light and halos that can occur in the final image when a bright light source such as the sun shines directly into the lens.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/02/iphone-16-pro-models-rumored-features/">iPhone 16 Pro Expected Later This Year With These 12 New Features</a></li></ul><br/>
ALD can also reduce ghosting, a type of image distortion where faint, secondary images appear in the photo, typically opposite a bright light source. This happens when light reflects back and forth between the surfaces of the lens elements and the camera sensor.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, ALD-applied materials can protect against environmental damage to the camera lens system without affecting the sensor's ability to capture light effectively. <br/>
<br/>
The Naver blog claims that the manufacturing process will be applied to a "Pro model" in Apple's "next-generation" iPhone lineup, which sounds like a reference to one or both premium models in the iPhone 16 series, although given the timing of the rumor, the possibility that this method is being tested for next year's iPhone 17 Pro models should not be discounted.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/">Seven Reasons to Wait for Next Year's iPhone 17</a></li></ul><br/>
Both upcoming iPhone 16 Pro models are expected to include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">tetraprism lens with up to 5x optical zoom</a> – a feature that is currently exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro Max in Apple's smartphone lineup. Apple usually launches its new-generation iPhones around mid-September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/naver/">Naver</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/iphone-16-pro-camera-reduced-lens-flare/">iPhone 16 Pro Camera May Be Less Prone to Lens Flare and Ghosting</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-camera-may-be-less-prone-to-lens-flare-and-ghosting.2424218/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Removes Game Boy Emulator iGBA From App Store Due to Spam and Copyright Violations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-removes-game-boy-emulator-igba-from-app-store-due-to-spam-and-copyright-violations.2424202/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 21:22:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Emulator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today said it removed Game Boy emulator iGBA from the App Store for violating the company's App Review Guidelines related to spam (<a href="https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/#spam">section 4.3</a>) and copyright (<a href="https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/#intellectual-property">section 5.2</a>), but it did not provide any specific details.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iGBA-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946239" /><br/>
iGBA was a copycat version of developer Riley Testut's <a href="https://github.com/CocoaBob/GBA4iOS">open-source GBA4iOS app</a>. The emulator rose to the top of the App Store charts <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/game-boy-emulator-in-app-store/">following its release this weekend</a>, but some people complained that the app was a blatant ripoff overlaid with ads.<br/>
<br/>
"So apparently Apple approved a knock-off of GBA4iOS," said Testut, in a <a href="https://www.threads.net/@rileytestut/post/C5u9xdDNCJ2">Threads post</a> on Saturday. "I did not give anyone permission to do this, yet it's now sitting at the top of the charts (despite being filled with ads + tracking)." He quipped that he was "so glad App Review exists to protect consumers from scams and rip-offs like this."<br/>
<br/>
An excerpt from section 5.2 of the App Review Guidelines, related to intellectual property:<blockquote>Make sure your app only includes content that you created or that you have a license to use. Your app may be removed if you've stepped over the line and used content without permission. Of course, this also means someone else's app may be removed if they've "borrowed" from your work.</blockquote>It is unclear if Apple removed iGBA because it felt the app ripped off GBA4iOS, or for other reasons. We have asked Apple for clarification about the app's removal, and we will update this article if we receive any additional information.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, iGBA allows iPhone users to load any Game Boy game ROMs downloaded from the web, but the app's removal makes it unclear if Apple will allow ROM-loading apps on the App Store. On its <a href="https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/55888/~/intellectual-property-%26-piracy-faq">customer support website</a> in the U.S., Nintendo says downloading pirated copies of its games is illegal. It is unclear if Nintendo contacted Apple.<br/>
<br/>
iGBA appeared in the App Store just over a week after Apple allowed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">"retro game console emulators"</a> on the App Store, but the guidelines are somewhat vague, so hopefully Apple will clarify exactly what is and is not permitted. iGBA can continue to be used by anyone who installed it on their iPhone before it was removed from the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
Testut has not said whether he will make his newer Nintendo game emulator <a href="https://faq.deltaemulator.com/">Delta</a> available on the App Store, should it be permitted, but he does plan to distribute it through his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/01/altstore-eu-iphone-patreon/">alternative app marketplace AltStore</a> on iPhones in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> Apple says that while iGBA's functionality was approved, it removed the app from the App Store after learning that it was a knockoff app that copied another developer's submission, which presumably refers to GBA4iOS.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emulator/">Emulator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/">Apple Removes Game Boy Emulator iGBA From App Store Due to Spam and Copyright Violations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-removes-game-boy-emulator-igba-from-app-store-due-to-spam-and-copyright-violations.2424202/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M4 Macs Are Expected to Launch in This Order Starting Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-macs-are-expected-to-launch-in-this-order-starting-later-this-year.2424174/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:40:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman recently reported that the first Macs with M4 series chips <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">will be released later this year</a>, with more models to follow next year. In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-14/humane-ai-pin-review-the-device-isn-t-going-to-kill-apple-s-iphone-luziqlew"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, Gurman shared a more specific roadmap for these Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-14/humane-ai-pin-review-the-device-isn-t-going-to-kill-apple-s-iphone-luziqlew">Here is the order</a> in which Gurman expects the Macs to launch:<blockquote>1. A low-end 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4, coming around the end of 2024.<br/>
2. A 24-inch iMac with the M4, also expected around the end of the year.<br/>
3. New 14-inch and 16-inch high-end MacBook Pros with M4 Pro/Max chips, due between the end of 2024 and early 2025.<br/>
4. A Mac mini in both M4 and M4 Pro configurations, coming between the end of 2024 and early 2025.<br/>
5. New 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Airs, slated for around spring 2025.<br/>
6. A Mac Studio with a high-end M4 chip, coming around the middle of 2025.<br/>
7. A Mac Pro with an M4 Ultra chip, due in the second half of 2025.</blockquote>Gurman reiterated that Apple has internally tested an M3 Ultra chip, which would be suitable for the Mac Studio and the Mac Pro, but he said it is "all but assured that at least some of Apple's high-end desktops" will skip the M3 chip series.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said that Apple will emphasize the artificial intelligence capabilities of the M4 chip series.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">M4 Macs Are Expected to Launch in This Order Starting Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-macs-are-expected-to-launch-in-this-order-starting-later-this-year.2424174/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s First AI Features in iOS 18 Reportedly Won&#039;t Use Cloud Servers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/apples-first-ios-18-ai-features-no-cloud/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-ai-features-in-ios-18-reportedly-wont-use-cloud-servers.2424167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:52:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/apples-first-ios-18-ai-features-no-cloud/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's first set of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new AI features planned for iOS 18</a> will not rely on cloud servers at all, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-14/humane-ai-pin-review-the-device-isn-t-going-to-kill-apple-s-iphone-luziqlew"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
"As the world awaits Apple's big AI unveiling on June 10, it looks like the initial wave of features will work entirely on device," said Gurman, in the Q&A section of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-14/humane-ai-pin-review-the-device-isn-t-going-to-kill-apple-s-iphone-luziqlew"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today. "That means there's no cloud processing component to the company's large language model, the software that powers the new capabilities."<br/>
<br/>
Apple will probably still offer some cloud-based AI features powered by Google's Gemini or another provider, according to Gurman. Apple has reportedly held discussions with companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">such as Google, OpenAI, and China's Baidu</a> about potential generative AI partnerships. iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/ios-18-reportedly-wont-have-apple-chatbot/">not expected to include Apple's own ChatGPT-like chatbot</a>, but it is unclear if Gemini or other chatbot will be directly integrated into iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
It is possible that Apple could offer some of its own cloud-based generative AI features in the future, as Apple supply chain analysts like Ming-Chi Kuo and Jeff Pu have said that the company is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-ai-server-spending-2024/">actively purchasing AI servers</a>.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 is rumored to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI features</a> for the iPhone's Spotlight search tool, Siri, Safari, Shortcuts, Apple Music, Messages, Health, Numbers, Pages, Keynote, and more. Gurman previously reported that generative AI will improve Siri's ability to answer more complex questions, and allow the Messages app to auto-complete sentences.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil iOS 18 and other software updates at its annual developers conference WWDC, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">runs from June 10 through June 14</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/apples-first-ios-18-ai-features-no-cloud/">Apple&#039;s First AI Features in iOS 18 Reportedly Won&#039;t Use Cloud Servers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-ai-features-in-ios-18-reportedly-wont-use-cloud-servers.2424167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Introduces Sitewide Savings on Galaxy Devices, Smart Monitors, TVs, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/samsung-sitewide-savings-galaxy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-introduces-sitewide-savings-on-galaxy-devices-smart-monitors-tvs-and-more.2424163/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:02:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/samsung-sitewide-savings-galaxy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung this weekend has the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor at a steep discount, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. In addition to this &#36;700 discount, you'll find deals on <a href="https://howl.me/clLNSBlHkaL">4K and 5K Samsung monitors</a>, including the Smart Monitor M8, as well as storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/samsung-viewfinity-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940238" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor is at a very solid second-best price this weekend, just &#36;50 higher compared to the previous record low price. This monitor has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also being discounted during this sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clP2G8L9fVC"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> in Warm White, down from &#36;699.99. This is a 4K smart monitor with a design that looks similar to the iMac line, and it's at another great second-best price during Samsung's monitor sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/smart-monitor-m8-samsung-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946191" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP2G8L9fVC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, Samsung has quite a few more monitor and TV deals, which we've rounded up below. Anyone shopping for a Samsung smartphone or tablet can also find a few offers on the Galaxy AI-powered Galaxy Z Flip5, Galaxy Z Fold5, and Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gYG78Q9">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gbHK6cQ">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNROoH7so">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2e77z0lE">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs/Audio</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN0R87SoM">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNX3ZnLNR">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNXcrr7pC">The Frame</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000 on select models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNYXDQ23m">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNWfhuoAS">85-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;2,399.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Smartphones/Tablets</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN3lYPzGg">Galaxy S24+</a> - Save up to &#36;1,050 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN39d8ucx">Galaxy S24 Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;900 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl1Y0enK9OW">Galaxy Z Fold5</a> - Save up to &#36;1,100 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl1Y0wHuCr6">Galaxy Z Flip5</a> - Save up to &#36;1,050 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl1Y0OGHMzE">Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra</a> - Get up to &#36;800 instant trade-in credit</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/samsung-sitewide-savings-galaxy/">Samsung Introduces Sitewide Savings on Galaxy Devices, Smart Monitors, TVs, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-introduces-sitewide-savings-on-galaxy-devices-smart-monitors-tvs-and-more.2424163/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Game Boy Emulator for iPhone Now Available in App Store Following Rule Change [Removed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/game-boy-emulator-in-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-boy-emulator-for-iphone-now-available-in-app-store-following-rule-change-removed.2424159/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:06:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/game-boy-emulator-in-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Emulator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A week after Apple updated its App Review Guidelines to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">permit retro game console emulators</a>, a <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/igba-gba-gbc-retro-emulator/id6482993626">Game Boy emulator for the iPhone called iGBA</a> has <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iosgaming/comments/1c35zop/new_gba_and_gbc_emulator_on_app_store/">appeared in the App Store</a> worldwide. The emulator is already one of the top free apps on the App Store charts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iGBA-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946239" /><br/>
<br/>
It was not entirely clear if Apple would allow emulators to work with all and any games, but iGBA is able to load any Game Boy ROMs that users download from the web and open via the Files app on the iPhone. Accordingly, it seems like there are no game restrictions for emulators, unless Apple mistakenly approved iGBA on the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
iGBA works with Game Boy, Game Boy Color, and Game Boy Advance games. It is important to note that it can be illegal to possess certain ROMs from game developers, but <a href="https://hh.gbdev.io/">homebrew Game Boy games</a> are typically in the clear.<br/>
<br/>
iGBA <a href="https://www.threads.net/@rileytestut/post/C5u9xdDNCJ2">appears to be a copy</a> of Riley Testut's <a href="https://github.com/CocoaBob/GBA4iOS">open-source GBA4iOS emulator</a>, but with ads that can track users. GBA4iOS is the predecessor to Testut's current Nintendo game emulator <a href="https://faq.deltaemulator.com/">Delta</a>, which can be installed on the iPhone outside of the App Store, and will soon be available through his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/01/altstore-eu-iphone-patreon/">alternative app marketplace AltStore</a> on iPhones in the EU. It is not clear if Testut plans to make Delta available in the App Store following the rule change.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> As noted <a href="https://www.threads.net/@parkerortolani/post/C5wo4-CPcrU">by Parker Ortolani</a>, the iGBA emulator has been removed from the App Store. Apple told us it removed the app for violating the company's app review guidelines <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/">related to spam and copyright</a>, after learning that it was a knockoff app that copied another developer's submission (likely referring to GBA4iOS).<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emulator/">Emulator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/game-boy-emulator-in-app-store/">Game Boy Emulator for iPhone Now Available in App Store Following Rule Change [Removed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-boy-emulator-for-iphone-now-available-in-app-store-following-rule-change-removed.2424159/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Opens Up Sitewide Sale With Record Low Prices on M3 MacBook Air, iPad, and Much More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/best-buys-sale-macbook-air-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-opens-up-sitewide-sale-with-record-low-prices-on-m3-macbook-air-ipad-and-much-more.2424104/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 07:41:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/best-buys-sale-macbook-air-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy this weekend has a big <a href="https://howl.me/clG8QCkba7O">sale on Apple MacBooks and iPads</a>, including new all-time low prices on the M3 MacBook Air, alongside the best prices we've ever seen on MacBook Pro, iPad, and more. Some of these deals require a <a href="https://howl.me/clsfFR2NQAO">My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total membership</a>, which start at &#36;49.99/year. In addition to exclusive access to select discounts, you'll get free 2-day shipping, an extended 60-day return window, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-best-buy-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940254" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ipad-best-buy-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946064" /><br/>
Starting with the cheapest iPad in this sale, you can get the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clEadOydYiR"><strong>&#36;249.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. My Best Buy Plus/Total members can also get a low price on the 256GB Wi-Fi model this weekend at &#36;379.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEadOydYiR"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl1VMDzTmnP"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-ipad-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940260" /><br/>
For a more recent model, Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi 10th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, which is an all-time low price at &#36;100 off. You'll find every model of the 10th generation iPad on sale at a record low price during this sale. This includes all Wi-Fi and cellular tablets, in all colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKbvh8PEh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKduB2Qbr"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKdXDXcha"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad for &#36;649.00</div></a></div><h2>13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/macbook-air-bb-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946063" /><br/>
Every model of the 2022 13-inch MacBook Air is <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI">available for &#36;150 off</a> this weekend at Best Buy. The 256GB model is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> and the 512GB model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a>. These deals beat the previous prices by about &#36;50, and you don't need to be a My Best Buy Plus or Total member to get them.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><h2>15-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-macbook-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940257" /><br/>
The 256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air is priced at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. You can also get the 512GB M2 model on sale at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Across the board these are the best prices we've ever seen on the M2 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><h2>15-inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/new-macbook-air-blue-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946062" /><br/>
For the latest M3 model of the 15-inch MacBook Air, you can get the 8GB RAM/256GB SSD 15-inch M3 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cl0EMZ1NuSk"><strong>&#36;1,149.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 8GB RAM/512GB SSD model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/cl0EMwzBSED"><strong>&#36;1,349.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00, and the 16GB RAM/512GB SSD model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/cl0EL5xNArX"><strong>&#36;1,549.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,699.00. These deals require a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You will need a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership to see this low price.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl0EMZ1NuSk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,149.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl0EMwzBSED"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl0EL5xNArX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,549.00</div></a></div><h2>M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/m3-macbook-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940256" /><br/>
These deals are focused on the 14-inch models of the MacBook Pro, and only a select few are being discounted for My Best Buy Plus/Total members. If you don't have a membership, you can still get these computers for solid second-best prices this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: My Best Buy Plus/Total membership required to see final deal price.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl1VVU58H79"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 14-inch MacBook Pro (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl1VWtbRCui"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 14-inch MacBook Pro (8GB/1TB) for &#36;1,599.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl1VW92Y095"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 14-inch MacBook Pro (16GB/1TB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/best-buys-sale-macbook-air-ipad/">Best Buy Opens Up Sitewide Sale With Record Low Prices on M3 MacBook Air, iPad, and Much More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-opens-up-sitewide-sale-with-record-low-prices-on-m3-macbook-air-ipad-and-much-more.2424104/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: M4 Mac Roadmap Leaked, New iPads in Second Week of May, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/top-stories-m4-mac-roadmap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-m4-mac-roadmap-leaked-new-ipads-in-second-week-of-may-and-more.2424097/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/top-stories-m4-mac-roadmap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's hardware roadmap was in the news this week, with things hopefully firming up for a launch of updated iPad Pro and iPad Air models next month while we look ahead to the other iPad models and a full lineup of M4-based Macs arriving starting later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/top-stories-13apr2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946171" /><br/>
We also heard some fresh rumors about iOS 18, due to be unveiled at WWDC in a couple of months, while we took a look at how things are going with the iPhone 15 Pro now that it's halfway through its flagship lifecycle, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Macs to Get AI-Focused M4 Chips Starting in Late 2024</h2><br/>
Apple plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">release its first Macs with the M4 series of chips in late 2024</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-AI-Optimized-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945901" /><br/>
The report says that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> lines will be the first to be updated with the M4 series of chips later this year, while other models like the MacBook Air, Mac mini, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro are expected to be updated with M4 series chips throughout 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the chips are "designed to highlight artificial intelligence" capabilities on the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iPads Likely to Launch During Second Week of May</h2><br/>
In the latest edition of his newsletter, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said new iPad Pro and iPad Air models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/gurman-new-ipads-first-week-of-may/">will likely launch during the second week of May</a>, following reported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/apple-suppliers-say-new-ipads-repeatedly-postponed/">manufacturing delays</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
He also said Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/when-to-expect-next-ipad-mini/">working on new iPad mini and entry-level iPad models</a>, but he does not expect those devices to launch until later this year.<br/>
<br/>
It has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ipad-launched-14-years-ago/">nearly 18 months since Apple last released new iPads</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Review: Six Months With the iPhone 15 Pro</h2><br/>
It's been a bit over six months since the iPhone 15 lineup came out in September, and <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera has been using an iPhone 15 Pro Max sans case since launch. Over on our YouTube channel, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/iphone-15-pro-six-month-review/">Dan did a long-term review</a> to demo how his phone has held up and his thoughts on the Action button, battery life, and camera features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iPhone-15-6-Months-Later-Thumb-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945764" /><br/>
If you're an ‌iPhone 15 Pro‌ owner, let us know how your battery life is holding up, whether you're regularly using the Action button, and anything else you've found interesting about your experience with Apple's latest high-end flagship phone!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Here Are All the Rumored iPhone 16 Colors</h2><br/>
We recently recapped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/all-the-rumored-iphone-16-colors/">all rumored color options for the iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max</a>, so be sure to check out the list to learn about the new options expected.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935159" /><br/>
At least two new color options are rumored for the lower-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus</a> models, including Purple and White, while the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">Pro models</a> could gain new Space Black and Rose Gold titanium finishes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 May Feature All-New 'Safari Browsing Assistant'</h2><br/>
One of the new generative AI features rumored to be coming to the iPhone with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> could be a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-18-safari-browsing-assistant-rumor/">browsing assistant in Safari</a>, according to backend code discovered on Apple's servers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
While no specific details about the browsing assistant are known, the feature could allow Safari to better compete with other AI-infused web browsers available on the iPhone, such as Microsoft Edge and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/arc-search-iphone-app-ai/">Arc Search</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The MacRumors Show: Apple Shortcuts and iOS 18 ft. Matthew Cassinelli</h2><br/>
Matthew Cassinelli, one of the minds behind Workflow, joined Dan and Hartley on this week's episode of <em>The MacRumors Show</em> to talk Apple Shortcuts and potential improvements and AI features coming to the app in iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/The-MacRumors-Show-Apple-Shortchuts-and-iOS-18.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946091" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/the-macrumors-show-apples-next-big-thing-robots/">Last week's episode</a> included discussion of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/apple-reportedly-investigating-robotics/">potential foray into robots</a>, along with discoveries made in the iOS 17.5 beta, rumors about a new Apple Pencil, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@TheMacRumorsShow"><em>The MacRumors Show</em> channel on YouTube</a>, and listen to the podcast in Apple Podcasts or your preferred podcast app.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/apr-11-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/top-stories-m4-mac-roadmap/">Top Stories: M4 Mac Roadmap Leaked, New iPads in Second Week of May, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-m4-mac-roadmap-leaked-new-ipads-in-second-week-of-may-and-more.2424097/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares 5 Helpful AirPods Tips and Tricks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/apple-shares-airpods-tips-and-tricks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-5-helpful-airpods-tips-and-tricks.2424062/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:26:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/apple-shares-airpods-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A recent <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bDI-WYr5aOM">video</a> uploaded to the Apple Support channel on YouTube offers five helpful tips and tricks for AirPods that you may not have known about.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bDI-WYr5aOM?si=qr80NVT4P65jJhvZ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
AirPods features highlighted in the video include <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102526">Audio Sharing</a>, <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102479">Live Listen</a>, <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/airpods/deva1bf8faad/1.0/web/1.0">Background Sounds</a>, <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102536">Announce Notifications with Siri</a>, and the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/airpods/deva392f031a/web">ability to rename AirPods</a> in the Settings app on the iPhone. Most of these functions are available on all AirPods models, but Announce Notifications with Siri does not work with first-generation AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
If you own AirPods Pro, also check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/new-airpods-pro-features-ios-17-how-to-use/">guide covering the latest features</a> added with iOS 17, such as Conversation Awareness and Personalized Volume.<br/>
<br/>
Waiting for new AirPods? Find out <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/">when to expect the AirPods 4 and new AirPods Max</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/apple-shares-airpods-tips-and-tricks/">Apple Shares 5 Helpful AirPods Tips and Tricks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-5-helpful-airpods-tips-and-tricks.2424062/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple Shortcuts and iOS 18 ft. Matthew Cassinelli</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-shortcuts-and-ios-18-ft-matthew-cassinelli.2424055/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 08:30:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Matthew Cassinelli, one of the minds behind Workflow, joins us on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/apples-ai-powered-shortcuts-for-ios-18/id1602394741?i=1000652267451">The MacRumors Show</a> to talk Apple Shortcuts and potential improvements and AI features coming to the app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/edlNruuPMCA?si=qVtbgoKh9mmxWzEH" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div> <br/>
Workflow was a unique iOS app that allowed users to create macros for executing specific sequential tasks on their device. In 2017, Apple acquired Workflow and, the following year, it was rebranded as "Shortcuts." Shortcuts have since become a key part of Apple's ecosystem and can be used for a huge range of powerful, automated actions. Matthew was present at Workflow throughout its transition to Apple and now offers his own library of complex Shortcuts, which you can <a href="https://matthewcassinelli.com">access over on his website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">report from <em>The Information</em></a> claimed that &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will introduce some major AI features to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and the Shortcuts app. Apple apparently wants ‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌ to be able to help users automate complex, multi-step tasks with voice-based commands and have much deeper integration with Shortcuts, such as by potentially helping users build them.<br/>
<br/>
We break down Apple Shortcuts for beginners and look at some of the many use-cases for the app, as well as consider where it could go next with AI. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/the-macrumors-show-wwdc-2024-announced/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple's recently rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/the-macrumors-show-apples-next-big-thing-robots/">"personal robotics" projects</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/everything-new-in-ios-17-5-beta-1/">iOS 17.5</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> rumors, and more. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">The MacRumors Show: Apple Shortcuts and iOS 18 ft. Matthew Cassinelli</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-shortcuts-and-ios-18-ft-matthew-cassinelli.2424055/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get the AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;189, Plus Low Prices on Apple Watch and iMac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-12-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-the-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-189-plus-low-prices-on-apple-watch-and-imac.2424052/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:49:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-12-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals can all be found on Amazon, which is hosting steep discounts on the AirPods Pro 2, Apple Watch Series 9, and the M3 iMac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0005.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847995" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/airpods-pro-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946011" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;60 off AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/09/get-the-airpods-pro-2-amazon/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon returned this week with a low price on the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C, available for &#36;189.00, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/red-apple-watch-9.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946009" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;104 off Apple Watch Series 9</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/apple-watch-series-9-295/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;104 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;295.20</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving on to the Apple Watch, Amazon introduced a new all-time low price on the 41mm GPS Series 9 model this week. You can get the (PRODUCT)RED model for &#36;295.20 in the M/L Sport Band size.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMac</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/imac-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946010" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;149 off M3 iMac</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JGD9X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/amazon-m3-imacs-low-prices/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JGD9X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-core/256GB) for &#36;1,149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/256GB) for &#36;1,349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KBG3M%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/512GB) for &#36;1,549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Capping off the week, Amazon introduced new record low prices across the M3 iMac lineup, providing &#36;149 off nearly every model. You'll need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see all of these deals at the checkout screen.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-12-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get the AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;189, Plus Low Prices on Apple Watch and iMac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-the-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-189-plus-low-prices-on-apple-watch-and-imac.2424052/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pixelmator Pro Adds Support for Editing Text in PDFs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/pixelmator-pro-3-5-8-pdf-text-editing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pixelmator-pro-adds-support-for-editing-text-in-pdfs.2424050/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:30:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/pixelmator-pro-3-5-8-pdf-text-editing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Pixelmator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.pixelmator.com/pro/">Pixelmator Pro 3.5.8</a> has gone live on the Mac App Store, and the latest update to the popular image editing app brings the ability to edit text in PDFs, along with a handful of other notable additions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/pixelmator-pro-pdf-text-editing.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946030" /><br/>
Pixelmator recently added support to the app for vector PDFs, which allows users to import image, shape, and text elements in the portable document format as separate layers. <br/>
<br/>
With the newest version, this support has been expanded so that users can edit imported text as regular text layers. In practice, this means existing text in PDFs can be more easily replaced, formatted, and styled using Pixelmator Pro tools. As the developers explain:<br/>
<blockquote>Typically, text in PDF documents is not directly editable. Instead, it's stored as vector shapes to keep documents looking consistent across various platforms and apps. To make text editable again, Pixelmator Pro extracts various embedded data from the original PDF, allowing it to recover the original text, fonts, and formatting. Even if some of these elements are missing, for instance, if the original font is not installed on your Mac, you can still import the text, select a different font, and continue with your edits.</blockquote>In addition, the new text editing abilities mean users can seamlessly export Apple Keynote and Pages projects and continue editing them in Pixelmator Pro. All text remains fully editable in its original fonts, including the SF Pro font that is used throughout the Apple ecosystem.  <br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere in this update, the Style tool has been improved to simplify the creation of custom outlines around text layers. Users now have the option to add strokes inside, within, or outside of the text, choose from various stroke ends and corners, and also add dashed strokes.<br/>
<br/>
Pixelmator Pro 3.5.8 also includes 12 new templates for web, social media, and more. All of the templates include a set of alternative color palettes for adjusting the theme to custom requirements. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.pixelmator.com/pro/">Pixelmator Pro</a> is available exclusively <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/pixelmator-pro/id1289583905">from the Mac App Store</a> as a free update for existing users and &#36;49.99 for new customers. A free seven-day trial of the software with no restrictions is also available on the <a href="https://www.pixelmator.com/pro/free-trial/">Pixelmator website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/pixelmator/">Pixelmator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/pixelmator-pro-3-5-8-pdf-text-editing/">Pixelmator Pro Adds Support for Editing Text in PDFs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pixelmator-pro-adds-support-for-editing-text-in-pdfs.2424050/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Browser Companies Criticize Apple&#039;s EU Choice Screen in iOS 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/apple-eu-default-browser-options-criticized/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/browser-companies-criticize-apples-eu-choice-screen-in-ios-17-4.2424048/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:26:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/apple-eu-default-browser-options-criticized/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Several third-party browser companies have experienced a spike in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> installs since Apple made major changes to iOS in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act in the European Union, but many are not happy with Apple's implementation of its default browser choice screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/alternative-browser-list-eu.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941009" /><br/>
In iOS 17.4, released last month, Apple no longer limits EU users to the handful of browser options that iOS currently offers as alternatives in other parts of the world. Instead, users in the EU who open Safari for the first time are presented with a choice screen that allows them to opt for a new default browser from a list of popular alternatives in their country.<br/>
<br/>
The change has led to a sharp increase in third-party browser usage, based on several reports. On Wednesday, <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/eus-new-tech-laws-are-working-small-browsers-gain-market-share-2024-04-10/">Reuters</a></em> reported that users of privacy-first browser Aloha had jumped 250% in March. The jump in users largely came in France, Belgium (3x growth), Germany, The Netherlands, Spain and Sweden (2.5x growth), and Denmark, Italy and Poland (2x growth).<br/>
<br/>
Aloha browser markets itself as a privacy focused alternative to browsers that earns its money through paid subscriptions rather than selling ads by tracking users. The Cyprus-based company says it has 10 million monthly average users.<br/>
<br/>
"Before, EU was our number four market, right now it's number two," Aloha CEO Andrew Frost Moroz said in an interview with <em>Reuters</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Norway's Vivaldi browser, Germany's Ecosia and U.S.-based Brave have all seen user numbers rise following the new regulation. U.S.-based DuckDuckGo, which has about 100 million users, and its more popular rival, Norway-based Opera, have also reported substantial increases.<br/>
<br/>
To be eligible for consideration in the alternative browsers list, companies must have the Default Browser Entitlement that is available to developers. Apple also requires that the app has been downloaded by at least 5,000 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users‌ across all 27 EU countries in the prior calendar year. Apple selects up to 11 of these for the browser choice screen in addition to Safari, updating the list once per calendar year. <br/>
<br/>
Google has also updated its Pixel software to show alternative browser choices, and says that new Android devices made by other companies will also display the choice screen in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
Despite users increasingly choosing alternative options, browser companies have criticized Apple and Google for the slow rollout of the change, and believe it is hampering the migration away from Safari and Chrome. Mozilla, which owns Firefox, estimates that only around a fifth of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users in the EU have received the iOS update, and claims that the rollout is much slower than Apple's previous software updates.<br/>
<br/>
Some alternative browser makers are also concerned that the design of choice screens is sub-optimal at best. For example, Vivaldi CEO Jon Stephenson von Tetzchner notes that Apple's choice screen only appears when &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users open Safari, while the list of browsers provides no additional information. <br/>
<br/>
"The process is just so convoluted that it's easiest for (users) to select Safari or potentially some other known name," he told <em>Reuters</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Vivaldi is also unhappy with the design. "The list of browsers does not show additional information and that does not help users to make a meaningful choice," a company spokesperson told <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/10/eu-dma-browser-choice-screen-early-impact/">TechCrunch</a></em>. "If the user has already selected a browser of their own choice, the choice screen can actively try to push them away from it, and may not even include it in the list that it presents to the user."<br/>
<br/>
Ecosia has also been critical, and says Apple's implementation involves an "overly complex installation process" and keeps Safari front and center on the user's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Home screen.<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission is currently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/eu-to-investigate-apple-dma-compliance/">investigating</a> Apple's choice screen design for suspected noncompliance. The probe is being conducted in consultation with browser companies, who are likely to encourage regulators to push for a stronger implementation to level the competitive playing field. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/apple-eu-default-browser-options-criticized/">Browser Companies Criticize Apple&#039;s EU Choice Screen in iOS 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/browser-companies-criticize-apples-eu-choice-screen-in-ios-17-4.2424048/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
