<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:04:06 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sales in China Dropped Significantly in Q1 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/iphone-sales-in-china-dropped-significantly/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-in-china-dropped-significantly-in-q1-2024.2424731/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:25:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/iphone-sales-in-china-dropped-significantly/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Counterpoint</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China declined significantly in the first quarter of 2024 as consumers turned to other premium smartphone brands, according to <a href="https://www.counterpointresearch.com/insights/china-smartphone-q1-2024/">Counterpoint research</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series-store.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913490" /><br/>
During the first quarter of the year, China's smartphone market experienced modest year-over-year growth of 1.5%, marking the second consecutive quarter of growth. This uptick in sales is largely attributed to strong sales performance from local manufacturers such as Huawei, which achieved a remarkable 69.7% growth compared to the same period last year. This growth was fueled by the launch of Huawei's Mate 60 series, a smartphone lineup that has significantly bolstered the company's dominance in the Chinese premium segment, typically characterized by devices priced over &#36;600.<br/>
<br/>
In contrast, Apple saw its smartphone sales in China plummet by 19.1% year-over-year in the same quarter. Analysts point to Huawei's resurgence as a direct challenge to Apple as the main reason for this, primarily in the premium segment where the two companies compete head-to-head. Counterpoint anticipates that upcoming &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models with new color options and AI features could help to rejuvenate Apple's sales in the Chinese market. Looking ahead, the smartphone market in China is projected to see low single-digit growth throughout 2024. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/counterpoint/">Counterpoint</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/iphone-sales-in-china-dropped-significantly/">iPhone Sales in China Dropped Significantly in Q1 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-in-china-dropped-significantly-in-q1-2024.2424731/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>FineWoven Accessories May Get One Last Outing Before Apple Pulls Plug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/finewoven-accessories-may-get-one-last-season/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/finewoven-accessories-may-get-one-last-outing-before-apple-pulls-plug.2424730/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:07:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/finewoven-accessories-may-get-one-last-season/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the weekend, Apple leaker and prototype collector Kosutami claimed that Apple has decided to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/">halt production</a> of FiveWoven accessories over durability concerns. In a further update, the leaker has now suggested we might yet see <a href="https://x.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1782646277525983293">one more round</a> of <a href="https://x.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1782629715335151821">FineWoven products</a> in a season of new colors before Apple finally says farewell to the material for good.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947658" /><br/>
Last September, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-finewoven/">stopped selling genuine leather accessories</a> in favor of a more environmentally friendly "FineWoven" material. The company describes FineWoven as "luxurious and durable microtwill," and sells FineWoven iPhone cases at &#36;59, MagSafe Wallets at &#36;59, AirTag holders at &#36;35, and Apple Watch bands at &#36;99. <br/>
<br/>
Many customers consider FineWoven products to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">subpar</a> compared to the leather Apple cases they replaced, and claim that the fabric is prone to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/">scratches</a>, stains, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/finewoven-iphone-cases-brown-like-rotten-banana/">discoloration</a>. If today's update is correct, Apple may have to brace itself for more unhappy FineWoven customers.<br/>
<br/>
Kosutami is known for revealing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/09/new-apple-watch-magnetic-band/">accurate information</a> about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/finewoven-cases-may-match-new-watch-band/">FineWoven accessories</a> in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/exclusive-first-look-finewoven-apple-watch-band/">past</a>, so their latest claim should not be discounted. FineWoven accessories in new color options were absent from Apple's spring refresh, so perhaps their swan song could come in September when Apple releases the iPhone 16 lineup. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/finewoven-accessories-may-get-one-last-season/">FineWoven Accessories May Get One Last Outing Before Apple Pulls Plug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/finewoven-accessories-may-get-one-last-outing-before-apple-pulls-plug.2424730/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta Expands VR Operating System to Third-Party Hardware Makers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/meta-expands-vr-operating-system/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-expands-vr-operating-system-to-third-party-hardware-makers.2424702/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:43:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/meta-expands-vr-operating-system/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Facebook parent company Meta <a href="https://www.meta.com/blog/quest/meta-horizon-os-open-hardware-ecosystem-asus-republic-gamers-lenovo-xbox/">today announced</a> the upcoming expansion of Meta Horizon OS, a virtual and augmented reality operating system that will be available to third-party hardware manufacturers that want to design their own headsets.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/meta-quest-3.jpg" alt="" width="1385" height="779" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914163" /><br/>
Right now, Meta sells the Quest line of headsets, but the company wants to provide the software for third-party VR and AR products in the future, much like Microsoft offers Windows for all manner of third-party PCs.<br/>
<br/>
Meta Horizon OS is the mixed reality operating system that Meta created for its own Quest headsets, and it has support for eye, face, hand, and body tracking along with passthrough, spatial anchors, scene understanding, and other features. There is a "social layer" that will allow the identities, avatars, and friends of users to move between virtual spaces on different devices.<br/>
<br/>
According to Meta, multiple companies are working on devices that will use Meta Horizon OS. ASUS ROG is developing a performance gaming headset and Lenovo is working on mixed reality devices for productivity, learning, and entertainment. Meta says that it is also creating a limited edition version of Meta Quest in partnership with Xbox.<br/>
<br/>
With the expansion of Meta Horizon OS to third-party hardware manufacturers, Meta is making it easier for any developer to ship VR software on the platform by removing barriers between the Horizon Store and App Lab.<br/>
<br/>
By creating an operating system that can be used by other hardware manufacturers, Meta is inserting itself into the growing AR/VR ecosystem and creating opportunities for it to outpace Apple in mixed reality development. Apple launched the Vision Pro headset earlier this year, but software is lacking given the high price and limited distribution of the device.<br/>
<br/>
According to a report from earlier today, interest in the Vision Pro is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/">already waning</a> at Apple's retail locations with fewer people requesting demos.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/meta-expands-vr-operating-system/">Meta Expands VR Operating System to Third-Party Hardware Makers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-expands-vr-operating-system-to-third-party-hardware-makers.2424702/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Nanoleaf&#039;s Skylight Adds Modular Smart Lighting to Your Ceiling</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-skylight/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-nanoleafs-skylight-adds-modular-smart-lighting-to-your-ceiling.2424700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:54:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-skylight&#038;post_date=1713833659/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/ceiling-lights/skylight/">Nanoleaf Skylight Smarter Kit</a> is Nanoleaf's first hardwired, permanent light, and it's also the first light that Nanoleaf designed specifically to be installed on ceilings.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/nanoleaf-skylight.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878921" /><br/>
As with Nanoleaf Light Panels, the Skylight is modular. A 3-panel starter kit is priced at &#36;250, and each add-on panel is &#36;70. Nanoleaf sells kits with more panels at a discount, so cost can go as low as &#36;62 per panel for a design that uses 12 panels.<br/>
<br/>
Ceiling lights come in a wide range of prices and &#36;250 is in the mid to high range, but there aren't many modular ceiling light options (as in hardwired with no visible cord), and none that I'm aware of that are both smart and offer multicolor and white lighting. Each square-shaped panel is made from a translucent white plastic that diffuses the light coming from the LEDs underneath.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-light-panels-components.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947489" /><br/>
The panels are just under 12 inches on each side, and they're about two inches thick. The plastic is a shinier material than the plastic used for the regular Nanoleaf Light Panels, and it just looks like white squares on the ceiling when the lights are not turned on. I don't mind the plastic because it blends well with a white ceiling when the lights are off. Square-shaped light panels have a modern vibe both on and off, and it isn't an aesthetic that's going to fit in with all decor styles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-light-panels-ff.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947488" /><br/>
Every panel is 1400 lumens, so the three panel kit is 4200 lumens. The amount of light needed to properly light a space is going to depend on the size of the area being lit and the desired brightness, but that should be enough light for a 15x15 room with 10 foot ceilings. I was impressed with the brightness of the Skylight panels, and three installed in my laundry room was more light than I'll ever need. I ultimately included two more panels for a total of five, but that was because I was replacing a fluorescent panel with popcorn texture underneath and I didn't want to have to repair the ceiling. I think my laundry room is now the brightest room in the house, and I use the lights dimmed down.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-skylight-bright.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947491" /><br/>
The Skylight can be installed by an electrician or as a DIY project with some basic electrical knowledge, and Nanoleaf does provide instructions and a video for completing the entire process. Creating a layout is the first step, and while the lights can be installed at angles and staggered, I did a straight line of five panels in a row. There's a ceiling plate that's screwed into the ceiling first, and the wires from the ceiling are connected to the main panel (with the breaker off of course). The panels are each two pieces, with a base that houses the LEDs and wires, and a cover.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-skylight-pastels.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947490" /><br/>
There's a single Main Controller panel that can control up to 99 additional dependent panels, and that's the one that goes up first. Nanoleaf included four screw holes on each panel that also serve as guides so you can mark on the ceiling where to drill, and drywall anchors and screws are included.<br/>
<br/>
Every panel has a terminal block that's covered by a panel that has to be unscrewed to get to the wires to connect one panel to another, and each panel is secured at all four corners, plus the wires are routed through holes at the sides. It's not difficult, exactly, but there are a lot of steps to go through, and it's frustrating working from below. I do think the guide holes helped a lot ensuring everything was lined up, and it ultimately turned out well.<br/>
<br/>
I think four drywall screws for every panel is a <em>lot</em>, especially because these panels aren't particularly heavy. In hindsight, I probably could have used two at a diagonal, and it's worth noting that there are going to be a lot of holes to repair in the ceiling if you install these panels and later want to remove them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-skylight-pinks.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947492" /><br/>
Once installed, the Skylight works like any other HomeKit-connected light. It's added to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> with a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; code, and setup is quick. Nanoleaf products only work with 2.4GHz networks, so you're going to need a setup that allows for a 2.4GHz connection. The Skylight is Wi-Fi only, but there it has Thread compatibility that can presumably be turned on if Nanoleaf decides to do so. It is not Matter-enabled.<br/>
<br/>
I don't own a single smart home product that does not occasionally have a connectivity issue, including Nanoleaf devices. When I got these panels, I debated installing the panels in my living room with vaulted ceilings (note: these can be installed on angled ceilings), but I was worried about access for troubleshooting because I'd need a tall, heavy ladder, so I tested the Skylight in one of my only rooms with lower ceilings.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-skylight-blues.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947493" /><br/>
I'm glad I did, because about a week after the Skylight was up, it lost connectivity. No amount of turning the power off or restarting my devices helped, and I had to get out a small ladder, pull off the main panel's cover, and long press the reset button to start over. I haven't had another disconnect, and it could have been caused by trying to use a motion sensor (I could NOT get it to work reliably and I haven't wanted to try again) or by turning the light off at the switch overnight, but it can happen.<br/>
<br/>
So far the Skylight doesn't seem to be less reliable than other Wi-Fi &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; devices or other Nanoleaf panels, but since it's on the ceiling it is decidedly more of a hassle to reset, which is something to keep in mind. I have also seen some complaints about Nanoleaf's customer service on Reddit and on Facebook, and while I haven't had a catastrophic product failure requiring help, I know some people have had issues getting support and replacements. Note that those complaints are more focused on the light panels than the Skylights, but I don't want to ignore potential customer service issues that could be a problem for some.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-skylight-brights.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947494" /><br/>
Each Skylight panel can be individually controlled with the Nanoleaf app and set to a different color or combination of colors and patterns. There are pre-designed options, plus tools for creating custom designs, and a section for downloading designs created by other Nanoleaf users.<br/>
<br/>
The Skylight has some unique pre-created patterns like Sun Shower and Shooting Stars that work particularly well on the ceiling, and there are window-style scenes like Blue Skies. The LEDs support 16 million colors and shades of white ranging from blue to yellow, plus there are more than 10 lighting patterns to use to shift between colors. There's also a rhythm feature that changes the color of the lights based on music or sound, and a fun AI option that creates a scene based on a typed phrase like "ocean waves" or "pink sunset."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-ai-scenes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947495" /><br/>
Colors on the light look best when in motion, and for some shades, there are dark and light spots that cause some unevenness. If you've used Nanoleaf's light panels on the wall, it's a similar effect, but it's something that you get used to and notice less with ceiling lights.<br/>
<br/>
I think multicolored lighting works well for accent lights, but I am less sure of it for light that provides as much illumination as the Skylight does. Setting the Skylight to a color like red, for example, means the room is <strong>RED</strong> and not outfitted with a tasteful red accent light in one area. Patterns that shift quickly can be almost overwhelming, and I don't like the music feature with the Skylight for that reason. I prefer to set the Skylight to softer, more pastel hues and warm whites, but it can definitely provide the ultimate mood lighting and set ambiance for movies and video games.<br/>
<br/>
There's one other thing that I want to mention before wrapping up this review, and that's control. This is a ceiling light that is connected to a light switch, and I don't have a good way to turn that light switch into a smart switch that can be used for changing colors, dimming, or even turning the light on and off. Nanoleaf doesn't have a switch, and there are a limited number of full light switch replacements for a situation like this.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nanoleaf-app-interface.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947496" /><br/>
I have a Lutron Caseta hub and system, but adding a Lutron smart light switch isn't a good idea because the Nanoleaf Skylight needs a constant connection and it's not an on/off situation. There are plenty of smart buttons, but nothing that seems to be designed to replace a light switch. For Hue lights, I solve this issue with the Lutron Aurora Dimmer Switches, but those are designed to work with the Hue app and not &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; in general. I need a physical button for the Skylight that also prevents the existing switch from being flipped, and I'm not sure how to solve that issue right now.<br/>
<br/>
Nanoleaf does have Sense+ smart switches that it has been working on since 2023, but I'm not sure when these are set to come out.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
Nanoleaf's Skylight is expensive and not without flaws, but it's also a one-of-a-kind product. It's modular so you can tune the number of panels to fit your space, it supports white and yellow light along with any color of the rainbow, and there are endless scenes and effects to play with.<br/>
<br/>
The Skylight's design isn't going to resonate with everyone, but for those who want a modern feel and who love color, it's worth checking out.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Skylight was popular enough that it sold out in most places. Nanoleaf <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/ceiling-lights/skylight/?category=skylight&amp;pack=smarter-kit&amp;size=3">has a sign up to get a notification</a> when it's back in stock, but it is still <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FNanoleaf-Ceiling-Lights-Skylight-Smarter%2Fdp%2FB0CRXXPCN2%2Fref%3Dasc_df_B0CRXXPCN2%2F">available from Amazon</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-skylight/">Review: Nanoleaf&#039;s Skylight Adds Modular Smart Lighting to Your Ceiling</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-nanoleafs-skylight-adds-modular-smart-lighting-to-your-ceiling.2424700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Camera Comparison: iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Oppo Find X7 Ultra</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-x7-ultra/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-find-x7-ultra.2424689/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:46:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-x7-ultra/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Oppo Find X7 Ultra's camera has <a href="https://www.dxomark.com/smartphones/#sort-camera/segments-%5B%22ultra%22%5D/device-Oppo%20Find%20X7%20Ultra">one of the highest rankings</a> on camera site DXOMark, coming in well ahead of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max. For that reason, we thought we'd compare the Oppo Find X7 Ultra to Apple's flagship <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to see how the cameras actually measure up in real life.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="#1 Ranked Camera vs iPhone 15 Pro Max" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vKSvQj8AkLY" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Oppo Find X7 Ultra has a 50-megapixel main lens, a 50-megapixel wide-angle lens, and two 50-megapixel telephoto lenses, one of which is a 3x periscope lens. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max has a 48-megapixel Main lens with multiple focal lengths, a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, and a 12-megapixel telephoto lens that supports 5x optical zoom. In terms of hardware, the main cameras are similar, but the Oppo has higher resolution options for the telephoto and wide-angle lenses.<br/>
<br/>
We shared a series of photos from each smartphone on our social media channels, without mentioning which one was the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. When we asked which images people liked better, our poll favored the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but overall, most people liked some images from the Oppo and some images from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. No surprises there, as with high-end smartphones, differences in camera quality can be miniscule. Choosing a favorite often comes down to processing done by each smartphone, and picking an image based on the look comes down to personal preference.<br/>
<br/>
For standard main camera photos taken during the daytime, the images come out almost the same. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can sometimes seem a little more washed out because it loses some of the saturation when raising highlights, while the Oppo tends to be more saturated. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; images can be brighter, which is preferable to some people, but the Oppo features more vibrant colors in a lot of shots. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sometimes boosts the warmth, and again, that's something that some people prefer.<br/>
<br/>
For night shots, the Oppo images came out better for the most part. The nighttime colors were more true to life, and there were fewer issues with reflections and flare. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; raised the brightness of some areas of nighttime shots just a little too much, though a couple of the low light images came out better because of some of the low light processing features Apple has built into the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
For telephoto images and Portrait images, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; had the edge in terms of focus and color, though the photos were sometimes softer than the Oppo's shots.<br/>
<br/>
Which images do you prefer? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-x7-ultra/">Camera Comparison: iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Oppo Find X7 Ultra</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-find-x7-ultra.2424689/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working to Secure Streaming Rights to FIFA Club World Cup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-fifa-tournament-rights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-to-secure-streaming-rights-to-fifa-club-world-cup.2424683/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:58:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-fifa-tournament-rights/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>FIFA</category>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working to secure an exclusive TV deal with soccer governing organization FIFA, reports <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/04/22/business/fifa-apple-tv-deal.html">The New York Times</a></em>. FIFA will launch a revamped version of Club World Cup in 2025, and Apple wants the TV rights. Club World Cup 2025 will feature 32 teams from each of the six confederations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/fifa.jpg" alt="" width="1535" height="863" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947662" /><br/>
An agreement between Apple and FIFA could be announced as soon as this month, and the first tournament will take place in the United States next summer. Apple could be paying around &#36;1 billion, and <em>The New York Times</em> says it is not yet clear if there will be any free-to-air rights. If not, the entire tournament could be available only to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has already shelled out &#36;2.5 billion to secure global broadcasting rights to Major League Soccer. MLS and League Cup games are streamed on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, with access priced at &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;99 per season for non-subscribers and &#36;12.99 per month or &#36;79 per season for those who subscribe to &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple sees live sports as a way to lure new customers to the &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; streaming service. In addition to the MLS deal, it has also secured a deal with Major League Baseball. Apple negotiated for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/19/apple-quits-nfl-sunday-ticket-negotiations/">NFL Sunday Ticket access</a>, and while that didn't work out, a report from <em><a href="https://theathletic.com/5430093/2024/04/22/nba-tv-rights-amazon-nbc/">The Athletic</a></em> suggests that Apple is still in the running to secure some streaming access to NBA games.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple introduced a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-hands-on/">dedicated Apple Sports app</a> that allows users to get real-time scores and stats for their favorite teams. The app is able to sync with the My Sports experience in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fifa/">FIFA</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-fifa-tournament-rights/">Apple Working to Secure Streaming Rights to FIFA Club World Cup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-to-secure-streaming-rights-to-fifa-club-world-cup.2424683/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Acquires French AI Company Specializing in On-Device Processing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acquires-french-ai-company-specializing-in-on-device-processing.2424672/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:01:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>France</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has acquired the Paris-based artificial intelligence startup Datakalab amid its push to deliver on-device AI tools.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Datakalab specializes in algorithm compression and embedded AI systems. The acquisition, finalized on December 17 last year, was quietly conducted but noted in a European Commission filing spotted by French publication <em><a href="https://www.challenges.fr/high-tech/ia-apple-rachete-la-start-up-parisienne-datakalab_890773">Challenges</a></em> (via <em><a href="https://iphonesoft.fr/2024/04/22/apple-rachete-start-up-francaise-datakalab-specialisee-ia-embarquee">iPhoneSoft</a></em>). While the financial details of the transaction remain undisclosed, the move is almost certainly part of Apple's broader strategy to bring more sophisticated AI technology to its devices, such as those expected to be introduced in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The company was established in 2016 by Xavier and Lucas Fischer and made significant strides in AI technology focusing on low-power, high-efficiency deep learning algorithms that function without relying on cloud-based systems. This approach aligns with Apple's oft-touted commitment to user privacy, data security, and reliable performance, as processing data locally minimizes the risk of data breaches and ensures faster processing times. The startup's expertise in compressing neural networks to work effectively on portable devices like smartphones and tablets is likely a key factor in Apple's interest.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> recently reported that Apple's LLM <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/">will run entirely on-device</a>, rather than via the cloud like most existing AI services.  Apple's AI tools may be less capable in certain instances than its direct cloud-based rivals, but Gurman suggested that the company could "fill in the gaps" by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">licensing technology from Google</a> and other AI service providers. <br/>
<br/>
Before its acquisition, Datakalab engaged in various high-profile projects, including collaborations with the French government and Disney. The company developed technology capable of analyzing human emotions by facial recognition and visual data, which were later used to monitor audience reactions in real-time during cinema screenings. The first look at Apple's new AI strategy is widely anticipated to arrive alongside previews of its next-generation operating systems at WWDC in early June.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/france/">France</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/">Apple Acquires French AI Company Specializing in On-Device Processing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acquires-french-ai-company-specializing-in-on-device-processing.2424672/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Air Stock Running Low Ahead of New Model Introduction</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/ipad-air-stock-running-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-stock-running-low-ahead-of-new-model-introduction.2424670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:29:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/ipad-air-stock-running-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Retail stock of the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> is starting to dwindle ahead of the widely anticipated arrival of new models early next month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Air-5-Colors-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1494" height="840" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-941843" /><br/>
Citing sources at multiple retail stores in the latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that inventory levels of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; are diminishing in Apple stores, a typical indicator that new versions are soon to be released. Unlike the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> apparently remains abundantly available, which suggests that Apple might be planning to sell through its current stock even after introducing an upgraded model. Historically, Apple has managed its inventory to align with the release cycles of its products, reducing shipments of older units to make room for the latest offerings. <br/>
<br/>
Expected changes coming to the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; include the more powerful <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip and an additional 12.9-inch display size option, while the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is rumored to receive OLED display technology, the M3 chip, and new accessories. The refreshed &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/gurman-new-ipads-first-week-of-may/">expected to be announced</a> during the second week of May.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/ipad-air-stock-running-low/">iPad Air Stock Running Low Ahead of New Model Introduction</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-stock-running-low-ahead-of-new-model-introduction.2424670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;100 Off Every Model of the 13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/best-buy-100-off-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-100-off-every-model-of-the-13-inch-m3-macbook-air.2424669/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:24:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/best-buy-100-off-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy today is taking &#36;100 off across the entire 13-inch M3 MacBook Air lineup, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/cl6aWzhUJR0"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model. For every version of the laptop these are all-time low prices, and they're available in all four colors of Midnight, Silver, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the entry-level 256GB laptop, Best Buy also has the 8GB RAM/512GB SSD 13-inch M3 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2vWqjoI"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> and the 16GB RAM/512GB SSD model for <a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2V0NjOE"><strong>&#36;1,399.00</strong></a>. Both of these are also &#36;100 discounts and record low prices on the just-released M3 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl6aWzhUJR0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2vWqjoI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB RAM/512GB SSD) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2V0NjOE"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB RAM/512GB SSD) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
These MacBook Air models just launched last month, coming in both 13-inch and 15-inch sizes. Both of the new MacBook Air machines include the M3 chip and focus on internal upgrades. Apple did not change the design of the MacBook Air with the 2024 update, using the same design that was first introduced in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/best-buy-100-off-m3-macbook-air/">Best Buy Takes &#36;100 Off Every Model of the 13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-100-off-every-model-of-the-13-inch-m3-macbook-air.2424669/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Orders Capacitive Button Components Allegedly for iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-orders-capactive-butttons-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-orders-capacitive-button-components-allegedly-for-iphone-16.2424660/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:08:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-orders-capactive-butttons-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Economic Daily News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has ordered a large number of capacitative button components from a Taiwan supplier that are allegedly for use in the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series, claims a new report out of Asia.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/unbox-therapy-15-buttons.jpg" alt="" width="2842" height="1572" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895008" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image credit: Unbox Therapy</em></div><br/>
According to the <em><a href="https://money.udn.com/money/story/11162/7914175">Economic Daily News</a></em>, Advanced Semiconductor Engineering won the order, which is said to include system-in-a-package (SIP) modules that will be used to integrate capcative components with two Taptic Engine motors, one on either side of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The claim in the report is that Apple will replace the existing physical buttons on both sides of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> with capacitive versions that will provide &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users with haptic feedback. The latter type of button detects pressure and emulates the press of a physical button via a haptic (or Taptic) engine which generates vibrations. <br/>
<br/>
Apple may well have ordered the buttons in preparation for future production plans, but this does not necessarily mean that they are destined for use in this year's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models. <br/>
<br/>
The earliest known prototypes of the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;‌ were thought to include haptic power and volume buttons. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/">Project Bongo</a>, as it was known internally, was a redesign of the volume and power buttons on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. However, it was scrapped in 2023 following unresolved technical issues, according to <em>MacRumors</em>' sources. After the cancelation of the Bongo project, Apple moved back to mechanical buttons for the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;‌.<br/>
<br/>
As a result, most rumors suggest that &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have all-mechanical buttons, and this includes the rumored addition of a fourth button. According to <em>The Information</em>, Apple will add a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">Capture Button</a>" to all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, but the button is expected to be mechanical rather than capacitive, and yet it will be able to respond to pressure and touch. <br/>
<br/>
The button will be used for taking photos and videos, and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will reportedly be able to zoom in and out by swiping left and right on the button, focus with a light press, and activate a recording with a more forceful press.<br/>
<br/>
Today's report claims the capacitive components will enter volume production in the third quarter of this year, which is unusually late in terms of Apple's typical initial &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; production run, so the order may be for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 lineup rather than this year's upcoming models. That said, as we saw with the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;‌ series, things can change fairly far into the process, so watch this space.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/udn-com/">Economic Daily News</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-orders-capactive-butttons-iphone-16/">Apple Orders Capacitive Button Components Allegedly for iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-orders-capacitive-button-components-allegedly-for-iphone-16.2424660/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Customer Interest Dying Down at Some Retail Stores</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down-at-some-retail-stores.2424651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:12:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, Apple's &#36;3,500 spatial computing device, appears to be following a pattern familiar to the AR/VR headset industry – initial enthusiasm giving way to a significant dip in sustained interest and usage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944159" /><br/>
Since its debut in the U.S. in February 2024, excitement for the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; has noticeably cooled, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. Writing in his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman reports a marked decline in the demand for retail demos and sales, based on the Apple Stores he has spoken to:<br/>
<blockquote>Demand for demos is way down. People who do book appointments often don't show up, and sales — at least at some locations — have gone from a couple of units a day to just a handful in a whole week. Apple also has had to step up the marketing on its online homepage. There's a huge promo for the Vision Pro at the top of the website — the most aggressive pitch since the device went on sale in early February.</blockquote>The trend that &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; appears to be following is less likely to be a retail anomaly, and more indicative of a broader issue that has plagued VR technology from its inception: Maintaining user engagement after the initial novelty wears off. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman offers his personal experience of Apple's headset as a microcosm of what he suspects is a wider user trend. His own usage has decreased from daily interactions to just once or twice a week. A significant barrier to more frequent use, he says, is a setup that involves attaching batteries, booting up, and navigating a complex interface, which makes traditional devices like laptops and smartphones more appealing for regular tasks. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman also blames the Vision Pro's lack of a "killer app" and compelling content for further diminishing the headset's appeal. He notes that it feels better suited to solitary activities – say, on a long flight or while working from home – rather than for use in social situations or around co-workers.<br/>
<br/>
It seems Apple still has a considerable task ahead in evolving the Vision Pro into a device that redefines everyday technology use. In the meantime, several bugs that initially plagued <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> have been resolved, although many of Apple's own apps are still not optimized for the device's operating system.<br/>
<br/>
In the last &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; update, Apple added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/testing-vision-pro-spatial-persona/">Spatial Personas</a>, which make it feel like you are in the same virtual room as another Vision Pro user. Spatial Personas can be used for watching movies and TV shows together, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and other video calls, using apps like Freeform, playing games, and more. However, the feature needs other Vision Pro owners to appreciate it, and as Gurman notes, they are still few and far between. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to produce fewer than 400,000 Vision Pro headsets in 2024 due to the complexity of manufacturing, according to analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. However, Apple is said to be already working on a new version of the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; for 2025 that will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">priced more affordably</a>. Meanwhile, the first incarnation of the headset is expected to arrive in additional countries later this year. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/">Apple Vision Pro Customer Interest Dying Down at Some Retail Stores</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down-at-some-retail-stores.2424651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Stops Production of FineWoven Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-stops-production-of-finewoven-accessories.2424610/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 06:03:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has stopped production of FineWoven accessories, according to the Apple leaker and prototype collector known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913676" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1782025156292198751">post on X</a> (formerly Twitter), Kosutami explained that Apple has stopped production of FineWoven accessories due to its poor durability. The company may move to another non-leather material for its premium accessories in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Kosutami has revealed accurate information about FineWoven accessories in the past. The leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/09/new-apple-watch-magnetic-band/">unveiled</a> Apple's plans to introduce new Apple Watch bands made of a "woven fabric material" over a month before they debuted, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/finewoven-cases-may-match-new-watch-band/">matching iPhone cases</a>. Kosutami also revealed the very <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/exclusive-first-look-finewoven-apple-watch-band/">first images of FineWoven accessories</a> shortly before the event in which they were officially announced. <em>MacRumors</em> understands the source of this latest information regarding the cessation of production to be the same as these previous FineWoven rumors that were ultimately accurate, so it should be taken seriously until we know more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-finewoven/">stopped selling leather accessories</a> in September last year, replacing them with a more environmentally friendly "FineWoven" material that the company describes as "luxurious and durable microtwill" made from 68% post-consumer recycled polyester. FineWoven <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> cases are priced at &#36;59, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Wallets at &#36;59, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> holders at &#36;35, and Apple Watch bands at &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
Accessories made of the material have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">very poorly received by customers</a>, citing poor durability and disappointing quality. FineWoven accessories in new color options were noticeably absent from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-refreshes-cases-and-watch-bands/">Apple's spring refresh</a>. If Apple has indeed stopped production of FineWoven accessories, it may be some time before the company's existing stock inventory begins to noticeably deplete. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/">Apple Reportedly Stops Production of FineWoven Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-stops-production-of-finewoven-accessories.2424610/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple Working on On-Device LLM for Generative AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-working-on-on-device-llm-for-generative-ai-features.2424609/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 05:35:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is developing its own large language model (LLM) that runs on-device to prioritize speed and privacy, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that Apple's LLM underpins upcoming generative AI features. "All indications" apparently suggests that it will run entirely on-device, rather than via the cloud like most existing AI services.<br/>
<br/>
Since they will run on-device, Apple's AI tools may be less capable in certain instances than its direct cloud-based rivals, but Gurman suggested that the company could "fill in the gaps" by licensing technology from Google and other AI service providers. Last month, Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">reported</a> that Apple was in discussions with Google to integrate its Gemini AI engine into the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. The main advantages of on-device processing will be quicker response times and superior privacy compared to cloud-based solutions. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's marketing strategy for its AI technology will apparently be based around how it can be useful to users' daily lives, rather than its power. Apple's broader AI strategy is expected to be revealed alongside previews of its major software updates at WWDC in June.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/">Gurman: Apple Working on On-Device LLM for Generative AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-working-on-on-device-llm-for-generative-ai-features.2424609/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Likely Planning to Skip M3 Mac Mini for M4 Refresh in Late 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini-for-m4-refresh-in-late-2024.2424607/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 05:16:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>M4 Macs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is likely to skip an M3 version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> in favor of a bigger update with M4 chips toward the end of the year, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Mini-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-946149" /><br/>
In the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that he does not expect Apple to refresh the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; with M3 chips. Apple last updated the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chips <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/new-m2-m2-pro-mac-mini/">in January 2023</a>. Other new features included two extra Thunderbolt 4 ports and an HDMI 2.1 port for &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro configurations, Wi-Fi 6E support with a compatible router, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously said that Apple is planning to release new &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models with M4 and M4 Pro chips "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">between the end of 2024 and early 2025</a>." Now, he has clarified that with new Mac minis arriving as soon as the end of the year, there is not sufficient "room for M3 models to come out before then, so it's probably safe to say that those Mac desktops will skip the M3 generation."<br/>
<br/>
Such a move would not be unprecedented since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> skipped the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip entirely, holding off until a bigger performance bump with the M3 chip late last year. With the M4 chip series, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; should get a significant CPU performance improvement compared to the existing models with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; series. The M4 chips are also rumored to have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">faster Neural Engine</a> for artificial intelligence tasks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macs/">M4 Macs</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini/">Apple Likely Planning to Skip M3 Mac Mini for M4 Refresh in Late 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini-for-m4-refresh-in-late-2024.2424607/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>LeBron James Spotted With Unreleased Beats Pill Speaker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lebron-james-spotted-with-unreleased-beats-pill-speaker.2424590/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:26:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of tonight's NBA playoff game, the Los Angeles Lakers <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lakers/reel/C5_8L_DPjYW/">posted an Instagram reel</a> showing superstar LeBron James arriving at Ball Arena in Denver carrying what appears to be an unreleased version of the Pill speaker from Apple's Beats brand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/lebron-unreleased-beats-pill.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947585" /><br/>
The original Beats Pill was a wireless Bluetooth speaker introduced in 2012 prior to Apple's acquisition of Beats Electronics. It received a few updates in its first several years on the market, with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/10/26/beats-pill-speaker-launches/">final revision being a redesigned Pill+</a> with a Lightning connector introduced under Apple's ownership in 2015.<br/>
<br/>
The Pill+ remained on the market for a number of years in that form before being <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">quietly discontinued</a> in early 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Based on today's video, it appears the Pill may soon be making a comeback, as the speaker in James' hand clearly shows a Beats logo and it includes a lanyard that was not present on previous versions of the speaker.<br/>
<br/>
With the direction of Apple's product lineup, a USB-C port for charging appears likely. And given the previous Pill+ was introduced almost nine years ago, there have been significant advances in Bluetooth and other technologies since that time, so this upcoming version is likely to be a significant improvement. Specific details on the speaker, including a release date, however, remain unknown.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">LeBron James Spotted With Unreleased Beats Pill Speaker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lebron-james-spotted-with-unreleased-beats-pill-speaker.2424590/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s Big iPad Sale Has &#36;100 Off iPad Mini, iPad Air, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/best-buys-big-ipad-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-big-ipad-sale-has-100-off-ipad-mini-ipad-air-and-more.2424564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:09:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/best-buys-big-ipad-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is back with a <a href="https://howl.me/clG8QCkba7O">new sale on Apple iPads</a>, including some of the best prices we've ever seen on iPad, iPad mini, and iPad Air. Additionally, we're still tracking a great deal on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, which is &#36;150 off right now at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/best-buy-blue-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937846" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-best-buy-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938106" /><br/>
Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi 10th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, which is an all-time low price at &#36;100 off. You'll find every model of the 10th generation iPad on sale at a record low price during this sale. This includes all Wi-Fi and cellular tablets, in all colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKbvh8PEh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKduB2Qbr"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKdXDXcha"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad for &#36;649.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ipad-mini-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926944" /><br/>
We're tracking discounts across the entire iPad mini 6 lineup at Best Buy this weekend, including second-best prices for multiple tablets. Prices start at <a href="https://howl.me/cl4ULPxMzsv"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4ULPxMzsv"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UMAu57Lv"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UNaOAqS8"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad mini for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UNMb7NwA"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad mini for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ipad-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930002" /><br/>
Best Buy has the 2022 iPad Air for &#36;100 off every configuration this weekend. These are solid second-best prices across the board, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/cl4UGX1cxXA"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UGX1cxXA"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UHF9fr6R"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;649.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UIg9rOk7"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;649.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UITHMucB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;799.99</div></a></div><h2>13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924749" /><br/>
Every model of the 2022 13-inch MacBook Air is <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI">available for &#36;150 off</a> this weekend at Best Buy. The 256GB model is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> and the 512GB model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a>. These deals beat the previous prices by about &#36;50, and you don't need to be a My Best Buy Plus or Total member to get them.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/best-buys-big-ipad-sale/">Best Buy&#039;s Big iPad Sale Has &#36;100 Off iPad Mini, iPad Air, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-big-ipad-sale-has-100-off-ipad-mini-ipad-air-and-more.2424564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Nintendo Emulators on App Store, Two New iOS 17 Features, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/top-stories-game-emulators-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-nintendo-emulators-on-app-store-two-new-ios-17-features-and-more.2424557/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/top-stories-game-emulators-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It was a big week for retro gaming fans, as iPhone users are starting to reap the rewards of Apple's recent change to allow retro game emulators on the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/top-stories-20apr2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947573" /><br/>
This week also saw a new iOS 17.5 beta that will support web-based app distribution in the EU, the debut of the first hotels to allow for direct AirPlay streaming to room TVs, a fresh rumor about the impending iPad Air update, and more details on the sequence of Apple's M4-based Mac updates starting later this year, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Delta Game Emulator Now Available From App Store on iPhone</h2><br/>
A few weeks after Apple updated its App Review Guidelines to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">allow retro game console emulator apps</a>, the popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">Nintendo emulator Delta is now available in the App Store</a>. Delta can emulate games released for many older Nintendo consoles, including the NES, SNES, Nintendo 64, Nintendo DS, and all Game Boy models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Delta-Emulator-Pokemon-Gen-3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947545" /><br/>
We published an article explaining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/what-to-know-about-iphone-app-store-emulators/">key facts about emulators in the App Store</a> and the legality of downloading games.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iOS 17.5 Beta Lets EU iPhone Users Download Apps Directly From Websites</h2><br/>
Starting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/">second beta of iOS 17.5</a>, released this week, large developers in the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">can now distribute apps directly on the web</a> instead of through the App Store or an alternative app marketplace.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-EU-iOS-Changes-Orange-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946723" /><br/>
To be eligible for this new Web Distribution feature, Apple says a developer must meet several requirements, including having an app that had more than one million annual installs on iOS in the EU in the prior calendar year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17's New AirPlay Feature for Hotel Room TVs Begins Rolling Out</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/ios-17-airplay-hotel-feature-now-available/">announced that AirPlay is now available at around 60 hotels</a> operated by IHG Hotels & Resorts in the U.S., Canada, and Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/IHG-Hotel-AirPlay.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947151" /><br/>
At hotels that offer the feature, guests can scan a unique QR code on their room's TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing them to wirelessly stream content from their iPhone or iPad. For example, they could stream Apple TV+ or Netflix shows, listen to music on Apple Music or Spotify, play games on Apple Arcade, or work out with Apple Fitness+.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 30 Rumored Upgrades Compared</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 16 lineup is still months away from being announced, there are already many rumors about the four devices that have been circulating for months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-15-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature-Cyan-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935694" /><br/>
If you own an iPhone 15 Pro or Pro Max model, and will be considering upgrading to the iPhone 16 Pro family, check out our new comparison chart that outlines <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">over 30 rumored new features and changes for the iPhone 16 Pro models</a>, and if you're an iPhone 15 or 15 Plus user, we're tracking <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/">over 15 changes expected for the iPhone 16 models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>12.9-Inch iPad Air Now Rumored to Feature Mini-LED Display</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">rumored 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> that is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/new-ipad-models-may-launch/">expected to be announced in May</a> will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/12-9-inch-ipad-air-mini-led-display-rumor/">equipped with a mini-LED display</a> like the current 12.9-inch iPad Pro, according to info shared this week by Ross Young, CEO of research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
The existing 10.9-inch iPad Air is equipped with a standard LCD panel, and the move to mini-LED technology for the 12.9-inch model would provide increased brightness for HDR content, deeper blacks, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Macs Are Expected to Launch in This Order Starting Later This Year</h2><br/>
In his <em>Power On</em> newsletter this week, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman outlined the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">order in which he expects Macs with the M4 family of chips to be released</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-AI-Optimized-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945901" /><br/>
Gurman said the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">entire Mac lineup will be updated</a> with the M4 chip or higher-end variants, starting with the MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini between late 2024 and early 2025, followed by the MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro between the spring and end of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/apr-18-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/top-stories-game-emulators-app-store/">Top Stories: Nintendo Emulators on App Store, Two New iOS 17 Features, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-nintendo-emulators-on-app-store-two-new-ios-17-features-and-more.2424557/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announced the 24-Inch iMac Three Years Ago Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announced-the-24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today.2424556/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:13:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today marks the three-year anniversary of Apple's announcement of the 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, a transformative redesign featuring the first integration of Apple silicon in the product line.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iMac-24-Apple-Newsroom-Gray-bg.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-930105" /><br/>
Apple unveiled the new 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; on April 20, 2021, almost nine years after the previous &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; redesign debuted. It replaced both the 21.5-inch and the 27-inch Intel iMacs, and represented a recommitment to the long-standing desktop product line.<br/>
<br/>
The highly anticipated redesign offers a much thinner and more compact body compared to its predecessors, available in an array of vibrant colors reminiscent of the original iMacs released in the late 1990s. The 24-inch 4.5K Retina display boasts 11.3 million pixels and support for 1 billion colors.<br/>
<br/>
The new model was not only notable for its updated design but also as the inaugural &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; to incorporate Apple silicon, one of the last Macs to make the transition away from Intel. Apple claimed that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip delivered up to 85% faster CPU performance and up to two-times faster GPU performance compared to the previous 21.5-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; models. The new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; also offered a 1080p <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> HD camera, studio-quality microphones, and a six-speaker sound system, as well as a color-matched Magic Keyboard with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple refreshed the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with the M3 chip, Wi-Fi 6E, and Bluetooth 5.3 in November 2023. Rumors suggest that a larger-screened &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; that could be positioned as an &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">launch in 2025</a>. In June 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that the high-end &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; was a year or two away from launching as work on the device was still in the early stages.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today/">Apple Announced the 24-Inch iMac Three Years Ago Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announced-the-24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today.2424556/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M4 MacBook Pro Lineup: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-macbook-pro-lineup-what-to-expect.2424533/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:02:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro&#038;post_date=1713574947/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>M4 MacBook Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to refresh the MacBook Pro with M4 chips starting in late 2024, and this guide aggregates everything that we know about Apple's M4 MacBook Pro plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945903" /><br/>
<h2 id="m4_update">M4 Update</h2><br/>
Apple built the M3 chip on a new 3-nanometer process, and we are not expecting a node change for the M4. It too will be a 3-nanometer chip, but Apple supplier TSMC could introduce updates that make it more efficient and faster.<br/>
<br/>
New artificial intelligence capabilities are rumored for Apple's upcoming products, and so the M4 will focus on AI. Apple wants to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">improve performance</a> for AI functionality, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">rumors suggest</a> that the M4 (and the A18 chips for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>) will have an upgraded Neural Engine with "significantly" more cores.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chips all have a 16-core Neural Engine, and Apple has not increased the Neural Engine cores for several years.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="entry-level_14-inch_macbook_pro">Entry-Level 14-Inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
With the M3 chip launch last year, Apple did away with the 13-inch MacBook Pro. It's been replaced with the 14-inch MacBook Pro, which Apple now offers with three different chip options.<br/>
<br/>
The entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro has an M3 chip and a &#36;1,599 starting price, and this is the model that will get the standard M4 chip. The current M3 chip has an 8-core CPU and up to a 10-core GPU, and the M4 could be similar.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="higher-end_14-inch_and_16-inch_macbook_pro_models">Higher-End 14-Inch and 16-Inch MacBook Pro Models</h2><br/>
For customers who want a more "pro" machine, the higher-end 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models are set to be refreshed with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips, which are more powerful versions of the faster M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
The current M3 Pro has up to a 12-core CPU and up to an 18-core GPU, while the M3 Max has up to a 16-core CPU and up to a 40-core GPU. CPU and GPU improvements for the M4 Pro and M4 Max aren't yet known.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design_changes">Design Changes?</h2><br/>
There are no rumors of a design change for the MacBook Pro at this time, and we're not quite due for one. Apple last updated the MacBook Pro design in 2021 with the transition to Apple silicon. In recent history, Apple has redesigned the MacBook in 2012, 2016, and 2021, so following that pattern, we'll see the next design tweak in 2025 or 2026.<br/>
<br/>
This year's M-series update will likely be limited to the MacBook Pro's internals.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, the entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro could get an M4 chip in late 2024, while the timeline for the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro refresh is estimated at late 2024 to early 2025.<br/>
<br/>
We could see the M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max variants come out all at once like the M3 chip lineup, or Apple could space them out across several months.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 MacBook Pro models came out in October 2023, so a refresh around October 2024 would come at the one-year mark.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/">Apple&#039;s M4 MacBook Pro Lineup: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-macbook-pro-lineup-what-to-expect.2424533/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Now Available on Apple&#039;s Refurbished Store in U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-in-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-now-available-on-apples-refurbished-store-in-u-s.2424524/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:34:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-in-us/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began selling certified refurbished Apple Watch Ultra 2 models in the U.S. for the first time since the device was released in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-blorange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911679" /><br/>
As of writing, refurbished Ultra 2 models with the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/FREG3LW/A/Refurbished-Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-GPS-Cellular-49mm-Titanium-Case-with-Blue-Ocean-Band">Blue</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/FREH3LW/A/Refurbished-Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-GPS-Cellular-49mm-Titanium-Case-with-Orange-Ocean-Band?fnode=c33d6587feda6a2d1b4df893338e0b10c6def7ee3d2db1465e981af4a26e20b29a9c5339994ab02294593ec3968732539fefa1c777bc2e2d0e1bd6aff98bcb1fe958a412ce82bc5f5b2e7389568d2e15">Orange</a>, or <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/FREJ3LW/A/Refurbished-Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-GPS-Cellular-49mm-Titanium-Case-with-White-Ocean-Band?fnode=e5406cc44be0df3204093d631dbb4976cebe18e711d09d02bbce5167a990eea5a25cbe8bf141f71311fff9fcc8eb7773853603822f89ae164ace9014c53293a3a11637451df5bf9098715a484e206991">White Ocean Band</a> are available for &#36;679, compared to &#36;799 brand new.<br/>
<br/>
Like new Ultra 2 models sold directly by Apple in the U.S. currently, we expect that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-website-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-removal/">Blood Oxygen app is deactivated</a> on the refurbished models, due to a legal battle with medical technology company Masimo. Last year, the U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/10/itc-opposes-apple-watch-sales-ban-pause/">banned Apple</a> from importing and selling Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing after it ruled that the feature infringed on Masimo's patents. Apple is appealing the decision, and could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-software/">re-enable the Blood Oxygen app with a watchOS update</a> if it is overturned.<br/>
<br/>
Availability began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-begins-rolling-out/">in the U.K. and China</a> earlier this week, and the Blood Oxygen app remains functional outside of the U.S. currently.<br/>
<br/>
There are no refurbished Apple Watch Series 9 models available on Apple's store in the U.S. yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-in-us/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Now Available on Apple&#039;s Refurbished Store in U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-now-available-on-apples-refurbished-store-in-u-s.2424524/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
