<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 03:01:21 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Photos App: All the New Features and Design Updates</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-photos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-photos-app-all-the-new-features-and-design-updates.2433290/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:51:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-photos&#038;post_date=1723251061/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app redesign has been one of the most controversial changes that Apple made in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and Apple has made several updates during the beta testing process. There is an entirely new unified look for the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app compared to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, along with some neat new features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-Photos-Feature-Chromatic.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961382" /><br/>
This guide aggregates everything different with the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, and it is up to date with Apple's latest changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="unified_design">Unified Design</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; does away with separate tabs in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, introducing an all-in-one view. The Photo Library is still the main focus of the app and what you'll see when you open up &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;, but you'll now scroll down to get to additional content rather than tapping on the separate For You and Albums tabs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photos-app-interface.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961377" /><br/>
The Photo Library grid displays approximately 30 images at one time, and to use the swipe gestures to display fewer or more images on the screen, you need to swipe down to get to the full Photo Library view. From here, you can pinch in or out to adjust the view.<br/>
<br/>
This is also where the Years and Months organizational options are for navigating through your past images. The Days option has been removed, and is instead accessible in a Recent Days Collection if you scroll down.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photos-app-collections.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961380" /><br/>
There is a quick access search icon in blue on every view in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, along with a Select button that lets you select multiple images for sharing, deleting, adding to an album, and more. Tap on Search to get into the Search interface, and Done when you're finished, or tap on Select and tap images to choose them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photos-app-select.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961378" /><br/>
You'll need to get used to swiping down to get to the full Photo Library view, and swiping back up to get to the other views in the app.<br/>
<br/>
Below the main &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; grid, you can swipe to see different collections of images that previously would have been listed under the For You tab, along with your Albums, which were also previously located in a separate app section.<br/>
<br/>
Much of what was in the prior version of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app is still in the new one, but with a different all-in-one screen organizational structure.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="filters_and_sorting">Filters and Sorting</h3><br/>
In the full Library View, which is accessible by swiping down, you can get to the filter and sort options. You can sort the Photo Library by either recently added or date captured.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photos-app-filters.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961379" /><br/>
The icon with two arrows houses filters, which include Favorites, Edited, &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;, Videos, and Screenshots. If you tap on one of these, you can filter out everything else to see just that category.<br/>
<br/>
With the separate View Options tab, you can remove Screenshots and Shared With You images from your Photo Library. View Options also has Zoom In, Zoom Out, and Aspect Ratio Grid tools, all of which were in the prior version of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="collections_and_customization">Collections and Customization</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app is focused on Collections, which are basically different albums that aggregate photos based on subject, location, type, and other parameters. Everything outside of the photo grid is considered a "Collection."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-collections.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961386" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Recent Days</strong> - Displays your recent images by date. You can scroll through or tap on the Collection name to see your entire Photo library organized by day. It's essentially equivalent to the Days view from the &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; Photo Library design.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Albums</strong> - A collection of all of the albums you've created, including Shared albums you're in.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>People and Pets</strong> - Albums organized by person or pet, with Apple using machine learning to detect the people in the images. The People and Pets album now supports Groups, so if you have many images featuring the same people, you'll see them grouped together. Groups are auto-generated if there are enough images, but you can also create them.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Memories</strong> - Houses the auto-generated slideshows that Apple creates, along with the new Apple Intelligence Memory Maker slideshows.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Trips</strong> - Shows your photos from different locations. Tapping into this Collection and then tapping the dates lets you see your trips by year.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Shared Albums</strong> - Albums that you share with others.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Pinned Collections</strong> - A selection of your favorite collections or albums.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Featured Photos</strong> - A rotating collection of your best images surfaced by the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Media Types</strong> - Lets you see images recorded with different camera settings. Options include Videos, Selfies, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-photos/">Live Photos</a>, Portrait, Panoramas, Slo-mo, Screenshots, Screen Recordings, Spatial, and RAW. This section used to be under the Albums tab.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Utilities</strong> - Essentially offers filters for different types of images, letting you quickly get to images with handwriting, receipts, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Wallpaper Suggestions</strong> - Images that the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app thinks would make ideal wallpapers, complete with different tints, colors for the time, and fonts.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="customization">Customization</h3><br/>
You can change the order that Collections are displayed under the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; grid, so you can get to your most used features first. To do this, scroll down to the bottom of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app and then tap on the Customize and Reorder option.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-collections-reorder.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961387" /><br/>
You can deselect a checkmark to remove a Collection, or tap and drag the three bars next to each Collection to rearrange the order. Tapping on X exits out of the menu and goes back to the main &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; view.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="pinned_collections">Pinned Collections</h3><br/>
Pinned Collections is a collection of your other Collections and albums. You can add anything you want to the Pinned Collections section, including albums, media types, other collections, and Utilities. It's basically a way to get one-tap access to any &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app category.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-collections-customization.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961388" /><br/>
This is a good section for adding content you like to access that isn't already included in one of the default Collections, such as the Map that lets you see where all of your photos were taken.<br/>
<br/>
If you often need to access your screenshots or your videos, those make good pinned collection options. You can also choose any person or pet from the People and Pets Collection, specific trips, and specific memories.<br/>
<br/>
Customizing this section can be done by tapping on one of Apple's suggestions, which are in green, or tapping on the Any Collection or Album option to select something custom. To remove a Pinned Collection, tap on the red "-" button, and to rearrange, tap and drag on the three bar icon.<br/>
<br/>
Pinned Collections stay in the Pinned Collections section, so you can't do something like turn a specific pet album into a separate Collection of its own.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="photo_editing">Photo Editing</h2><br/>
The interface for editing one of your images hasn't changed too much, but there are some updates. Rather than tapping on the "Edit" button at the top right of the app, you'll now need to tap on the icon that looks like three slider bars to get into the editing interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photo-editing-tools.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961389" /><br/>
The Share Sheet icon and Delete icon are in the same spots, and there's still a heart for favoriting images and an info button that also transforms with a sparkle icon when there's something in the image that can be identified, like a plant or animal.<br/>
<br/>
All of the same photo management features like Copy, Duplicate, Hide, Slideshow, and Add to Album can be accessed by tapping the three dots in the upper right corner. Tapping the X there now exits the editing view, which is a departure from the prior back arrow on the left side of the app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple hasn't changed the actual editing tools, and they're all still in the same spots.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="utilities">Utilities</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, the Utilities album was limited to Imports, Duplicates, Hidden, and Recently Deleted, but in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, the new Utilities Collection houses a lot more image types.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-photos-utilities.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955074" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Hidden - Images you've hidden from view in the photo grid. Requires a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> scan to access.</li><br/>
 <li>Recently Deleted - Images you've deleted in the last 30 days. Requires a &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; scan to access.</li><br/>
 <li>Duplicates - If you have duplicate images, you can use this to merge them. This section doesn't show up if you don't have duplicate images.</li><br/>
 <li>Receipts - Shows pictures of receipts, or images your device thinks are receipts.</li><br/>
 <li>Handwriting - Displays all images that have handwriting in them.</li><br/>
 <li>Illustrations - Shows paintings and drawings.</li><br/>
 <li>QR Codes - Surfaces images that have QR codes in them.</li><br/>
 <li>Recently Saved - All images recently saved to your library.</li><br/>
 <li>Recently Viewed - All images you've looked at recently.</li><br/>
 <li>Recently Edited - All images you've edited recently.</li><br/>
 <li>Documents - Features images that have documents in them.</li><br/>
 <li>Imports - Shows imported images.</li><br/>
 <li>Map - Opens up the map where you can see all of your images based on location.</li><br/>
 <li>Recovered - This album only shows up if you have a missing image after an update, such as an image taken with a third-party app that didn't make it into your library.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="search_improvements">Search Improvements</h2><br/>
Apple made several improvements to the Search function in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app. You can search using natural language, and get a lot more specific than before. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photos-search.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961390" /><br/>
Not only can you search for a specific person, for example, you can find photos where they're only wearing blue, or were holding an ice cream. Some example search terms:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Me with food</li><br/>
 <li>Cats outside</li><br/>
 <li>Bugs on plants</li><br/>
 <li>Pancakes with banana</li><br/>
 <li>Flowers from last year</li><br/>
 <li>Cat in a box</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can essentially describe any photo that you remember and the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app might be able to find it based on your description. You can also now search for specific parts of videos that you've captured and the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app will go right to the scene in the video if it recognizes what you've typed.<br/>
<br/>
For all of the search features, the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app needs to index your library because this is done on-device, and indexing can take quite a long time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="memory_maker_apple_intelligence">Memory Maker (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
Memory Maker is a feature that lets you create a custom Memory Movie from your photos and videos using a text prompt. You can get to the Memory Maker in the Memories Collection in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-memory-maker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960208" /><br/>
Tap on the "Create" option to start a new memory based on a phrase. You can type in something like "My cat over the years" "exploring Ireland," "yummy food," or "happy photos with Eric." The &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app will search through your library for the best images, creating a mini narrative with a beginning, middle, and end.<br/>
<br/>
Your memory will be set to music, with Apple selecting songs that go along with the topic. You can select a new song to go along with the memory, and if you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscription, it will use &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; songs. You can also edit the timeline and the title for further customization.<br/>
<br/>
Memory Movies can be shared on social networks or in messages, added to your Favorites, or AirPlayed to an Apple device.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="clean_up_apple_intelligence">Clean Up (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
Part of Apple Intelligence, Clean Up can be used to intelligently identify background objects in your photos so you can remove them with a tap. It's designed to help you quickly and easily eliminate distractions from your photos, but it's not coming until later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-photos-clean-up-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961392" /><br/>
<h2 id="image_playground_integration_apple_intelligence">Image Playground Integration (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
Image Playground, the app that will let you generate images based on text prompts, will integrate with the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app to create images that feature your friends and family members.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956654" /><br/>
Image Playground is also an Apple Intelligence feature that will be coming in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
Additional information on new features that Apple has added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-photos/">iOS 18 Photos App: All the New Features and Design Updates</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-photos-app-all-the-new-features-and-design-updates.2433290/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV 4K vs. Google TV Streamer Buyer&#039;s Guide: All Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-4k-vs-google-tv-streamer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-4k-vs-google-tv-streamer-buyers-guide-all-differences-compared.2433277/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:47:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-4k-vs-google-tv-streamer&#038;post_date=1723240045/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/google-tv-streamer-announced/">announced</a> the Google TV Streamer as a replacement for the Chromecast, setting its sights on directly rivalling the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K, so how do the two devices compare?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/google-tv.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="563" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960978" /><br/>
Fundamentally, the Google TV Streamer is designed with a focus on deep integration with Google's ecosystem including services like Google <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, YouTube, and Google Assistant. It is also positioned as a smart home hub, supporting Matter and Thread protocols to control a wide range of smart home devices.<br/>
<br/>
In contrast, the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K is deeply embedded within Apple's ecosystem, providing access to services such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, with support for features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>. Its compact, black puck design allows it to blend effortlessly into most home entertainment setups, while offering powerful performance with the A15 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
While both devices support 4K resolution and advanced HDR formats, they differ in their storage options, connectivity features, and additional functionalities. The Google TV Streamer emphasizes an AI-powered user experience with personalized content recommendations and generative AI screensavers, whereas the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K offers ecosystem advantages like &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; and Fitness+ for a more integrated Apple experience. All of the key differences between the two devices are listed below:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Google TV Streamer</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Designed to sit in front of the TV, with a noticeable design intended to blend with home decor</td><br/>
 <td>Compact, black puck design that can be easily hidden or integrated into a home entertainment system</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6.4" x 3.0" x 1.0"</td><br/>
 <td>3.66" x 3.66" x 1.2"</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 5.7 ounces</td><br/>
 <td>Weighs 7.3 ounces (Wi-Fi)<br/>
Weighs 7.5 ounces (Wi-Fi + Ethernet)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Google TV (Android TV)</td><br/>
 <td>tvOS</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Google Assistant</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Google Home, Thread, and Matter</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;, Thread (Wi-Fi + Ethernet), and Matter</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>SDR video, Dolby Vision, HDR10+, HDR10, HLG</td><br/>
 <td>SDR video, Dolby Vision, HDR10+, HDR10, HLG, HEVC, H.264, MPEG-4, HDMI Quick Media Switching</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Dolby Digital, Dolby Digital Plus, Dolby Atmos</td><br/>
 <td>HE-AAC, AAC, Protected AAC, MP3, Apple Lossless, FLAC, AIFF, WAV, AC-3 Dolby Digital 5.1, E-AC-3 Dolby Digital Plus 7.1, Dolby Atmos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Aggregates content from various streaming services and presents personalized recommendations</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app aggregates content from various services and provides a unified watchlist</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>AI-powered content suggestions and generative AI screensavers</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Deep integration with Google services like Google &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;, YouTube, and Google Assistant. Supports casting from Android devices</td><br/>
 <td>Deep integration with Apple ecosystem, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, and &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; for casting from iOS devices</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Improved processor, 22% faster than previous Chromecast</td><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>HDMI 2.1, Bluetooth 5.1, Gigabit Ethernet, Thread, USB-C</td><br/>
 <td>HDMI 2.1, Bluetooth 5.0, Infrared, Gigabit Ethernet (Wi-Fi + Ethernet), Thread (Wi-Fi + Ethernet)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>32GB storage</td><br/>
 <td>64GB storage (Wi-Fi)<br/>
128GB storage (Wi-Fi + Ethernet)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Support for external storage and flash drives</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Voice Remote with customizable button, textured back, and remote finder</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; Remote with touch surface, volume control on face, and remote finder</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Hazel (Google Store exclusive) and Porcelain</td><br/>
 <td>Available in Black only</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&#36;99.99</td><br/>
 <td>&#36;129 (Wi-Fi)<br/>
&#36;149 (Wi-Fi + Ethernet)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Releases September 24, 2024</td><br/>
 <td>Released November 4, 2022</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Choosing between the Google TV Streamer and the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K ultimately depends on your specific needs and the ecosystem you are already invested in. For those deeply integrated into the Google ecosystem, the Google TV Streamer is clearly the best choice. It is designed to work seamlessly with Google services like Google &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;, YouTube, and Google Assistant, making it ideal for users who rely on these platforms. It also supports playback from external storage devices. The device's support for Matter and Thread protocols also makes it a strong contender for those with a smart home setup. Additionally, its AI-powered content recommendations and generative AI screensavers provide a personalized and modern user experience.<br/>
<br/>
On the other hand, the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K is perfect for users who are heavily entrenched in the Apple ecosystem. With seamless access to &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, and &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj;, this device is tailored for those who use Apple devices and services. The A15 Bionic chip ensures excellent performance, making it suitable for users who require a particularly robust device for streaming and light gaming. The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K's compact design allows it to fit discreetly into any home entertainment setup, and its integration with &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;, Matter, and Thread makes it a strong choice for those looking to manage their smart home devices through Apple's ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
Each device has unique strengths that cater to slightly different user needs based on ecosystem. Ultimately, if your primary concern is deep integration with Google services and a focus on smart home connectivity, the Google TV Streamer is the way to go. Conversely, if you are looking for a device that offers powerful performance and extensive access to Apple services, the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K will be your best bet. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-4k-vs-google-tv-streamer/">Apple TV 4K vs. Google TV Streamer Buyer&#039;s Guide: All Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-4k-vs-google-tv-streamer-buyers-guide-all-differences-compared.2433277/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Scosche&#039;s Modular BaseLynx 2.0 is Great for Multi-Device Charging</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/scosche-baselynx/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-scosches-modular-baselynx-2-0-is-great-for-multi-device-charging.2433275/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:25:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/scosche-baselynx&#038;post_date=1723238739/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For people who have multiple devices to charge or who want a family charging hub, Scosche makes a BaseLynx modular charging kit that can be added to and upgraded as needed. The Baselynx has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/scoshe-baselynx-modular-charging-station/">around since 2020</a>, but an updated 2.0 version <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/04/scosche-baselynx-charging-system/">came out last year</a> with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> support and Apple Watch fast charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/scosche-baselynx-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-879602" /><br/>
There are multiple BaseLynx 2.0 components that can be purchased separately or in a bundle. The BaseLynx is made from a lightweight plastic material, but it doesn't look out of place in an office or home environment. Right now, the BaseLynx 2.0 is only available in white, but Scosche is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/10/ces-2024-baselynx-qi2-charger/">working on a new Qi2 version</a> that will come in black.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2msiqwt-baselynx2-2-in-1-charging-stand-with-magsafe-white">BaseLynx 2.0 2-in-1 Stand</a> features an upright &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charger that can charge a compatible <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at up to 15W, plus it has a smaller platform at the bottom for charging Qi-compatible AirPods or other devices that don't need much power.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scosche-baselynx-components.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961343" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2awwt-baselynx2-watch-white">BaseLynx 2.0 Watch</a> is a magnetic Apple Watch charger that supports fast charging with compatible Apple Watch models. It has a simple design with a small curved arm that has the charging puck at the top.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2mdpwt-baselynx2-vertical-multi-device-charging-station">BaseLynx 2.0 Vert</a> is the most versatile component in the setup, featuring three USB-C ports with a shared 60W output for charging iPads, iPhones, and other USB-C devices. The Vert has four metal bars with silicone padding to hold your devices in place while they charge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scosche-baselynx-connectors.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961344" /><br/>
You can stack three devices in the bars, though depending on the placement of other components, you might be able to fit one more. The Vert comes with one USB-C cable, but you'll need to supply other short cables to go along with it. I bought 12-inch and 6-inch cables, and found that 12 inches is the ideal cable size to use with the charger.<br/>
<br/>
You plug one end of the cable into your device and the other end into the Vert, and then put it in one of the Vert's slots, so the cable needs to be long enough for that. Six inches is long enough for an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but not something larger like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>. I definitely wish the USB-C ports were on the back of the Vert to better hide cabling for a cleaner look. With one port in use, a device gets the full 60W. With two, it's split into 30W, and with three, each port gets 20W.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scosche-baselynx-assembled.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961345" /><br/>
There's also a <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2peacwt-baselynx2-end-cap-white">BaseLynx 2.0 End Cap</a>, which adds extra charging power to a BaseLynx setup. It has a 125V AC outlet for connecting laptop chargers or other devices, and a dedicated 67W USB-C port, both of which can be used at the same time. Because the Vert only has 60W of shared power, the End Cap is a better option for charging a laptop.<br/>
<br/>
Each BaseLynx component comes with a removable cable component that snaps on to one side, and this is what's removed to connect more than one module together. Because each one can be charged individually, you can opt to use them in separate locations, but the idea is to connect multiple chargers together to create a customized charging station. With four modules, it is 13 inches long and 3.5 inches wide, so you do need a larger-sized desk or enough counter/table space to accommodate it. While I don't mind the design, it has a somewhat blocky aesthetic that might not be for everyone. In terms of space, it takes up less desk area than the multiple chargers I had before, and it offers a good balance of charging capability and space used.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scosche-baselynx-on-desk-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961346" /><br/>
The End Cap is designed to fit on the end, as the name suggestions, but the other components can fit together in any arrangement. There are connectors and holes on each piece (covered by the aforementioned cable components and snap-in protectors) that link together. The option to arrange the modules is nice because you can set it up in an optimal arrangement for your usage needs.<br/>
<br/>
You can connect a surprising number of modules to a single setup, and Scosche uses a points-based system to make it simple. The Vert is five points, the 2-in-1 Stand is two points, the Watch charger is one point, and the End Cap is 0 points. Configurations can have fifteen total points, so you can connect three just Verts, two Verts, two 2-in-1 stands, and a Watch charger, or any other combination of components.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scosche-baselynx-side-view.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961347" /><br/>
The setup that I tested with the Vert, 2-in-1 Stand, Watch charger and End Cap is eight points, so I could add additional components in the future if I need to charge more devices. With that kind of expandability, you can set up a charging station that can work for all members of your household or multiple people in an office.<br/>
<br/>
Any setup of 15 points or less only needs one power source and one cable, so it significantly cuts down on cables that you need to plug in and have on your desk. Having fewer cables and needing fewer outlets is something that I love about the Scosche BaseLynx system. I have test devices so I have a few more Apple products than the average person, and it streamlined my desk setup.<br/>
<br/>
With the BaseLynx setup that includes the End Cap, Vert, Apple Watch charger, and 2-in-1 charger, I can charge two iPhones (one is USB-C), an &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, an Apple Watch, AirPods, and a Steam Deck. If I use a multi-port power adapter with the End Cap, that would expand a bit more. Most devices charge at maximum speed with this setup, though the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is charging at 20W with all ports engaged, and the 13 Pro Max is limited to its maximum wireless charging speed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scoshe-baselynx-top-view.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1180" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961348" /><br/>
I tested charging speeds for all of the components, and there were no surprises. The 2-in-1 Stand charged my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from 0 to 38 percent in an hour in three tests, and from 0 to 39 percent in another two tests. The Apple Watch charger fast charged my Series 9 as expected (I charge in 20 minute increments twice a day), and in a timed test, it hit 70 percent in 30 minutes when starting from a dead battery. The Vert power split worked as described as well, with a 20/20/20 split with all three ports in use. Those ports are ideal for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and I charge my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> and Steam Deck with the End Cap that supports 67W or a power adapter plugged into the included outlet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
All of the components are useful, but if I had to choose one or two, the Vert and the End Cap are the most versatile. Having a multi-port stand for my larger devices that keeps them tucked out of the way frees up a lot of desktop space, and it's turned out to be very convenient. I have seen multi-port charging stations that are cheaper on Amazon, but most of these use USB-A and are bulkier than Scosche's system. It is worth noting that there are no USB-A ports available, so if you have things that charge with USB-A, you'll need a USB-C to USB-A adapter.<br/>
<br/>
I don't think the design of the BaseLynx 2.0 is going to be for everyone, especially those who are not fans of upright chargers like the Vert or who don't have a need for multi-device charging, but if you do need to charge a lot of devices, it's space saving. I think it works best as a communal charging option in a centralized location, and that's probably what will appeal to most people.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/scosche-baselynx-wide-view.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961349" /><br/>
As with most third-party charging solutions for Apple devices, the downside to Scosche's BaseLynx 2.0 is the price. The full kit is &#36;280, and a standard kit is &#36;180, with Apple selling both of these accessories. The other modules can be purchased separately, but prices are only cheaper if you only want one or two components. Even at these prices, if you have a lot of devices or want something that will work for multiple people in the family, the BaseLynx 2.0 setup is a good option. It's slim, it's modular and can be added to over time, and it keeps devices out of the way while they're charging.<br/>
<br/>
Scosche previewed a Qi2 version of the BaseLynx 2.0 earlier this year, and it's set to come out later this year. Qi2 offers the same charging speed as &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; without the need for licensing Apple technology, so it is possible that model will be cheaper and it may be worth waiting for.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ6C2LL/A/scosche-baselynx-20-pro-kit">BaseLynx 2.0 Pro Kit</a> that has the End Cap, Vert, 2-in-1 Charger, and Apple Watch Charger is available for &#36;280 from Apple, while <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ6F2LL/A/scosche-baselynx-20-kit">the standard kit</a> with Vert and 2-in-1 Charging Stand is available for &#36;180. The individual components can be purchased directly from Scosche.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2awwt-baselynx2-watch-white">BaseLynx 2.0 for Apple Watch</a> is &#36;70, the <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2msiqwt-baselynx2-2-in-1-charging-stand-with-magsafe-white">2-in-1 MagSafe Stand</a> is &#36;100, <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2mdpwt-baselynx2-vertical-multi-device-charging-station">the Vert</a> is &#36;80, and <a href="https://www.scosche.com/bl2peacwt-baselynx2-end-cap-white">the End Cap</a> is &#36;50.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Scosche provided MacRumors with a BaseLynx 2.0 Pro Kit for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/scosche-baselynx/">Review: Scosche&#039;s Modular BaseLynx 2.0 is Great for Multi-Device Charging</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-scosches-modular-baselynx-2-0-is-great-for-multi-device-charging.2433275/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Discounts Hit Every MacBook Air Alongside AirPods Max and iPad Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-9-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-discounts-hit-every-macbook-air-alongside-airpods-max-and-ipad-sales.2433274/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:11:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-9-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best Apple-related deals are headlined by massive discounts across the M2 and M3 MacBook Air family, with as much as &#36;249 off these computers. You'll also find great deals on AirPods Max, iPad, and iPad mini, plus savings on third-party accessories including Samsung's Smart Monitor M80D and Anker's new products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0008.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847998" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macbook-air-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961301" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;249 off M2 and M3 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/amazon-m2-m3-macbook-air-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.98</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The star deals of the week focused on both the M2 and M3 MacBook Air, with up to &#36;249 off these computers on Amazon. In regards to the newer M3 models, you can get the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;849.98, and the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;1,049.98, both of which are best-ever prices on the computer.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitor</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/samsung-monitor-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961300" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;251 off Samsung's Smart Monitor M80D</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-448/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;251 OFF</div>Samsung 32-Inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;447.90</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week also introduced a new record low price on Samsung's 32-inch Smart Monitor M80D, which is the newest version of the monitor. It's available for &#36;447.90 right now on Amazon, down from &#36;699.99.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/airpods-max-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961299" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;149 off AirPods Max</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/airpods-max-hit-399-99-amazon/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best AirPods discount this week was on the AirPods Max, which hit &#36;399.99 and is still available at this price in every color on Amazon. This is only about &#36;5 higher compared to the low price we tracked during Prime Day in July.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/anker-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961298" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Buy 2, get 15% off Anker's new Prime accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fanker-prime%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/anker-new-charging-accessories/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fanker-prime%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY 2, GET 15% OFF</div>Anker Prime Launch Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker introduced a new lineup of "Prime" accessories this week, and alongside the launch there's a bundle offer on the Anker website. If you buy two of the new devices, you can get 15 percent off your order. You can find the full list of compatible products for this BOGO deal <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/anker-new-charging-accessories/">in our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ipad-mini-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961297" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;119 off iPad mini 6</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/amazon-low-prices-ipad-mini/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9LPNLG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;529.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 returned to its all-time low price of &#36;379.99 this week on Amazon. This isn't the only model on sale either, you can also get the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet and both cellular models on sale for record low prices right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ipad-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961296" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;100 off 9th gen iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/amazon-9th-10th-gen-ipads/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;105 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;224.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Earlier in the week, Amazon discounted the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th generation iPad to &#36;229.00, and this price has dropped even further as we head into the weekend. You can now get the iPad for &#36;224.00, down from &#36;329.00, making a new all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-9-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Discounts Hit Every MacBook Air Alongside AirPods Max and iPad Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-discounts-hit-every-macbook-air-alongside-airpods-max-and-ipad-sales.2433274/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps on Web Now Supports Firefox Browser</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/apple-maps-on-web-firefox-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-on-web-now-supports-firefox-browser.2433268/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:47:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/apple-maps-on-web-firefox-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		<category>Firefox</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple updated its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> on the web feature to add support for the Firefox browser this week. Firefox users on Mac, PC, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> can now <a href="https://beta.maps.apple.com/">visit Apple Maps on the web</a>, and the site works as intended.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-maps-on-web.jpg" alt="" width="2496" height="1404" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959915" /><br/>
Prior to yesterday, attempting to visit the &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; website popped up an error message that the Firefox browser was not supported. Apple's support document for its web-based Maps feature now lists Safari, Edge, Chrome, and Firefox as supported browsers on Mac and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and Edge, Chrome, and Firefox on Windows PCs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple rolled out support for &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; on the web in July, and it is available in a public beta capacity. The web interface can be used to get walking and driving directions, search for locations, find places to visit, view ratings and hours, and browse through a curated collection of Guides.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also added support for ordering food directly from the Maps app from supported restaurants, and discovering places to eat, shop, and explore in cities worldwide. Apple is working to introduce Look Around for street level location viewing in the coming months, and developers are able to link out to maps on the web in their apps.<br/>
<br/>
Google Maps has long offered a web-based mapping option, but getting directions with &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; has been limited to the Maps app on Apple devices. &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; on the web can be <a href="https://beta.maps.apple.com/">found on the Apple Maps website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Maps on the web is only available in English at the current time, but Apple will add support for additional languages in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/firefox/">Firefox</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/apple-maps-on-web-firefox-support/">Apple Maps on Web Now Supports Firefox Browser</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-on-web-now-supports-firefox-browser.2433268/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Now Lets You Generate Two Images Per Day For Free</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/chatgpt-two-images-per-day-for-free/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-now-lets-you-generate-two-images-per-day-for-free.2433264/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:15:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/chatgpt-two-images-per-day-for-free/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI on Thursday <a href="https://x.com/OpenAI/status/1821644904843636871">announced</a> that ChatGPT now allows users to create up to two images per day for free, with no subscription required. The images are generated by OpenAI's image generation model DALL-E 3.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ChatGPT-Images.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961310" /><br/>
"Just ask ChatGPT to create an image for a slide deck, personalize a card for a friend, or show you what something looks like," said OpenAI, in a post shared on X.<br/>
<br/>
Additional image generation with DALL-E 3 continues to require a ChatGPT Plus subscription, priced at &#36;20 per month.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously announced that ChatGPT will be integrated into Siri across iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia starting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/ios-18-chatgpt-later-this-year/">later this year</a>. Siri will be able to show ChatGPT answers directly in response to questions and other prompts, but the user will have to grant permission every single time they want to use ChatGPT via Siri.<br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT will also be available within Apple's system-wide Writing Tools feature, allowing users to quickly generate text and images. Apple said ChatGPT will be powered by OpenAI's latest GPT-4o model on its software platforms.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone, iPad, and Mac users will be able to use ChatGPT without creating an account, and this will presumably now include the ability to generate up to two images per day for free. ChatGPT Plus subscribers will be able to connect their accounts to access paid features on these devices, including additional image generation.<br/>
<br/>
Apple ensured that OpenAI will not store ChatGPT requests made from its devices, and it said users' IP addresses will be obscured.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/chatgpt-two-images-per-day-for-free/">ChatGPT Now Lets You Generate Two Images Per Day For Free</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-now-lets-you-generate-two-images-per-day-for-free.2433264/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Brings Adaptive Lighting to Matter Smart Lights</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/ios-18-brings-adaptive-lighting-to-matter/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-brings-adaptive-lighting-to-matter-smart-lights.2433262/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:08:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/ios-18-brings-adaptive-lighting-to-matter/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		<category>Home</category>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		<category>Matter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> expands Adaptive Lighting support to Matter-compatible smart lights, <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/8/24215517/ios-18-homekit-adaptive-lighting-matter-smart-bulbs"><em>The Verge</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/matter-iot-standard.jpg" alt="" width="1720" height="879" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840201" /><br/>
Adaptive Lighting was introduced in iOS 14, providing a way to automatically adjust the color temperature of smart lights throughout the day. The feature currently only works with HomeKit-enabled devices, but it will be extended to smart lights that are compatible with the Matter standard with &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
Matter, a smart home interoperability protocol developed collaboratively by Apple, Google, Amazon, and other smart home brands, seeks to create a unified, platform-agnostic ecosystem for smart devices. Adaptive Lighting is an exclusive feature of the Apple Home ecosystem, meaning it is not included in the Matter specification itself. <br/>
<br/>
The expansion of Adaptive Lighting to Matter devices was discovered in the latest beta version of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;. Users running the beta reported seeing a new toggle for Adaptive Lighting in the settings of their Matter-compatible smart lights within the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
Confirmation of the feature's development also came from Nanoleaf, whose CEO Gimmy Chu stated that the company is "one of the partners that are part of the launch of Adaptive Lighting on Matter products." It is highly likely that other major smart lighting brands, such as Philips Hue, will also support the feature in due course.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the expanded support for Adaptive Lighting, &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; brings a range of other smart home enhancements to the Home app such as improved guest access controls, support for robotic vacuum cleaners like the iRobot Roomba, and hands-free unlocking of smart doors. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home/">Home</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/matter/">Matter</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/ios-18-brings-adaptive-lighting-to-matter/">iOS 18 Brings Adaptive Lighting to Matter Smart Lights</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-brings-adaptive-lighting-to-matter-smart-lights.2433262/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Foxconn Hires 50,000 More Workers as Apple Boosts iPhone 16 Production</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/foxconn-hires-50000-more-workers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foxconn-hires-50-000-more-workers-as-apple-boosts-iphone-16-production.2433258/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:24:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/foxconn-hires-50000-more-workers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Foxconn</category>
		<category>BusinessKorea</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has ramped up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> production in expectation of high demand, leading Foxconn to hire 50,000 new workers in just two weeks, <em><a href="https://www.businesskorea.co.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=222752">BusinessKorea</a></em> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
Apple apparently decided to boost production by 10% this year, aiming for a total output of 90 million &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, in expectation of strong sales. The company has intensified production efforts with its primary manufacturing partner, Foxconn, in Zhengzhou, China. The factory, known as the world's largest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> production base, is now operating at full capacity, having brought in 50,000 additional workers within the last two weeks. <br/>
<br/>
Foxconn's Zhengzhou facility is central to Apple's global supply chain, responsible for approximately 80% of the company's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; production. As the peak season for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; production typically begins in August and extends through December, Foxconn's recruitment drive is crucial in meeting the increased output required during this period. Local media outlets have reported that Foxconn has significantly raised wages and bonuses to attract the necessary labor force. In late July, the company advertised an increased hourly wage of up to 25 yuan and raised the hiring bonus from 6,000 yuan to 7,500 yuan as of August.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also reportedly planning to produce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-to-manufacture-pro-iphone-models-in-india/">larger variety of iPhone models in India</a> starting with the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup. The new devices are expected to launch next month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foxconn/">Foxconn</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/businesskorea-co-kr/">BusinessKorea</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/foxconn-hires-50000-more-workers/">Foxconn Hires 50,000 More Workers as Apple Boosts iPhone 16 Production</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foxconn-hires-50-000-more-workers-as-apple-boosts-iphone-16-production.2433258/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 vs. iOS 18.1: New Features, Release Timing, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1-new-features-release-timing-and-more.2433249/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 06:30:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As a result of the first Apple Intelligence features being delayed, iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 are currently in beta testing simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Below, we explain the differences between the two upcoming software updates, including new features and estimated release timing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
<h3>iOS 18.0</h3><br/>
iOS 18 introduces new customization options for the Home Screen and Control Center, a redesigned Photos app, numerous enhancements to the Messages app, an option to lock apps behind Face ID or Touch ID, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Home-Screen.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954462" /><br/>
The highlight of iOS 18 is Apple Intelligence, but the rollout of these artificial intelligence features was pushed back to iOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
On the other hand, the fifth developer beta of iOS 18 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/ios-18-beta-5-features/">includes some changes</a> that are not yet available in the first iOS 18.1 developer beta, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/safari-distraction-control-hands-on/">new Distraction Control tool in Safari</a> for erasing distracting elements from a web page. That feature and the other changes should be added to later iOS 18.1 beta versions.<br/>
<br/>
Read our in-depth <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a> to learn more about the update.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iOS 18.1</h3><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">first Apple Intelligence features are now available to test</a> in the iOS 18.1 developer beta, which is only available for the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max currently. The features available to try so far include new writing tools, suggested replies in the Messages app, email summarization, phone call recording, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
Apple Intelligence features that are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">not yet available</a> to try include Image Playground for custom-generated images, Genmoji for custom-generated emoji, and several enhancements to Siri, including ChatGPT integration, richer language understanding, deeper per-app controls, on-screen awareness, personalized context, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Release Timing</h2><br/>
<h3>iOS 18.0</h3><br/>
iOS 18 will likely be released in mid-September, based on the timing of previous major releases:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iOS 17: September 18, 2023</li><br/>
<li>iOS 16: September 12, 2022</li><br/>
<li>iOS 15: September 20, 2021</li><br/>
<li>iOS 14: September 16, 2020</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>iOS 18.1</h3><br/>
iOS 18.1 will likely be released in late October, based on the timing of previous similar updates:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iOS 17.1: October 25, 2023</li><br/>
<li>iOS 16.1: October 24, 2022</li><br/>
<li>iOS 15.1: October 25, 2021</li><br/>
<li>iOS 14.1: October 20, 2020</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Latest Versions</h2><br/>
As of August 9, the latest iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 betas are as follows:<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-5-to-developers/">iOS 18 Developer Beta 5</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-ios-18-public-beta-3/">iOS 18 Public Beta 3</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">iOS 18.1 Developer Beta 1</a></li><br/>
<li>iOS 18.1 Public Beta not currently available</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Install Betas</h2><br/>
<h3>Developer Betas</h3><br/>
iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 are both available as developer betas.<br/>
<br/>
To enroll in Apple's developer beta program, visit <a href="https://developer.apple.com/">developer.apple.com</a>, sign in to your Apple ID, and accept the terms and conditions of the Apple Developer Agreement.<br/>
<br/>
Since 2023, installing iOS developer betas no longer requires being enrolled in the Apple Developer Program for &#36;99/year. Anyone with an Apple ID can accept the Apple Developer Agreement and access the betas for free.<br/>
<br/>
After accepting the agreement, open the Settings app on your iPhone and tap General  Software Update  Beta Updates. This is where the iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 developer betas are listed, and you can tap on one to begin the installation process. Note that the iPhone must be signed in to the same Apple ID set up as a developer account.<br/>
<br/>
Due to software bugs and other potential issues, we recommend installing the iOS 18 or iOS 18.1 betas on a secondary iPhone, rather than the device that you use daily. We also highly recommend <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/iphone/iph3ecf67d29/ios">backing up your iPhone to your Mac</a> before installing beta software on the device, to prevent data loss in the event something goes wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Step-by-step guide:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-18-developer-beta-iphone/">How to Get the iOS 18 Developer Beta on Your iPhone</a><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Public Betas</h3><br/>
iOS 18 is available as a public beta, but iOS 18.1 is not currently.<br/>
<br/>
To enroll in Apple's free public beta program, visit <a href="https://beta.apple.com/">beta.apple.com</a>, sign in to your Apple ID, and accept the terms and conditions. <br/>
<br/>
After signing up, open the Settings app on your iPhone and tap General  Software Update  Beta Updates. This is where the iOS 18 public beta is listed, and you can tap on it to begin the installation process. Note that the iPhone must be signed in to the same Apple ID enrolled in the public beta program.<br/>
<br/>
Due to software bugs and other potential issues, we recommend installing the iOS 18 public beta on a secondary iPhone, rather than the device that you use daily. We also highly recommend <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/iphone/iph3ecf67d29/ios">backing up your iPhone to your Mac</a> before installing beta software on the device, to prevent data loss in the event something goes wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Step-by-step guide:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">How to Install the iOS 18 Public Beta</a><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatible iPhones</h2><br/>
iOS 18 is compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17 is:<ul><div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max </li><br/>
</div></ul><div style="float: right; width: 50%;"><ul><li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XR </li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (2nd generation or later) </li></ul></div><div style="clear:both;"></div>While the iOS 18.1 beta is currently limited to the iPhone 15 Pro models, the update should be released for all of the iPhones listed above eventually. However, Apple Intelligence features will remain exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro models and newer.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1/">iOS 18 vs. iOS 18.1: New Features, Release Timing, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1-new-features-release-timing-and-more.2433249/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>When to Expect New M4 MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-new-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-and-mac-pro-models.2433246/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 05:15:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac Studio</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac Pro</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple intends to update its entire Mac lineup to the M4 processor over the next 12 months, which will make it the first time that Apple has used the same chip generation across all of its Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/M4-Real-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950312" /><br/>
Apple will update its MacBook Pro, Mac mini, and iMac lines with its latest M4 chip as early as this year, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-08/mac-mini-m4-apple-plans-to-release-smallest-desktop-computer-yet"><em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman</a>, with the Mac mini also set to feature its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">first redesign since 2010</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Following the launch of the M4 iPad Pro in May, Apple will continue the M4 transition with the above mentioned Macs, and complete it with updates for the MacBook Air, Mac Pro, and Mac Studio in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman's sources tell him there are MacBook Airs in development for the spring, and Mac Pro and Mac Studio models are planned for the middle of next year. <br/>
<ul><li>M4 MacBook Air  Spring 2025</li><br/>
<li>M4 Mac Pro  Summer 2025</li><br/>
<li>M4 Mac Studio  Summer 2025</li></ul>Like it did with the iPad Pro, Apple appears to be skipping straight to the M4 chip for the Mac Studio and Mac Pro, meaning these models will not see an M3 chip update at all. <br/>
<br/>
Like the M3, the M4 is built on a 3nm process, but with enhancements from Apple supplier TSMC for improved performance and power efficiency. The M4 also includes an improved Neural Engine that fuels accelerated AI workloads. Apple says it is the company's most powerful Neural Engine ever, capable of 38 trillion operations per second.<br/>
<br/>
The Mac Studio is likely to be equipped with a variation of the M4 processor, which could be an M4 Ultra or Max chip. The current Mac Studio comes in both M2 Max and M2 Ultra variants.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the Mac Pro will feature the top-tier M4 chip, codenamed "Hidra," which could be marketed as an "Ultra" or "Extreme" variant. Apple is developing this more powerful chip in response to criticism that the M2 Ultra wasn't sufficient for a high-end machine. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has said the ultra-thin M4 iPad Pro serves as a model for its upcoming design philosophy, with the company planning to offer "the thinnest and lightest products" in each category across the tech industry. Aside from the Mac mini, we don't know when each model will get the ultra-thin treatment, but Gurman has previously reported that Apple is already working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/">thinner version of the MacBook Pro</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac-Studio">Mac Studio (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Pro">Mac Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-studio.237">Mac Studio</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-pro.1">Mac Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/">When to Expect New M4 MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-new-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-and-mac-pro-models.2433246/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Using the New &#039;Search Here&#039; Feature in Apple Maps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-search-here-feature-apple-maps-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-using-the-new-search-here-feature-in-apple-maps.2433243/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 04:03:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-search-here-feature-apple-maps-ios&#038;post_date=1723212182/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, Apple Maps has gained a new "Search here" button that makes it much easier to find what you're looking for in areas that aren't your current location or when you're exploring any new place on the map.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-maps-search-here-ios-18-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-961326" /><br/>
In earlier versions of iOS, if you search nearby for, say, gas stations or restaurants in Apple Maps, and then drag the map to another location with your finger, it will usually (but not always) auto-populate the new area with search results for the same request.<br/>
<br/>
That behavior hasn't changed in iOS 18, but what you now get in addition is a "Search here" button that gives you more manual fine-grained control of the area in which to search. This is especially useful if you adjust the zoom level of the map, or scroll away only slightly from the original search  two instances where auto-populating results can be spotty or sometimes not appear at all.<br/>
<br/>
Google Maps has had this feature for years, so it's good to see that Apple Maps has finally adopted it. iOS 18 also adds other improvements to Apple Maps, including topographic maps complete with trail networks and hikes (a feature that Apple first brought to the Apple Watch last year), as well as options to save favorite trails, download them for offline use, add notes, and get information like elevation and length.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-apple-maps-search-here.jpg" alt="maps" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961168" /><br/>
iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">currently in public beta</a> and will be officially released in the fall, around mid-September, when the iPhone 16 series is launched.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-search-here-feature-apple-maps-ios/">iOS 18: Using the New &#039;Search Here&#039; Feature in Apple Maps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-using-the-new-search-here-feature-in-apple-maps.2433243/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games and Spotify Say Apple&#039;s Latest DMA Changes Are &#039;Illegal&#039; and &#039;Deliberately Confusing&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/epic-games-spotify-apple-dma-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-and-spotify-say-apples-latest-dma-changes-are-illegal-and-deliberately-confusing.2433232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:58:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/epic-games-spotify-apple-dma-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/app-store-external-links-european-union/">updated its Digital Markets Act</a> compliance plan in the European Union today, making changes related to external linking. Developers are now free to direct users to non-App Store purchase options for in-app content such as subscriptions, with no restrictions or control over the messaging to customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801789" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/Apple-vs-Spotify-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple made the update to comply with the European Commission's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">objection to its anti-steering rules</a>, but there is a new fee structure that's complicated and not easy to digest. Shortly after Apple announced its new terms, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> CEO Tim Sweeney took to social media to call Apple's commission "an illegal new 15% junk fee." He went on to say that the terms make it "completely uneconomical for developers to distribute their apps through both the Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and competing iOS app stores."<br/>
<br/>
Sweeney has been outspoken about Apple's Digital Markets Act changes since the first updates were introduced in February, and he has long accused Apple of malicious compliance.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">In the European Union where the new DMA law opens up app store competition, Apple continues its malicious compliance by imposing an illegal new 15% junk fee on users migrating to competing stores and monitor commerce on these competing stores.<a href="https://t.co/YUYwsnrh32">https://t.co/YUYwsnrh32</a> <a href="https://t.co/xAWGkOWPrH">pic.twitter.com/xAWGkOWPrH</a></p>&mdash; Tim Sweeney (@TimSweeneyEpic) <a href="https://twitter.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1821594291602649143?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 8, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Spotify likewise didn't have anything nice to say about the updated link rules. In a statement to <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/spotify-and-epic-games-call-apples-revised-dma-compliance-plan-confusing-illegal-and-unacceptable/">TechCrunch</a></em>, Spotify said the revisions are "deliberately confusing," but "at first glance," Apple is continuing to "blatantly disregard" the requirements of the DMA.<br/>
<blockquote>We are currently assessing Apple's deliberately confusing proposal. At first glance, by demanding as much as a 25% fee for basic communication with users, Apple once again blatantly disregards the fundamental requirements of the Digital Markets Act (DMA). The European Commission has made it clear that imposing recurring fees on basic elements like pricing and linking is unacceptable. We call on the Commission to expedite its investigation, implement daily fines and enforce the DMA.</blockquote><br/>
According to Apple, the new initial acquisition fee that developers who use links have to pay reflects the value that the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; provides when connecting developers to customers in the EU. The second store services fee reflects the ongoing services and capabilities that Apple provides developers, such as app distribution, &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; trust and safety, promotional tools, anti-fraud checks, and more.<br/>
<br/>
EU developers who choose to use links to direct customers to purchase options outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will pay between 10 percent and 27 percent commission, depending on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; terms they've agreed to and whether they belong to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Small Business Program. Developers operating under the new DMA business terms that support alternative payment methods and distributing apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; must also pay the Core Technology Fee in addition to the store services fee and the initial acquisition fee.<br/>
<br/>
The 10 to 27 percent commission for developers that adopt linking out is under the 15 to 30 percent commission that was required prior to any of the DMA changes, but &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; and Spotify do not feel that Apple's fees are fair. As &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; and Spotify are major companies, they would need to pay the 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee to Apple, which would cost tens of thousands per month.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/apple-approves-epic-games-store-eu/">bring an Epic Games Store</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in the European Union, and Sweeney today said that the plan is still on track. The store is set to launch<br/>
"soon," and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; will charge developers 12 percent for payments that it processes and 0 percent for third-party payments.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, the European Commission <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-fights-2-billion-eu-fine-spotify/">fined Apple &#36;1.95 billion</a> for not allowing streaming music apps like Spotify to tell users about cheaper subscription prices outside of the app. Apple in response created a Music Streaming Services Entitlement that would require Spotify to pay a 27 percent commission on website purchases made through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. The fee for the new Link Entitlement is the same for an app of Spotify's size.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/epic-games-spotify-apple-dma-changes/">Epic Games and Spotify Say Apple&#039;s Latest DMA Changes Are &#039;Illegal&#039; and &#039;Deliberately Confusing&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-and-spotify-say-apples-latest-dma-changes-are-illegal-and-deliberately-confusing.2433232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nanoleaf Launches EXPO Smart LED Display Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/nanoleaf-smart-led-display-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-expo-smart-led-display-cases.2433227/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:17:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/nanoleaf-smart-led-display-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Smart lighting company <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/">Nanoleaf</a> today announced the launch of the EXPO Smart LED Display Case, a new product that it is debuting in partnership with design studio Fantaqi.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nanoleaf-display-case-1.jpg" alt="" width="1456" height="816" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961155" /><br/>
The EXPO has built-in multi-color lighting that highlights sneakers, figurines, or other collectibles. Each EXPO Case is made from ABS resin, and the cases are modular, so you can use several together with unique lighting scenes. Display cases can be set up in any arrangement, and up to 300 can be connected together.<br/>
<br/>
Nanoleaf designed the EXPO with full-coverage lighting that is diffused across the ceiling of each case for uniform illumination that showcases the user's favorite items. A magnetic sensing door provides subtle lighting effects when the display lid is opened and closed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nanoleaf-display-case-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961156" /><br/>
Using the Nanoleaf app. The LEDs in the EXPO Cases can be set to animated colorways through multiple curated scenes like Hypno Beat and Flames. As with other Nanoleaf devices, the EXPO Cases support community created scenes and allow for custom user designed scenes. The EXPO Case layout is reflected in the Nanoleaf app for optimum display of lighting scenes across each custom layout.<br/>
<br/>
Other supported features include the Rhythm music visualizer for timing light animations to the beat of music, Desktop Screen Mirror, and AI Magic Scenes for creating a scene based on a word or phrase. The EXPO Cases can also be controlled via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> integration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nanoleaf-display-case-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961157" /><br/>
The Nanoleaf x Fantaqi EXPO Display Cases can be <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/">purchased from the Nanoleaf website</a> as of today. A Smarter Kit with four cases is available for &#36;299.99, and a one case expansion pack is available for &#36;79.99.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/nanoleaf-smart-led-display-case/">Nanoleaf Launches EXPO Smart LED Display Cases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-expo-smart-led-display-cases.2433227/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Now Allows Up to 20 Photos and Videos for Carousel Posts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/instagram-20-photos-carousel-posts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-now-allows-up-to-20-photos-and-videos-for-carousel-posts.2433221/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:51:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/instagram-20-photos-carousel-posts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram today expanded the number of photos and videos that can be added to a single carousel post, reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/8/24216111/instagram-carousel-post-expansion">The Verge</a></em>. Standard grid posts have long been limited to a total of 10 images and videos, but the limit has now doubled.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Instagram-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786417" /><br/>
On Instagram, carousel posts allow users to "photo dump" multiple photos and videos at one time, and a user's followers can use swipe gestures to view all of them. Multi-image posts show up on a user's page and in the Instagram feed.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram rival TikTok supports posts with up to 35 photos, so the new limit brings Instagram closer to the TikTok's image options. Instagram has been testing higher image limits since earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
Support for more images in a single post is rolling out for users around the world as of today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/instagram-20-photos-carousel-posts/">Instagram Now Allows Up to 20 Photos and Videos for Carousel Posts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-now-allows-up-to-20-photos-and-videos-for-carousel-posts.2433221/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung&#039;s New 32-Inch Smart Monitor M8 Drops to &#36;448 on Amazon (&#36;251 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-448/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-new-32-inch-smart-monitor-m8-drops-to-448-on-amazon-251-off.2433211/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:25:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-448/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung's newest 32-inch Smart Monitor M80D is being discounted to a new record low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;448.08</strong></a>, down from &#36;699.99. This sale is only available in the Warm White color, and it can be delivered as soon as August 10.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-smart-monitor-m80d-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958530" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This new deal beats the previous record low by about &#36;50, and right now it's only available on Amazon. This version of the monitor launched back in June, and it retains many features of the previous model like USB-C charging connectivity, AirPlay 2 support, an integrated webcam, and several smart TV features that enable it to be used when not connected to a PC.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;251 OFF</div>Samsung 32-Inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;448.08</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In terms of new features, the M80D includes a Multi Control feature that allows images and text to be moved between the display and a Galaxy Book, Tablet, or Phone. You can also pair Galaxy Buds to the monitor for a spatial audio experience with head tracking, as well as guided workouts when paired with a Galaxy Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-448/">Samsung&#039;s New 32-Inch Smart Monitor M8 Drops to &#36;448 on Amazon (&#36;251 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-new-32-inch-smart-monitor-m8-drops-to-448-on-amazon-251-off.2433211/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Loosens App Store External Linking Rules and Changes Fee Structure in European Union</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/app-store-external-links-european-union/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-loosens-app-store-external-linking-rules-and-changes-fee-structure-in-european-union.2433208/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:00:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/app-store-external-links-european-union/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="http://developer.apple.com/news">is today announcing</a> some updates to its Digital Markets Act compliance plan in the European Union, with changes to external linking that give developers more freedom to direct customers to non-App Store purchase options and sales.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
EU developers that are operating under the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> business terms or the prior &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; purchase terms can update their apps to communicate and promote offers for purchases available through websites, alternative app marketplaces, other apps, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Links to external sources can direct customers outside of the app or to a website with a web view that is available directly in the app. Apple is not directing the design of communications provided to customers, nor is the company dictating what developers are able to say.<br/>
<br/>
Developers can provide information about lower prices outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, more affordable subscriptions, or any offer available in or outside the app. External links and offer pages can include explanations and instructions about how customers can subscribe to offers outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; app, though Apple says that communications have to provide accurate information on the digital goods or services available for purchase.<br/>
<br/>
Links can be tapped, clicked, or scanned to take users to their destination, and developers have no restrictions on the number of URLs they include. Links with additional parameters, redirects, and intermediate links are allowed, but not for ad tracking purposes.<br/>
<br/>
Developers do not have to opt in to the new terms with the Core Technology Fee to take advantage of these link entitlement changes, but must agree to the StoreKit External Purchase Link Entitlement Addendum, which is coming this fall. These terms require developers to use the StoreKit External Purchase APIs, report external purchase transactions, and pay fees and commissions.<br/>
<br/>
There are two fees that are associated with directing customers to purchase options outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. A 5 percent initial acquisition fee is paid for all sales of digital goods and services that the customer makes on any platform that occur within a 12-month period after an initial install. The fee does not apply to transactions made by customers that had an initial install before the new link changes, but is applicable for new downloads.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the initial acquisition fee reflects the value that the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; provides when connecting developers with customers in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
The store services fee, which is in addition to the initial acquisition fee, is a commission that developers pay Apple on all sales of digital goods and services that the customer makes on any platform that occur within a fixed 12-month period from the date of an install, including app updates and reinstalls.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the store services fee reflects the ongoing services and capabilities that Apple provides developers, including app distribution and management, &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; trust and safety, re-discovery, re-engagement and promotional tools and services, anti-fraud checks, recommendations, and ratings and reviews.<br/>
<br/>
While the initial acquisition fee is the same for both developers that use the link entitlement under the new business terms and those that use link entitlements under the current terms, the store services fee varies. For the new business terms, the base fee is 10 percent, but it drops to 5 percent for &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Small Business Program participants and auto-renewal subscriptions after one year. These fees are in addition to the Core Technology Fee of 0.50 euros per first annual install over one million first annual installs.<br/>
<br/>
For developers who stick with the standard Apple Developer Program License Agreement, the standard store services fee is 20 percent, but it drops to 7 percent for &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Small Business Program participants and auto-renewal subscriptions after one year. The standard &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; terms do not require a Core Technology Fee. Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/fee-calculator-for-apps-in-the-eu/">has a fee calculator</a> that can help EU developers figure out what they'll need to pay.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>New business terms</strong> - Includes using alternative payment methods in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; or distributing outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; - 5% initial acquisition fee and 5% to 10% store services fee depending on app size, plus Core Technology Fee. Total is 10% to 15% commission, along with the CTF, though Apple estimates that 99% of developers will not be eligible to pay the CTF. There is also a payment processing fee of 3% when using the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s payment options.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Standard business terms</strong> - 5% initial acquisition fee and 7% to 20% store services fee depending on app size. Total is 12% to 27% commission.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There is one other notable change that Apple is making, and that's giving customers an option to turn off in-app disclosure sheets. By default, Apple will still warn users when they are clicking a link that takes them to non-Apple purchase methods and options, but customers can choose to turn off these warnings when an app links to an external channel. An app that links to an in-app web view will only need to display the disclosure sheet once per session.<br/>
<br/>
More information about these changes can be found on <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/">Apple's developer website</a> and in the specific <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/alternative-payment-options-on-the-app-store-in-the-eu/#whats-new">Digital Markets Act page</a> that Apple updates regularly.<br/>
<br/>
EU developers can begin planning external linking options for their apps now, and customers will have access to these changes with the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, tvOS 18, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> this fall.<br/>
<br/>
As with all of the updates that Apple has made to comply with the Digital Markets Act, these changes are only applicable in the European Union. There are no &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes in other countries.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/app-store-external-links-european-union/">Apple Loosens App Store External Linking Rules and Changes Fee Structure in European Union</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-loosens-app-store-external-linking-rules-and-changes-fee-structure-in-european-union.2433208/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M4 Mac Mini to Become Apple&#039;s Smallest Ever Computer With Complete Redesign</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-mac-mini-to-become-apples-smallest-ever-computer-with-complete-redesign.2433207/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:29:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>M4 Mac mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to debut completely redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> models with the M4 and M4 Pro chips later this year, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-08/mac-mini-m4-apple-plans-to-release-smallest-desktop-computer-yet"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Black-Ortho-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-961271" /><br/>
The new &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be the first major design change to the machine since 2010, making it Apple's smallest ever desktop computer. The new &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will apparently approach the size of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, but it may be slightly taller than the current model, which is 1.4 inches high. It will continue to feature an aluminum shell. Individuals working on the new device apparently say that it is "essentially an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> in a small box."<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to have tested &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models with at least three USB-C ports on the back, as well as an area for the power cable and an HDMI port. There will continue to be two versions of the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;: one with the standard M4 chip, similar to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, and one with an M4 Pro chip. The base model is set to begin shipping from suppliers this month ahead of release later in the year, while the high-end model will not be ready until October.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 generation of Apple silicon will purportedly be the first time that Apple has used the same chip generation across all of its Macs, with refreshes to add the M4 chip to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, MacBook Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> planned to take place over the next year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/">M4 Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">M4 Mac Mini to Become Apple&#039;s Smallest Ever Computer With Complete Redesign</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-mac-mini-to-become-apples-smallest-ever-computer-with-complete-redesign.2433207/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Delays Launch of Arc Soundbar Successor to Focus on Fixing App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delays-product-launces-to-fix-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-delays-launch-of-arc-soundbar-successor-to-focus-on-fixing-app.2433204/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 07:46:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delays-product-launces-to-fix-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos will delay two major product releases that were originally planned later this year in order to focus on improving the quality of its app, according to the company's CEO.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
Speaking on his <a href="https://s22.q4cdn.com/672173472/files/doc_financials/2024/q3/FINAL-SONO-3Q24-Earnings-Transcript-docx.pdf">third quarter earnings call</a>, Sonos chief Patrick Spence told investors that it was "deeply disappointing for me personally" for the company to be on track for the first three quarters of the year, only to revise its expectations for the fourth quarter due to "challenges with our new app."<br/>
<br/>
Sonos in May released its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">redesigned app</a> with customizable home screen and a more personalized listening service, but Sonos customers quickly found that the app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/sonos-said-rolling-out-widely-criticized-app-redesign-took-courage/">lacked several key features</a>, and suffered from multiple bugs. Complaints across social media called the app a "step back" for removing playlist management, alarms, and other features.<br/>
<br/>
As a result of the app problems, the Sonos chief said two major product releases  one of which was likely to be the successor to Sonos' flagship Arc soundbar, according to <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/7/24215589/sonos-q3-2024-earnings-ace-headphone-buggy-app">The Verge</a></em>  would now be delayed to focus on improving the company's software.<br/>
<br/>
Spence told investors:<br/>
<blockquote>"The app situation has become a headwind to existing product sales, and we believe our focus needs to be addressing the app ahead of everything else," said Spence. "This means delaying the two major new product releases we had planned for Q4 until our app experience meets the level of quality that we, our customers and our partners expect from Sonos. While this has the painful effect of reducing our Q4 sales expectations, we believe it will set our future products up for greater success over the medium to long term."</blockquote>Spence reiterated an outline of future feature plans that he previously laid out in an <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/blog/update-on-the-sonos-app">apology to users last month</a>, with Sonos planning to push updates on a bi-weekly basis. Among the scheduled plans, alarms are set to be addressed in September, while edit mode for playlists and a queue will come in September or October.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/hands-on-sonos-ace-headphones/">Hands-On With the New Sonos 'Ace' Headphones</a></li></ul><br/>
Spence said that Sonos is working hard to earn back customer trust through the continual app improvements. "I want to reiterate again that the entire team and I are committed to making this right with our customers and partners," he added. "It's my #1 focus, and I will not rest until we're in a position where we've addressed these issues and have customers raving about Sonos again."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delays-product-launces-to-fix-app/">Sonos Delays Launch of Arc Soundbar Successor to Focus on Fixing App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-delays-launch-of-arc-soundbar-successor-to-focus-on-fixing-app.2433204/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Big Discounts Across Entire M2/M3 MacBook Air Lineup With Up to &#36;250 Off</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/amazon-m2-m3-macbook-air-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-discounts-across-entire-m2-m3-macbook-air-lineup-with-up-to-250-off.2433199/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 07:11:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/amazon-m2-m3-macbook-air-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week has a massive sale <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">across the MacBook Air lineup</a>, including both the M2 and M3 MacBook Air models. We tracked many of these deals from Best Buy last week, but Amazon's sales this week don't require any exclusive membership, and in some cases they're even beating the low prices from last week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macbook-air-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-961113" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the M2 MacBook Air, Amazon is offering up to &#36;254 off these models, including a new all-time low price on the 512GB model. Prices start at &#36;799.00 for the 256GB M2 MacBook Air in all colors, and increase to &#36;944.16 for the 512GB MacBook Air in Midnight.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;254 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;944.16</div></a></div><h2>13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/15-inch-m3-macbook-air.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947373" /><br/>
<br/>
For the newer models, Amazon is taking &#36;249 off the 13-inch M3 MacBook Air with multiple all-time low prices. You can get the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;849.98 in every color, down from &#36;1,099.00. Both 512GB models are on sale as well with best-ever prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,049.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BNQC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.98</div></a></div><h2>15-Inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Finally, Amazon also has the 15-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;249-&#36;250 off every model. These start at &#36;1,049.98 for the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air, down from &#36;1,299.00, and again include both 512GB models. Overall, every 15-inch M3 MacBook Air deal from Amazon this week represents new all-time low prices on each model, beating the deals we saw just last week by about &#36;50.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/amazon-m2-m3-macbook-air-discounts/">Amazon Introduces Big Discounts Across Entire M2/M3 MacBook Air Lineup With Up to &#36;250 Off</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-discounts-across-entire-m2-m3-macbook-air-lineup-with-up-to-250-off.2433199/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Future Lynk &amp; Co Vehicles Likely to Support Apple Car Keys</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/future-lynk-and-co-model-apple-car-keys/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/future-lynk-co-vehicles-likely-to-support-apple-car-keys.2433194/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 06:17:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/future-lynk-and-co-model-apple-car-keys/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Car Keys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/carkey/">Car Keys</a> feature appears to be coming to future Lynk & Co models, based on code changes discovered by <em>MacRumors</em> in Apple's Wallet app backend.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Lynk-Co-Logo.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961105" /><br/>
&zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; allows an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or Apple Watch with NFC capabilities to unlock a vehicle through the Wallet app. A digital version of a car key is stored in Wallet, and unlocking can be done simply by holding an Apple Watch or &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; near a compatible vehicle's NFC reader.<br/>
<br/>
2021 - 2024 Lynk & Co 01 vehicles already support Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>. However, cars do not have NFC functionality by default, so this is a feature that would need to be implemented by the automobile manufacturer in future models. <br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.arenaev.com/europebound_lynk___co_z20_spotted_for_the_first_time-news-3744.php">Z20</a> is believed to be Lynk & Co's next car launch  and the company's first electric vehicle  so support for &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; could well be introduced with this model, which is expected to launch in various European markets.<br/>
<br/>
What can be done with &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; may vary by car manufacturer, but at a minimum, &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; can be used to unlock your car, lock your car, and start your car, which are the features available with a physical key. <br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; in 2022, and car manufacturers like BMW, Rivian, Kia, and Hyundai have all implemented support for &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj;. Apple maintains a full list of vehicles that support &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; on its <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/carplay/available-models/">CarPlay model availability webpage</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/carkey/">Car Keys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/future-lynk-and-co-model-apple-car-keys/">Future Lynk &amp; Co Vehicles Likely to Support Apple Car Keys</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/future-lynk-co-vehicles-likely-to-support-apple-car-keys.2433194/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
