<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 16:09:52 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music and iTunes Store Experiencing Outage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-music-itunes-store-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-and-itunes-store-experiencing-outage.2420590/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 16:04:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-music-itunes-store-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and the iTunes Store are experiencing issues, according to Apple's System Status page. &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; may be slow or unavailable for some users.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-813608" /><br/>
As for iTunes, some users are running into problems, and Apple is investigating as of right now. <br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, these issues began at 6:49 p.m. Eastern Time. There is no word yet on when service will resume functioning as normal. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-music-itunes-store-outage/">Apple Music and iTunes Store Experiencing Outage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-and-itunes-store-experiencing-outage.2420590/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Confirms iOS 17.4 Lets Video Calling Apps Turn Off Reactions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-confirms-ios-17-4-reactions-change/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-ios-17-4-lets-video-calling-apps-turn-off-reactions.2420585/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 14:48:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-confirms-ios-17-4-reactions-change/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today publicly confirmed that iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 allow developers of video calling apps to turn off the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-reaction-effects-facetime/">Reactions feature</a> by default in their apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/ios-17-facetime-effects.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1070" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900390" /><br/>
As we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/apple-api-for-turning-off-3d-gesture-effects/">reported earlier this month</a>, developers can control the default behavior of Reactions in their apps with a new API for iOS 17.4, iPadOS 17.4, and likely macOS 14.4. The updates are expected to be released to the public in March.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/ios-ipados-release-notes/ios-ipados-17_4-release-notes">developer notes</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-release-candidate/">iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Release Candidates</a>:<blockquote>Developers can control the default behavior of Reactions with the key […] This is controlled per application and user choice will override application declared defaults.</blockquote>For example, video conferencing app Zoom could use Apple's new API to turn off the Reactions feature in its app by default. iPhone and iPad users who manually turn Reactions back on in Control Center would still be able to use the feature in the app. <br/>
<br/>
Reactions remain turned on by default on iOS 17.4 overall, so they still work in FaceTime and in apps that do not use the API without any further steps required.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Reactions</h2><br/>
Starting with iOS 17, iPadOS 17, and macOS Sonoma, you can make hand gestures during video calls in the FaceTime app and other video conferencing apps to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-reaction-effects-facetime/">fill the screen with 3D effects</a>. For example, you can hold two thumbs up to show fireworks on the screen, or make two peace signs with your hands to show confetti.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, many users are unaware that this new feature is turned on by default, which has led to some awkward and embarrassing moments during important video calls, such as online therapy sessions and business meetings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-media-max-width="560"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Fetterman released the confetti on Zoom on MSNBC <a href="https://t.co/fpylDiU1uc">pic.twitter.com/fpylDiU1uc</a></p>&mdash; Andy Kaczynski (@KFILE) <a href="https://twitter.com/KFILE/status/1761108102575710607?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 23, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Instead of turning off Reactions by default altogether, Apple is allowing developers to control the feature on a per-app basis with this new API.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a> assisted with this story.</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-confirms-ios-17-4-reactions-change/">Apple Confirms iOS 17.4 Lets Video Calling Apps Turn Off Reactions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-ios-17-4-lets-video-calling-apps-turn-off-reactions.2420585/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Spring Apple Watch Band Colors Coming Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-watch-bands-spring-colors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-spring-apple-watch-band-colors-coming-soon.2420576/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:53:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-watch-bands-spring-colors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple often refreshes Apple Watch band colors on a seasonal basis, and code in iOS 17.4 suggests that new spring colors will be coming soon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-watch-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928995" /><br/>
As found by <a href="https://twitter.com/SteveMoser"><em>MacRumors</em> contributor Steve Moser</a>, the spring colors include Light Blue, Ocean Blue, Pink, Raspberry, Soft Mint, and Sunshine (likely a light yellow). There are also two Hermes colors, Bleu Céleste and Jaune de Naples.<br/>
<br/>
When released, these colors will be available for watch faces that support different color options, and they'll be listed in a Spring 2024 section in the Apple Watch app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. Right now, the colors are not showing up there.<br/>
<br/>
Apple often also uses these same colors for new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; cases and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> cases. If we get a spring event this year around the end of March, we can expect to see these band options and possibly new cases that offer the same colors.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-watch-bands-spring-colors/">New Spring Apple Watch Band Colors Coming Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-spring-apple-watch-band-colors-coming-soon.2420576/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working on Beats Solo 4 Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-working-on-beats-solo-4-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-on-beats-solo-4-headphones.2420574/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:23:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-working-on-beats-solo-4-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on an updated version of its popular Beats Solo on-ear headphones, according to code located in the iOS 17.4 release candidate that Apple put out today. <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris found several references to the Beats Solo 4 headphones, including images. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/new-beats-solo-4.jpg" alt="" width="1129" height="635" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938522" /><br/>
The Beats Solo 4 look similar to the Solo 3 headphones, but have design tweaks that bring them in line with the Beats Studio Pro. Spatial Audio is supported according to the code, but we don't know what other features to expect at this time. <br/>
<br/>
There are three colors in the files, including black, pink, and blue. We can expect some of the changes that were brought to the Beats Studio Pro last year, such as improved sound quality and support for Personalized Spatial Audio. The headphones will support the same gestures as the Studio Pro, with a press on the "b" button to play/pause and answer calls, a double press to skip songs, and a long press to activate <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. Apple will also likely swap the old micro-USB port for a new USB-C port to bring the headphones in line with the rest of its products. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here are some videos of the new Beats Solo 4 <a href="https://t.co/I9MwTDUUaR">https://t.co/I9MwTDUUaR</a> <a href="https://t.co/nx8wdP23At">pic.twitter.com/nx8wdP23At</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1762559410654822768?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 27, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple first released the Solo 3 headphones way back in 2016, and while there have been multiple color updates, nothing else has changed since then. The Solo 4 will be the first major update to the on-ear headphones in many years. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-working-on-beats-solo-4-headphones/">Apple Working on Beats Solo 4 Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-on-beats-solo-4-headphones.2420574/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Cancels Electric Car Project</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cancels-electric-car-project.2420570/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has canceled all plans to release an autonomous, electric vehicle, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-27/apple-cancels-work-on-electric-car-shifts-team-to-generative-ai">Bloomberg</a></em>. Apple has been working on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a> for more than a decade and invested millions of dollars into development before deciding it was not a viable project.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774150" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple's Chief Operating Officer Jeff Williams today told approximately 2,000 employees working on the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; that the project was canceled, and the information reportedly came as a surprise.<br/>
<br/>
Work on the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; is winding down and many of the people that were working on the car will move to Apple's artificial intelligence division to work on generative AI under AI chief John Giannandrea.<br/>
<br/>
There are a number of hardware engineers and car designers that were on the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; team, and there will be layoffs. Some of the employees may be able to shift to other divisions within the company.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, there were rumors that the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project had been scaled back, with Apple abandoning plans for a full driverless car with autonomous capabilities. Apple shifted focus to an electric vehicle with fewer self-driving features, and the vehicle would have been on par with Tesla's technology. Apple was aiming to release the car sometime around 2026, but now those plans have been shelved completely.<br/>
<br/>
News of the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; first surfaced in 2014, and since then, the project has been rife with problems. The focus of the work has changed and evolved multiple times, and Apple has had several leadership changes due to internal strife. Apple Watch chief Kevin Lynch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/09/kevin-lynch-apple-car-project/">took over the project in 2021</a>, and he worked to scale down the project while still putting out a viable car.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, senior Apple executives made the decision to wind down the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project in recent weeks.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">Apple Cancels Electric Car Project</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cancels-electric-car-project.2420570/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Release Candidate Versions of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-versions-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2420564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 10:25:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded release candidates of upcoming iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to developers for testing purposes, with the updates coming one week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/">Apple seeded the fourth betas</a>. The RCs are the final versions of the software that will be released to the public next week so long as no bugs are found during this final testing process.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932463" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. A free or paid <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 introduces sweeping changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps operate in the European Union, paving the way for alternative app marketplaces, alternative payment systems, third-party browser engine support, and NFC access for banks and third-party payment providers. These features are limited to the EU, and won't be available in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
There are, however, changes to gaming apps, and with the launch of iOS 17.4, Apple will be allowing cloud gaming apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW. Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system. Along with these updates, iOS 17.4 adds new emoji characters, transcripts for podcasts in the Podcasts app, support for using SharePlay with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, Stopwatch Live Activities, and more. Apple's release notes for the update are below.<blockquote><strong>Emoji</strong><br/>
- New mushroom, phoenix, lime, broken chain, and shaking heads emoji are now available in the emoji keyboard<br/>
- 18 people and body emoji add the option to face them in either direction<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Apple Podcasts</strong><br/>
- Transcripts let you follow an episode with text that highlights in sync with the audio in English, Spanish, French and German<br/>
- Episode text can be read in full, searched for a word or phrase, tapped to play from a specific point and used with accessibility features such as Text Size, Increase Contrast, and VoiceOver<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update includes the following enhancements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Music recognition lets you add songs you have identified to your Apple Music Playlists and Library, as well as Apple Music Classical<br/>
- Siri has a new option to announce messages you receive in any supported language<br/>
- Stolen Device Protection supports the option for increased security in all locations<br/>
- Battery Health in Settings shows battery cycle count, manufacture date, and first use on iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models<br/>
- Call Identification displays Apple-verified business name, logo, and department name when available<br/>
- Business updates in Messages for Business provide trusted information for order status, flight notifications, fraud alerts or other transactions you opt into<br/>
- Apple Cash virtual card numbers enable you to pay with Apple Cash at merchants that don't yet accept Apple Pay by typing in your number from Wallet or using Safari AutoFill<br/>
- Fixes an issue where contact pictures are blank in Find My<br/>
- Fixes an issue for Dual SIM users where the phone number changes from primary to secondary and is visible to a group they have messaged<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222">https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</a></blockquote>Full details on everything new in iOS 17.4 can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-beta-features/">our iOS 17.4 features guide</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds Release Candidate Versions of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-versions-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2420564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds macOS Sonoma 14.4 Beta 5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2420566/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 10:24:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fifth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-4/">release of the fourth beta</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 introduces some of the features in the iOS 17.4 beta, such as new emoji characters. We don't know what Mac-specific features are included, and little else was found in the betas so far. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-5/">Apple Seeds macOS Sonoma 14.4 Beta 5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2420566/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases visionOS 1.1 Beta 4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-beta-4.2420567/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 10:23:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released fourth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1 update for developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The new update comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-1/">release of the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 brings support for iMessage Contact Key Verification and it adds Apple device management to the Vision Pro. With this functionality, IT departments at companies and educational institutions can manage Vision Pro headsets in the same way they manage iPhones, iPads, and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's beta notes, users can now reposition volumetric scenes closer than before, enabling easier direct interaction with the volumetric scene content. That means objects can be placed closer to you.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also improved Personas in &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1, making them look more natural and lifelike than before. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-beta-4/">Apple Releases visionOS 1.1 Beta 4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-beta-4.2420567/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds tvOS 17.4 Beta 5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-5-to-developers.2420565/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 10:21:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fifth beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/">release of the fourth tvOS 17.4 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.4 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes.<br/>
<br/>
The tvOS 17.4 update adds support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> SharePlay on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;. The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; user can pull up an &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; QR code that can be scanned by anyone, which then allows multiple people to contribute to what's playing via &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;. An &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscription is not required.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-5/">Apple Seeds tvOS 17.4 Beta 5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-5-to-developers.2420565/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos to Launch &#36;449 Headphones in June to Compete With Apple&#039;s AirPods Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/sonos-headphones-june-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-to-launch-449-headphones-in-june-to-compete-with-apples-airpods-max.2420563/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 10:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/sonos-headphones-june-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos, known for its range of speakers and home theater products, is set to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/">enter the headphone market</a> in 2024. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/sonos-headphones-set-top-box/">Rumors last year</a> indicated Sonos would release headphones as soon as April 2024, but a new report today from <em>Bloomberg</em> suggests Sonos has delayed the launch due to a software issue.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Green-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936393" /><br/>
The headphones are expected to be available for purchase in the first half of June, with the launch pushed back while the software problem is addressed. Sonos is solving a problem with how the headphones connect to Wi-Fi networks.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos is aiming to take on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> with the Sonos headphones, which will have a price tag of &#36;449 and an over-ear design. The headphones will be available in black and white, and are expected to include features like voice control navigation and synchronization with Sonos speakers, soundbars, and subwoofers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; headphones are priced at &#36;549, but third-party retailers often have them available at a discount. Apple has not updated the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; since their 2020 launch, and they are nearing four years old.<br/>
<br/>
We are expecting a refresh at some point this year, but rumors indicate Apple doesn't have plans for major new features. Instead, the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; will get a USB-C port, new colors, and little else.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos is well-established in the speaker market and is the go-to for those who don't mind an expensive home theater setup, so the Sonos headphones could sell well if Sonos offers high-quality sound and deeper customization than is available with Apple's audio products.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos CEO Patrick Spence confirmed in November 2023 that Sonos is set to enter a new market, and he said the company's offering would "delight customers and drive immediate revenue." Spence said Sonos will generate more than &#36;100 million from new products in 2024, and that the new device would account for a large portion of the revenue in the second half of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to headphones, Sonos also plans to unveil a set-top box to rival the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. That device could come as soon as late 2024. If Sonos sees success with the headphones, earbuds that rival the AirPods could come in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/sonos-headphones-june-launch/">Sonos to Launch &#36;449 Headphones in June to Compete With Apple&#039;s AirPods Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-to-launch-449-headphones-in-june-to-compete-with-apples-airpods-max.2420563/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air on Sale for &#36;949 at Best Buy (&#36;150 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/13-inch-m2-macbook-air-drops/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-on-sale-for-949-at-best-buy-150-off.2420553/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 08:12:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/13-inch-m2-macbook-air-drops/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air has dropped to <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPZTZF5dZ"><strong>&#36;949.00</strong></a> today on Best Buy, down from &#36;1,099.00. Best Buy offers free next-day shipping as well as in-store pickup for most locations, and has all four colors of Space Gray, Silver, Midnight, and Starlight at this price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/macbook-air-spacegray-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1428" height="802" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-887878" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is a second-best price on the 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air and it's been a few months since we last tracked an all-time low price on this model. MacBook Air deals in 2024 have so far been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/best-buy-lowest-prices-ipad-macbook/">focused on the 15-inch M2 models</a>, so if you've been waiting for a markdown on the 13.6-inch M2 computer, now is a great time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPZTZF5dZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy also has the 512GB model of the 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air on sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckQP5k7JDAC"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,399.00. Compared to past sales, this is a second-best price and still a solid discount on the 2022 notebook.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckQP5k7JDAC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/13-inch-m2-macbook-air-drops/">Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air on Sale for &#36;949 at Best Buy (&#36;150 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-on-sale-for-949-at-best-buy-150-off.2420553/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates Internal &#039;Unreleased Products&#039; Document Amid Rumors of New iPads and Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-updates-unreleased-products-document/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-internal-unreleased-products-document-amid-rumors-of-new-ipads-and-macs.2420551/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 07:52:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-updates-unreleased-products-document/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated an internal support document about "unannounced or unreleased products," according to a proven source familiar with the matter. The update comes amid rumors that Apple is planning to release new iPads and Macs soon, although there is no guarantee that these things are directly related, and coincidences happen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
The document informs Apple support advisors how to respond to a customer's potential questions about unannounced products and services, or announced but still unreleased products. The document was "restructured and optimized" today, according to Apple's changelog, but we do not know what specific changes were made.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to announce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">updated iPad Pro, iPad Air, and MacBook Air models by late March</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
The next iPad Pro models are widely expected to be the first iPads equipped with brighter and more vivid OLED displays. Other rumored or likely features for the iPad Pro include the M3 chip, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">MagSafe wireless charging</a>, a redesigned Magic Keyboard with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">larger trackpad and an aluminum top casing</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/">landscape-oriented front camera</a>.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">larger 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> is expected alongside an updated 10.9-inch model. Other rumored or likely features for the iPad Air include the M2 chip, a redesigned rear camera bump, Wi-Fi 6E support, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air are expected to be updated with the M3 chip simultaneously, with key benefits over the M2 chip including faster performance and hardware-accelerated ray tracing for improved graphics rendering in games.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes are expected for the MacBook Air this year, but the laptops will likely gain support for Wi-Fi 6E like other Macs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already updated the 14-inch MacBook Pro, 16-inch MacBook Pro, and 24-inch iMac with the M3 chip in October 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Apple often releases a new iPhone color option in March or April too.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-updates-unreleased-products-document/">Apple Updates Internal &#039;Unreleased Products&#039; Document Amid Rumors of New iPads and Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-internal-unreleased-products-document-amid-rumors-of-new-ipads-and-macs.2420551/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPadOS 18 Rumored to Drop Support for These iPad Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-18-rumored-to-drop-support-for-these-ipad-models.2420545/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:55:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPadOS 18 will drop support for iPad models equipped with the A10X Fusion chip, according to a post on X today from a private account with a proven track record of sharing build numbers for upcoming iOS and iPadOS updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPad-Air-5.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938463" /><br/>
This means that iPadOS 18 would not be compatible with the first-generation 10.5-inch iPad Pro or the second-generation 12.9-inch iPad Pro models released in 2017. It almost certainly means that iPadOS 18 would drop support for iPad models powered by the regular A10 Fusion chip too, including the sixth-generation and seventh-generation iPads.<br/>
<br/>
The post was spotted by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>, and it has since been deleted. However, this was likely because the account prefers to keep a low profile, and many of its previously-deleted posts contained accurate information.<br/>
<br/>
If this rumor is accurate, iPadOS 18 would be compatible with the following iPad models:<ul><li>iPad Pro: 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad Air: 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad mini: 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad: 2020 and later</li></ul>Apple is expected to announce iPadOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the update should be released to all users with a compatible iPad in September. So far, key new features rumored for the update include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI functionality for Siri and more</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support in the Messages app</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The same source also expects iOS 18 to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/">iPadOS 18 Rumored to Drop Support for These iPad Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-18-rumored-to-drop-support-for-these-ipad-models.2420545/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumored to Be Compatible With These iPhone Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-be-compatible-with-these-iphone-models.2420543/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:31:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will be compatible with the iPhone XR, and thereby also the iPhone XS and iPhone XS Max models with the same A12 Bionic chip, according to a post on X today from a private account with a proven track record of sharing build numbers for upcoming iOS updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-18-Mock-iPhone-16-Feature-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936483" /><br/>
The post was spotted by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>, and it has since been deleted. However, this was likely because the account prefers to keep a low profile, and many of its previously-deleted posts contained accurate information.<br/>
<br/>
If this rumor is accurate, iOS 18 would be compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17:<ul><li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XR</li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (2nd generation)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (3rd generation)</li></ul>Apple is expected to announce iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the update should be released to all users with a compatible iPhone in September. So far, the update is rumored to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI functionality for Siri and more</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support in the Messages app</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/">design changes</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The same source expects iPadOS 18 to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/">drop support for iPad models with the A10X Fusion chip</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">iOS 18 Rumored to Be Compatible With These iPhone Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-be-compatible-with-these-iphone-models.2420543/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Major Shareholders Planning to Force Apple to Reveal Use of AI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/shareholders-to-force-apple-to-reveal-ai-use/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-shareholders-planning-to-force-apple-to-reveal-use-of-ai.2420535/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:18:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/shareholders-to-force-apple-to-reveal-ai-use/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some of Apple's biggest investors are set to pressure the company tomorrow to reveal its use of artificial intelligence tools (via the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/387c446c-55e0-4f54-a4b4-80bf9d5bc2f3"><em>Financial Times</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Apple's annual shareholder meeting takes place tomorrow, allowing those with a major stake in the company to put forward proposals. One resolution proposed by the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) asks Apple to disclose its use of AI and any ethical guidelines that the company has adopted regarding the technology.<br/>
<br/>
The resolution is set to be supported by Norges Bank Investment Management and Legal & General, Apple's eighth and 10th-largest shareholders. Norges Bank, which operates the world's biggest sovereign wealth fund, wrote in its voting disclosures that Apple's board should account for "social consequences of its operations and products." Likewise, Legal & General said that Apple "discloses very little about its approach to managing AI-related risks."<br/>
<br/>
Legal & General met with Apple to discuss AI, but it declined to increase transparency around its development and use of the technology. "Apple should be transparent in their uses of AI and their risk management processes," the company said.<br/>
<br/>
The major investor advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services is encouraging Apple investors to support the AI resolution, arguing that Apple's guidelines "do not specifically identify the potential risks resulting from the use of AI" and, as a result, "there are concerns regarding shareholders' ability to properly evaluate the risks associated with the use of AI."<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, Apple is urging investors to reject the resolution, claiming that "the scope of the requested report is overly broad and could encompass disclosure of strategic plans and initiatives harmful to our competitive position." Shareholder petitions in the United States are usually non-binding, but those that review support from more than 30% of investors usually put sufficient pressure on the company to act. Apple is widely expected to announce a range of new AI features for its devices at WWDC later this year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/shareholders-to-force-apple-to-reveal-ai-use/">Major Shareholders Planning to Force Apple to Reveal Use of AI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-shareholders-planning-to-force-apple-to-reveal-use-of-ai.2420535/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus to Feature ProMotion Always-On Displays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/iphone-17-always-on-promotion-displays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-and-iphone-17-plus-to-feature-promotion-always-on-displays.2420522/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:13:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/iphone-17-always-on-promotion-displays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next year's iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus will adopt OLED displays with low-power backplane technology, bringing ProMotion to Apple's standard iPhone models for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/iPhone-15-Pro-Multi-Purpose-button-Mute-Switch-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890433" /><br/>
The current iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus use low-temperature polycrystalline silicon (LTPS) panels, while Apple's iPhone 15 Pro models use more advanced low-temperature polycrystalline oxide (LTPO) panels. LTPO panels support ProMotion, allowing the display to ramp up to a 120Hz refresh rate for smoother scrolling and video content when required. <br/>
<br/>
ProMotion also allows the display to ramp down to a more power-efficient refresh rate as low as 1Hz, which is why the iPhone 15 Pro screens feature an always-on capability that shows the Lock Screen's clock, widgets, notifications, and wallpaper even when the device is locked.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to retain the use of the less advanced LTPS panels in this year's iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus to maintain differentiation between its standard and Pro models, meaning Apple's 2025 iPhone series will be the first to feature ProMotion and always-on displays across the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=26198">The Elec</a></em>, Chinese supplier BOE is hoping to supply Apple with LTPO panels for the iPhone 17 series, but questions still remain about whether it can reach the required production capacity while maintaining Apple's quality control standards. <br/>
<br/>
If BOE cannot meet the requirements, Apple will likely turn to other suppliers like Samsung and LG Display for the LTPO panels, and rely on BOE for LTPS-based OLED panels for its legacy iPhone models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/#whats_next_for_the_iphone_se">rumored iPhone SE 4</a>.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/iphone-16-pro-to-feature-taller-aspect-ratio/">display analyst Ross Young</a>, this year's iPhone 16 Pro models will feature a taller aspect ratio of 19.6:9, a change that will trickle down to the standard iPhone 17 models the following year. The devices are expected to increase from 6.12- and 6.69-inches to 6.27- and 6.86-inches, respectively. This represents a display size increase of 2.5% on both devices.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/22/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/">Six Reasons to Wait for Next Year's iPhone 17</a></li></ul><br/>
All in all, this means that the standard ‌iPhone‌ 17 models look set to receive a substantial panel upgrade, with larger sizes as well as LTPO for ProMotion and always-on displays.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/iphone-17-always-on-promotion-displays/">iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus to Feature ProMotion Always-On Displays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-and-iphone-17-plus-to-feature-promotion-always-on-displays.2420522/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Air Lineup: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-ipad-air-lineup-what-to-expect.2420486/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 15:38:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1709001532/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2024 iPad Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In 2023, Apple didn't make any updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup, and it's been even longer since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> was refreshed. Apple last unveiled a new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; in March 2022, so we're at the two-year mark and it's overdue for an update. Luckily, rumors suggest that we're going to get new iPads as soon as March, and there are exciting changes in store for the Air lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
In this guide, we've rounded up all of the rumors about the new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="size_and_design">Size and Design</h2><br/>
Apple is planning for another 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; that's similar in design to the current version, but for the first time, we're expecting <em>two</em> &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models rather than one. As with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> lineup, Apple will release the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; in two sizes.<br/>
<br/>
The standard 10.9-inch model will be the smaller size, and at the larger end, Apple is working on a 12.9-inch version. At 12.9 inches, the larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be the same size as the current 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There aren't rumors of design changes, so we can expect both models to have the same edge-to-edge display with slim bezels and an aluminum chassis with flat, rounded edges that wrap around the screen. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has always been a bit thicker than the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with thicker bezels, and that's going to continue.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that the upcoming &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models that will also be refreshed in March will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/">have thinner frames</a> due to the swap over to OLED display technology. With OLED, the new larger-screened &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will be over 1mm thinner, while the 11-inch model will be almost 1mm thinner.<br/>
<br/>
The changes to &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; thickness should be quite noticeable and the design will distinguish the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; from the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, even though Apple will have two iPads that are roughly the same size.<br/>
<br/>
We've also seen leaked renders of the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which suggest that the new models could have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/">redesigned rear camera</a> with a protruding pill-shaped camera bump similar to the design that we're expecting for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> camera.<br/>
<br/>
Based on rumors, we won't see design changes, but Apple will likely introduce new color options. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; comes in a range of pastel colors right now, and Apple could introduce a selection of new shades.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="m3_chip">M3 Chip</h2><br/>
Since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip came out, Apple has used M-series chips in the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models. This time around, we're expecting Apple to bring either the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip or the M3 chip to the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip is the prior-generation M-series chip that first came out in 2022, and it's almost two years old. The argument for the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; is that it would give Apple a way to further distinguish the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; from the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, plus it would keep costs down. The 3-nanometer M3 chips are more expensive to produce than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple opts for the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, it will bring speed and power efficiency improvements, but it would be a much smaller bump than the M3 chip. It is not entirely clear which chip Apple will use.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip came out last year, and it's the first chip built using next-generation 3-nanometer architecture. It has an 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU, and it supports hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for games with better graphics.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's M3 Macs are able to play console-level games like Death Stranding and Resident Evil, so we can expect the same technology for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; if it ends up with the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 offers 2.5x better GPU speeds than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; in the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with half the power. As for the CPU, the M3 is up to 30 percent faster than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; performance cores and up to 50 percent faster than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; efficiency cores.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="bluetooth_and_wi-fi">Bluetooth and Wi-Fi</h2><br/>
Since the current &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is two years old, it's lacking some of the general technology improvements that Apple has brought to other devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been updating its products with Bluetooth 5.3, so we can expect that to come to the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;. Bluetooth 5.3 brings more reliable connectivity with Bluetooth accessories as well as better power efficiency for longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 6E is also expected, and it will let &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models connect to faster 6GHz Wi-Fi networks.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad_air_vs._ipad_pro">iPad Air vs. iPad Pro</h2><br/>
Display technology will be one of the main distinguishing factors between the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. While the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will have an OLED display, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models will continue to use more affordable LCD display technology.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> on the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and instead the current model has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> power button, which Apple may maintain in order to keep the premium &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; feature exclusive to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
We're not expecting major differences in performance as both models rumored to use the M3 chip, but the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; may have more memory for the OLED display. Rear camera technology will also be a differentiator because the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; has a dual camera setup with Wide and Ultra Wide lenses, while the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has just a single-lens Wide camera.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="pricing">Pricing</h2><br/>
The current 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;599, and the new model is likely to have the same starting price.<br/>
<br/>
As for the 12.9-inch version, it would make the most sense to price it at &#36;200 over the 11-inch model, so it could start at &#36;799. Prior to when the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; was updated with mini-LED, there was a &#36;200 price difference between the two sizes. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is to offer customers more options at a wider range of price points. For around the price of the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, customers will instead be able to opt for a larger 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/21/new-ipads-and-macbook-airs-spring-2024-rumor/">said multiple times</a> that new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models will come in the March/April timeframe, and the latest news suggests a release toward the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">end of March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple sometimes holds a spring event right around March, so we could be hearing news about a possible event in the next week or two.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/">Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Air Lineup: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-ipad-air-lineup-what-to-expect.2420486/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix No Longer Allowing Subscribers to Pay Through Apple&#039;s App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/netflix-stops-allowing-app-store-payment/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-no-longer-allowing-subscribers-to-pay-through-apples-app-store.2420481/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 14:27:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/netflix-stops-allowing-app-store-payment/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix subscribers who still pay their monthly fees through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> in-app purchase system will soon need to add a new payment method to keep their accounts active, Netflix is telling customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884792" /><br/>
Though Netflix stopped allowing customers to subscribe to its streaming service on iOS devices <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/12/28/netflix-no-more-itunes-billing-options/">way back in 2018</a>, it has allowed customers that were already subscribed that way to continue using in-app purchase to pay. Payment through Apple's platform is set to stop, however, because Netflix does not want to continue to pay Apple a 15 percent cut of those subscription fees.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/02/26/netflix-billing-app-store-support-ending/">9to5Mac</a></em>, the U.S. Netflix support site now says that customers in "some" countries will need to add a new payment method. It isn't clear which countries the new Netflix policy is applicable to, but given that it was added to the U.S. site, it likely applies to customers in the United States.<br/>
<blockquote>Some Apple-billed members in select countries may be prompted to add a new payment method to continue their subscription.</blockquote><br/>
There is no word on how many Netflix subscribers are still paying through in-app purchase since it's been nearly six years since Netflix removed the option. Since 2018, Netflix has required customers who have Apple devices to sign up for a new Netflix subscription on the Netflix website. There is no option to subscribe through the Netflix app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and these devices open to a sign-in screen.<br/>
<br/>
When Netflix first removed the option to pay through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, it said customers who paid for subscriptions with in-app purchases could continue to use that billing method until their accounts were canceled, but Netflix seems to have run out of patience.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> Netflix has clarified that the changes affect basic plan members in some countries including the US and Canada, and it does not impact all Netflix users. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/netflix-stops-allowing-app-store-payment/">Netflix No Longer Allowing Subscribers to Pay Through Apple&#039;s App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-no-longer-allowing-subscribers-to-pay-through-apples-app-store.2420481/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Offers Massive &#36;600 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, Available for &#36;999.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/samsung-viewfinity-massive-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-offers-massive-600-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-available-for-999-99.2420449/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:47:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/samsung-viewfinity-massive-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung kicked off a <a href="https://howl.me/clq2oxlzaSU">new sale on computer monitors</a> this week, including a match of the all-time low price on the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor. You can get this display for <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"><strong>&#36;999.99</strong></a> on Samsung's website, down from &#36;1,599.99. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-Slimfit-Camera-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%3Fth%3D1">Amazon is matching this sale</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/viewfinity-feb-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934207" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is a massive &#36;600 discount on the Smart Monitor, which features a matte 5K display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4. The monitor is a good (and cheaper) alternative to Apple's Studio Display. The last time we tracked this deal was about one month ago, so if you've been waiting for a solid markdown on the Samsung display, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;600 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;999.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the ViewFinity display sale, Samsung has a few other monitor discounts right now, which we've listed below. You can also find other Samsung products on sale this week, including offers and savings on <a href="https://howl.me/clIpsUUt4NJ">Galaxy smartphones, watches, and tablets</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clIpn1jjNHg">27-inch Smart Monitor M8</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;649.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvB7Tvgrn">34-inch ViewFinity Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clIpmLoB8FX">49-inch Odyssey G9 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvCVqsFVX">55-inch Odyssey Ark Mini-LED Curved Gaming Screen</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/samsung-viewfinity-massive-discount/">Samsung Offers Massive &#36;600 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, Available for &#36;999.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-offers-massive-600-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-available-for-999-99.2420449/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Could Revive iPhone Sales in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/ios-18-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-ai-features-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china.2420448/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:35:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/ios-18-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>'s rumored AI features could revive faltering <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China, according to <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240223PD204.html"><em>DigiTimes</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
In a paywalled report, <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></em> explains that despite the Chinese market pivoting toward high-end devices, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales have reportedly struggled since the start of 2024 in the region against rival brands offering generative AI features and foldable displays.<br/>
<br/>
In December 2023, Apple reportedly saw a 13% decline in revenue in China, following months as the top smartphone brand in the country by shipments, and there have been further reports of even more severe declines of up to 40% in recent weeks. Chinese consumers apparently see Apple's diminutive selection of AI features as contradictory to its image as a pioneering brand. <br/>
<br/>
<em>&zwnj;DigiTimes&zwnj;</em> reiterated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">previous rumors</a> suggesting that &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will contain a number of new AI features, but cautioned that Apple needs to make significant progress in the AI space to meet consumer expectations and revive the company's popularity in China amid fierce competition from brands like Huawei, which are heavily investing in AI research and development. <br/>
<br/>
On an earnings call earlier this year, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said the company was working on generative AI and would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">share details "later this year."</a> Apple is expected to preview &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the update should be released in September. Some new AI features could be exclusive to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models later in the year, with the lineup rumored to get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">"significantly" upgraded Neural Engine</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/ios-18-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china/">iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Could Revive iPhone Sales in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-ai-features-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china.2420448/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
