<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 03:00:46 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: What&#039;s New With the Maps App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-maps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-whats-new-with-the-maps-app.2433808/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:18:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-maps&#038;post_date=1723857524/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Almost all of Apple's built-in apps are getting new features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and that includes the Maps app. The Maps app isn't getting any fun new AI additions, but Apple does have some useful changes in store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Generic-iOS-18-Maps-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961870" /><br/>
<h2 id="hiking_trails">Hiking Trails</h2><br/>
Apple added topographic maps to the Apple Watch last year, and now detailed topographic maps are also coming to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. The Maps app features detailed trail networks and hikes, including all 63 U.S. national parks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-hikes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961875" /><br/>
You can do a search for "hikes" or "hiking routes" in the Maps app to see nearby trail options, with Apple including hike length, elevation, ratings, and other details.<br/>
<br/>
Hikes can be filtered by length, route type (loop, point to point, or out and back), and elevation, and can be saved for offline access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-hike-filters.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961876" /><br/>
You can zoom into hiking areas to see specific trails, or search for trails. If you tap on a trail, Apple has information that includes length, highest point, lowest point, and distance. You can also see a full overview of the trail's path and get lengths for each section.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-find-trails.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961877" /><br/>
Trails and hikes are separate entities in the Maps app. A search for hikes essentially brings you to the general area where specific trails are located, and you can zoom in with the Maps app to find the trail you want to take.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="custom_routes">Custom Routes</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> supports custom routes in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, so you can plan out a specific hiking route that you want to take. At a trailhead, you can tap on the "Create a Custom Route" option to initiate the custom routing experience.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-custom-route.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961878" /><br/>
From there, you tap on the map to begin setting points for your route, and the Maps app will provide length and elevation details. You can also have the Maps app finish a route automatically by tapping on the Reverse, Out and Back, or Close Loop options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-custom-route-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961879" /><br/>
For hikes and trails, the Maps app will not let you create an unsafe route that does not stick to existing trails, so it's difficult to make a dangerous map out into the middle of nowhere.<br/>
<br/>
Route creation is not limited to hikes and trails. You can add a pinned spot to a map, tap on the "More" option and choose Create Custom Route.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="search_here">Search Here</h2><br/>
Apple made it easier to search in locations you might be thinking of visiting or those you want to explore by adding a "Search here" button. If you look up a place, such as San Diego, and then tap on search, it'll search in the area that's on your screen rather at your physical location.<br/>
<br/>
If you search for something and then pan around the map, the search will update reliably in the new location. When you zoom in, you'll see a dedicated "Search here" button that gives you more control over where you want to search.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="saving_favorites">Saving Favorites</h2><br/>
If you find a favorite hike, trail, or custom route, you can save it to your Library to save it for later. To do so, find the relevant hike and then tap on the "Add to Library" button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-trail-save-library.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961880" /><br/>
You can rename hikes and add specific information that you might want to revisit later, as well as download the route for offline usage.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping on the "+" button when viewing any location on the map, including a hike, will also add that location to the library.<br/>
<br/>
Favorites are stored in the Maps app and can be accessed by tapping on your profile picture and choosing the Library section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="library">Library</h2><br/>
All saved content from the Maps app including locations, routes, guides, and pins are stored in the new Library section of the Maps app rather than in separate sections as in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-library.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961881" /><br/>
The Library also shows all of your Recently Added content.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="notes">Notes</h2><br/>
You can tap on any place in the Maps app and select the Add a Note option from the menu. From there, you can make a note about what you want to remember about a location.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-maps-add-a-note.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961882" /><br/>
Notes are private and are kept on-device. They are only visible to the note creator.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
Additional information on new features that Apple has added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-maps/">iOS 18: What&#039;s New With the Maps App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-whats-new-with-the-maps-app.2433808/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple is Opening Up the iPhone&#039;s NFC Chip: What You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-nfc-chip-ios-18-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-is-opening-up-the-iphones-nfc-chip-what-you-need-to-know.2433801/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:45:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-nfc-chip-ios-18-1&#038;post_date=1723848345/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>NFC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of iOS 18.1 this fall, Apple will allow third-party developers to support NFC contactless transactions for payments and more. Right now, the NFC chip is locked down, and it's primarily only used for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, but a number of new capabilities will be coming when Apple expands access to NFC.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-Tap-to-Pay-on-iPhone-avail-FR-transaction.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922462" /><br/>
<h2 id="nfc_capabilities_in_third-party_apps">NFC Capabilities in Third-Party Apps</h2><br/>
With NFC access, banks will be able to offer direct contactless payment options that serve as an alternative to &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, but it app developers will be able to do more, too. Some ways Apple says NFC can be used:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Contactless payments in stores</li><br/>
 <li>Car keys</li><br/>
 <li>Closed-loop transit cards</li><br/>
 <li>Corporate badges</li><br/>
 <li>Student IDs</li><br/>
 <li>Government IDs (coming in the future)</li><br/>
 <li>Home keys</li><br/>
 <li>Hotel keys</li><br/>
 <li>Merchant loyalty and reward cards</li><br/>
 <li>Event tickets</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="security_protections">Security Protections</h2><br/>
Apple is creating several new APIs that will power the contactless transactions. The APIs will use the Secure Enclave in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, with sensitive information stored directly on device.<br/>
<br/>
Developers will have to request access to the NFC and Secure Enclave entitlement, sign a commercial agreement with Apple, and pay associated fees. Apple plans to make sure that only authorized developers who meet regulatory and industry requirements and commit to Apple's security and privacy standards can get access to the APIs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="default_contactless_app_options">Default Contactless App Options</h2><br/>
Once these features go live, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users can open up the app and then hold the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; near an NFC terminal to make a payment. So if you want to pay at a store using your bank's NFC payment service, you'd open your bank app and then double-click the side button on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to initiate a transaction.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party apps will also be able to be set as default contactless apps in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
Transactions will be verified with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_pay_and_apple_wallet">Apple Pay and Apple Wallet</h2><br/>
The NFC APIs are separate from &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; and Apple Wallet, which is why you will need to open up a third-party app to use its NFC capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="available_countries">Available Countries</h2><br/>
Apple's NFC and Secure Enclave APIs are coming to developers in Australia, Brazil, Canada, Japan, New Zealand, the UK, and the United States.<br/>
<br/>
Support will come to additional locations in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/11/apple-opens-iphone-nfc-access-eu/">already opened up</a> the NFC chip in the European Economic Area.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ios_18.1_launch_date">iOS 18.1 Launch Date</h2><br/>
The new APIs will launch in iOS 18.1, which is an update that Apple is testing at the current time. iOS 18.1 will likely be released a few weeks after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and we are expecting to see it sometime in October.<br/>
<br/>
In past years, .1 updates have come out between October 20 and October 25, so the week of October 21 is likely when we will see iOS 18.1 come out.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nfc/">NFC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-nfc-chip-ios-18-1/">Apple is Opening Up the iPhone&#039;s NFC Chip: What You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-is-opening-up-the-iphones-nfc-chip-what-you-need-to-know.2433801/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Five New Features Coming in tvOS 18 This Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/tvos-18-five-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/five-new-features-coming-in-tvos-18-this-fall.2433796/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:06:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/tvos-18-five-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, and the other fall updates, Apple plans to release an updated version of tvOS. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> software updates often don't get much attention because they tend to introduce a limited number of new features, but there are some interesting additions coming this year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LC4CBHVRoNg" title="tvOS 18: Best NEW Features Coming to Apple TV" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li><strong>InSight</strong> - InSight is like Amazon X-ray, providing information about actors, character, and music from &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ movies and shows in real-time. If you pause a show that's playing, you can see details on the actors, the song that's playing, and more. If you're using an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as a remote for an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, you can get InSight information right on your phone. Note that this feature only works with &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ content right now.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Enhance Dialogue and Subtitles</strong> - Enhance Dialogue is setting that already exists, but Apple is making it better with machine learning and computational audio improvements. It'll be better at improving vocal clarity over loud music, action scenes, and background noise. Plus Apple updated it so it works with HDMI-connected speakers, when playing content on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, when using AirPods, and with other Bluetooth audio devices. As a bonus, Apple is also improving subtitles, so they'll appear intelligently such as when content is muted or when a TV show or movie is rewound.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>FaceTime Updates</strong> - When you use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> with your &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; as the camera, you can now see real-time Live Captions during the call. This works in English in the United States and Canada. Semi-related, there is a new option to use SharePlay so everyone can contribute songs to a party playlist by scanning a QR code.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>New Screen Savers</strong> - Apple is adding new screen saver options, including Portraits (shows your Portrait images), TV and Movies, and Snoopy.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Projector Support</strong> - If you have a projector, you'll be pleased to hear that tvOS 18 adds support for the 21:9 aspect ratio used by most projectors.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
What do you think of the new features coming in tvOS 18? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/tvos-18-five-features/">Five New Features Coming in tvOS 18 This Fall</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/five-new-features-coming-in-tvos-18-this-fall.2433796/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Low Prices Hit AirTag, Studio Display, iPad Pro, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-low-prices-hit-airtag-studio-display-ipad-pro-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-low-prices-hit-airtag-studio-display-ipad-pro-and-more.2433793/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:21:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-low-prices-hit-airtag-studio-display-ipad-pro-and-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some of this week's best Apple deals include all-time low prices for the Apple Studio Display and M4 iPad Pro, both of which are available on Amazon. We're also tracking great discounts on Bluetooth trackers, Sony's popular noise canceling headphones, and portable power stations from Anker and Jackery.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/hero-new-blue-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961852" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bluetooth Trackers</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/airtag-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961851" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Apple and Anker Bluetooth trackers</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/10/airtag-anker-bluetooth-trackers/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 2 Pack for &#36;29.88</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1723214719490"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week started with a handful of discounts on popular Bluetooth trackers, including Apple's AirTag and Anker's brand of Eufy SmartTrack accessories. Although all-time low prices are no longer available on some devices, you can still find all of them on sale today on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sony Headphones</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/sony-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961862" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;150 off Sony WH1000XM4 Headphones</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-15268034?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.sony.com%2Faudio%2Fheadphones%2Fheadband%2Fp%2Fwh1000xm4-b">Sony</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-15268034?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.sony.com%2Faudio%2Fheadphones%2Fheadband%2Fp%2Fwh1000xm4-b"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>Sony WH1000XM4 Headphones for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Sony this week introduced a steep new discount on the WH1000XM4 Wireless Premium Noise Canceling Headphones, available for &#36;199.99 direct from its website, down from &#36;349.99. These headphones feature premium noise cancellation and up to a 30 hour battery life, and this discount is available in all three colors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/studio-display-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961850" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;299 off Apple Studio Display</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/apple-studio-display-low-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Standard Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week discounted the Apple Studio Display (standard glass) to &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,599.00, which is a match of the all-time low price on the monitor. You can also find low prices on the VESA mount adapter model and tilt- and height-adjustable stand model on Amazon right now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/m4-ipad-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961848" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on M4 iPad Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>11-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi0 for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has Apple's 256GB Wi-Fi 11-inch M4 iPad Pro for &#36;899.00, down from &#36;999.00. This is a new record low price on the tablet, and there are also multiple other sales on both 11-inch and 13-inch Wi-Fi models happening this week on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Portable Power Stations</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/anker-jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958617" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker and Jackery power stations</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ_1723559358185">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/amazon-power-stations-anker-jackery/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ_1723559358185"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus Power Station for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1754-SOLIX-C800-Plus%2Fdp%2FB0C5CBDX2P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>Anker SOLIX C800 Power Station for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week also saw the return of major discounts on Anker's and Jackery's best portable power stations, with as much as &#36;1,750 off these accessories. Many of the Anker deals do require a Prime membership, while others require you to clip an on-page coupon. You can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/amazon-power-stations-anker-jackery/">visit our original post</a> for the full list of power stations on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/samsung-smart-monitor-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961849" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;700 off Samsung's ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, plus other deals</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/samsungs-back-to-school-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung opened up its back to school sale this week, and it includes a match of the all-time low price on the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor. This display is priced at &#36;899.99 (&#36;700 off), and you'll find even more deals on monitors, TVs, and smartphones in this sale.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-low-prices-hit-airtag-studio-display-ipad-pro-and-more/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Low Prices Hit AirTag, Studio Display, iPad Pro, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-low-prices-hit-airtag-studio-display-ipad-pro-and-more.2433793/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Android Phones Exposed to Remote Access Vulnerability</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/android-phones-exposed-to-remote-vulnerability/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/android-phones-exposed-to-remote-access-vulnerability.2433786/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:50:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/android-phones-exposed-to-remote-vulnerability/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>Cybersecurity</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some Android smartphones have been found to contain a hidden security vulnerability that could allow remote access to user data, alarming cybersecurity experts and leading to a halt in the use of these devices by a major intelligence contractor, <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2024/08/15/google-sold-android-phones-with-hidden-insecure-feature-companies-find/"><em>The Washington Post</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/Google-Logo-Feature-Slack.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-837104" /><br/>
The vulnerability, identified by the security firm iVerify, involves a pre-installed application known as Showcase.apk, which, though dormant by default, can be activated to potentially allow unauthorized remote access to the devices. The Showcase.apk application was discovered within certain models of Android phones, including Google Pixel devices.<br/>
<br/>
According to iVerify, the application appears to have been designed for use in retail environments, allowing employees to demonstrate the device's features to customers. However, researchers found that when activated, the application could connect to a server via an unsecured "http" connection, making it vulnerable to interception by cybercriminals. This flaw could enable attackers to execute code remotely, potentially injecting malicious code or spyware and gaining access to sensitive data stored on the device.<br/>
<br/>
Palantir Technologies, a data analysis platform vendor that often works with government agencies and other security-sensitive clients, expressed grave concerns about the implications of this vulnerability. The company has ceased the use of Android phones for their employees as a result.<br/>
<br/>
The presence of this vulnerability on Pixel devices is particularly notable since they are known for receiving timely security updates directly from Google. Google has now announced that it will issue an update to remove the Showcase.apk application from all supported Pixel devices. Distributors of other Android phones will also be officially notified of the issue.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cybersecurity/">Cybersecurity</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/android-phones-exposed-to-remote-vulnerability/">Android Phones Exposed to Remote Access Vulnerability</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/android-phones-exposed-to-remote-access-vulnerability.2433786/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s AirPods Lineup to Get These Updates in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/apple-airpods-lineup-updates-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-lineup-to-get-these-updates-in-2024.2433764/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:52:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/apple-airpods-lineup-updates-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to upgrade its entire AirPods lineup this year in one form or another, with a combination of new model launches and upcoming software updates for existing devices. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/airpods-school.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905460" /><br/>
Whether you're holding out for the next generation of AirPods or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, or just want to know what new features are on the way for your current earbuds, keep reading for the full lowdown on what to expect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 3</h2><br/>
Fourth-generation AirPods are expected to arrive in late 2024, with Apple planning to release two versions at different price points. Both models will feature a redesigned look, including a USB-C port instead of a Lightning port, shorter stems similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, along with an updated fit and enhanced audio quality.<br/>
<br/>
The higher-end version is expected to include Active Noise Cancellation (ANC), making ANC available at a lower price point for the first time. They are also likely to have a speaker in the charging case that can play a sound for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> location tracking. This model will be more affordable than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; (&#36;249) but will not include features like silicone ear tips. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/AirPods-Fourth-Generation-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905655" /><br/>
One of the key aspects the next-generation AirPods are likely to bring over from the second-generation ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌ is the H2 chip. Both the second- and third-generation AirPods currently feature the H1 chip. The H2 chip is accompanied by Bluetooth 5.3 connectivity, which offers faster and more reliable connectivity with Bluetooth accessories, as well as improved power efficiency, which can contribute to longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the H2 chip provides an "exceptional acoustic experience" when paired with a new low-distortion audio driver and custom amplifier in the ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌. The ‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌ offer richer bass and clearer sound across a wider range of frequencies partly due to the computational audio improvements facilitated by the H2 chip, so similar enhancements seem highly likely to come to the fourth-generation AirPods. <br/>
<br/>
The launch of the two <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a> models is expected in September or October 2024, which will also see the current AirPods 2 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a> discontinued.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro</h2><br/>
Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> update introduces several enhancements for the current second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, leveraging machine learning and AI. New head gestures will allow users to control &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; hands-free—nodding to answer a call or shaking their head to decline. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> Interactions will also enable hands-free management of calls, messages, and notifications without speaking.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; adds Voice Isolation to &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, improving call clarity by filtering out background noise and focusing on your voice, similar to an existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> feature. Additionally, the Adaptive Audio feature, which adjusts sound and noise cancellation based on your environment, will now offer a customizable setting for finer control.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862208" /><br/>
According to Apple, the ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌ provide the best wireless audio latency ever for mobile gaming, thanks to improvements coming in ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;‌. Improved latency means that you'll see little to no delay when taking an action in the game and hearing the resulting sound, making for a more responsive experience.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will introduce a "hearing aid mode" to &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;. Although they already have a Conversation Boost feature, this update further positions them as a potential hearing aid device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected introduce a redesigned third-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; in 2025, with refined design and better audio quality, along with a faster processor.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
&zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are the oldest current-generation AirPods product still in Apple's lineup. It's been over three years since Apple launched &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in December 2020, and only recently have we begun hearing rumors about Apple's plans for a new-generation model that is coming later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will replace the Lightning port found on the current-generation &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; for a USB-C port. This will ensure the headphones comply with European regulations, and will bring consistency across the company's AirPods lineup. This of course means &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; 2 will come supplied with a USB-C to USB-C charging cable, rather than a Lightning to USB-C cable. Apple will also need to offer a USB-C to 3.5mm audio accessory cable so that users can plug &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; 2 into 3.5mm audio ports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Dark-Red-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877636" /><br/>
The Bluetooth 5.3 specification can already be found in the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, and the latest Apple Watch models. It is also supported by all Mac models released in 2023. Therefore it's almost inevitable that the second-generation ‌&zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;‌ will similarly feature the latest Bluetooth standard.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to offer second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in fresh colors, although what those colors might be remains unknown. &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are currently available in Space Gray, Silver, Green, Sky Blue, and Pink, although interchangeable ear cushions allow for many color combinations.<br/>
<br/>
While there are no rumors that claim &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; 2 will feature the H2 chip, it would seem reasonable to expect them to do so. Apple's custom silicon chip is designed specifically for earbuds and headphones, and enables improved computational audio to enhance sound quality on the current-generation ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌ and improves battery life with better energy efficiency. Without the H2 chip, &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; would also miss out on Adaptive Audio features including Personalized Volume and Conversation Awareness.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Coming to All AirPods Models</h2><br/>
Personalized Spatial Audio is a feature that already exists for movies, TV shows, and music. It uses the TrueDepth camera on your ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ to scan your face and ears, developing a personal profile that customizes Spatial Audio just for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Spatial-Audio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1698" height="978" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-787199" /><br/>
With ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;‌, Apple is expanding Personalized Spatial Audio to gaming, with the aim of delivering more immersive sound for gameplay. Personalized Spatial Audio for Gaming will support &zwnj;AirPods 3&zwnj; and 4, &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, and &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/apple-airpods-lineup-updates-this-year/">Apple&#039;s AirPods Lineup to Get These Updates in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-lineup-to-get-these-updates-in-2024.2433764/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games Store Launches on iPhone in EU, Brings Fortnite Back to iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/epic-games-store-launches-ios-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-store-launches-on-iphone-in-eu-brings-fortnite-back-to-ios.2433762/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:40:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/epic-games-store-launches-ios-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After a four-year absence, <em>Fortnite</em> is making its return to iPhones – but only for users in the European Union. This comeback is part of the broader launch of the <a href="https://store.epicgames.com/en-US/mobile/ios">Epic Games Store for iPhone</a>, which went live today in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/epic-games-store.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1350" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961828" /><br/>
The return of <em>Fortnite</em> to iOS comes as a result of the EU's Digital Markets Act, which has forced Apple to allow third-party app marketplaces on its platform. Users in the EU can now download the Epic Games Store by <a href="https://store.epicgames.com/en-US/mobile/ios">visiting Epic's website</a> on their iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Fortnite</em>'s availability is undoubtedly the headline feature of the Epic Games Store launch. The popular battle royale game was removed from the App Store in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">2020</a> following a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">dispute between Epic and Apple</a> over in-app purchase systems. Prior to that, <em>Fortnite</em> on iOS made more than &#36;700 million over two years, while Apple collected more than <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/19/apple-earned-over-100-million-from-fortnite/">&#36;100 million in revenue</a> from the 30 percent cut that it took from <em>Fortnite</em> in-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
Otherwise, the current game catalog in the iOS Epic Games Store is limited, featuring only a handful of Epic's own titles such as <em>Fortnite</em> and <em>Rocket League Sideswipe</em>. However, the company says it plans to expand the library over time and is in discussions with third-party mobile developers. <br/>
<br/>
Going forward, Epic will have to deal with navigating Apple's new fee structure, including a "Core Technology Fee" of €0.50 per install per year after the first million installs. This fee applies to both the Epic Games Store itself and the games within it, effectively doubling the charge for popular titles like <em>Fortnite</em>. The EU commission is currently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">investigating</a> whether Apple's new fee structure complies with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
The Epic Games Store is only available on iPhones running iOS 17.4 or later, while iPad users will have to wait until the release of iPadOS 18 to access the store on their devices. Epic says it plans to expand the availability of its store to other regions where regulations permit, with Japan slated for a 2025 launch. The company has set a goal of reaching 100 million mobile downloads of its store by the end of the year, made up of combined game installs across both iOS and Android.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/epic-games-store-launches-ios-eu/">Epic Games Store Launches on iPhone in EU, Brings Fortnite Back to iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-store-launches-on-iphone-in-eu-brings-fortnite-back-to-ios.2433762/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All Four iPhone 16 Pro Colors Revealed in New Image</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-four-iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed-in-new-image.2433761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:14:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Leaker <a href="https://x.com/sonnydickson/status/1824381930579824739?s=46">Sonny Dickson</a> is back today with a new dummy unit image showing all four <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> color variants, including the rose gold or "bronze" unit that replaces Blue Titanium in the existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/sonny-iphone-16-pro-colors.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961824" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to come in black, white or silver, gray or "Natural Titanium," and a rose or rose gold color replacing Blue Titanium, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <a href="https://x.com/VNchocoTaco/status/1772522408144191732">other leakers</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Dickson's image shows what we can expect, particularly in terms of the rose gold variant, which was recently described by one leaker as having more of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/">bronze-like hue</a>. Apple did not include a gold option in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, so a similar variant could see heightened demand.<br/>
<br/>
One <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/iphone-16-pro-new-polished-titanium-finish/">rumor</a> suggests that Apple is using an improved process for finishing and coloring titanium, which will result in a glossier look than the brushed aluminum finish of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models. The glossy finish could look much more like the stainless steel that Apple used in prior years, but it will be more resistant to scratches.<br/>
<br/>
We don't actually know the official color names yet, but Apple may choose to stick with the Titanium colorway branding it used for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models. The next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is due to arrive around mid-September, so we will know for sure soon. Dickson revealed the colors for the standard (non-Pro) &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/">last month</a>. What do you think of the new colors? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/">All Four iPhone 16 Pro Colors Revealed in New Image</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-four-iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed-in-new-image.2433761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These New Macs Are Coming in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024.2433739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:34:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's almost September, but Apple still has multiple new product launches planned for 2024. New <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models and Apple Watches are coming in September, and we're also going to get at least three Mac updates with M4 chips this year, according to rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Silver-Ortho-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961274" /><br/>
Here's what's on the horizon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
Apple plans to refresh both the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models, adding M4 chips. The MacBook Pro lineup was last updated in October 2023, so the machines are due for a yearly refresh.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did away with the 13-inch MacBook Pro last year, so there's now an entry-level 14-inch model, and that's what's going to get the standard M4 chip that was used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Middle tier and higher-end 14-inch models will get the M4 Pro and M4 Max chips, as will the 16-inch models. The M4 chips are built on the 3-nanometer process, but compared to the M3 chips, they have improved performance, efficiency, and AI capabilities. Apple introduced a new, more powerful Neural Engine.<br/>
<br/>
There are no design updates expected for the MacBook Pro models this year, with Apple focusing on internal improvements. Specifically, the M4 chip will be the star of the upgrade, and Apple is aiming to get its entire Mac lineup on the same M4 chip series across 2024 and 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac mini</h2><br/>
Unlike the MacBook Pro, Apple does have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/">design refresh planned</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be Apple's smallest computer to date, even smaller than the prior-generation version.<br/>
<br/>
It is expected to be around the size of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, though it will be thicker than the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; and the current &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, which is 1.4 inches tall. The machine will continue to be made from aluminum, just in an overall smaller package.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has tested &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models that have at least three USB-C ports, along with an HDMI port and a power cable.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to use the M4 and M4 Pro chips for the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models, and since these never got an M3 update, they'll go from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> to M4 and will see some notable performance improvements.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMac</h2><br/>
The 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> is also expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/m4-macbook-pro-mac-mini-imac-2024/">see an update</a> this year, going from the M3 chip to the M4 chip. Design changes are not rumored for the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, so we can expect to see the same 24-inch display with multiple color options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is still exploring a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/apple-still-working-on-larger-imac/">version of the iMac</a> with a larger ~30-inch display, but an &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with a bigger display is not expected in 2024, and it's not clear if it will come in 2025, either.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Possible Launch Timeline</h2><br/>
Apple does not typically unveil Macs at its September events, which focus on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the Apple Watch. We're expecting Apple to hold an event around September 10 to unveil new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, but Macs will likely come later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
When Apple has Macs to unveil around fall, it often introduces the machines in October or November. Last year, for example, Apple held a Mac-centric event in October to refresh the MacBook Pro and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;. October/November events aren't as consistent as &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; events, so nailing down a target date is tougher. Apple has held second fall events on these dates in the past:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 30, 2023</strong> - Scary Fast event with MacBook Pro and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 18, 2021</strong> - Unleashed event with new MacBook Pro models and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>November 10, 2020</strong> - One More Thing event with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, and MacBook Pro.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 30, 2018</strong> - Apple refreshed the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 27, 2016</strong> - Apple unveiled a new MacBook Pro and &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Apple could also skip an event and unveil the new Macs with a press release, though the small event we got last year for the M3 MacBook Pro and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; models could be repeated in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Macs Coming in 2025</h2><br/>
While the MacBook Pro, &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, and &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; are expected to get the M4 chip before the end of the year, M4 updates for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> won't be happening until 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/">These New Macs Are Coming in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024.2433739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Will Require Users to Update Screen Recording App Permissions Monthly</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/macos-sequoia-screen-recording-app-permissions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-will-require-users-to-update-screen-recording-app-permissions-monthly.2433732/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/macos-sequoia-screen-recording-app-permissions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, Apple is requiring users to regularly reauthorize permissions for screen recording apps, a move that has not been popular with some Mac users. Popups for screen recording app permissions have been showing weekly up throughout the beta testing process, but Apple has tweaked the frequency in response to user feedback.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-6/">latest macOS Sequoia beta</a> prompts users to review their screen recording app permissions once a month, an update over the more frequent weekly popups. The prompt reminds users that screen recording apps have access to their screens and audio.<br/>
<blockquote>[App Name] is requesting to bypass the system private window picker and directly access your screen and audio. This will allow [App Name] to record your screen and system audio, including personal or sensitive information that may be visible or audible.</blockquote><br/>
When the popup shows up, there's now an option to "Allow For One Month" to let the app function as normal, or to open System Settings to get to the screen recording options. &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; was also requiring users to approve screen recording apps after restarting their Macs, and this requirement has been removed.<br/>
<br/>
It does not appear that there is a way for users to permanently give screen recording access to recording functionality, but a monthly popup is at least more convenient than a weekly popup.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/macos-sequoia-screen-recording-app-permissions/">macOS Sequoia Will Require Users to Update Screen Recording App Permissions Monthly</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-will-require-users-to-update-screen-recording-app-permissions-monthly.2433732/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.6, Downgrading No Longer an Option</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6-downgrading-no-longer-an-option.2433728/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:20:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 17.6, preventing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from downgrading to that version of iOS. The update is no longer being signed after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/apple-releases-ios-17-6-1/">released iOS 17.6.1 on August 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" /><br/>
Apple regularly stops signing older version of iOS, typically within a week or two after a new version is released. When Apple stops signing an update, it can no longer be installed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; due to a server-side software verification check, so those who have updated to the latest version of iOS cannot downgrade.<br/>
<br/>
Preventing downgrading encourages users to keep their operating systems up to date with the latest security fixes.<br/>
<br/>
This policy encourages users to keep their operating systems up to date, ensuring they have the latest security enhancements.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.6 focused on introducing security fixes, while iOS 17.6.1 added a fix for a bug that could prevent the enabling or disabling of Advanced Data Protection.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.5.1 addressed a corruption bug that could cause <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">deleted photos to reappear on an iPhone</a>. There were no notable features in the iOS 17.6 update, with Apple adding unspecified bug fixes and security updates.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.6, Downgrading No Longer an Option</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6-downgrading-no-longer-an-option.2433728/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>United States Fines T-Mobile &#36;60 Million for Failing to Prevent Unauthorized Access to Sensitive Customer Data</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/t-mobile-60-million-data-breach-fine/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/united-states-fines-t-mobile-60-million-for-failing-to-prevent-unauthorized-access-to-sensitive-customer-data.2433723/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:32:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/t-mobile-60-million-data-breach-fine/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile was fined &#36;60 million by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the US (CFIUS) for negligence surrounding data breaches, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-14/us-watchdog-cfius-discloses-60-million-fine-against-t-mobile">Reuters</a></em>. CFIUS penalized T-Mobile for failing to prevent or disclose unauthorized access to sensitive customer data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/T-Mobile-Generic-Feature-Pink-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951944" /><br/>
When T-Mobile merged with Sprint, it signed a national security agreement with CFIUS, which is what led to the fine earlier this year. T-Mobile is owned by German company Deutsche Telekom, and T-Mobile agreed to protect consumer data as part of the Sprint acquisition. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/16/t-mobile-data-breach/">Back in 2021</a>, T-Mobile suffered a major breach that impacted over 100 million of its users, just a year after it acquired Sprint.<br/>
<br/>
CFIUS does not typically name the companies that it fines, but T-Mobile has been called out in an effort to push companies to comply with national security rules associated with acquisitions.<blockquote>In 2024, following an initial Notice of Penalty issued in 2023, CFIUS resolved an enforcement action against T-Mobile US, Inc. ("T-Mobile"), a telecommunications company, resulting in a &#36;60 million penalty. As publicly disclosed by T-Mobile, the company entered into a National Security Agreement ("NSA") with CFIUS in 2018 in connection with T-Mobile's merger with Sprint and the foreign ownership of the resulting entity. CFIUS determined that between August 2020 and June 2021, in violation of a material provision of the NSA, T-Mobile failed to take appropriate measures to prevent unauthorized access to certain sensitive data and failed to report some incidents of unauthorized access promptly to CFIUS, delaying the Committee's efforts to investigate and mitigate any potential harm. CFIUS concluded that these violations resulted in harm to the national security equities of the United States. T-Mobile has worked with CFIUS to enhance its compliance posture and obligations and has committed to working cooperatively with the U.S. Government to ensure compliance with its obligations going forward.</blockquote>T-Mobile told <em>Reuters</em> that it experienced technical issues when integrating with Sprint, which affected information from "a small number of law enforcement information requests." T-Mobile claims to have swiftly dealt with the issue and reported it "in a timely manner."<br/>
<br/>
CFIUS said that T-Mobile's lack of timely reporting prevented CFIUS from investigating and mitigating potential harm to U.S. national security.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/t-mobile-60-million-data-breach-fine/">United States Fines T-Mobile &#36;60 Million for Failing to Prevent Unauthorized Access to Sensitive Customer Data</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/united-states-fines-t-mobile-60-million-for-failing-to-prevent-unauthorized-access-to-sensitive-customer-data.2433723/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Gaining Support for Analytics, Scheduling Posts, Multiple Drafts and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/threads-analytics-post-scheduling/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-gaining-support-for-analytics-scheduling-posts-multiple-drafts-and-more.2433721/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:25:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/threads-analytics-post-scheduling/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Threads, Meta's social network that's meant to rival X, today announced <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2024/08/new-threads-features-for-creators-and-businesses/">several new features</a> that are available or coming soon. For creators, Threads is launching analytics for performance measurement.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
Users can see view numbers, replies, reposts, and quotes, along with follower count over time and follower demographics like age, location, and gender.<br/>
<br/>
Threads on the web is gaining support for writing and saving multiple drafts of posts before sharing them with an audience. Up to 100 ideas can be saved in the new Drafts section. To go along with drafts, Threads plans to add scheduling, so Threads can be created and scheduled to go up at a later date and time. Multiple posts can be scheduled per day, multiple days in advance.<br/>
<br/>
While these features are available only on the web at the current time, Threads plans to bring them to the mobile versions of the app in the future. Insights and multiple drafts are rolling out now, and scheduling posts will be coming soon.<br/>
<br/>
It has now been just over a year since Threads launched, and it has over 28 million daily active users. Meta has been regularly adding new features to the social network to put it on par with X (formerly Twitter).<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/threads-analytics-post-scheduling/">Threads Gaining Support for Analytics, Scheduling Posts, Multiple Drafts and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-gaining-support-for-analytics-scheduling-posts-multiple-drafts-and-more.2433721/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Display Panels for M4 MacBook Pro Shipping Ahead of Q4 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/display-panels-for-m4-macbook-pro-shipping-ahead-of-q4-launch.2433715/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Display panels destined for the 14-inch and 16-inch M4 models are shipping to Apple in July and August, timing that makes sense for a launch in the fourth quarter, according to display analyst Ross Young.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/M4-Real-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950311" /><br/>
Young shared the information <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1824130598975443363">in a tweet</a> for subscribers, confirming rumors that new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4 chips will come out before the end of the year. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said earlier this month that Apple will update the MacBook Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> lines with M4 chip technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/">in late 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models will get M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max chips. The entry-level 14-inch model will have the M4, while higher end 14-inch models and 16-inch models will get the M4 Pro and M4 Max, which have not yet been unveiled. Apple first introduced the M4 in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> in May.<br/>
<br/>
No redesign is expected, but Apple will overhaul the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; that's expected to be refreshed alongside the MacBook Pro models. The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will feature a smaller footprint, and it will be Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">smallest ever computer</a>. It could be around the size of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, though a little taller.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 chip is built on TSMC's 3-nanometer process, much like the M3, but there are performance and efficiency improvements. Apple also included a new, more powerful Neural Engine for AI workloads.<br/>
<br/>
With new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch models planned for Apple's annual September event, new Macs could come out at a second event in October or November or they could be unveiled through a press release.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/">also plans to refresh</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> with M4 chips, but those updates will not happen until 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/">Display Panels for M4 MacBook Pro Shipping Ahead of Q4 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/display-panels-for-m4-macbook-pro-shipping-ahead-of-q4-launch.2433715/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Rolling Out Soon in California</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-rolling-out-soon-in-california.2433707/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:17:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		<category>California</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[California will <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/drivers-licenses-and-state-ids-in-apple-wallet-are-coming-soon-to-california/">soon start rolling out support</a> for digital driver's licenses and IDs in the Apple Wallet app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch, becoming the sixth state to implement the feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-california-drivers-license.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961769" /><br/>
Wallet app integration is part of California's mobile driver's license effort, which kicked off a year ago. More than 500,000 people have already added a driver's license or ID to the California DMV Wallet app, where California tested the option before rolling it out to the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>"We're excited to be working with the state of California to bring IDs in Apple Wallet to Apple's home state soon, and provide residents with an easy, secure, and private way to present their California driver's license and state ID in person and in app using Apple Wallet," said Jennifer Bailey, Apple's vice president of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet. "Whether using IDs in Apple Wallet to breeze through travel, or to securely verify age or identity at businesses, California driver's licenses and state IDs in Apple Wallet make ID presentment seamless -- all with the security built into iPhone and Apple Watch."</blockquote><br/>
IDs and licenses stored in the Wallet app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> can be used for TSA screenings at select airports and for age verification at select stores. Right now, California's mobile wallet support is still in a pilot stage, and only 1.5 million participants are able to sign up.<br/>
<br/>
California requires people to continue to carry a physical license or ID card because the digital license is not accepted by law enforcement, state government agencies, and most businesses.<br/>
<br/>
Evidence that Apple Wallet integration was coming to California first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/iphone-drivers-license-support-coming-california/">surfaced earlier in August</a> when a hidden landing page on the DMV website was discovered, but California and Apple are officially announcing the feature today.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced a new Wallet app that supported digital IDs back in 2022, but states have been slow to adopt the feature. So far, only Arizona, Colorado, Georgia, Maryland, and Ohio have implemented support. Apple said in 2022 that Connecticut, Iowa, Kentucky, Oklahoma, and Utah are also working on support.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/california/">California</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/">iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Rolling Out Soon in California</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-rolling-out-soon-in-california.2433707/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Primate Labs Debuts New Geekbench Suite for AI-Centric Workloads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/primate-labs-geekbench-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/primate-labs-debuts-new-geekbench-suite-for-ai-centric-workloads.2433705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/primate-labs-geekbench-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Geekbench</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following extended testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/geekbench-ml-macos/">under the "Geekbench ML" name</a>, Primate Labs is officially launching its new benchmarking suite optimized for AI-centric workloads under the name <a href="https://www.geekbench.com/ai/">Geekbench AI</a>. The tool seeks to measure hardware performance under a variety of workloads focused on machine learning, deep learning, and other AI-centric tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/geekbench-ai.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961692" /><br/>
Geekbench AI 1.0 examines some of the unique workloads associated with AI tasks and seeks to encompass the variety of hardware designs employed by vendors to tackle these tasks, delivering a three-score summary as part of its benchmarking results to reflect a range of precision levels: single-precision, half-precision, and quantized data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/geekbench-ai-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961693" /><br/>
In addition to these performance scores, Geekbench AI also includes an accuracy measurement on a per-test basis, allowing developers to improve efficiency and reliability while assessing the benefits and drawbacks of various engineering approaches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/geekbench-ai-mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961694" /><br/>
Finally, the 1.0 release of Geekbench AI includes support for new frameworks and more extensive data sets that more closely reflect real-world inputs, improving the accuracy evaluations in the suite.<br/>
<br/>
Geekbench AI is <a href="https://www.geekbench.com/ai/download/">available for an array of platforms</a>, including iOS, macOS, Windows, Android, and Linux.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/geekbench/">Geekbench</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/primate-labs-geekbench-ai/">Primate Labs Debuts New Geekbench Suite for AI-Centric Workloads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/primate-labs-debuts-new-geekbench-suite-for-ai-centric-workloads.2433705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Developers Must Share Phone Number and Address on EU App Store to Meet &#039;Trader&#039; Requirement Starting in October</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-must-share-phone-number-and-address-on-eu-app-store-to-meet-trader-requirement-starting-in-october.2433704/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:54:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=a0nevv65">today reminded developers</a> who plan to distribute apps in the European Union to submit <a href="https://developer.apple.com/help/app-store-connect/manage-compliance-information/manage-european-union-digital-services-act-trader-requirements/">their trader status</a>, a requirement that will see the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> sharing the address, phone number, and email address of each developer. The information will be displayed on a developer's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; page.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/app-store-trader-requirement-dsa.jpg" alt="" width="1538" height="865" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961762" /><br/>
The Digital Services Act (DSA) in the European Union requires Apple to verify and display trader contract information for all "traders" who are distributing apps on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the European Union. Developers who make money from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; through an upfront cost or through in-app purchases are considered traders, regardless of size.<br/>
<br/>
Contact information for each developer that is classified as a trader will be publicly available, and many developers are unhappy with the requirement. Independent developers and small companies may not have business addresses and phone numbers to provide, and are understandably reluctant to provide their personal contact information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will require trader status to submit app updates starting on October 16, 2024. Trader information must be provided before an app can be submitted for review. On February 17, 2025, apps without trader status will be removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the EU until trader status is provided and verified.<br/>
<br/>
As displaying trader status is a Digital Services Act requirement in the European Union, Apple does not have a choice on implementing the feature. Developer contact information will be displayed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; product page when an app is distributed in any of the 27 territories in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
More information on determining who is a trader and who needs to provide contact details can be <a href="https://developer.apple.com/help/app-store-connect/manage-compliance-information/manage-european-union-digital-services-act-trader-requirements/">found on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/">Developers Must Share Phone Number and Address on EU App Store to Meet &#039;Trader&#039; Requirement Starting in October</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-must-share-phone-number-and-address-on-eu-app-store-to-meet-trader-requirement-starting-in-october.2433704/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Watch Ultra More Popular Than Apple Watch SE</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-se/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-apple-watch-se.2433700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:57:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-se/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Ultra is considerably more popular than the entry-level <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> despite its high price point, according to a <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/apple-watch-models-trend-toward-the">new report</a> from Consumer Intelligence Research Partners (CIRP).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-1-1.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-866346" /><br/>
The report provides a detailed look at how the various Apple Watch models are performing in the market. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, introduced in September 2023 alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, is the most popular model in the lineup as of the June 2024 quarter. It captured 43% of total Apple Watch sales in the United States, making it the top choice among customers. The Series 8, which Apple no longer sells directly but is still available through various retailers, followed with a 19% share. Combined, these two models accounted for nearly two-thirds of all Apple Watch sales during the period.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra and Ultra 2, which represent the high-end segment of the lineup, contributed 20% of total sales. Despite their advanced features and premium positioning, the Ultra models have a smaller market share compared to the high-end variants of other Apple products like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. For instance, premium models in these categories typically account for a quarter or more of total sales. The CIRP report indicates that the Ultra 2 had a slightly higher share than the original Ultra during the June 2024 quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/cirp-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="827" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-961744" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; held a 12% market share. This model continues to attract buyers who are looking for a more affordable entry point into the Apple Watch, yet its market presence is significantly smaller than that of the higher end models. The Nike-branded version of the Apple Watch, which is essentially a variant of the Series 8 and 9, accounted for a modest 5% of the market.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's strategy of offering a range of models at different price points appears to mirror its approach with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. However, there are some notable differences in consumer behavior across these product lines. While the premium models of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; often capture a larger share of sales, the Apple Watch lineup sees stronger performance in its mid-range models. The CIRP report suggests that the Series 8 and Series 9, positioned as a mid-tier option in terms of pricing and features, is particularly attractive to consumers, while the Ultra models, despite their higher price and more advanced capabilities, appeal to a smaller segment of the market. The low-cost &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; and Nike models appeal to an even smaller segment of the market.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-se/">Report: Apple Watch Ultra More Popular Than Apple Watch SE</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-apple-watch-se.2433700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;200 Off M4 iPad Pro, Starting at &#36;899</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-200-off-m4-ipad-pro-starting-at-899.2433698/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:33:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a large collection of discounts on the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2024 M4 iPad Pro</a> at Amazon, which includes multiple all-time low prices on both 11-inch and 13-inch models. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
For the smaller 11-inch M4 iPad Pro, Amazon has an all-time low price on the entry-level 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. Amazon has every model of the 11-inch iPad Pro on sale right now, including both Wi-Fi and cellular versions.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;899.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,484.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6RX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J89FYD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,899.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JBX6ML%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;2,099.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-Inch</h3><br/>
Similar to the 11-inch models, Amazon has every Wi-Fi and cellular version of the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro on sale this week. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J98W75%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,197.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, and totals up to &#36;200 off these devices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J98W75%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,197.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J776JL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,379.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6S6LS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,839.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,099.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J85MZM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,287.92, down from &#36;2,399.00</li></ul>  Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;200 Off M4 iPad Pro, Starting at &#36;899</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-200-off-m4-ipad-pro-starting-at-899.2433698/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card Named Best in Customer Satisfaction for Fourth Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-for-fourth-year.2433696/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:18:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> has been <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-by-jd-power/">recognized</a> as the best co-branded credit card for customer satisfaction with no annual fee for the fourth consecutive year by J.D. Power.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/apple-card-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-785924" /><br/>
As highlighted by Apple in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-by-jd-power/">press release</a> earlier today, this is the fourth year in a row that the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;, issued by Goldman Sachs, has earned the top spot in J.D. Power's 2024 U.S. Credit Card Satisfaction Study. The study measures overall customer satisfaction by assessing performance across several categories, including Account Management, Customer Service, and New Account Experience. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; was first introduced in 2019 and is deeply integrated into the Wallet app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, allowing users to track their spending in real time, categorize transactions, and set up payment plans. The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; also offers up to three percent Daily Cash on purchases, which can be used instantly or saved for future expenses. With &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; Family, users can share an &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; account with other members of their Family Sharing group. The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; also features an integrated a Savings account option, providing users with the ability to automatically deposit their Daily Cash rewards into the account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction/">Apple Card Named Best in Customer Satisfaction for Fourth Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-for-fourth-year.2433696/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
