<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 09:03:18 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s Everything New in the Messages App on iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/everything-new-in-ios-18-messages-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-everything-new-in-the-messages-app-on-ios-18.2429423/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 08:25:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/everything-new-in-ios-18-messages-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> adds many new features to the Messages app, including the ability to schedule messages to be sent later, the ability to use any emoji or sticker as a Tapback, text formatting options like bold and italics, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Messages-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955693" /><br/>
iOS 18 is currently available in beta for members of the Apple Developer Program, with a public beta to follow in July. The software update should be widely released in September, and it is compatible with the iPhone XS and newer.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we outline everything new in the Messages app on iOS 18, including some smaller changes that Apple's website does not mention.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Schedule Messages</h2><br/>
iMessages can now be scheduled to be sent at a later date and time in both individual and group conversations. As of the first iOS 18 beta, you can schedule a message to be sent up to 14 days later. After scheduling a message, it becomes visible to you in a dotted-line bubble, with edit, delete, and reschedule options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-Send-Later-iOS-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955789" /><br/>
To access this feature, tap the plus sign to the left of the text field, tap More, and tap Send Later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tapback Changes</h2><br/>
<h3>Redesigned Tapbacks</h3><br/>
The classic set of Tapback icons are now colorful, including the heart, thumbs up, thumbs down, HA HA, exclamation marks, and question mark.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954501" /><br/>
<h3>Emoji Tapbacks</h3><br/>
You can now use any emoji or sticker as a Tapback.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-4.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954505" /><br/>
<h3>Improved Visibility</h3><br/>
It is now easier to view multiple Tapback reactions on a single message.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Text Formatting and Effects</h2><br/>
Bold, italics, underline, and strikeout formatting is finally available for iMessages. In addition, there are all-new text effects that can animate words within an iMessage, including Big, Small, Shake, Nod, Explode, Ripple, Bloom, and Jitter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-1.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954499" /><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Text-Effects-iMessage.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955785" /><br/>
<h2>Messages via Satellite <span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 22px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4e6c99; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px;">U.S. Only</span></h2><br/>
iOS 18 allows you to send and receive both iMessages and SMS messages via a satellite connection, even if there is no emergency.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Messages-via-Satellite.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955787" /><br/>
This feature will work with messages, emoji, and Tapbacks, and all iMessages sent over satellite are secured with end-to-end encryption.<br/>
<br/>
Messages via satellite is available on all iPhone 14 models and newer in the U.S. only at launch.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/13/ios-18-messages-via-satellite-first-look/">Hands-on demo videos</a> show the feature in action.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>RCS Support <span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 22px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4e6c99; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px;">Later This Year</span></h2><br/>
Apple's website says that iOS 18 will support RCS (Rich Communication Services) in the Messages app. While this feature is not enabled in the first iOS 18 beta, Apple said it will be rolled out later this year, likely by time iOS 18 is widely released.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-WWDC-Slide.png" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955808" /><em>WWDC keynote slide confirming RCS support on iOS 18</em></div><br/>
RCS support will result in the following improvements to the default messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices:<ul><br/>
 <li>Higher-resolution photos and videos</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages</li><br/>
 <li>Typing indicators</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts</li><br/>
 <li>Wi-Fi messaging</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats, including the ability for iPhone users to leave a conversation that includes Android users</li></li><br/>
</ul>SMS continues to be supported as well.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Emoji and Link Card Changes</h2><br/>
When you send a message with only a single emoji, it now appears even larger than before.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-Link-Cards.jpg" alt="" width="2358" height="1323" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955800" /><br/>
Link cards are now more colorful, with the background better matching the linked content.<br/>
<br/>
For some links, you can now choose between full-size and compact link cards, and there is an option to send a link as plain text instead.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Other Changes</h2><br/>
<ul><li>Any app can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-hide-lock-apps/">locked behind Face ID</a>, Touch ID, or an iPhone's passcode on iOS 18, including the Messages app.</li><br/>
<li>iOS 18 can <a href="https://x.com/rjonesy/status/1801636095219929407">solve math equations in the text field</a> of any app, including the Messages app.</li><br/>
<li>iOS 18 adds contact photos next to names in the Messages app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/13/ios-18-carplay-features/">on CarPlay</a>.</li></ul><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/everything-new-in-ios-18-messages-app/">Here&#039;s Everything New in the Messages App on iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-everything-new-in-the-messages-app-on-ios-18.2429423/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;200 Off M1 iPad Air and &#36;100 Off iPad Mini 6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/best-buy-ipad-air-ipad-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-200-off-m1-ipad-air-and-100-off-ipad-mini-6.2429418/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:44:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/best-buy-ipad-air-ipad-mini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a pair of deals on Apple's <a href="https://howl.me/cmtYt3Ri3Wl">sixth-generation iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmtYtvdOtL2">fifth-generation iPad Air</a>, which are available on Best Buy and Amazon. Both of these sales are notable for having nearly every model of each tablet on sale right now, with as much as &#36;200 off select models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ipads-deals-june.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953676" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 64GB Wi-Fi M1 iPad Air, Best Buy has this model for <a href="https://howl.me/cmtYvqU5f2K"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.99. This is an all-time low price on this model of the 2022 iPad Air, and it's available in every color. You'll also find the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air on sale, as well as both cellular devices, one of which is only available on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYvqU5f2K"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYwMCr9pa"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYxGHWtUw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3J64H8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced new M2 iPad Air models last month, which is why we're seeing steep discounts on the previous generation models more often. You can still <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/80-off-the-m2-ipad-air/">save a bit of money on the 2024 models</a> if you're interested in owning the latest version.<br/>
<br/>
Secondly, Amazon has the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for <a href="https://howl.me/cmtYBUAuoIt"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;499.99. This one is a second-best price on the iPad mini, and it's available in every color. You'll find every iPad mini 6 model on sale right now, with the exception of the 256GB cellular model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYBUAuoIt"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYDzYvcml"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYFeiVGqs"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad mini for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/best-buy-ipad-air-ipad-mini/">Best Buy Takes &#36;200 Off M1 iPad Air and &#36;100 Off iPad Mini 6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-200-off-m1-ipad-air-and-100-off-ipad-mini-6.2429418/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: These Apple Intelligence Features Won&#039;t Be Ready Until 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-siri-improvements-coming-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-these-apple-intelligence-features-wont-be-ready-until-2025.2429408/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 05:01:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-siri-improvements-coming-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is not expected to introduce its most significant Apple Intelligence features in September when ‌iOS 18‌ sees a public release. Instead, many will come alongside a Siri overhaul in a future ‌iOS 18‌ update that's set to be introduced in 2025. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954498" /><br/>
That doesn't mean Siri will not have any improvements when iOS 18 initially launches. According to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-16/when-is-apple-intelligence-coming-some-ai-features-won-t-arrive-until-2025-lxhjh86w"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, Siri in iOS 18 will still have some "new bells and whistles" come September, including a new interface that glows a light around the edge of the screen, richer natural language capabilities that will allow Siri to understand you even if you stumble over your words, a greater knowledge of Apple products to power on-device support, and a Type to Siri option for entering queries via text.<br/>
<br/>
But according to Gurman, we will have to wait until next year to see Apple's most significant enhancements to Siri. An iOS 18 update in 2025 should bring with it the following improvements to Apple's virtual assistant:<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Personal Context: </strong>Siri will have the ability to draw from your photos, calendar events, Messages, and other apps to inform responses to queries. Apple gave an example of a person asking when their mom's flight is landing, which Siri figured out based on recent text conversations and emails.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Semantic indexing:</strong> Apple Intelligence creates an on-device semantic index to store data retrieved from your emails, images, websites you visit, and apps you use.</li><br/>
<li><strong>App Control:</strong> ‌Siri will be able to‌ control all individual features in apps for the first time, expanding the range of functions the personal assistant can perform. ‌Siri‌ will be able to do things like open specific documents, move a note from one folder to another, delete an email, summarize an article, email a web link, and open a particular news site in Apple News. </li><br/>
<li><strong>On-screen awareness:</strong> With onscreen awareness, Siri will be able to understand and take action with users' content in more apps over time. For example, if a friend texts a user their new address in Messages, the receiver can say, "Add this address to his contact card."</li></ul>Like these Siri improvements, Apple Intelligence features will initially only support American English, and support for additional languages and regions won't arrive until 2025. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>AI Updates Coming Later in 2024</h2><br/>
Gurman notes that some of the Mail app's new AI features won't be ready until "later in 2024." These include a redesign that can group emails in categories like newsletters, announcements and shopping. Swift Assist, a new programming companion for Xcode that uses cloud-based AI models, is similarly not expected to arrive until later in the year. Siri integration with ChatGPT may also miss the initial release, though Gurman thinks it should be ready later in 2024, based on language Apple has used in its marketing materials. <br/>
<br/>
Going on past release timelines, these features are likely to arrive in an iOS 18.1 or iOS 18.2 update around October or December.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the missing enhancements, the initial version of Apple Intelligence will still offer a plethora of features, according to Gurman. It will leverage AI to prioritize notifications and provide quick recaps of your alerts and text messages. The software will also have the capability to summarize webpages, voice memos, meeting notes, and emails. Additionally, it will introduce new writing tools, image generation, and custom AI-generated emojis called Genmoji. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-siri-improvements-coming-2025/">iOS 18: These Apple Intelligence Features Won&#039;t Be Ready Until 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-these-apple-intelligence-features-wont-be-ready-until-2025.2429408/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Developing Thinner MacBook Pro, Apple Watch, and iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developing-thinner-macbook-pro-apple-watch-and-iphone.2429400/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 02:22:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple intends to slim down the MacBook Pro, Apple Watch, and iPhone, with the new ultra-thin M4 iPad Pro a sign of the company's new design trajectory, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPod-Nano-vs-iPod-Pro-Ad-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="721" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949953" /><br/>
When the M4 iPad Pro was unveiled last month, Apple touted it as the company's thinnest product ever, and even compared it to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/08/ipod-nano-appears-in-new-ipad-pro-ad/">2012 iPod nano</a> to emphasize its slim dimensions. <br/>
<br/>
Writing in the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-16/when-is-apple-intelligence-coming-some-ai-features-won-t-arrive-until-2025-lxhjh86w">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman says that like the iPad Pro, Apple is now focused on delivering the thinnest possible devices across its lineups without compromising on battery life or major new features.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman writes that the new iPad Pro is the "beginning of a new class of Apple devices," and that Apple's aim is to offer "the thinnest and lightest products in their categories across the whole tech industry."<br/>
<br/>
Apple now reportedly has its sights on making thinner versions of iPhone, Apple Watch, and MacBook Pro over the next couple of years.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman's sources tell him Apple is now focused on developing a significantly skinnier iPhone in time for the iPhone 17 line in 2025, corroborating a May report by <em>The Information</em>. According to the latter report, Apple is planning to launch an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/slimmer-iphone-17-major-redesign-rumor/">all-new thinner iPhone 17</a> model next year that will allegedly feature a "major redesign" akin to the iPhone X.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">reported</a> that Apple is planning a complete revamp of the Apple Watch for the device's tenth anniversary, dubbed "Apple Watch X." <br/>
<br/>
Since the original Apple Watch was unveiled in 2014 and launched in 2015, Gurman is unsure whether the ‌Apple Watch X‌ will be released in 2024 or 2025. However, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">claimed</a> that this year's upcoming Apple Watch will have a larger screen and thinner design, which sounds like the sort of major overhaul and design signature that Gurman has suggested.<br/>
<br/>
In 2021, Apple significantly redesigned the MacBook Pro, making it thicker and heavier. A major highlight of the redesign was the reintroduction of several ports that were removed in previous iterations in favor of chassis thinness. MacBook Pro models now include an HDMI port, an SD card slot, MagSafe 3 charging port, three Thunderbolt 4 (USB-C) ports, and a headphone jack. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/">Apple Developing Thinner MacBook Pro, Apple Watch, and iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developing-thinner-macbook-pro-apple-watch-and-iphone.2429400/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Watch Series 10 to Get Larger Screen and Thinner Design</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-to-get-larger-screen-and-thinner-design.2429393/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 01:20:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year's Apple Watch Series 10 will be thinner and come in larger screen sizes than previous models, according to Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-9-display.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913380" /><br/>
In his latest industry note <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/2h24-新款apple-watch關注焦點-series-10-鉑力特-3d列印-the-focus-of-the-2h24-new-apple-watch-series-10-and-98075c44ce92">shared on Medium</a>, Kuo said the screen size options on the next-generation Apple Watch will increase from 41mm to 45mm, and from 45mm to 49mm, while being encased in a thinner design. For reference, the Apple Watch Ultra has a 49mm case.<br/>
<br/>
As for Apple Watch Ultra, Kuo said it will remain "roughly the same" this year, although if production yields meet expectations, a new dark/black case color option could be made available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will also start using 3D printing technology to manufacture Apple Watch components later this year, following extensive testing which has significantly improved the production efficiency. Kuo said BLT will be the supplier of 3D-printed components.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">reported</a> that the 2024 Apple Watch could be labeled the "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>" to celebrate the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch, but Kuo made no mention of this possibility in his latest note. <em>Bloomberg</em> also said that Apple is considering a magnetic band attachment system that will allow the design to be made thinner, but it is unclear whether the system will be ready or present on the 2024 Apple Watch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">Kuo: Apple Watch Series 10 to Get Larger Screen and Thinner Design</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-to-get-larger-screen-and-thinner-design.2429393/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon&#039;s Weekend Sale Has Record Low Prices on M3 MacBook Air, Available From &#36;899</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/15/amazons-weekend-sale-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-weekend-sale-has-record-low-prices-on-m3-macbook-air-available-from-899.2429282/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 09:52:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/15/amazons-weekend-sale-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this weekend has record low prices on every <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">M3 MacBook Air</a>, including the 13-inch and 15-inch models. Amazon introduced this sale about one week ago and it remains one of the only retailers to have these all-time low prices on the 2024 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/15-inch-m3-macbook-air.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947373" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has &#36;200 off the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> in every color, down from &#36;1,099.00. You can also find both 512GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air on sale at best-ever prices, both hitting &#36;170 off original prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,129.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BNQC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Secondly, you can get the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX235DJ6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,129.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. Similar to the 13-inch models, both 512GB models are available on sale as well, and some have delivery dates for as soon as June 17 for United States residences, while others are slipping into July.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX235DJ6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,129.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23S6XV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;210 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,489.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you need help deciding the right MacBook Air to purchase, be sure to read our buyer's guide <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-generations-compared/">comparing each generation of the computer</a>. Additionally, we have a guide that breaks down all of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/">differences between the 13-inch and 15-inch sizes</a> of the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/15/amazons-weekend-sale-m3-macbook-air/">Amazon&#039;s Weekend Sale Has Record Low Prices on M3 MacBook Air, Available From &#36;899</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-weekend-sale-has-record-low-prices-on-m3-macbook-air-available-from-899.2429282/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: WWDC Recap With iOS 18, Apple Intelligence, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/15/top-stories-wwdc-2024-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-wwdc-recap-with-ios-18-apple-intelligence-and-more.2429272/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/15/top-stories-wwdc-2024-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WWDC 2024 kicked off on Monday with a jam-packed keynote revealing iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and more, all fueled by upcoming Apple Intelligence technology.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/top-stories-15jun2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955611" /><br/>
We've highlighted the major announcements below, but be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/wwdc-2024-recap/">check out our recap post</a> that includes a video going over the highlights plus links to all of our coverage from the big day!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces iOS 18 With Customizable Home Screen and Control Center and Much More</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-ios-18-with-new-customization-features-and-more/">announced iOS 18</a>, which includes a wide range of new features and changes for the iPhone, including new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-home-screen/">customization options for the Home Screen</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-ios-18-control-center-multiple-screens/">Control Center</a>, a redesigned Photos app, the ability to use any emoji as a Tapback in the Messages app, an option to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/08/ios-18-face-id-app-locking-rumor/">lock apps behind Face ID or Touch ID</a>, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
The tentpole feature of iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence</a>, which is Apple's new suite of generative AI features coming to the iPhone, iPad, and Mac later this year. Read on for more details about Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>'Apple Intelligence' Unveiled for iPhone, iPad, and Mac</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence</a> can summarize text and notifications, create custom emoji and images, and more. Siri is also getting smarter with Apple Intelligence, with richer language understanding and more per-app controls. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/">Siri will also be able to access ChatGPT</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954498" /><br/>
These new AI-powered features will be available on the iPhone 15 Pro or newer, or any Mac or iPad equipped with an M1 chip or newer. Apple Intelligence will be available when iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia are released to the public later this year, but the features will have a beta label at launch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Unveils macOS 15 Sequoia With iPhone Mirroring, Passwords App, More</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia is the name</a> for this year's major update to the Mac operating system!<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/sequoia.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954485" /><br/>
Key new features beyond Apple Intelligence include the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/">mirror your iPhone onto your Mac</a>, the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/">Passwords app</a> coming to the iPhone with iOS 18, improved window tiling, and more.<br/>
<br/>
macOS Sequoia is currently in beta, and it will be widely released later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Previews watchOS 11 With New Health and Workout Features</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-previews-watchos-11-with-new-health-and-workout-features/">watchOS 11's key new features</a> and changes for the Apple Watch include the ability to pause your Activity rings without disrupting your award streak, a new Vitals app that provides overnight health metrics, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/13/watchos-11-live-activities-suggested-widgets/">Live Activities support in the Smart Stack</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-features.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955600" /><br/>
Like the other software updates unveiled at WWDC, watchOS 11 is currently in beta for developers and will be widely released later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>tvOS 18 Adds 'InSight' to Identify Actors and Songs in Apple TV+ Shows and More</h2><br/>
While it did not receive too much attention at WWDC, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-gaining-insight-feature/">tvOS 18 is coming to the Apple TV</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/tvos-18-insight.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955603" /><br/>
The software update includes a handful of new features and changes, including an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-gaining-insight-feature/">"InSight" feature that can identify actors and songs in Apple TV+ shows</a>, updates to the Enhance Dialogue feature and subtitles, additional screen savers, 21:9 video playback support for playing movies and shows on projectors, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces visionOS 2 With Ultra-Wide Mac Virtual Display, Travel Mode on Trains, and More</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-visionos-2/">visionOS 2 is the first-ever major software update for Apple's Vision Pro</a> spatial computer, which launched in the U.S. earlier this year and will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/vision-pro-launching-in-more-countries/">available in eight more countries by mid-July</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Mac-Virtual-Display.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954438" /><br/>
visionOS 2 can turn existing 2D photos into spatial photos with machine learning, adds new hand gestures for frequently used features like Home View and Control Center, introduces a larger ultra-wide version of Mac Virtual Display, expands Travel Mode to trains, supports a physical mouse, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jun-13-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/15/top-stories-wwdc-2024-recap/">Top Stories: WWDC Recap With iOS 18, Apple Intelligence, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-wwdc-recap-with-ios-18-apple-intelligence-and-more.2429272/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Give Siri a New Name With iOS 18&#039;s Vocal Shortcuts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-rename-siri/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-give-siri-a-new-name-with-ios-18s-vocal-shortcuts.2429243/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:33:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-rename-siri/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> added a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-18-accessibility-features/">Vocal Shortcuts accessibility feature</a>, and now that &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is available in a beta capacity, users have figured out that this option can be used to give <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> a new wake word.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
With Vocal Shortcuts, you can assign a custom phrase that &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can understand to launch shortcuts and complete "complex tasks," and one of the shortcuts you can set up is an alternative for "Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;."<br/>
<br/>
To set up a Vocal Shortcut for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, open up the Settings app, go to Accessibility, and scroll down to Vocal Shortcuts. From there, choose "Set Up Vocal Shortcuts," and select "&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;" (not &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; Request). Type in the new name that you want to use to activate &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, such as "Computer."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/siri-vocal-shortcut-setup.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955565" /><br/>
Once your new name is set, you can say that name to activate &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. Note that this is limited to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and it does not sync to other devices like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> so you'll still need to use "&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;" for those devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/siri-vocal-shortcut-setup-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955566" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iOSBeta/comments/1dfeobg/ios_18_db1_vocal_shortcuts_can_be_used_to_trigger/">As noted on Reddit</a>, if you set this up, you need to pause to wait for it to activate before you give a command. With &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, you can say an entire phrase, like "Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; what time is it?" without stopping. That does not work with the Vocal Shortcut setup. You need to state the wake word, pause, and then give the command once the wake word has activated &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Because of the delay, this isn't likely an option that most people are going to want to use permanently, though &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will still activate with "Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;" as well as the shortcut.<br/>
<br/>
Vocal Shortcuts can be used to set a voice command to run any shortcut, plus you can set up triggers for apps, system features like taking a screenshot, changing volume, scrolling, activating Control Center, and more. Vocal Shortcuts can be paired with a custom sound instead of speech, and it is a useful accessibility option aimed at those who need alternative ways to activate system features.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-rename-siri/">You Can Give Siri a New Name With iOS 18&#039;s Vocal Shortcuts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-give-siri-a-new-name-with-ios-18s-vocal-shortcuts.2429243/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos&#039; Privacy Policy Change Suggests It Might Sell Your Data</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/sonos-privacy-policy-change-suggests-it-might-sell-your-data/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-privacy-policy-change-suggests-it-might-sell-your-data.2429242/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:04:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/sonos-privacy-policy-change-suggests-it-might-sell-your-data/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular audio company Sonos recently updated its U.S. privacy policy to make a small but notable change that seemingly puts customer data at risk. As noted by Louis Rossmann (via <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/6/14/24178433/sonos-privacy-policy-customer-data-controversy">The Verge</a></em>), the new Sonos privacy policy removes a line about not selling customer data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/sonos-roam-feature.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-792626" /><br/>
In the 2023 version of its privacy policy, Sonos had this sentence: "We do not and will not sell your personal data to third parties." The statement has been removed from the 2024 version of the privacy policy in the United States, though it is still present in privacy policies in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
The change to the privacy policy has <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sonos/comments/1desj5c/sonos_updates_tos_and_removes_clause_explicitly/">sparked commentary on Reddit</a> from Sonos customers who have become increasingly unhappy with the company in recent months. Back in May, Sonos rolled out a new app design that has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/sonos-said-rolling-out-widely-criticized-app-redesign-took-courage/">been widely criticized</a> for missing a long list of features like editing a song queue, managing playlists, shuffling a music library, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos users already unhappy with the app changes feel that the privacy policy update is another nail in the coffin for Sonos. From Reddit user <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sonos/comments/1desj5c/sonos_updates_tos_and_removes_clause_explicitly/">RemarkableAgent1350</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>What is happening at Sonos? This hurts to read, especially after all the app drama - and from a company that I loved. This just might be the straw that broke the camel's back, so to speak. I think I'm done with Sonos.</blockquote><br/>
The removal of that line from the privacy policy doesn't mean Sonos is definitely selling customer data, and the company has not responded queries about what the change means as of yet.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/sonos-privacy-policy-change-suggests-it-might-sell-your-data/">Sonos&#039; Privacy Policy Change Suggests It Might Sell Your Data</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-privacy-policy-change-suggests-it-might-sell-your-data.2429242/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Gains Emergency SOS Live Video Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-gains-emergency-sos-live-video-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-gains-emergency-sos-live-video-support.2429240/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:29:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-gains-emergency-sos-live-video-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> is giving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users who find themselves in an emergency situation a way to provide more information and context to emergency responders with an update to Emergency SOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/emergency-sos.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955647" /><br/>
Emergency SOS now supports live video, which means once the SOS feature is activated, streaming video and recorded media can be sent to emergency personnel. Emergency dispatchers can send a request for a user to share either live video or a video from the camera roll, which Apple says should make it easier and faster to get help.<br/>
<br/>
Video is sent over a secure connection to the emergency dispatcher. The option could allow those in emergency situations to send key information for location purposes, to assess injury or risk, or to be used as evidence at a later date.<br/>
<br/>
Emergency SOS is a feature on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch that automatically calls the local emergency number and shares location information with emergency services. It is the backbone of the Crash Detection, Fall Detection, and Emergency SOS via satellite features.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-gains-emergency-sos-live-video-support/">iOS 18 Gains Emergency SOS Live Video Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-gains-emergency-sos-live-video-support.2429240/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains How iOS 18 Genmoji Work</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/apple-explains-ios-18-genmoji/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-ios-18-genmoji-work.2429239/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:55:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/apple-explains-ios-18-genmoji/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of the Apple Intelligence features coming in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> is Genmoji, which will allow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users to use AI to generate all-new emoji characters based on text input. The Genmoji will look similar to emoji, but are custom created, according to an <a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2024/10220/">iOS 18 WWDC session focused on Genmoji</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Genmoji-iOS-18.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954516" /><br/>
Emoji are not images, but are instead pictographs that are encoded in the Unicode Standard and rendered by each platform. Emoji are added by the Unicode Consortium, which raised some questions about how Apple's Genmoji solution will work.<br/>
<br/>
As it turns out, Apple has designed an NSAdaptiveImageGlyph API for Genmoji and also other images like stickers and Memoji, and this API makes them behave like emoji. It is powered by a standard image format in a square aspect ratio with support for multiple resolutions, and it is augmented with metadata. This setup means that Genmoji and other content using NSAdaptiveImageGlyph can be used with and formatted alongside regular text, similar to emoji.<br/>
<br/>
Genmoji can be used alone, copied, pasted, and sent as stickers. They can be used inline with text, and they respect line height and text formatting. Anywhere that can support rich text can support Genmoji, according to Apple. <br/>
<br/>
Genmoji are not Unicode and may not be appropriate for some data such as identifiers, phone numbers, email addresses, and will not be supported as widely as emoji. Prior versions of iOS, iPadOS, and macOS, as well as apps that do not support rich text will denote Genmoji with a text description.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features like Genmoji are not yet in the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; developer beta, but Apple plans to let developers begin testing Apple Intelligence sometime this summer. Genmoji and Apple Intelligence will be available to the public this fall, but they will be limited to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and iPads and Macs with M-series chips.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/apple-explains-ios-18-genmoji/">Apple Explains How iOS 18 Genmoji Work</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-ios-18-genmoji-work.2429239/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Select a Preferred Home Hub in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-preferred-home-hub/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-select-a-preferred-home-hub-in-ios-18.2429237/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-preferred-home-hub/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Home app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> allows <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> users who have more than one device that serves as a home hub to select which one should be used as the preferred hub. It is a small but useful change because it prevents &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; from choosing a hub that is further away from most &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; products or that has a weaker connection. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/homekit-showdown-2-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826321" /><br/>
In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and earlier, there has been no way to select a home hub, and &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; has picked randomly. That can lead to connectivity issues in some situations. For those who do not care about which home hub &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; selects, Automatic Selection remains an option.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> are able to serve as home hubs, but the option to set a preferred hub seems to be limited to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; as of right now, because Apple has not yet provided a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; beta to developers. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/preferred-home-hub-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="672" height="767" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955650" /><em><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/HomeKit/comments/1df0nkg/new_preferred_home_hub_in_ios18/">Image from Reddit</a></em></div><br/>
Other features coming in &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; include Customize Access for managing how and when people access devices like alarm systems, door locks, and garage door openers, with support for guest schedules. There's also a new Express Mode for unlocking door locks automatically as you approach, and support for robot vacuum cleaners is set to come later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-preferred-home-hub/">You Can Select a Preferred Home Hub in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-select-a-preferred-home-hub-in-ios-18.2429237/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Redesigning TestFlight App in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/apple-redesigning-testflight-app-in-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-redesigning-testflight-app-in-ios-18.2429234/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:31:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/apple-redesigning-testflight-app-in-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		<category>App Store Connect</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to overhaul the design of its TestFlight app that is available to developers for beta testing their apps, and the updated design was highlighted in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fkeUvZ4NRhg">WWDC session on App Store Connect</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/testflight-redesign.jpg" alt="" width="2722" height="1531" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955569" /><br/>
TestFlight in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> features a new invitation experience that will better showcase the app by highlighting key information including app name and icon, screenshots, developer name, build expiration date, and app description.<br/>
<br/>
The refreshed design looks much more similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> than the current TestFlight interface, which provides little in the way of app data beyond the features that are being tested. Apple's current design assumes that testers are familiar with an app that they're invited to test, while the refresh provides key information to testers who might not be in tune with what an app is designed to do.<br/>
<br/>
Along with design changes, the new version of the app lets developers enroll testers that meet multiple criteria, such as specific devices and operating system versions. TestFlight will only allow testers that meet the criteria to accept a public TestFlight invitation.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet released the redesigned TestFlight app, but it will likely come at some point this summer or in the fall when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; goes live.<br/>
<br/>
Other changes planned for &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Connect include a Nominations option for developers to inform the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Editorial Team about new content for consideration for an &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; feature, and alerts when an app gets an &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; feature that include marketing assets for social media.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store-connect/">App Store Connect</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/apple-redesigning-testflight-app-in-ios-18/">Apple Redesigning TestFlight App in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-redesigning-testflight-app-in-ios-18.2429234/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Solo Buds Unboxed, Available to Order Starting Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/beats-solo-buds-unboxing-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-solo-buds-unboxed-available-to-order-starting-next-week.2429228/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:03:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/beats-solo-buds-unboxing-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Beats Solo Buds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zkafMX3viGE">Beats Solo Buds unboxing video</a> on YouTube, providing a closer look at the wireless earbuds before they launch next week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/beats-solo-buds-red-pairing.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948608" /><br/>
Priced at &#36;79.99, the Beats Solo Buds feature up to 18 hours of battery life, a USB-C carrying case, and Find My support on both iOS and Android. However, they lack active noise cancellation, and the carrying case does not have a built-in battery and can only charge the earbuds when a USB-C cable is connected to an external power source.<br/>
<br/>
More details about the earbuds can be found in our initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">coverage of the Beats Studio Buds announcement</a> back in late April.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zkafMX3viGE?si=UxtgnuCCQCCOYCfB" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Beats Solo Buds will be available to pre-order on Apple's online store <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/beats-solo-buds-launch-date/">starting Tuesday, June 18</a>, ahead of a Thursday, June 20 launch.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats-solo-buds/">Beats Solo Buds</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/beats-solo-buds-unboxing-video/">Beats Solo Buds Unboxed, Available to Order Starting Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-solo-buds-unboxed-available-to-order-starting-next-week.2429228/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 and tvOS 18 Reintroduce SharePlay for Apple Music on HomePods and Apple TV</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-tvos-18-shareplay-homepod-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-and-tvos-18-reintroduce-shareplay-for-apple-music-on-homepods-and-apple-tv.2429222/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:38:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-tvos-18-shareplay-homepod-apple-tv/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		<category>SharePlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 and tvOS 18 reintroduce SharePlay for Apple Music on the HomePod, HomePod mini, and Apple TV. The feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/shareplay-music-control-homepod-apple-tv/">first appeared</a> in the iOS 17.4 and tvOS 17.4 betas earlier this year, but it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/apple-removes-shareplay-apple-tv-homepod/">was removed</a> before those updates were released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/SharePlay-Music-Control-Expanding-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933114" /><br/>
This feature allows others to control Apple Music playback on your HomePod or Apple TV with permission, regardless of whether they subscribe to the service. The primary user can decide whether to approve or deny each request.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already rolled out a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/13/whats-new-carplay-ios-17/">similar feature for CarPlay</a> last year, allowing anyone in a car to control music playback via SharePlay with permission.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomePod</h2><br/>
While playing a song in the Music app on your iPhone, tap the SharePlay icon at the bottom of the screen to bring up a QR code, which another person can scan with their iPhone or Android smartphone's camera to request access to music playback controls. Even a screenshot of the QR code suffices for remote access.<br/>
<br/>
The feature works on both the HomePod and HomePod mini, and we could imagine the QR code eventually being shown on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/20/homepod-with-screen-delayed-next-year/">long-rumored HomePod with a screen</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple TV</h2><br/>
With the tvOS 18 update, the Music app on the Apple TV can also show a QR code on the TV that guests can scan to request access to music controls.<br/>
<br/>
The expansion of this feature to the Apple TV and the HomePod is useful for house parties, allowing everyone to be the DJ.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18, tvOS 18, and HomePod software version 18 are currently in beta, and the updates will be widely released later this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shareplay/">SharePlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/ios-18-tvos-18-shareplay-homepod-apple-tv/">iOS 18 and tvOS 18 Reintroduce SharePlay for Apple Music on HomePods and Apple TV</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-and-tvos-18-reintroduce-shareplay-for-apple-music-on-homepods-and-apple-tv.2429222/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Reportedly Planning to Charge Apple for Violating Digital Markets Act</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/eu-plans-to-fine-apple-over-dma-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-reportedly-planning-to-charge-apple-for-violating-digital-markets-act.2429205/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:06:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/eu-plans-to-fine-apple-over-dma-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The European Commission plans to charge Apple for violating the Digital Markets Act after determining that the iPhone maker is not complying with obligations to allow app developers to "steer" users to offers outside of the App Store without fees, according to the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/31a996d5-b472-4357-953e-ace078494604"><em>Financial Times</em></a>, which cites three people familiar with the matter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
It appears that the EU is taking issue with Apple's <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/core-technology-fee/">Core Technology Fee</a>, but the exact charges that it allegedly plans to bring against Apple are unclear.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could face non-compliance fines of up to 5% of its average daily worldwide revenue, which is currently just over &#36;1 billion, according to the report.<br/>
<br/>
The report said the EU's findings are preliminary, so Apple may still have time to make any necessary changes on iOS before the charges are formally laid by regulators. In the event the EU moves forward with the charges, they would be formally announced by the European Commission over the "coming weeks," the report added.<br/>
<br/>
Apple made <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">major changes to the App Store, Apple Pay, Safari, and more</a> on the iPhone in the EU as part of iOS 17.4 earlier this year. Apple now allows alternative app marketplaces, but it still charges a Core Technology Fee. Apple also introduced a default web browser selection screen in Safari, now allows third-party web browsers to use web engines other than its own WebKit engine on the iPhone, and now allows third-party mobile wallet apps to access the iPhone's NFC chip for contactless payment functionality.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/eu-plans-to-fine-apple-over-dma-report/">EU Reportedly Planning to Charge Apple for Violating Digital Markets Act</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-reportedly-planning-to-charge-apple-for-violating-digital-markets-act.2429205/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Talk Show Live From WWDC 2024 Now Available on YouTube</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024-now-available-on-youtube.2429171/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:21:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Talk Show Live From WWDC 2024 is <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J7al_Gpolb8">now available to watch</a> on YouTube. <a href="https://daringfireball.net/"><em>Daring Fireball</em></a>'s John Gruber discussed Apple Intelligence and other WWDC announcements with Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi, marketing chief Greg Joswiak, and AI/machine learning head John Giannandrea in front of a live audience.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/J7al_Gpolb8?si=bKr6LuiH1qFjUjIp" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
The on-stage interview took place on Tuesday evening at the California Theatre in San Jose, California, and it ran for nearly two hours.<br/>
<br/>
Also check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/13/the-macrumors-show-wwdc-2024-recap-from-apple-park/">special WWDC episode of <em>The MacRumors Show</em> filmed at Apple Park</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024/">The Talk Show Live From WWDC 2024 Now Available on YouTube</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024-now-available-on-youtube.2429171/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Father&#039;s Day Deals on AirPods, MacBooks, iPads, Sonos Speakers, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-best-fathers-day-deals-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-fathers-day-deals-on-airpods-macbooks-ipads-sonos-speakers-and-more.2428449/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-best-fathers-day-deals-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking a huge collection of discounts on Apple products and related accessories this weekend as we head into the final days before Father's Day this Sunday, June 16. With two days to go until Father's Day, most orders placed today will probably miss the delivery window, but there are steep discounts here that are worth looking into even if they arrive a bit after the holiday. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/Fathers-Day-Deals-2020.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-745702" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
These sales include discounts on AirPods, iPads, MacBooks, Sonos speakers, and other products. All of the deals listed in this article have already begun, and most of them will last until Sunday, June 16, unless otherwise stated.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best Father's Day Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"><strong>Sonos Father's Day deals</strong></a> on speakers, subwoofers, and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmpNnKXxDCO"><strong>Samsung's new 2024 monitors</strong></a> - Save 10% when you buy 2, or 15% when you buy 3</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659964727"><strong>Eufy SmartTrack Link 4-Pack</strong></a> for &#36;48.99, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497"><strong>Anker MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</strong></a> for &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>AirPods 2</strong></a> for &#36;79.99 at Amazon (&#36;49 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTH5K5R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>Apple Watch Series 9</strong></a> for &#36;299.99 at Amazon (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJ8FZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>AirPods Max</strong></a> for &#36;449.00 at Amazon (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22TZBC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>13-inch M3 MacBook Air</strong></a> for &#36;899.00 at Amazon (&#36;200 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airpods-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954132" /><br/>
AirPods deals are in abundance this week, perfectly timed for anyone who wants to pick up a pair for Father's Day. The rarest discount is &#36;100 off the AirPods Max, but you'll also find steep markdowns on AirPods 2, AirPods 3, and AirPods Pro 2, all on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;139.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJ8FZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-watch-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954133" /><br/>
Similar to AirPods, we're tracking discounts across the entire Apple Watch lineup this week, including the Apple Watch SE, Apple Watch Series 9, and Apple Watch Ultra 2. These deals can all be found on Amazon this time around, and most color and band combinations are delayed beyond Father's Day.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTH5K5R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSVDF576%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><h2>M2 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m2-ipad-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954134" /><br/>
Amazon has up to &#36;80 off the M2 iPad Air this weekend, starting at &#36;569.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air, down from &#36;599.00. These models just launched last month, and included the M2 chip, Touch ID, a Retina display, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5VFYQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;569.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6FSV3%2Fref%3Dtwister_B0D3KGR4NB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26_encoding%3DUTF8%26geniuslink%3Dtrue%26th%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;659.00, down from &#36;699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7TK2G%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,034.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li></ul><h3>13-inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5XNCT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;754.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8W54H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;849.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7YQC1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,034.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5WM18%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,219.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li></ul><h2>M1 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m1-ipad-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954135" /><br/>
Over at Best Buy, you can find &#36;200 off the previous generation M1 iPad Air in every color of every configuration. Prices start at &#36;399.99 for 64GB Wi-Fi, and include both Wi-Fi and cellular models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmpJt3y7y0e"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmpJvw2p62E"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmpJws4mVoX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (64GB Cellular) for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmpJw4XAAF7"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (256GB Cellular) for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><h2>M2 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/2022-ipad-pro-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954136" /><br/>
Similar to the M1 iPad Air, Best Buy also has great discounts on the previous generation M2 iPad Pro at up to &#36;500 off select tablets. You'll find steep markdowns on both 11-inch and 12.9-inch models, with the majority of the deals focused on Wi-Fi models.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmpI1MV96zD">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li></ul><h3>12.9-inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmpI5pKofqR">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;899.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li></ul><h2>M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/new-macbook-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954140" /><br/>
Deals on the M3 MacBook Air are mainly focused on 13-inch models, at both Amazon and Best Buy. Amazon has the best deal on the 256GB entry-level model, down to just &#36;899.00 this week and &#36;200 off the original price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22TZBC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmpJL3MEd8e"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;259 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,139.05</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX21ZSBM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,329.00</div></a></div><h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/old-macbook-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954139" /><br/>
Just like the M3 MacBook Air, deals on the previous generation model are focused on the 13-inch sizes. Amazon has &#36;170 off every model in every colorway, starting at &#36;829.00 for 256GB and rising to &#36;1,029.00 for 512GB.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;829.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3CGXWN4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,029.00</div></a></div><h2>Sonos</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/sonos-fathers-day-blue.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954109" /><br/>
Sonos began its <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Father's Day sale</a> last week, and it's still going on this weekend. In this sale, you can find steep discounts on select home theater audio equipment. This includes record low prices on the Sonos Arc soundbar (&#36;719), as well as various discounted bundles, all of which are rare deals we haven't tracked since earlier in the year.<br/>
<br/>
This sale has a good balance between individual Sonos products and bundles that should help elevate your home theater setup with various soundbars, subwoofers, and speakers. Highlights of the event include the <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Sonos Arc for &#36;719</a> (&#36;180 off) and <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sonos Sub Gen 3 for &#36;639</a> (&#36;160 off), which are rarely discounted outside of holiday events like this one. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Speakers and Soundbars</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100">Era 100 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;199, down from &#36;249</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/move-2">Move 2 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;336, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-300">Era 300 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;359, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/beam">Beam (Gen 2) Soundbar</a> - &#36;399, down from &#36;499</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sub (Gen 3) Subwoofer</a> - &#36;639, down from &#36;799</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Arc Soundbar</a> - &#36;719, down from &#36;899</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Bundles</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc-mount-set">Arc + Wall Mount Bundle</a> - &#36;798, down from &#36;978</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/multiroom-entertainment-set-arc-and-move-2">Arc + Move 2 Speaker Bundle</a> - &#36;1,055, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/personal-entertainment-set-sonos-ace-arc">Arc + Sonos Ace Headphones Bundle</a> - &#36;1,168, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/3-1-entertainment-set-beam-sub">Beam + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,038, down from &#36;1,298</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/surround-set-arc-era-100-pair">Arc + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,117, down from &#36;1,397</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-arc-sub">Arc + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,358, down from &#36;1,698</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/premium-immersive-set-beam-sub-era-100-pair">Beam + Sub + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,436, down from &#36;1,796</li></ul><h2>Charging Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/anker-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954158" /><br/>
Amazon this weekend has a large collection of discounts from <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Anker</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">Eufy</a>, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Jackery</a>, including a wide array of wall chargers, Bluetooth trackers, and other USB-C accessories. Some of these deals will require you to clip an on-page coupon then head to the checkout screen before you see the final sale price, and some require a Prime membership.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Eufy</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659902126">SmartTrack Link 1-Pack</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659917907">SmartTrack Link 2-Pack</a> - &#36;29.88, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659964727">SmartTrack Link 4-Pack</a> - &#36;48.99, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;16.98, down from &#36;29.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Anker</h3><br/>
<strong>Audio</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;64.99, down from &#36;79.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Portable Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1717512554052">MagGo Power Bank 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1717512037932">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;38.24 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Power Stations</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1717513024737">MagGo 3-in-1 Folding Charging Station</a> - &#36;93.49, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;112.46, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Wall Chargers</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;42.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;49.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Hubs</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<h3>Jackery</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D2KZY522%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NXT41HEMR2FG%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NXT41HEMR2FG_1717512999884">Explorer 600 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;419.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LPIOTAJGGK4P%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LPIOTAJGGK4P_1713373339383">Solar Generator 300 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2HOQ15SVTKP5E%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2HOQ15SVTKP5E_1713373175628">Expansion Battery Pack for 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;509.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li> <br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB083KBKJ8Q%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1KHS8AIX808CW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1KHS8AIX808CW_1713373227768">Explorer 1000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;619.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.231PUR2N7PBPM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.231PUR2N7PBPM_1713373287626">Explorer 2000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU_1710770037246">Expansion Battery Pack for 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.B0BZ8DZ3HR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3M5389ELMN7TD_1713385917457%26th%3D1">Explorer 3000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;2,149.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-best-fathers-day-deals-2024/">The Best Father&#039;s Day Deals on AirPods, MacBooks, iPads, Sonos Speakers, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-fathers-day-deals-on-airpods-macbooks-ipads-sonos-speakers-and-more.2428449/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s What&#039;s New in Apple Wallet on iOS 18 for Event Tickets and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/whats-new-in-apple-wallet-on-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-whats-new-in-apple-wallet-on-ios-18-for-event-tickets-and-more.2429198/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:32:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/whats-new-in-apple-wallet-on-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 includes a handful of enhancements to the Wallet app on the iPhone, with new features for Apple Pay, Apple Cash, event tickets, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Wallet-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955476" /><br/>
Below, we outline everything new for the Wallet app on iOS 18, based on information from <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/new-features-come-to-apple-services-this-fall/">Apple's press release</a> and a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2024/10108/">WWDC 2024 coding session</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Redesigned Event Tickets</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/redesigned-event-tickets-in-Wallet-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955528" /><br/>
Event tickets have an all-new design in the Wallet app on iOS 18, complete with relevant info like a map of the stadium and other venues, local weather forecasts, recommended Apple Music playlists for concerts, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Event Tickets as Live Activities</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Live-Activities-Event-Tickets.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955525" /><br/>
Event tickets now work with the Live Activities feature, so you can view your seating information on the Lock Screen and in the Dynamic Island when you are near the venue. Live Activities also appear on the Apple Watch on watchOS 11.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tap to Cash</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/tap-to-cash-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954862" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/11/tap-to-cash-ios-18-pay-touch-iphones/">Tap to Cash</a> is a new iOS 18 feature that allows users in the U.S. to send and receive Apple Cash by simply holding two iPhones together.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tap to Add New Cards to Wallet App</h2><br/>
A new Tap to Provision feature on iOS 18 will allow users to add eligible credit or debit cards to the Wallet app by simply tapping their card on the back of their iPhone. Apple says this feature will only be available in select countries.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pay in Any Desktop Browser</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Pay-Code-Scan-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955376" /><br/>
iPhone users who update to iOS 18 will be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/13/ios-18-apple-pay-in-any-desktop-browser/">use Apple Pay in desktop web browsers beyond Safari</a>, such as Chrome, Edge, Firefox, and others. The computer running the browser can even be a Windows PC instead of a Mac.<br/>
<br/>
Any website that implements the latest version of Apple Pay will support this new system. When a customer checks out with Apple Pay in a desktop browser other than Safari, a code will appear on the screen that can be scanned in the Camera app on an iPhone running iOS 18 or later, allowing them to complete the purchase on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pay Adds Credit Card Rewards</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Pay-rewards-and-installments-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955527" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 18, Apple Pay will allow users to redeem rewards and access installment loan offerings from eligible credit and debit cards.<br/>
<br/>
Here are the details from Apple:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>The ability to redeem rewards will be available beginning in the U.S. with Discover and Synchrony, and across Apple Pay issuers with Fiserv.</li><br/>
<li>The ability to access installments from credit and debit cards will roll out starting in Australia with ANZ; in Spain with CaixaBank; in the U.K. with HSBC and Monzo; and in the U.S. with Citi, Synchrony, and issuers with Fiserv.</li><br/>
<li>Users in the U.S. will be able to apply for loans directly through Affirm when they check out with Apple Pay.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Card Data in More Budget Apps</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Card-FinanceKit.jpeg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955532" /><br/>
Apple has made its <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/financekit">FinanceKit</a> API available to all developers, meaning that any finance or budgeting app will be able to display Apple Card, Apple Card Savings, and Apple Cash balance and transaction details with a user's permission.<br/>
<br/>
This feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/">debuted with iOS 17.4</a>, but it was limited to select apps like Copilot.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/whats-new-in-apple-wallet-on-ios-18/">Here&#039;s What&#039;s New in Apple Wallet on iOS 18 for Event Tickets and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-whats-new-in-apple-wallet-on-ios-18-for-event-tickets-and-more.2429198/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 14 vs. iPhone 16: 30+ Upgrades to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16-30-upgrades-to-expect.2422087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16&#038;post_date=1718384400/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 14</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>No Top Comments</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After over a year of reports, there are now more than a dozen specific rumors about the features and improvements set to be offered by the two non-Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models later in 2024. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPhone-14-vs-16-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-941488" /></div><br/>
While the upgrades that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; offers over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> will likely be at the center of Apple's marketing strategy later this year, many users are on two-year upgrade cycles, so the features introduced on both the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will stack up. All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their two direct forerunners are listed below, using information from a range of reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">previously covered</a>. We will update this article as more rumors emerge in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
This guide focuses on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, but to learn about how we are expecting the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro to improve on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">see our other comparison article</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design">Design</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to largely carry over the design of their predecessors. As a result, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will be a relatively significant evolution over the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌, featuring slightly rounded edges, a frosted glass back, and a vertical rear camera arrangement to facilitate spatial video capture. Other important design changes are expected to include the removal of the mute switch in favor of the Action button introduced on last year's Pro models and the introduction of an all-new "Capture" button.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Aluminum chassis with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Aluminum chassis with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Glossy glass back</td><br/>
 <td>Color-infused frosted glass back</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Notch" TrueDepth camera array</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Diagonally arranged rear camera array</td><br/>
 <td>Vertically arranged rear camera array to support spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action Button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>"Capture Button" to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="displays">Displays</h3><br/>
For &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; users, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will offer many of the display upgrades that came to the previous generation, as well as a more efficient OLED panel thanks to micro-lens technology.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>800 nits max brightness (typical)</td><br/>
 <td>1,000 nits max brightness (typical)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1,200 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 <td>1,600 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>2,000 nits peak brightness (outdoor)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="cameras">Cameras</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; introduced a major camera upgrade for Apple's standard smartphone lineup, bringing over the 48-megapixel camera of the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro. With a number of other improvements such as spatial video capture, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; should be a significant camera upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.5 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.6 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x and 1x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, and 2x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_memory_and_connectivity">Chip, Memory, and Connectivity</h3><br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models rumored to receive the same A18 chip as the Pro models, the new models could offer a major performance improvement over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, which features the A15 Bionic chip first introduced in 2021. The 2GB of additional memory and the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip are also due to be notable upgrades. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N5P" enhanced 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory (+33%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting denser batteries and faster charging capabilities. It is worth noting that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus is rumored to feature a smaller battery than its predecessors, but it is not clear how this will affect actual battery life. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 14</strong>: 3,279 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 14 Plus</strong>: 4,325 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 3,561 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 4,006 mAh battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 27W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging (48% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; (33% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Setting to prevent charging above 80%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Battery manufacture date, first use, and cycle count information in Settings</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will be the first standard-line <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to support Apple Intelligence, Apple's upcoming artificial intelligence system, thanks to the more powerful Neural Engine in the A18 chip. The device is also rumored to tout upgraded microphones and new color options. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Support for Apple Intelligence</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Midnight, Starlight, (PRODUCT)RED, Blue, Purple, and Yellow</td><br/>
 <td>Available in Blue, Pink, Green, Black, and White</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; was a fairly significant upgrade over the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ in 2023, introducing a more modern design with the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;, a USB-C port, and a 48-megapixel camera. The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will build on these upgrades, offering the Capture and Action buttons, Apple Intelligence, and spatial video capture. With over 30 upgrades rumored to be in store, many ‌current &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ users will find upgrading to an ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model worthwhile, if not essential.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to launch in the fall. Apple usually hosts an event every September to unveil new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, with launch following just over a week later. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16/">iPhone 14 vs. iPhone 16: 30+ Upgrades to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16-30-upgrades-to-expect.2422087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
