<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:04:37 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Demand Soars as Apple Widens Lead Over Samsung and Xiaomi</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/ipad-demand-soars-as-apple-widens-lead/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-demand-soars-as-apple-widens-lead-over-samsung-and-xiaomi.2457065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:16:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/ipad-demand-soars-as-apple-widens-lead/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Canalys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple led the global tablet market in the first quarter of 2025, achieving 14% year-over-year shipment growth amid heightened demand for iPads, according to new data from <a href="https://www.canalys.com/newsroom/worldwide-tablet-market-q1-2025">Canalys</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/m3-ipad-air-new-green.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1001086" /><br/>
Worldwide tablet shipments reached 36.8 million units in the first quarter 2025, representing an 8.5% year-over-year increase. Apple shipped 13.7 million iPads during the quarter, up from 12.1 million in the first quarter of 2024, raising its global market share from 35.5% to 37.3%. The company's performance came in the context of growing replacement demand for tablets first purchased during the early stages of the COVID-19 pandemic, supported by recent hardware updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's shipment growth outpaced the broader market average and occurred despite increased competitive pressure from Chinese vendors including Xiaomi, Huawei, and HONOR. According to Canalys, these brands gained market share by targeting lower cost segments with wide device portfolios and by leveraging ecosystem integration across devices. Xiaomi, in particular, saw a 56.1% year-over-year increase in tablet shipments, reaching 3.1 million units and surpassing Lenovo for the first time.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/canalys/">Canalys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/ipad-demand-soars-as-apple-widens-lead/">iPad Demand Soars as Apple Widens Lead Over Samsung and Xiaomi</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-demand-soars-as-apple-widens-lead-over-samsung-and-xiaomi.2457065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Tiburon to macOS Pacific: Which Name Will Apple Use This Year?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/macos-16-name-possibilities/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-tiburon-to-macos-pacific-which-name-will-apple-use-this-year.2457063/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:49:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/macos-16-name-possibilities/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Every year heading into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC</a>, one thought on many Mac fans' minds is what Apple will choose as the name for the next version of macOS. The tradition dates all the way back to the beginning of Mac OS X with its big cat names like Leopard, and Apple shifted to California-themed names with the unveiling of OS X Mavericks in 2013.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-2024-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983350" /><br/>
Back in 2014, we discovered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/04/24/future-os-x-names-california/">more than 20 California-themed trademark applications</a> filed by various limited-liability companies, which were all but certain to be shell companies created by Apple to hide its identity. Over time, some of the trademarks like Yosemite, Sierra, Mojave, Monterey, Mojave, Ventura, Sonoma, and Sequoia were indeed used as macOS names, while trademark applications for other names were abandoned.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has still proceeded to use some of the names with abandoned trademark filings as macOS names, such as Big Sur in 2020. So, there is still a possibility that macOS 16 will use one of the names that Apple had filed to protect many years ago.<br/>
<br/>
Here is a list of the remaining macOS name possibilities that Apple had filed to protect:<ul><br/>
  <li>California</li><br/>
  <li>Condor</li><br/>
  <li>Diablo</li><br/>
  <li>Farallon</li><br/>
  <li>Grizzly</li><br/>
  <li>Mammoth</li><br/>
  <li>Miramar</li><br/>
  <li>Pacific</li><br/>
  <li>Redtail</li><br/>
  <li>Redwood</li><br/>
  <li>Rincon</li><br/>
  <li>Shasta</li><br/>
  <li>Skyline</li><br/>
  <li>Tiburon</li><br/>
</ul>Apple's trend of using Tiburon in iPhone marketing images in recent years has led some fans to speculate that macOS 16 could be named macOS Tiburon, but this is obviously far from concrete evidence. Indeed, it was once a trademarked name, though.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iPhone-Tiburon.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001590" /><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/WWDC-2024-Tiburon.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001592" /><br/>
Of course, there is no guarantee that Apple will ever use any of these names. It is simply fun to think about the possibilities each year.<br/>
<br/>
WWDC 2025 begins <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">on Monday, June 9</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/macos-16-name-possibilities/">macOS Tiburon to macOS Pacific: Which Name Will Apple Use This Year?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-tiburon-to-macos-pacific-which-name-will-apple-use-this-year.2457063/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Has Low Prices on Apple Pencil Pro (&#36;99) and AirTag 4-Pack (&#36;79.98)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/amazon-low-apple-pencil-airtag/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-low-prices-on-apple-pencil-pro-99-and-airtag-4-pack-79-98.2457057/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:13:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/amazon-low-apple-pencil-airtag/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a handful of Apple accessory discounts on Amazon, including an all-time low price for the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil Pro</a> and a solid deal on the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirTag 4-Pack</a>. Neither deal requires a coupon code this time around, as both have been applied automatically by Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956589" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the Apple Pencil Pro, you can get this accessory for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is a match for the record low price on the Apple Pencil Pro, and it's a deal that doesn't typically stick around long on Amazon, so if you've been waiting for it to return, be sure to check it out soon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Secondly, Amazon has the AirTag 4-Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.98</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. This is a second-best price on the accessory, and you can find the 1-Pack on sale as well on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;24.95</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airtag-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940079" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;79.98</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/amazon-low-apple-pencil-airtag/">Amazon Has Low Prices on Apple Pencil Pro (&#36;99) and AirTag 4-Pack (&#36;79.98)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-low-prices-on-apple-pencil-pro-99-and-airtag-4-pack-79-98.2457057/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV 4K: Play Game Console or Cable Box Audio on HomePod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-tv-4k-play-game-console-audio-homepod/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-4k-play-game-console-or-cable-box-audio-on-homepod.2457056/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:01:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-tv-4k-play-game-console-audio-homepod&#038;post_date=1747242114/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple TV 4K (second- and third-generation) is capable of relaying audio from a compatible TV to a HomePod – even when you're not using your Apple TV. This allows you to stream audio from a TV-connected game console or other set-top box straight to Apple's smart speakers. Keep reading to learn more and how to set it up.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/PS5-AppleTV-and-HomePod-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800425" /><br/>
The second- and third-generation Apple TV 4K supports two additional connection standards, called ARC and eARC. ARC (Audio Return Channel) is a feature of HDMI 1.4 that enables audio from a device to be sent to a compatible TV and relayed through its HDMI port to a separate audio receiver, speaker, or sound bar. Meanwhile, eARC (enhanced ARC) adds support for the passthrough of higher bandwidth audio like Dolby Atmos, as well as 5.1 and 7.1 surround sound.<br/>
<br/>
On Apple TV 4K, ARC and eARC support effectively allows a HomePod or HomePod mini (or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/create-homepod-mini-stereo-pair/">stereo-paired Homepods</a> in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/set-up-home-theater-audio-homepod-apple-tv-4k/">Home Theater Audio setup</a>) to play audio from other TV-connected devices like a cable box, PS5, or Xbox Series X. The following steps show you how to get it set up. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Set Up ARC or eARC on Apple TV 4K</h2><br/>
Make sure that your TV supports ARC or eARC. You can check if it does by seeing if there's an ARC label next to the HDMI port that your Apple TV is connected to. Alternatively, check your TV manual or try contacting the TV manufacturer.<br/>
<ol><li>On your Apple TV, launch the <strong>Settings</strong> app.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Video and Audio ➝ Audio Output</strong>.<br/>
<li>Under "Default Audio Output," make sure the HomePod(s) in the same room as your TV are selected.</li><br/>
<li>Under "Audio Return Channel," select <strong>Play Television Audio</strong>. You'll know ARC or eARC is enabled when it says On (ARC) or On (eARC).</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/tvos-16-apple-tv-settings-video-audio-default-audio-output-homepod-selected.jpg" alt="settings" width="1560" height="884" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001553" /><br/>
<br/>
If ARC or eARC doesn't work for you after following the above steps: assuming your TV supports the standard, check whether you need to turn on ARC, eARC, or HDMI-CEC in your TV's settings.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-tv-4k-play-game-console-audio-homepod/">Apple TV 4K: Play Game Console or Cable Box Audio on HomePod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-4k-play-game-console-or-cable-box-audio-on-homepod.2457056/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps to Feature Custom City Experience for Formula 1 Grand Prix</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/apple-maps-to-feature-experience-for-formula-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-to-feature-custom-city-experience-for-formula-1-grand-prix.2457053/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 05:56:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/apple-maps-to-feature-experience-for-formula-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/apple-maps-brings-a-detailed-city-experience-to-formula-1-grand-prix-de-monaco/">announced</a> a new custom city experience and guide for the upcoming Formula 1 TAG Heuer Grand Prix de Monaco 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Apple-Maps-F1-Monaco-Grand-Prix-hero.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2161" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1001544" /><br/>
<br/>
The new Detailed City Experience includes custom-designed 3D Monégasque landmarks of significant locations, such as Casino de Monte-Carlo, Fairmont Monte Carlo, Hôtel de Paris Monte-Carlo, Yacht Club de Monaco, and the F1 Paddock Club. When dark mode is enabled at dusk, the 3D rendition of Monaco gains a unique moonlit glow effect.<br/>
<br/>
There are also new details to represent road markings, land cover, trees, and public transit routes, and important navigation details like turn lanes, medians, bus and bike lanes, and pedestrian crossings. There is also a new windshield view for drivers, which displays a road-level view as the user approaches interchanges.<br/>
<br/>
The F1 racetrack will be highlighted with markers for the circuit's turns, as well as 3D representations of grandstands, footbridges, the finish line, and more. The Maps app will also show advisories like road closures. Apple senior vice president of services, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a>, said:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Apple Maps is the best way to navigate and explore the world, so we're excited to bring this amazing experience to F1 fans and attendees of the Grand Prix de Monaco. Whether fans are there in person or watching from afar, the beautifully designed Detailed City Experience and Monaco Grand Prix features give them an incredible view into Monaco, just in time for the race and the upcoming premiere of F1 The Movie.<br/>
<br/>
They'll be able to navigate the principality during the iconic Formula 1 TAG Heuer Grand Prix de Monaco 2025 and hunt down key landmarks in Monaco and the race, to truly feel part of the action ahead of the film's launch at the end of June.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
In celebration of next month's release of Apple Original Films' "F1 The Movie," starring Brad Pitt, Maps users will also be able to explore a custom Guide featuring the world's most iconic F1 racetracks, including Monaco and other tracks featured in the movie. <br/>
<br/>
The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> experience rolls out later today. The Formula 1 Grand Prix de Monaco takes place from May 23 to May 25. Apple's original "F1 The Movie" debuts on June 25.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/apple-maps-to-feature-experience-for-formula-1/">Apple Maps to Feature Custom City Experience for Formula 1 Grand Prix</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-to-feature-custom-city-experience-for-formula-1-grand-prix.2457053/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: 2027 iPhones Could Adopt Advanced AI Memory Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/2027-iphones-advanced-ai-memory-tech/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-2027-iphones-could-adopt-advanced-ai-memory-technology.2457050/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:35:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/2027-iphones-advanced-ai-memory-tech/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is believed to be developing several technological innovations to mark the 20th anniversary of the iPhone, and one key technology it's considering is Mobile High Bandwidth Memory (HBM), according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.etnews.com/20250514000084">ETNews</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/M3-chip-series-unified-memory-architecture.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1350" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920050" /><br/>
HBM is a type of DRAM that stacks memory chips vertically  and connects them via tiny vertical interconnects called Through-Silicon Vias (TSVs) to dramatically boost signal transmission speeds. It's primarily used in AI servers today, and is often referred to as AI memory due to its ability to support AI processing alongside GPUs. <br/>
<br/>
Mobile HBM is what the term suggests – a variant of the technology for mobile devices that is designed to deliver very high data throughput while minimizing power consumption and the physical footprint of the RAM dies. Apple is looking to enhance on-device AI capabilities, and <em>ETNews</em> reports that connecting mobile HBM to the iPhone's GPU units is  being considered as a strong candidate for achieving this goal.<br/>
<br/>
The technology could be key for running massive AI models on-device, such as for large language model inference or advanced vision tasks, without draining battery or increasing latency.<br/>
<br/>
The report indicates that Apple may have already discussed its plans with major memory suppliers like Samsung Electronics and SK hynix, both of which are developing their own versions of mobile HBM.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung is reportedly using a packaging approach called VCS (Vertical Cu-post Stack), while SK hynix is working on a method called VFO (Vertical wire Fan-Out). Both companies aim for mass production sometime after 2026.<br/>
<br/>
As always though, there are manufacturing challenges. Mobile HBM is a lot more expensive to manufacture than current LPDDR memory. It could also face thermal constraints in slim devices like iPhones, and the 3D stacking and TSVs require highly sophisticated packaging and yield management.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple does adopt this technology for its 2027 iPhone lineup, it would be yet another example of the company pushing the envelope for its 20th anniversary iPhone, which is rumored to feature a completely bezel-less display that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/20th-anniversary-iphone-no-visible-frame-bezels/">curves around all four edges of the device</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/2027-iphones-advanced-ai-memory-tech/">Report: 2027 iPhones Could Adopt Advanced AI Memory Technology</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-2027-iphones-could-adopt-advanced-ai-memory-technology.2457050/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>20th Anniversary iPhone&#039;s Display May Have No Visible Frame or Bezels</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/20th-anniversary-iphone-no-visible-frame-bezels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/20th-anniversary-iphones-display-may-have-no-visible-frame-or-bezels.2457049/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 02:35:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/20th-anniversary-iphone-no-visible-frame-bezels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly considering a radical redesign for the 20th anniversary iPhone that could feature a completely bezel-less display that curves around all four edges of the device, claims a new report out of Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/bezel-less-iphone-concept.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001516" /><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.etnews.com/20250514000320">ETNews</a></em> writes that Apple is aiming to use "four-edge bending" display technology for the 2027 iPhone that would curve not just along the left and right sides as seen in some current smartphones, but also wrap around the top and bottom edges. This would create a truly borderless visual experience with content flowing seamlessly across all sides of the device.<br/>
<br/>
This follows a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/20th-anniversary-iphone-all-screen-design/">report</a> by <em>Bloomberg</em> over the weekend that said Apple plans to launch a "mostly glass, curved iPhone without any cutouts in the display." <em>The Information</em> last week also cited <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/20th-anniversary-iphone-all-screen-report/">multiple sources</a> claiming that at least one new iPhone model launching in 2027 will have a truly edge-to-edge display. <em>Bloomberg</em> previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/apple-new-20th-anniversary-design-iphone-pro/">reported</a> that the device would be a Pro model in Apple's 2027 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Based on the latest report, the ambitious design would eliminate traditional screen borders entirely, potentially marking one of the most significant design shifts in the iPhone's history since the 10th anniversary iPhone X, which saw Apple drop the Home button, introduce a notched display, and adopt an intuitive swipe gesture-based navigation interface.<br/>
<br/>
The new display technology is said to be part of Apple's broader push toward next-generation hardware for the commemorative iPhone. The company is also reportedly looking to develop an OLED display driver IC (DDI) based on 16nm FinFET process technology, instead of the traditional 28nm planar process currently used.<br/>
<br/>
The display driver technology would apparently deliver significant power efficiency improvements, which is likely to be increasingly important as smartphones get thinner and enhanced on-device AI features demand more power. The report also claims that Apple's 20th anniversary iPhone could include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/2027-iphone-game-changing-silicon-battery/">pure silicon batteries</a> instead of graphite-based ones for increased energy density.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to begin discussions with OLED suppliers Samsung Display and LG Display about implementing the advanced technologies for the anniversary model, according to the report.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Technical Challenges</h2><br/>
Achieving a four-sided curved all-display design would present Apple with some major technical challenges, such as placing the front-facing sensors, cameras, and speakers under the display. <br/>
<br/>
As a stepping stone towards this all-screen design in 2027, <em>The Information</em> on Tuesday reported that the iPhone 18 Pro and iPhone 18 Pro Max will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-rumor/">equipped with under-screen Face ID</a>, with only a small pinhole remaining for the front camera on those devices. Counterpoint Research vice president Ross Young has since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-again-rumored/">corroborated</a> the report.<br/>
<br/>
As for the front-facing camera, several Android phones already feature under-display selfie cameras, and Apple has reportedly been working on its own solution for some time. According to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/">April 2024 report</a>, LG Innotek – one of Apple's Korean suppliers – is developing under-display cameras that leave no visible hole when inactive. These systems use a "freeform optic" multiple lens array designed to reduce image distortion and improve brightness, compensating for the light loss that typically occurs when a camera sits behind a display.<br/>
<br/>
However, another concern adopting a four-sided curved all-screen design would be structural integrity, since bending the screen on all sides would introduce new stress points that could be more vulnerable to damage from drops. The described design could also require big changes to user interaction. With no bezels to rest fingers on, Apple would likely need to develop new palm-rejection algorithms and potentially revise iOS gesture navigation for edge-sensitive input.<br/>
<br/>
Assuming the reports are accurate, Apple has some major hardware and software hurdles to overcome over the next two years. If the company can pull it off though, such a design sounds like a fitting way to celebrate two decades of Apple's most iconic product. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/20th-anniversary-iphone-no-visible-frame-bezels/">20th Anniversary iPhone&#039;s Display May Have No Visible Frame or Bezels</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/20th-anniversary-iphones-display-may-have-no-visible-frame-or-bezels.2457049/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 18 Pro Models Again Rumored to Feature Under-Screen Face ID</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-again-rumored/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-pro-models-again-rumored-to-feature-under-screen-face-id.2457034/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:23:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-again-rumored/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Face ID</category>
		<category>iPhone 18</category>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 17 Pro models are still around four months away, there are already rumors about next year's iPhone 18 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iPhone-Top-Left-Hole-Punch-Face-ID-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000739" /><br/>
The latest word comes from Counterpoint Research vice president Ross Young, who has a good track record with display-related information for future Apple products. In a <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1922462041882952044">social media post today</a>, he relayed more information that suggests the iPhone 18 Pro models will be equipped with an under-screen Face ID system.<br/>
<br/>
"At the SID Business Conference today, OTI Lumionics CEO Michael Helander confirmed that they expect phones with under panel Face ID using their materials to be available for sale in 2026," wrote Young. "This suggests that iPhone 18 Pro models will have under panel Face ID with other brands and models to follow."<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, <em>The Information</em>'s Wayne Ma also reported that iPhone 18 Pro models will feature under-screen Face ID. He said the devices will have only a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-rumor/">small hole in the top-left corner of the screen</a>, to accommodate the front camera. The devices will no longer have a pill-shaped cutout at the top of the screen, according to the report, but is unclear if that means the Dynamic Island feature will be discontinued.<br/>
<br/>
Apple should release the iPhone 18 Pro models in September 2026.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/face-id/">Face ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-18/">iPhone 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-again-rumored/">iPhone 18 Pro Models Again Rumored to Feature Under-Screen Face ID</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-pro-models-again-rumored-to-feature-under-screen-face-id.2457034/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Android 16 Getting Live Updates, Similar to iPhone&#039;s Live Activity</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/android-16-live-activity-copy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/android-16-getting-live-updates-similar-to-iphones-live-activity.2457032/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/android-16-live-activity-copy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today previewed the <a href="https://blog.google/products/android/material-3-expressive-android-wearos-launch/">next-generation version of Android</a>, which has an updated design language that's more expressive, and a range of new features. One of the main new additions is Live Updates, a feature that mirrors Live Activity on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/android-live-updates.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="563" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001496" /><br/>
Live Updates lets Android users track progress notifications from apps in real-time, much like Live Activity. Google says that Live Updates will work with top delivery, ride share, and navigation apps.<br/>
<br/>
With Live Activity, incoming food deliveries, sports games, and more can be tracked from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Lock Screen or with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, and Google's feature works in a similar way. Android users will see Live Updates on the lock screen and home screen, and can tap into a menu bar option to get more information.<br/>
<br/>
Google is revamping Android with an interface focused on color, movement, and haptics, and it'll be interesting to see how it compares to the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> redesign that Apple has in the works.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Introducing Material 3 Expressive" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M8OkHgELmmI" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Google took some cues from Apple on security, adding a Find Hub that's similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> app for tracking people, items, and devices, with Google even teaming up with airlines for luggage recovery. There's also an Advanced Protection option that looks similar to Lockdown Mode, offering additional safeguards against malware and suspicious contact for journalists and politicians.<br/>
<br/>
More new features that are coming to Android 16 will be introduced at Google I/O next week.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/android-16-live-activity-copy/">Android 16 Getting Live Updates, Similar to iPhone&#039;s Live Activity</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/android-16-getting-live-updates-similar-to-iphones-live-activity.2457032/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>More Than 1 Billion RCS Messages Are Sent Daily on Android and iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/android-ios-rcs-messages-1-billion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-than-1-billion-rcs-messages-are-sent-daily-on-android-and-ios.2457030/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:23:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/android-ios-rcs-messages-1-billion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over a billion <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a> messages are sent on a daily basis in the United States, <a href="https://blog.google/products/android/billion-rcs-messages/">Google said today</a>. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, or Rich Communication Services, is a communication protocol that replaced the prior SMS and MMS messaging standards.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/RCS-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994897" /><br/>
It was developed by the GSM Association, but Google has been championing it for years. Apple held out on adopting &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; for quite some time, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">finally added support</a> with the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. On devices running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; is the default messaging protocol for texts between an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> user and an Android user.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's adoption of &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; has undoubtedly increased the number of &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; messages sent per day, but Google's 1 billion figure includes Android to Android text messages along with Android to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; text messages (and vice versa).<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; is a notable improvement over SMS and MMS, and it makes for a better texting experience between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users and Android users, as Android users can't take advantage of iMessage. Some of the &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; features:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Support for higher resolution photos and videos.</li><br/>
 	<li>Support for larger file sizes and file sharing.</li><br/>
 	<li>Audio messages.</li><br/>
 	<li>Cross-platform emoji reactions.</li><br/>
 	<li>Real-time typing indicators and read receipts.</li><br/>
 	<li>Better group chats with support for removing people.</li><br/>
 	<li>The option to send messages over cellular or Wi-Fi.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
For &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; conversations, iMessage is still the default, but &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; has made "green bubble" texting with Android users less of a hassle.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; is supported by the major carriers in the United States, but some smaller carriers like Boost Mobile, Mint Mobile, Ting, and others have yet to add support.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/android-ios-rcs-messages-1-billion/">More Than 1 Billion RCS Messages Are Sent Daily on Android and iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-than-1-billion-rcs-messages-are-sent-daily-on-android-and-ios.2457030/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Ecovacs&#039; New X9 Pro Omni Robot Vacuum Features HomeKit Integration</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ecovacs-x9-pro-omni-robot-homekit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ecovacs-new-x9-pro-omni-robot-vacuum-features-homekit-integration.2457027/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:15:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ecovacs-x9-pro-omni-robot-homekit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Home</category>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ecovacs today announced the launch of its new flagship robot vacuum, <a href="https://www.ecovacs.com/us/deebot-robotic-vacuum-cleaner/deebot-x9-pro-omni">the X9 Pro Omni</a>. The robot is able to vacuum and mop floors, and it includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> integration so it can be controlled using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/ecovacs-x9-pro-omni-robot.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001490" /><br/>
The X9 Pro Omni is a sensor-laden cleaning bot that can vacuum and mop floors throughout the home, while also using AI to navigate obstacles like pets, items on the floor, furniture, and more. The bot is able to map an entire home with its 3D sensors, detecting walls and using a moving mop and side brush to get debris out of corners and along walls.<br/>
<br/>
Like the prior-generation X8 Pro Omni, the new X9 model features Ecovacs' standout mopping feature, the Ozmo Roller Mop that self washes as it cleans, so that dirty water isn't spread over the floor. The X9 Pro Omni has separate clean and dirty water tanks in the robot itself, which is a unique cleaning feature, plus the mopping brush offers more downward pressure than traditional mop heads for a better clean. The mop is able to lift when the robot encounters carpets, so water does not get on rugs or carpeted areas, and it has hot air drying when cleaning is finished.<br/>
<br/>
As for vacuuming, the X9 Pro Omni uses what Ecovacs calls "Blast" technology, with a 100W high-torque motor and optimized airflow path for better, quieter suction. There is a ZeroTangle brush for pet and human hair that does not get clogged up, cutting down on maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
The X9 Pro Omni refills itself at a base station equipped with clean water, a dust bag, cleaning fluid, and a dirty water reservoir, and all of its functions are controlled via the Ecovacs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> app. There are a range of cleaning modes, from just vacuuming to a deep clean, and there are options for using the robot as a home camera that can move from room to room.<br/>
<br/>
The X9 Pro Omni is one of a handful of robot vacuums that offers Matter integration, and with Matter, it is able to connect to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;. As of iOS 18.4, Apple's Home app has supported robot vacuums, which means you can ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to vacuum or mop your house. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can be used for an overall cleaning, or you can ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to clean specific rooms. The Home app is also available, as is the Ecovacs app.<br/>
<br/>
The X9 Pro Omni can be <a href="https://www.ecovacs.com/us/deebot-robotic-vacuum-cleaner/deebot-x9-pro-omni">purchased from the Ecovacs website</a> for &#36;1,300, which includes a limited time &#36;300 discount to celebrate the launch. We'll have a review of the new robot coming in the next few weeks.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home/">Home</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ecovacs-x9-pro-omni-robot-homekit/">Ecovacs&#039; New X9 Pro Omni Robot Vacuum Features HomeKit Integration</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ecovacs-new-x9-pro-omni-robot-vacuum-features-homekit-integration.2457027/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Brings Contactless Payments to German iPhones Under New EU Rules</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/paypal-contactless-payments-germany/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/paypal-brings-contactless-payments-to-german-iphones-under-new-eu-rules.2457024/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:04:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/paypal-contactless-payments-germany/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>PayPal</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this month, PayPal said that it would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/05/paypal-iphone-contactless-payments/">debut contactless iPhone payments</a> in Germany, and German <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users now appear to be able to use the feature. According to German site <em><a href="https://www.iphone-ticker.de/kontaktlos-zahlen-mit-paypal-nfc-funktion-erreicht-erste-nutzer-in-deutschland-256414/">iPhone Ticker</a></em>, some PayPal customers in Germany have access to PayPal as an alternative to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/paypal-tap-to-pay-germany.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="674" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000659" /><br/>
PayPal can be used for NFC tap to pay functionality just like &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, with payments initiated in the same way. PayPal users in Germany are able to set PayPal as the default payment app over &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, using the side button to bring up PayPal as a payment option for one-tap contactless payments in retail locations.<br/>
<br/>
If PayPal is not set as the default payment method, contactless payments can be made by opening up the PayPal app.<br/>
<br/>
PayPal is able to offer direct tap to pay options in Germany because the Digital Markets Act in Europe forced Apple to allow third-party apps to use the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s NFC chip. Apple has historically restricted access to NFC for payment purposes, only allowing contactless payments with &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
With the new regulations, third-party apps from payment services and banks can access the full functionality of the NFC chip, giving &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users an alternative to &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; and the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
Germany is PayPal's first test market, but the rollout is likely to expand to other European countries in the coming months. To use PayPal for contactless payments, German &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will need the latest version of the PayPal app and a compatible debit or credit card. PayPal can be used in retail stores where Mastercard payments are accepted.<br/>
<br/>
PayPal's tap to pay options are limited to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and the feature does not work on the Apple Watch because Apple has not been required to open up NFC on the Apple Watch. PayPal won't be able to bring the contactless payment option to the United States or other countries unless those locations adopt similar rules requiring Apple to expand NFC access.<br/>
<br/>
To attract customers to use PayPal instead of &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, PayPal is offering cashback promotions in the PayPal app, and will eventually add a pay over time feature with options for six, 12, and 24 monthly installments for purchases.<br/>
<br/>
NFC access is available for banking and wallet apps in the European Economic Area, which includes the 27 European Union countries plus Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/paypal/">PayPal</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/paypal-contactless-payments-germany/">PayPal Brings Contactless Payments to German iPhones Under New EU Rules</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/paypal-brings-contactless-payments-to-german-iphones-under-new-eu-rules.2457024/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 18.5 Adds Synchronized Dolby Atmos Playback for AirPlay and Bluetooth Speakers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/tvos-18-5-dolby-atmos-synchronization/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-5-adds-synchronized-dolby-atmos-playback-for-airplay-and-bluetooth-speakers.2457010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:12:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/tvos-18-5-dolby-atmos-synchronization/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The tvOS 18.5 update that Apple released yesterday adds support for synchronizing Dolby Atmos playback to speakers over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> or Bluetooth, according to <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106336">Apple's release notes</a> for the update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" /><br/>
The feature could help address some persistent syncing issue that some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> users have encountered when trying to play audio with Dolby Atmos. There are multiple complaints <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/appletv/comments/1htwhux/apple_tv_keeps_getting_out_of_sync_with_audio/">on Reddit</a> and <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255553402?sortBy=rank">the Apple Support forums</a> about Dolby Atmos audio syncing issues with sound bars and speakers, including those connected via &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; and Bluetooth, such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>.<br/>
<br/>
On affected devices, users find that dialog and other audio can be slightly out of sync with the content that's playing, so lips do not move correctly when people speak in TV shows and movies, and sound effects like explosions are delayed. Switching to 5.1 surround sound eliminates the problem, but people with expensive audio setups have been understandably disappointed not to be able to use Dolby Atmos.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the new Dolby Atmos synchronization feature for &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; and Bluetooth speakers can be found by going to Settings &gt; Video and Audio &gt; Wireless Audio Sync.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/tvos-18-5-dolby-atmos-synchronization/">tvOS 18.5 Adds Synchronized Dolby Atmos Playback for AirPlay and Bluetooth Speakers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-5-adds-synchronized-dolby-atmos-playback-for-airplay-and-bluetooth-speakers.2457010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Remotely Control Your iPhone Camera – No Apple Watch Needed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/remotely-control-iphone-camera-no-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/remotely-control-your-iphone-camera-–-no-apple-watch-needed.2457009/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:59:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/remotely-control-iphone-camera-no-apple-watch&#038;post_date=1747162781/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Photography</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Remotely controlling the shutter on your iPhone's camera lets you include yourself in the photo while avoiding the limitations of a selfie. For example, it allows you to take a picture of a wider scene with you included in the frame, which is ideal for landscape shots or group photos. If your iPhone is on a tripod, taking the shot remotely also reduces the risk of camera shake. Here's how to do it – and you don't need an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/iphone12protriplelenscamera.jpg" alt="" width="1843" height="985" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-764718" /><br/>
There are more ways than one to take a picture on your iPhone remotely. If you have an Apple Watch, you can open the Camera Remote app that comes included in watchOS (see the second set of steps below). If you don't have an Apple Watch, here's how to use Voice Control.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Use Voice Control to Take a Photo</h2><br/>
If you don't have an Apple Watch, don't worry. You can also use Voice Control to remotely control the camera on your iPhone. That's because you can trigger the camera shutter with the volume buttons, which can also be controlled with your voice. Here's how it works.<br/>
<ol><li>Launch the <strong>Settings</strong> app and tap <strong>Accessibility</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Voice Control</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Turn on the switch next to <strong>Voice Control</strong> so it's in the green ON position. (You should see a Voice Control active symbol and a little orange dot icon at the top of the screen indicating that Voice Control is using the microphone.)</li><br/>
<li>Next, launch the <strong>Camera</strong> app and line up your shot.</li><br/>
<li>When you're ready, say "Turn up the volume," to activate the camera's shutter and take the picture.</li><br/>
<li>When you're finished, you can disable Voice Control by toggling the switch again in Settings.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/enable-voice-control-ios.jpg" alt="settings" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001475" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Control Your iPhone's Camera With Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<ol><li>Launch the <strong>Camera</strong> Remote app on your wrist.</li><br/>
<li>Position your iPhone to frame the shot you want to take.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>Shutter</strong> button on your Apple Watch screen.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/remotely-control-iphone-camera1.jpg" alt="camera remote" width="1656" height="890" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800673" /><br/>
By default, the shot is taken after three seconds to give you time to move into position, but you can disable the time and control other settings including flash, and Live Photo by tapping the <strong>ellipsis</strong> (three dots) button. The menu that this calls up also lets you switch between the front and rear iPhone camera.<br/>
<br/>
Final tip: If you're familiar with the Shortcuts app, you can find a shortcut in the Gallery called "Say Cheese" that lets you use Siri to control your iPhone's camera remotely. Once you've added it to your active shortcuts and given it permission to access your camera and microphone, you'll be able to take photos remotely by saying "Hey Siri, say cheese."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photography/">Photography</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/remotely-control-iphone-camera-no-apple-watch/">Remotely Control Your iPhone Camera – No Apple Watch Needed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/remotely-control-your-iphone-camera-–-no-apple-watch-needed.2457009/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple and Universal Music Announce &#039;Sound Therapy&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-music-sound-therapy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-and-universal-music-announce-sound-therapy.2457005/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:21:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-music-sound-therapy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Universal Music Group today jointly <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/universal-music-group-and-apple-music-announce-sound-therapy/">introduced</a> a new "Sound Therapy" collection of wellness playlists, consisting of popular songs with added sound waves or white noise to help listeners focus, relax, and sleep better.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Apple-Music-Sound-Therapy.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001465" /><br/>
Sound Therapy features three categories: Focus, Relax, and Sleep. The playlists include extended, instrumental, and reimagined versions of popular tracks from artists such as Imagine Dragons, Katy Perry, Kacey Musgraves, and others.<br/>
<br/>
The playlists were crafted by a team of producers, scientists, and audio engineers at Sollos, a music-wellness venture within Universal Music Group.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's announcement explains further:<blockquote>Songs have been enhanced with auditory beats or colored noise to help encourage specific brain responses. Gamma waves and white noise — a whoosh-like combination of every sound frequency — may help with focusing; theta waves could aid in relaxation; and delta waves and pink noise — a deeper, gentler variation akin to rain or wind — might assist in achieving better sleep. A dreamy version of Katy Perry's "Double Rainbow," for example, could help listeners drift off to sleep, while an Imagine Dragons track might help them tackle a to-do list.</blockquote>The playlists are powered by Universal's proprietary audio technologies, and they are backed by scientific research, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/73l5uchNd74?si=kExE4ALmWdkFx4o5" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
"Sound Therapy harnesses the power of sound waves, psychoacoustics, and cognitive science to help listeners relax or focus the mind," says Apple's announcement.<br/>
<br/>
Sound Therapy is available exclusively on Apple Music.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; fullscreen *; clipboard-write" frameborder="0" height="450" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;border-radius:10px;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.music.apple.com/us/playlist/sound-therapy-sleep/pl.44a3d784112843c0b58b0db613eaebf4"></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-music-sound-therapy/">Apple and Universal Music Announce &#039;Sound Therapy&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-and-universal-music-announce-sound-therapy.2457005/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s List of iOS 19 Accessibility Features Includes Two CarPlay Upgrades and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-two-ios-19-carplay-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-list-of-ios-19-accessibility-features-includes-two-carplay-upgrades-and-more.2457003/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:55:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-two-ios-19-carplay-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Accessibility</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 19 will not be unveiled until June, but Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/apple-unveils-powerful-accessibility-features-coming-later-this-year/">previewed</a> a long list of new accessibility features that will be coming with the software update, including two CarPlay enhancements that can benefit both drivers and passengers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/CarPlay-Hero.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992659" /><br/>
We already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-ios-19-accessibility-features/">highlighted some of the key new features</a>, ranging from a new Accessibility Reader to a Magnifier app on the Mac. Below, we have pasted Apple's entire list of additional features, including some of the smaller ones.<br/>
<br/>
For CarPlay, this includes support for the Large Text option that has long existed on iPhones. Apple is also expanding the Sound Recognition feature for drivers or passengers who are deaf or hard of hearing. CarPlay will be able to provide a notification if it hears a crying baby inside the vehicle, and it will also be able to alert users to sounds outside the vehicle, such as horns and sirens from police cars, ambulances, and fire trucks.<br/>
<br/>
Here is the complete list of additional features, as worded by Apple:<ul><br/>
  <li><strong>Background Sounds</strong> becomes easier to personalize with new EQ settings, a timer to stop sounds automatically, and new automation actions in Shortcuts. Helps minimize distractions and may aid tinnitus.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Personal Voice</strong> now creates a voice in under a minute using 10 phrases, with more natural results thanks to on-device AI. Adds support for Spanish (Mexico).<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Eye Tracking</strong> users on iPhone and iPad can use a switch or dwell to make selections. Keyboard typing is improved across iPhone, iPad, and Vision Pro with a dwell timer, fewer steps, and QuickPath.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Head Tracking</strong> allows users to control iPhone and iPad with head movements.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-preparing-to-launch-mind-control-support/"><strong>Brain Computer Interfaces (BCIs)</strong> now supported</a> via a new Switch Control protocol for users with severe mobility disabilities.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Assistive Access</strong> adds a simplified Apple TV app and an API for developers to create tailored apps for users with intellectual and developmental disabilities.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Music Haptics</strong> becomes more customizable, allowing users to feel haptics for vocals only or an entire song, with adjustable intensity.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Sound Recognition</strong> adds <em>Name Recognition</em> to alert users when their name is called.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Voice Control</strong> adds a programming mode in Xcode, vocabulary syncing, and expands language support to Korean, Arabic (Saudi Arabia), Turkish, Italian, Spanish (Latin America), Mandarin Chinese (Taiwan), English (Singapore), and Russian.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Live Captions</strong> adds support for English (India, Australia, UK, Singapore), Mandarin Chinese (Mainland China), Cantonese (Mainland China, Hong Kong), Spanish (Latin America, Spain), French (France, Canada), Japanese, German (Germany), and Korean.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>CarPlay</strong> now supports Large Text and enhanced Sound Recognition to detect a crying baby, horns, and sirens for deaf or hard-of-hearing users.<br/>
  </li><br/>
  <li><strong>Share Accessibility Settings</strong> lets users quickly share their accessibility preferences with another iPhone or iPad — ideal for temporary device use in public or shared spaces.<br/>
  </li><br/>
</ul>iOS 19 will be unveiled during the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">WWDC 2025 keynote on Monday, June 9</a>. Following months of beta testing, the software update should be released in September, bringing these features to the masses. Many of the accessibility features will also be available on iPadOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/accessibility/">Accessibility</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-two-ios-19-carplay-features/">Apple&#039;s List of iOS 19 Accessibility Features Includes Two CarPlay Upgrades and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-list-of-ios-19-accessibility-features-includes-two-carplay-upgrades-and-more.2457003/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;167 Off M4 MacBook Air, Starting at &#36;849</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/amazon-m4-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-167-off-m4-macbook-air-starting-at-849.2457002/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:53:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/amazon-m4-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has low prices across <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">nearly the entire M4 MacBook Air</a> lineup, with up to &#36;167 off both 13-inch and 15-inch models. Many of the notebooks in this sale are seeing delayed delivery estimates, with most arriving in late May or early June, but if you're interested you can lock in these deals now ahead of those delivery dates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/M4-MacBook-Air-13-and-15-inch-Feature-Pink-and-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994260" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 13-inch models, Amazon has up to &#36;155 off all three of the new configurations of this notebook. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model, then raise to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9NV7L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a> for the 16GB/512GB model and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBHQPQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,245.26</strong></a> for the 24GB/512GB model. All of these are solid second-best prices on the M4 MacBook Air, and only a few dollars higher compared to their all-time low prices..<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9NV7L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBHQPQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;155 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,245.26</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the larger display models, Amazon has both 512GB versions of the 15-inch M4 MacBook Air on sale this week, as well as the 256GB model. The 16GB/512GB model is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC2XD2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,249.00</strong></a> and the 24GB/512GB model is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD8V9HW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,432.00</strong></a>. Across the board, these are all record low prices on the 15-inch M4 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBDCFH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC2XD2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD8V9HW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;167 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,432.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/amazon-m4-macbook-air/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;167 Off M4 MacBook Air, Starting at &#36;849</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-167-off-m4-macbook-air-starting-at-849.2457002/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 to Upgrade iPhone&#039;s Music Haptics Feature in Two Ways</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-music-haptics-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-to-upgrade-iphones-music-haptics-feature-in-two-ways.2457001/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:35:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-music-haptics-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Accessibility</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 introduced an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/iphone/iphff2ceeb16/ios">accessibility feature called Music Haptics</a> that has value for everyone. When the feature is turned on, the iPhone's Taptic Engine taps and vibrates to match the audio of a song playing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/apple-music-ios-18-haptics-playlists/">in Apple Music</a>, Shazam, and supported third-party apps, so long as the device is connected to a Wi-Fi or cellular network.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-18-Music-Haptics.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950832" /><br/>
With iOS 19, Music Haptics will get better in two ways.<br/>
<br/>
Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/apple-unveils-powerful-accessibility-features-coming-later-this-year/">announced</a> that Music Haptics will be even more customizable starting later this year. First, users will have the option to receive haptic feedback for vocals only. Second, users will be able to adjust the overall intensity of taps, textures, and vibrations. These enhancements are expected to roll out with iOS 19, which will be unveiled during the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">WWDC 2025 keynote on June 9</a> and released to the general public in September.<br/>
<br/>
Music Haptics is supported on the iPhone 12 and newer, excluding the latest iPhone SE.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/accessibility/">Accessibility</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-music-haptics-improvements/">iOS 19 to Upgrade iPhone&#039;s Music Haptics Feature in Two Ways</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-to-upgrade-iphones-music-haptics-feature-in-two-ways.2457001/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Will Improve iPhone Feature That Lets You Preserve Your Voice</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-to-enhance-personal-voice-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-improve-iphone-feature-that-lets-you-preserve-your-voice.2456999/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:56:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-to-enhance-personal-voice-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Accessibility</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A few years ago, Apple introduced a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/104993">Personal Voice feature</a> that allows those at risk of losing their ability to speak to create a synthesized voice that sounds similar to their actual voice, so they can continue to communicate with others. The feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/17/ios-17-personal-voice-feature/">debuted on the iPhone with iOS 17</a>, and it will be getting even better on iOS 19.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Personal-Voice-iPhone-Feature.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896144" /><br/>
Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-ios-19-accessibility-features/">announced</a> that Personal Voice will be faster and easier to use on iOS 19, thanks to advancements in on-device machine learning and artificial intelligence. Apple says users will be able to create a smoother, more natural-sounding voice in less than a minute, down from 15 minutes when the feature initially launched.<br/>
<br/>
Personal Voice will also add support for Spanish (Mexico), according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Personal Voice integrates with another accessibility feature called Live Speech, which lets users type what they want to say to have it be spoken aloud during in-person conversations, phone calls, and FaceTime video calls.<br/>
<br/>
Personal Voice is also available on the iPad and Mac, and the enhancements to the feature will extend to iPadOS 19 and macOS 16.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/accessibility/">Accessibility</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-to-enhance-personal-voice-feature/">iOS 19 Will Improve iPhone Feature That Lets You Preserve Your Voice</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-improve-iphone-feature-that-lets-you-preserve-your-voice.2456999/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: 	Apple Preparing to Launch Mind-Control Support for iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-preparing-to-launch-mind-control-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-preparing-to-launch-mind-control-support-for-iphones.2456996/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:18:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-preparing-to-launch-mind-control-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Accessibility</category>
		<category>The Wall Street Journal</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to allow users to natively control iPhones, iPads, and other devices using brain signals later this year, <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/apple-brain-computer-interface-9ec69919"><em>The Wall Street Journal</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Logo-Spotlight-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-915203" /><br/>
The initiative involves a partnership with Synchron, a neurotechnology startup that produces an implantable brain-computer interface (BCI) device called the Stentrode. The Stentrode enables users with severe motor impairments, such as those caused by amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), to control Apple devices using neural signals detected from within blood vessels located above the brain's motor cortex.<br/>
<br/>
The Stentrode is implanted through the jugular vein and rests inside a blood vessel on the surface of the brain. The device contains 16 electrodes that can detect motor-related brain activity without requiring open-brain surgery. These neural signals are then translated into digital commands that allow users to interact with an interface.<br/>
<br/>
Synchron has implanted the Stentrode in ten patients since 2019 under the FDA's investigational device exemption. One test participant based in Pennsylvania with ALS, who cannot use his arms or hands, is able to use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> and other Apple devices through thought alone, although it is slower than conventional input mechanisms.<br/>
<br/>
In 2014, Apple introduced the "Made for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>" hearing aid protocol as a Bluetooth standard that enables seamless wireless communication between hearing aids and Apple devices. The company is now apparently pursuing a similar approach with brain-computer interfaces, aiming to establish a dedicated industry standard in collaboration with Synchron.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is apparently planning to add support for BCIs into its existing Switch Control accessibility framework, which allows input from non-standard devices such as joysticks and adaptive hardware. The company reportedly intends to release this new standard later in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Synchron's approach differs significantly from that of other companies such as Neuralink, which is developing a more invasive implant called the N1. Neuralink's device contains more than 1,000 electrodes embedded directly into brain tissue, providing a higher-resolution neural data stream. This allows for more complex control, including moving a cursor across a screen and typing using mental intention.<br/>
<br/>
See <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250513927084/en/Synchron-To-Achieve-First-Native-Brain-Computer-Interface-Integration-with-iPhone-iPad-and-Apple-Vision-Pro">Synchron's full press release</a> for more information.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/accessibility/">Accessibility</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-wall-street-journal/">The Wall Street Journal</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-preparing-to-launch-mind-control-support/">Report: 	Apple Preparing to Launch Mind-Control Support for iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-preparing-to-launch-mind-control-support-for-iphones.2456996/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
