<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 03:01:06 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card Turns 5, Still U.S. Only</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-card-turns-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-turns-5-still-u-s-only.2434116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-card-turns-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yesterday marked the fifth anniversary of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/20/apple-card-launches-widely-in-us/">saw an official release</a> on August 20, 2019. The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; is Apple's first and only Apple-branded credit card, made available in partnership with Goldman Sachs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/apple-card-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="1144" height="644" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-735877" /><br/>
At launch, the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; was only available in the United States, and today, five years later, it is still limited to the United States and has not expanded to additional countries. Just a month after the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;'s debut, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/09/30/tim-cook-visits-germany/">interested in expanding</a> the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; to multiple countries, but that it would take time due to various regulations around the world.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors of &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; talks in Europe, and Apple trademarked &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; in Europe, Hong Kong, and Canada, but no deals have emerged. &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; expanding to additional countries is even more up in the air with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">upcoming decoupling</a> from Goldman Sachs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning to end its partnership with Goldman Sachs in 2025, and it will need to find a new &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; provider in the United States. Apple and Goldman Sachs ran into trouble with customer service issues for disputed &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions, as well as complaints with wait times for Apple Savings account withdrawals.<br/>
<br/>
Goldman Sachs even ended up <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-fed-probes-goldman-sachs-consumer-business-wsj-2023-01-20/">being investigated</a> by the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau because of customer complaints, which led to a souring of the bank's relationship with Apple. Goldman Sachs now plans to get out of consumer banking entirely.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; is a no-fee credit card with no annual fees, no international fees, no fees for making a late payment, and no fees for exceeding a credit limit. There aren't consumer protections like one might get with an American Express card, but there is deep integration with the Wallet app for tracking spending.<br/>
<br/>
Apple provides 1 percent Daily Cash back on all purchases, 2 percent for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> purchases, and 3 percent for &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; purchases from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>. Daily Cash is sent to customers each day, hence the name.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not commented on the possibility of expanding &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; to additional countries in some time, and there is no word on whether that's still the plan.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-card-turns-5/">Apple Card Turns 5, Still U.S. Only</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-turns-5-still-u-s-only.2434116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google&#039;s Pixel AI Image Creation and Editing Tools Are Kind of Terrifying</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/googles-pixel-ai-image-creation-and-editing-tools-are-kind-of-terrifying.2434114/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:19:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google last week introduced the Pixel 9 smartphone lineup, with a selection of new devices that are focused on AI. All of the Pixel 9 phones support Gemini AI, and Google has also added AI-based image generation and editing tools. Reviewers have been testing the new smartphone features, and the AI image generation is probably going to turn into a PR nightmare for Google based on what's come out so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/google-pixel-9.jpg" alt="" width="2050" height="1153" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962164" /><br/>
Google introduced an AI image generation app for the Pixel phones, called Pixel Studio. It's designed to create stickers and images using text-based prompts, and it looks and sounds a lot like Apple's planned Image Playground. So far, reviewers have been able to create all manner of questionable images with Pixel Studio, ranging from a Nazi version of Spongebob to Elmo with an AK47.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/pixel-studio-digital-trends.jpg" alt="" width="3240" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962163" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Image via Digital Trends</div></em><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.digitaltrends.com/mobile/i-tried-google-pixel-studio-app-image-generator-problems-concerns/">Digital Trends</a></em> had no trouble getting Pixel Studio to make images of beloved cartoon characters doing questionable activities. Guns, drugs, and alcohol were not off-limits, nor were offensive situations like school shootings. Pixel Studio did not generate these kinds of images unless asked, but that's most likely what people will immediately do with the feature rather than generating images of cute cats and bunnies.<br/>
<br/>
Google said that there were "safety checks" in place to keep Pixel Studio from being "used nefariously," and there are some. Pixel Studio will not create images of humans, and Google is tweaking the AI in response to reviews. After speaking with Google, <em>Digital Trends</em> was no longer able to get Pixel Studio to create cartoon characters using cocaine or dressed as German soldiers.<br/>
<br/>
Even more concerning than Pixel Studio is Google's "Reimagine" tool, which can add objects to photos that you've already taken. <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/21/24224084/google-pixel-9-reimagine-ai-photos">The Verge</a></em> used it to add corpses, bombs, drugs, and disasters to images, and objects included in photos look so realistic that it's difficult to tell when an image has been edited. Google is able to do a pretty good job matching lighting and perspective to the original photo, and there are no watermarks or flags on social media. Google does add a metadata tag, but that's easy enough to eliminate with a screenshot.<br/>
<br/>
You can, of course, use Reimagine for adding sunsets and rainbows to your image, just like you can use Pixel Studio for creating fun pictures, and both AI features work great, so these tools aren't all bad. <em><a href="https://www.androidauthority.com/30-pixel-studio-creations-3473158/">Android Authority</a></em> shared a post with Oreo pizza, a giraffe surfing, and kittens playing basketball, for example. As <em>The Verge</em> points out, you could always add a body to an image or create a picture of Elmo with a gun, but it would take some Photoshop skill and time to do so. With the Pixel phones, it takes just a thought and a few seconds to create that kind of image, and it's right there on the smartphone for anyone to use.<br/>
<br/>
In statements to <em>The Verge</em> and <em>Digital Trends</em>, Google said that it designed its generative AI tools to "respect the intent of user prompts" which can lead to the creation of content "that may offend" when the user asks for it. But Google claims that there are "Terms of Service" on what content is not allowed, and that safeguards will be continually refined.<br/>
<br/>
Apple hasn't yet introduced its image generation tools, Image Playground or Genmoji, and the media surrounding the Pixel 9 launch gives us some insight into what the response might be like if Apple doesn't get it just right. With AI, it's likely that people are going to be able to find workarounds even if Apple puts numerous safeguards in place. Apple so far has shied away from photorealistic AI images, but Google is going all in, and it's going to be much harder to trust photos on social media and the internet going forward.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/">Google&#039;s Pixel AI Image Creation and Editing Tools Are Kind of Terrifying</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/googles-pixel-ai-image-creation-and-editing-tools-are-kind-of-terrifying.2434114/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>App Store VP Departs as Apple Prepares for Organizational Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/app-store-organizational-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-vp-departs-as-apple-prepares-for-organizational-changes.2434107/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:11:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/app-store-organizational-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> vice president Matt Fischer is set to leave the company as Apple prepares for an &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; reorganization to deal with regulatory changes, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-21/apple-s-app-store-head-to-leave-in-reorganization-amid-global-scrutiny">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
Apple plans to split its &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; group into two teams, one that handles the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and a second team that oversees alternative app distribution. As of earlier this year, Apple has supported iOS app downloads from alternative app stores and from websites in the European Union, a change that the company had to make to comply with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
To handle ongoing compliance with EU regulations for app distribution and alternative payment methods, &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; chief <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phil-schiller/">Phil Schiller</a> is changing the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s hierarchy.<br/>
<br/>
Fischer joined Apple in 2003 to oversee iTunes marketing, but he has served as the vice president of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; since 2010. In an email to Apple employees today, Fischer said that he had been thinking about leaving Apple for some time, and the reorganization provided the right opportunity.<br/>
<br/>
With Fischer leaving, &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; senior director Carson Oliver will oversee the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and Ann Thai, a director who oversees &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; features, will head up the team that handles alternative app distribution.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/app-store-organizational-changes/">App Store VP Departs as Apple Prepares for Organizational Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-vp-departs-as-apple-prepares-for-organizational-changes.2434107/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PSA: There&#039;s a New Character Bug That Can Cause iPhones to Crash</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-character-bug-respring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-theres-a-new-character-bug-that-can-cause-iphones-to-crash.2434102/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:25:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-character-bug-respring/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There is a new character bug that can result in a respring on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, reports <em><a href="https://infosec.exchange/@kpwn/113000348717635390">TechCrunch</a></em>. Typing "":: in the search field after swiping over to the App Library will cause the Springboard to reset, dropping you back at the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Lock Screen. A respring is not a full reset, and it only takes a few seconds for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to be functional again.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
Typing the same characters into the Settings app search interface will cause the Settings app to crash, but putting it in a Spotlight search doesn't seem to impact anything. The respring seemed to only happen on devices running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> when we tested, but putting those characters into a search interface on a device running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> does result in some odd behavior, such as the characters disappearing and the Settings app crashing.<br/>
<br/>
You can actually type in just "": and any other character to cause the respring to happen, so it's something related to the first three symbols in a four character sequence.<br/>
<br/>
Character bugs have in the past spread though Messages and have allowed users to crash the iPhones of others, but this is a much more insignificant issue because the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; owner needs to manually type (or paste) the characters into a search interface. There does not appear to be a way to affect an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; through Messages or another texting platform.<br/>
<br/>
It's likely Apple will address the issue with an iOS update in the near future.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-character-bug-respring/">PSA: There&#039;s a New Character Bug That Can Cause iPhones to Crash</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-theres-a-new-character-bug-that-can-cause-iphones-to-crash.2434102/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Max: One Year Review</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review.2434095/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:53:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been almost a year since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models were released, so <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera decided to do a one-year check-in review on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max to see how it's performed over the last 12 months.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vSX-9cRPZx4" title="iPhone 15 Pro Max: One Year Later Review" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Unsurprisingly, Dan has seen some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> battery degradation, and it's dropped to 89 percent. That's with regular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> usage, running betas, and standard day-to-day use. Even at 89 percent, the battery can still last for a full day without needing a charge.<br/>
<br/>
As for the titanium chassis, it's held up well. There are a few nicks due to minor drops, but the display has seen a lot more damage with several scratches, some of which are deep.<br/>
<br/>
The transition to USB-C has been a little tough just because there are still people with Lightning iPhones. If someone wants to borrow your charger, you may not have the right cable if you've switched to USB-C and they're still on Lightning.<br/>
<br/>
Dan uses the Action Button for opening up the Camera app, but there's so much more that the Action Button can do in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and it's going to get a lot more useful in the future. You can set Control Center controls to the Action Button, and developers can make new controls for apps that you can use.<br/>
<br/>
There's not too much to say about the triple-lens camera setup, which is great. The 5x zoom lens is excellent for taking portrait pictures of people, and it's been a solid improvement. Otherwise, the cameras are fantastic with a lot of focal length versatility thanks to the new zoom option.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max has held up well, and if you have one (or a Pro), there's no real need to upgrade to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. The A17 Pro in the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is incredibly fast and there's no way most people are even reaching the limits of its capabilities at this time, and Apple isn't adding too much more than an extra Capture Button and a slightly larger display in 2024. You can already use Apple Intelligence if you have an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; model, so there's not a lot to get out of a year-over-year upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
If you have an older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it's worth looking at the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, or even an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; when prices drop and they're discontinued. All of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have a chip compatible with Apple Intelligence, a Capture Button, and an Action Button, so there's a lot to gain coming from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> or earlier.<br/>
<br/>
How has your &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; held up if you have one? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review/">iPhone 15 Pro Max: One Year Review</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review.2434095/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Fifth watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-fifth-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2434094/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:50:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the fourth beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to give the new features a try ahead of when the software launches this fall. The fifth beta comes a week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-4/">after the fourth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957264" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-vitals.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; can be downloaded after signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's beta software website</a> and upgrading your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to the public beta version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. You'll need to open up the Watch app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, go to General, select Software Update, and choose the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Public Beta option under Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, Apple added a new Vitals app that can be used to give you a daily overview of your health metrics, letting you know if anything is out of the ordinary. It compares information collected at night like heart rate, sleep, respiratory rate, and oxygen level to your levels over the previous weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Smart Stack has new widgets like Translate and Shazam, plus it's smarter because it is able to suggest widgets based on time, date, location, and daily routine. Interactive widgets let you access app features from the Smart Stack, and it also supports Live Activities.<br/>
<br/>
Training Load is a new way of measuring how the intensity and duration of workouts impact the body over time, with Apple providing an effort level for cardio-based workouts to help you know when to rest and when to push harder.<br/>
<br/>
You can now customize your Activity Ring requirements for different days of the week, and Apple added support for rest days. Taking a break from activity will no longer ruin a streak because you can pause for a day, a week, a month, or more.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include more workout types, Check In for Messages, a revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face, improvements to Double Tap, and more, with additional information <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">available in our watchOS 11 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-5/">Apple Releases Fifth watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-fifth-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2434094/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Launches Stand One Max Qi2 Charging Hub for iPhone, Apple Watch and AirPods</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-stand-one-max-qi2-charging-hub-for-iphone-apple-watch-and-airpods.2434088/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nomad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nomad today introduced its latest multi-device charger, debuting a new version of the Stand One Max with Qi2 support. Rather than continuing to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, Nomad is transitioning to Qi2, the latest Qi charging standard that is able to charge iPhones at &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nomad-stand-one-max-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962082" /><br/>
The Stand One Max can charge an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at up to 15W, and we were able to test the charger out ahead of launch. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max charged from 0 to 39 percent in an hour, which is essentially identical to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging speeds.<br/>
<br/>
The Stand One Max features an upright charging base for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a small charging arm for the Apple Watch and a Qi-based platform for charging the AirPods. It's a compact design that takes up little room on a desk, and as with all Nomad products, it is well-made. Nomad had a prior version of the Stand One Max, but the new version moves the Apple Watch charger lower to allow for compatibility with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s StandBy mode.<br/>
<br/>
The Stand One Max is crafted from solid metal and it has a shiny glass cover panel. It can be purchased in silver or carbide colors, and the close to 2 pound weight adds stability, as does the rubber bottom. An &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be positioned on the magnetic base in portrait or landscape mode, so StandBy is supported. The angle of the charging base cannot be adjusted, but it is tilted back slightly for a comfortable viewing position on a desktop or nightstand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nomad-stand-one-max-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962083" /><br/>
In addition to charging a MagSafe-compatible &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at up to 15W, the Stand One Max has an Apple Watch fast charger so that it can charge the Series 7 or later at the fastest possible speed. The position of the Apple Watch charger allows for Night Stand mode to be used, which also wasn't possible with the prior iteration. The AirPods charger charges at 5W, and there is a small indentation to guide positioning.<br/>
<br/>
The relocated position of the Apple Watch charger is convenient because it no longer prevents the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from charging in landscape mode, and there is no loss of functionality. The AirPods charger is pushed back behind the Apple Watch charger, and the overall footprint is about the same. It is a better design than the prior Stand One Max, and it is less expensive with the transition to Qi2.<br/>
<br/>
The new Stand One Max is priced at &#36;150, which is &#36;30 lower than the price of the prior &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; version. You will need to supply your own 30W power adapter, but a USB-C power cable is included. The Stand One Max can be <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/stand-one-max-carbide-3rd-gen">purchased from the Nomad website</a> as of today.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad is also offering a flash sale on its <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/base-one-max-3-in-1-silver">Base One Max chargers</a> this week, discounting them by 30 percent with the promo code BM130. The Base One Max has a flat charging base so it can charge non-MagSafe smartphones.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nomad/">Nomad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max/">Nomad Launches Stand One Max Qi2 Charging Hub for iPhone, Apple Watch and AirPods</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-stand-one-max-qi2-charging-hub-for-iphone-apple-watch-and-airpods.2434088/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon&#039;s New Accessory Sale Includes Deals on AirTag, Eufy SmartTrack, and Jackery Power Stations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/amazon-airtag-eufy-jackery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-new-accessory-sale-includes-deals-on-airtag-eufy-smarttrack-and-jackery-power-stations.2434084/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 08:17:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/amazon-airtag-eufy-jackery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a big collection of discounts on Bluetooth trackers and portable power stations, including Apple's own AirTag, Anker's more affordable brand of Eufy SmartTrack accessories, and power stations from Jackery. All of these deals can be found on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airtag-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940079" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the AirTag, you can get the 1 Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;24.99</strong></a> and the 4 Pack of trackers for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;99.00. These are both solid second-best prices on the AirTag.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/eufy-smartrack-link.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955367" /><br/>
<br/>
Anyone who needs a Bluetooth tracker but wants to save a bit of money should look at Anker's Eufy brand of trackers, which are on sale on Amazon right now and compatible with Find My on Apple devices. These start at just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214586794"><strong>&#36;15.99</strong></a> for one tracker and raise to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"><strong>&#36;48.99</strong></a> for a 4 Pack. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214586794"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 1 Pack for &#36;15.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 2 Pack for &#36;29.88</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;21 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 4 Pack for &#36;48.99 (Prime members only)</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you want a tracker that you can fit in a wallet, Eufy's SmartTrack Card is a great solution at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1723214719490"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.99. Most of Eufy's trackers can be delivered between August 22 and August 27, and none of these deals require a coupon code in order to see the final sale prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1723214719490"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962136" /><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Jackery has a large collection of discounts on its best portable power stations on Amazon this week, starting at &#36;199.99 for the Explorer 100 Plus Power Station, down from &#36;229.00. Most of these deals require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ_1723559358185">Explorer 100 Plus Power Station with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;199.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.FK2BIIO8032Y%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.FK2BIIO8032Y_1723559560854">Solar Generator 240 with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;269.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1S26WFMTGKTLG%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1S26WFMTGKTLG_1723559487405">Explorer 1000 Power Station (version 2)</a> - &#36;629.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.399U48EASRUZ2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.399U48EASRUZ2_1723559529144">Explorer 2000 Pro Power Station</a> - &#36;1,499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.35XLU54M76H6P%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.35XLU54M76H6P_1723559651126">Explorer 3000 Pro Power Station</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/amazon-airtag-eufy-jackery/">Amazon&#039;s New Accessory Sale Includes Deals on AirTag, Eufy SmartTrack, and Jackery Power Stations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-new-accessory-sale-includes-deals-on-airtag-eufy-smarttrack-and-jackery-power-stations.2434084/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: iCloud Is the Most Popular Apple Subscription Service in the US</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/icloud-storage-most-popular-apple-service/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-icloud-is-the-most-popular-apple-subscription-service-in-the-us.2434083/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 08:04:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/icloud-storage-most-popular-apple-service/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Paid <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> storage overwhelmingly remains the most popular Apple service in the United States, according to a <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/icloud-storage-remains-apples-most">new report</a> from Consumer Intelligence Research Partners (CIRP).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iCloud-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-803318" /><br/>
Nearly two-thirds of Apple customers in the United States opt for paid &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage, surpassing other services like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> in terms of user adoption. In comparison, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ have achieved moderate penetration rates among Apple customers, with 42% and 32% adoption, respectively. &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;, the company's extended warranty service, sees even lower adoption, with only 17% of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> buyers opting for the additional coverage. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-services-cirp.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="934" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-962128" /><br/>
These other services, while significant contributors to Apple's Services revenue, operate in highly competitive markets, unlike the cloud storage market where no service is able to offer such a deeply integrated experience with Apple devices as &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;. Many users opt for just one music service and multiple video subscriptions, which limits the growth potential for Apple's subscription offerings. As Apple's hardware sales growth slows, the company has increasingly turned to its services segment as a source of revenue.<br/>
<br/>
Paid &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; subscriptions start at &#36;0.99 per month for 50GB of storage, &#36;2.99 per month for 200GB, and &#36;9.99 per month for 2TB. These standalone &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage plans can also be bundled with other Apple services through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a>, which offers three tiers: the Individual plan at &#36;16.95 per month includes 50GB of &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>; the Family plan at &#36;22.95 per month includes 200GB of &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage and extends those services to up to six family members; and the Premier plan at &#36;32.95 per month includes 2TB of &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage and adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ and Apple Fitness+.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/icloud-storage-most-popular-apple-service/">Report: iCloud Is the Most Popular Apple Subscription Service in the US</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-icloud-is-the-most-popular-apple-subscription-service-in-the-us.2434083/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s September Event: New Products to Expect Beyond the iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-september-event-new-products-to-expect-beyond-the-iphone-16.2434080/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:53:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will hold its annual iPhone event next month, with some signs pointing to September 10 as the date that the company will announce its new flagship iPhone 16 lineup. But it's worth noting that there are a few more products expected to be unveiled as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Event-October-2023.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919098" /><br/>
Keep reading to learn everything we know about what else Apple is expected to announce at the event beyond the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
Apple is expected to release a thinner version of the Apple Watch in 2024, but it likely won't look significantly different from current models, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Larger display sizes are anticipated, and Apple plans to continue offering two models.<br/>
<br/>
The larger of the two standard Apple Watch casing sizes, the 45mm model, is expected to become the smallest option, while an all-new 49mm casing size, matching the current Apple Watch Ultra, is expected to be introduced as the new larger option.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> also predicts that the 2024 Apple Watch Series 10 will feature a slimmer design with larger screens. Kuo expects the Series 10 to come in 45mm and 49mm sizes, an increase from the current 41mm and 45mm options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-9-display.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913380" /><br/>
The next-generation Apple Watch is expected to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/next-apple-watch-thinner-logic-board-rumor/">resin-coated copper</a>, which will allow for a thinner logic board and enhance durability and water resistance. A thinner logic board would create additional internal space for other components.<br/>
<br/>
Previously, Mark Gurman mentioned that Apple was considering a magnetic band attachment system that could free up more space inside the Apple Watch, but his latest reports do not mention this feature. If implemented, the magnetic band system might make existing bands incompatible with new models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also been working on features for hypertension and sleep apnea detection in the Series 10, but Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">indicates</a> these may not be ready for launch. Apple is reportedly facing reliability issues with the hypertension feature, which could cause delays, and the sleep apnea detection relies on blood oxygen monitoring, a feature Apple has temporarily removed from the Apple Watch due to patent concerns.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 3</h2><br/>
When Apple Watch Ultra 2 debuted last year, key new features included a 50% brighter display, a faster S9 chip, a "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watch without touching the screen, on-device Siri, and increased internal storage. This year's iteration could be much more modest, though.<br/>
<br/>
Initially, it was believed that Apple was working on an Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display, which would provide increased brightness, better contrast, and improved battery efficiency. However, these plans appear to have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">postponed indefinitely</a>. <br/>
<br/>
As a result, the design of the Apple Watch Ultra 3 is likely to remain largely unchanged. Reporter Mark Gurman recently said that this year's third-generation Apple Watch Ultra will have "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">roughly the same look as the original,</a>." He has previously suggested a totally redesigned "Apple Watch X" with a thinner case and magnetic bands is coming, but this is likely to be a different model to the Ultra, and he said it would be released "in 2024 or 2025."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
According to Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, the Apple Watch Ultra 3 is expected to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/">"almost no" new hardware upgrades</a> compared to the Apple Watch Ultra 2. His phrasing would seem to suggest that the rumored blood pressure and sleep apnea detection features will be machine learning / software-based, relying on existing sensors. However, Mark Gurman says the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will feature a new processor that succeeds last year's S9 chip, and that this could "lay the groundwork for some AI enhancements down the road."<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 was expected to include improved health tracking capabilities such as blood pressure monitoring and sleep apnea detection, aligning with the rumored features of the Apple Watch Series 10, but those features could be further out, as mentioned above.<br/>
<br/>
On the flip side, Apple is rumored to be adopting new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/09/2024-apple-watch-more-power-efficient-display/">low-energy OLED panel technology</a> in new Apple Watch models to further reduce the power consumption of its always-on display. If that's the case, it's unlikely that Apple would use the technology in its latest Series model without also bringing it to its latest Apple Watch Ultra model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE 3</h2><br/>
Apple's third-generation Apple Watch SE may feature significant changes according to recent reports. Research analyst David Hsieh suggests the new model will have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/08/apple-watch-series-x-larger-display-rumor/">larger display</a>, matching the Apple Watch Series 8 with 41mm and 45mm case sizes. This represents an increase from the current 40mm and 44mm options, potentially offering about 12% more screen area.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Watch-SE-3-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918243" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reports that Apple is likely to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/apple-watch-se-plastic/">rigid plastic</a> instead of aluminum for the watch's body. This material change could lower production costs and appeal to parents buying for children. These updates indicate Apple's strategy to create a more accessible smartwatch option, balancing modern features with affordability and durability.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4 (Possibly)</h2><br/>
The fourth-generation AirPods are anticipated to launch in either September or October, with Apple planning to offer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">two versions at different price points</a>, so there's a decent chance we could see them next month during Apple's iPhone 16 event. Both models will sport a redesigned look, featuring a USB-C port instead of the Lightning port, shorter stems similar to the AirPods Pro, an improved fit, and enhanced audio quality.<br/>
<br/>
The higher-end version is expected to include Active Noise Cancellation (ANC), introducing ANC at a more affordable price point for the first time. This version is also likely to feature a speaker in the charging case for Find My location tracking. While it will be less expensive than the AirPods Pro (&#36;249), it wont include features like silicone ear tips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/AirPods-Fourth-Generation-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905655" /><br/>
The next-generation AirPods are expected to inherit the H2 chip from the second-generation AirPods Pro. Currently, the second- and third-generation AirPods use the H1 chip. The H2 chip brings Bluetooth 5.3 connectivity, which offers faster and more reliable connections with Bluetooth accessories, as well as improved power efficiency that can lead to longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple claims that the H2 chip delivers an "exceptional acoustic experience" when paired with a new low-distortion audio driver and custom amplifier in the AirPods Pro. This combination results in richer bass and clearer sound across a wider range of frequencies, thanks to computational audio enhancements enabled by the H2 chip. It's highly likely that similar improvements will be featured in the fourth-generation AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max 2 (Possibly)</h2><br/>
Apple could release second-generation AirPods Max at its September event, but like AirPods 4, these could appear later in October, with rumors only pointing to a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/">late 2024</a>" release. The AirPods Max are currently the oldest model in Apple's AirPods lineup, having been released in December 2020. Over three years later, rumors have started to surface about a new-generation model expected to arrive later this year.<br/>
<br/>
One significant change will be the replacement of the Lightning port with a USB-C port, aligning with European regulations and creating uniformity across Apple's AirPods lineup. As a result, the AirPods Max 2 will include a USB-C to USB-C charging cable instead of the previous Lightning to USB-C cable. Additionally, Apple will need to offer a USB-C to 3.5mm audio cable so users can connect the AirPods Max 2 to devices with 3.5mm audio ports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Black-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877635" /><br/>
The Bluetooth 5.3 specification, already present in the AirPods Pro 2, iPhone 15 lineup, and the latest Apple Watch models, is almost certain to be included in the second-generation AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release the new AirPods Max in fresh colors, though the exact shades are unknown. Currently, they are available in Space Gray, Silver, Green, Sky Blue, and Pink, with interchangeable ear cushions for custom color combinations.<br/>
<br/>
Although there are no specific rumors about the H2 chip in AirPods Max 2, it seems likely they will include it. The H2 chip, designed for Apples earbuds and headphones, enhances audio quality, improves battery life, and supports features like Personalized Volume and Conversation Awareness.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iPhone Cases and Apple Watch Bands</h2><br/>
As is typical of September Apple events, it's likely that new iPhone cases and Apple Watch bands will be released in a variety of fresh colors. The new cases and bands sometimes become available to order on Apple's online store just minutes after the event ends.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/march-2023-apple-watch-bands.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888020" /><br/>
Notably, this year the larger of the two standard Apple Watch casing sizes in the Apple Watch Series models, the 45mm size, is expected to become the smallest option. An all-new 49mm casing size, matching the current Apple Watch Ultra, is expected to be introduced as the new larger option. Given that the 49mm Apple Watch Ultra is compatible with bands designed for the 45mm Apple Watch Series models, it is possible that Apple Watch bands could be compatible across both Series 10 models and the Apple Watch Ultra for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Software for Apple Products</h2><br/>
iOS 18 for the iPhone, iPadOS 18 for iPad, watchOS 11 for the Apple Watch, and tvOS 18 for the Apple TV are all expected to be released in September following several months of beta testing, and Apple will likely provide release dates for these software updates. Sometimes the updates are released within days of the event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Public-Beta-Thumb-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958424" /><br/>
For all the details on the new software features you can expect, check out our dedicated roundups for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/#tvos_and_the_tv_app">tvOS 18</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/">Apple&#039;s September Event: New Products to Expect Beyond the iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-september-event-new-products-to-expect-beyond-the-iphone-16.2434080/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The iPhone 16 Is Getting an Action Button: Here&#039;s Everything It Will Do</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-16-everything-new-action-button-will-do/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-iphone-16-is-getting-an-action-button-heres-everything-it-will-do.2434070/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 05:22:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-16-everything-new-action-button-will-do/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Action Button</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus models are widely expected to inherit the Action button first seen on last year's iPhone 15 Pro models. The Action button replaces the traditional Ring/Silent switch  a staple of the iPhone since it launched in 2007. For users unfamiliar with the Action button, here's a rundown of its functions  including some new features that iOS 18 will bring to the table for all iPhone models with an Action button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Action-Button-Translate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911022" /><br/>
The Action button replaces the single-function switch used to toggle between ring and silent, offering additional options so users can choose between quickly accessing the camera or flashlight, activate Voice Memos, Focus modes, Translate, and accessibility features like Magnifier. Users can also associate it with Shortcuts for more options. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-pro-how-to-customize-action-button/">iPhone 15 Pro: How to Customize the Action Button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-pro-assign-two-shortcuts-action-button/">iPhone 15 Pro: How to Assign Two Functions to the Action Button</a></li></ul><br/>
A press-and-hold gesture with fine-tuned haptic feedback and visual cues in the Dynamic Island ensure the new Action button launches the intended action, which users can customize in Settings and assign to different actions. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Existing Action Button Functions</h2><br/>
Here's what the Action button can be programmed to do:<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Accessibility</strong>: Access to various accessibility settings, such as VoiceOver, Zoom, AssistiveTouch, Live Speech, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Shortcuts</strong>: Open your favorite app, or run a shortcut created in or downloaded from the Shortcuts app, such as sending a message, playing a playlist, or controlling smart home devices.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Silent Mode</strong>: Like the Ring/Silent switch on existing iPhone models, toggle silent mode on or off, which will mute or unmute the ringer and alerts.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Camera</strong>: Take a photo, selfie, video, portrait, or portrait selfie with a single press of the Action button.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Flashlight</strong>: Turn on or off the flashlight on the back of the device.<br/>
<li><strong>Focus</strong>: Activate or deactivate a Focus mode.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Magnifier</strong>: Activate the Magnifier app to use the iPhone's camera as a magnifying glass to zoom in on small text or objects.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Translate</strong>: Launch the Translate app and start a conversation or text translation with a single press of the Action button.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Voice Memos</strong>: Start or stop recording a voice memo with the Voice Memos app.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Action Button Functions Coming in iOS 18</h2><br/>
iOS 18 allows the Action button to be assigned to one of the dozens of controls available in the new Control Center gallery, allowing the Action button to invoke Dark Mode, Airplane Mode, Personal Hotspot, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Control-Center-Toggles-for-Action-Button-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955224" /><br/>
Available Control Center actions in iOS 18 will include:<div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Calculator</li><br/>
  <li>Stopwatch</li><br/>
  <li>Alarm</li><br/>
  <li>Home</li><br/>
  <li>Timer</li><br/>
  <li>Dark Mode</li><br/>
  <li>Scan Code</li><br/>
  <li>Airplane Mode</li></ul></div><div style="float: right; width: 50%;"><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Cellular Data</li><br/>
  <li>Personal Hotspot</li><br/>
  <li>Dark Mode</li><br/>
  <li>Quick Note</li><br/>
  <li>Remote</li><br/>
  <li>Wallet</li><br/>
  <li>Tap to Cash</li><br/>
  <li>Ping My Watch</li><br/>
</ul></div><br/>
<div style="clear:both;"></div><br/>
These new options are in addition to the actions that were already available for the Action button on iOS 17, including Ring/Silent, Do Not Disturb, Camera, Flashlight, Voice Memo, Magnifier, Translate, Shortcut, and Accessibility. Some of the new Control Center options were already possible with the Shortcut or Accessibility options.<br/>
<br/>
Multiple rumors have suggested that all the iPhone 16 models will also have an all-new button that's designed to make it easier to capture photos when the devices are held in landscape mode. Check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/iphone-16-capture-button-features/">dedicated article on the subject</a> to learn more about what it will do. Apple is expected to announce the new iPhone 16 lineup next month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/action-button/">Action Button</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-16-everything-new-action-button-will-do/">The iPhone 16 Is Getting an Action Button: Here&#039;s Everything It Will Do</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-iphone-16-is-getting-an-action-button-heres-everything-it-will-do.2434070/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>UK Antitrust Watchdog Closes Apple App Store Investigation, Case to Be Reconsidered Under New Digital Rules Regime</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/uk-antitrust-watchdog-closes-probe-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-antitrust-watchdog-closes-apple-app-store-investigation-case-to-be-reconsidered-under-new-digital-rules-regime.2434068/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 04:37:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/uk-antitrust-watchdog-closes-probe-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The UK's Competition and Market Authority (CMA) today <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/cma-looks-to-new-digital-markets-competition-regime-to-resolve-app-store-concerns">announced</a> it had closed an investigation into Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> policies, as it expects to consider the concerns under a new digital markets competition regime which is expected to come into force later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/app-store-blue-banner-uk-fixed.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-804521" /><br/>
Originally initiated in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/04/uk-watchdog-apple-investigation/">March 2021</a>, the CMA's investigation set out to determine whether or not Apple has a dominant position in connection with the distribution of apps on Apple devices in the UK  and, if so, whether Apple imposes unfair or anti-competitive terms on developers using the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, such as by charging a 30% commission on transactions. <br/>
<br/>
The watchdog opened a similar probe into Google, which it believed breached UK competition law by making app developers use its own billing system for in-app purchases. The CMA now says it has closed the Competition Act cases into Google's Play Store and Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; on the grounds of administrative priorities and has not taken any decisions as to whether the Competition Act 1998 has been infringed.<br/>
<br/>
Despite both investigations being closed, the competition regulator says it may use new powers given to it via the UK's new Digital Markets, Competition and Consumers Act to address its concerns "more holistically" with a view to boosting competition in the app market. From the CMA's press release:<br/>
<blockquote>In light of recent developments, in particular the passing in May of the Digital Markets, Competition and Consumers Act (DMCCA), the CMA has assessed its existing Competition Act investigation into Google's Play Store and its parallel case into Apple's App Store rules against its administrative priorities and decided to close these cases at this point. Should Apple or Google each or both be designated as having 'strategic market status' in connection with any digital activities in the mobile sector, the CMA will be able to use its new powers to consider the range of issues raised by parties more holistically than it otherwise could under these specific Competition Act investigations. This will also enable the CMA to consider what, if any, interventions may be needed following any designation.</blockquote>Published in January 2024, the <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/overview-of-the-cmas-provisional-approach-to-implement-the-new-digital-markets-competition-regime">new digital markets competition regime paper</a> gives the CMA the ability to impose requirements on the conduct of firms in digital markets where those firms have been designated as having Strategic Market Status (SMS)  and to impose significant fines against firms if those requirements are breached.<br/>
<br/>
In that paper, the CMA also confirmed it expects to launch around three to four SMS investigations within the first year of the new digital markets competition regime coming into force, which is expected later this year. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/uk-antitrust-watchdog-closes-probe-app-store/">UK Antitrust Watchdog Closes Apple App Store Investigation, Case to Be Reconsidered Under New Digital Rules Regime</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-antitrust-watchdog-closes-apple-app-store-investigation-case-to-be-reconsidered-under-new-digital-rules-regime.2434068/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Can&#039;t Release Old App for Customers Unhappy With Design Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/sonos-not-rereleasing-old-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-cant-release-old-app-for-customers-unhappy-with-design-changes.2434045/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/sonos-not-rereleasing-old-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos won't be able to re-release its old app to appease customers that have been dissatisfied with the new version of the app, Sonos CEO Patrick Spence today said on Reddit <em>(via <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/20/24224754/sonos-ceo-old-s2-app-re-release-cant-be">The Verge</a>)</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
Spence said that he was "hopeful" the old app would be able to be re-released up until "very recently" as an alternative for people having issues, but Sonos found that doing so would ultimately make the issues worse because of backend updates to cloud servers and the software that runs on speakers.<br/>
<blockquote>Everything has been on the table in terms of finding the fastest path to fixing your systems. In fact, until very recently I'd been hopeful that we could re-release the old app (S2) as an alternative for those of you that are having issues that we've not yet resolved.<br/>
<br/>
The trick of course is that Sonos is not just the mobile app, but software that runs on your speakers and in the cloud too. In the months since the new mobile app launched we've been updating the software that runs on our speakers and in the cloud to the point where today S2 is less reliable &amp; less stable then what you remember. After doing extensive testing we've reluctantly concluded that re-releasing S2 would make the problems worse, not better. I'm sure this is disappointing. It was disappointing to me.</blockquote><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/sonos-bring-back-old-app/">Earlier this month</a>, <em>The Verge</em> reported that Sonos was considering bringing back the original version of its app, and Sonos was reportedly hopeful that allowing customers to revert to the old app would provide an interim solution as the company works to improve the new app. It sounds like that plan has been scrapped, which is unfortunate for customers who are having problems with the redesign.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">redesigned version of its app</a> back in May, and it has turned out to be a disaster for the company. Sonos customers quickly found that the new app lacked several key features and was riddled with bugs, and there have been ongoing complaints for months.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/">issued an apology</a> in July and shared an outline of future update plans that will see missing features returned in September and October. In August, Sonos said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delays-product-launces-to-fix-app/">it would delay</a> two upcoming product launches planned for 2024 to focus on improving the app.<br/>
<br/>
In today's Reddit post, Spence said that the "original architect of the Sonos platform" has been put back in charge, and that the company has also "pulled together the very best and most experienced engineers" that it has to work on the app until it is fixed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/sonos-not-rereleasing-old-app/">Sonos Can&#039;t Release Old App for Customers Unhappy With Design Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-cant-release-old-app-for-customers-unhappy-with-design-changes.2434045/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Photography Awards Highlight Best Images of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-photography-awards-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-photography-awards-highlight-best-images-of-2024.2434042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:42:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-photography-awards-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Every year, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Photography Awards (IPPA) selects the best photographs captured with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and the 2024 award winners <a href="https://www.ippawards.com/?v=7516fd43adaa">were announced today</a>. Many of this year's winning images were taken with Apple's most recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Blue-Three-Quarters-Perspective-Camera-Closeup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909012" /><br/>
The grand prize image features a boy at an aquarium, with the photo shot in black and white using an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iphone-photography-award-main-winner.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="795" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962058" /><br/>
The first place image includes a group of swimmers at a lifeguard camp from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 Pro Pro Max, while the second place image features children in Cambodia shot on an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/first-place-ippa-winner-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="600" height="761" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962059" /><br/>
There are also winners across a number of categories, including abstract, animals, architecture, children, cityscape, landscape, lifestyle, nature, people, portrait, series, still life, travel, and other. All of the winning images can be <a href="https://www.ippawards.com/2024-winning-photographers/?v=7516fd43adaa">viewed on the IPPA website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
IPPA has been running the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Photography Awards since 2007, and 2024 marks the 17th annual competition. The contests are open to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users worldwide, and images can be edited with iOS apps. It is worth noting that it costs money to send in a photo, but Apple devices are provided as prizes.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-photography-awards-2024/">iPhone Photography Awards Highlight Best Images of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-photography-awards-highlight-best-images-of-2024.2434042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for Beats Studio Pro With Audio Sharing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro-with-audio-sharing.2434041/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:30:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Beats Studio Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware for the Beats Studio Pro over-ear headphones. The Beats Studio Pro can be updated to firmware version 2C301, up from the prior 2B68 firmware that was installed on the headphones at launch. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/beats-studio-pro-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903700" /><br/>
Today's firmware update introduces support for audio sharing, a feature that was not available at launch. Audio sharing is designed to allow two people to listen to music from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Share Audio option was not there on the old 2B68 firmware. <a href="https://t.co/5xLX46lElP">pic.twitter.com/5xLX46lElP</a></p>&mdash; Jonathan Forsander (@jforsander) <a href="https://twitter.com/jforsander/status/1826027992134595029?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 20, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple introduced the Beats Studio Pro headphones <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/beats-studio-pro-debut/">just over a year ago</a>, marking an update to the original Studio headphones that made the Beats brand popular. The &#36;350 Beats Studio Pro headphones feature Active Noise Cancellation support, Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking, multiple audio profiles, and improved audio quality with better bass performance compared to prior models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not include an Apple audio chip in the Beats Studio Pro, instead opting for a custom Beats chip that provides better feature parity between iOS and Android devices. The Beats chip supports one-touch pairing and setup, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> integration, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> support, but automatic switching between devices is not available.<br/>
<br/>
As with all of Apple's headphone and earbud products, firmware updates for the Beats Studio Pro are delivered over-the-air. Firmware will be installed while the Beats headphones are charging and are in Bluetooth range of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, or Mac that's connected to Wi-Fi.<br/>
<br/>
On Android devices, users will need to download the Beats app for Android and connect the Android device to a power outlet to initiate a firmware update. There is no word on what's new in the firmware.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats-studio-pro/">Beats Studio Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro/">Apple Releases New Firmware for Beats Studio Pro With Audio Sharing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro-with-audio-sharing.2434041/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Major &#039;National Public Data&#039; Leak Worse Than Expected With Passwords Stored in Plain Text</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/npd-data-leak-plain-text/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-national-public-data-leak-worse-than-expected-with-passwords-stored-in-plain-text.2434039/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:42:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/npd-data-leak-plain-text/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this month, data broker National Public Data (NPD) announced that there had <a href="https://nationalpublicdata.com/Breach.html">been a major data breach</a> that saw hackers obtain millions of names, email addresses, phone numbers, social security numbers, and mailing addresses stored in its database. NPD is a company that does employee background checks, aggregating public data from numerous sources and selling it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-security-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1145" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796484" /><br/>
NPD's security was clearly lacking to allow for the breach in the first place, but a new report from <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2024/08/national-public-data-published-its-own-passwords/"><em>KrebsOnSecurity</em></a> suggests that an NPD sister site made an even more grievous error, hosting an easily accessible plaintext archive with usernames and passwords.<br/>
<br/>
RecordsCheck.net, a site affiliated with NPD that hosts much of the same information, had a "members.zip" file that was downloadable until yesterday. It had source code and plain text usernames and passwords for RecordsCheck users, including logins belonging to NPD's founder, Salvatore Verini. The logins that were made available through RecordsCheck allowed access to the same data that was available via NPD.<br/>
<br/>
After being alerted by KrebsOnSecurity, RecordsCheck removed the file, and NPD is shutting down the site, according to Verini. He told the KrebsOnSecurity that the file had an "old version of the site with non-working code and passwords."<br/>
<br/>
There are websites <a href="https://www.npdbreach.com/">that are available</a> to see if your information was leaked in the NPD breach, and it is advisable to lock down your credit.<br/>
<br/>
The NPD leak included decades of information, including data from people who are now deceased. 137 million email addresses <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2024/08/nationalpublicdata-com-hack-exposes-a-nations-data/">were leaked</a>, as were 272 million social security numbers. A lawsuit has <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/social-security-number-leak-npd-breach-what-to-know/">since been filed</a> against NPD.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/npd-data-leak-plain-text/">Major &#039;National Public Data&#039; Leak Worse Than Expected With Passwords Stored in Plain Text</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-national-public-data-leak-worse-than-expected-with-passwords-stored-in-plain-text.2434039/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Gives Customers 45 Days to Extend AppleCare+ Coverage After Expiration</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/applecare-coverage-extension-period-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-gives-customers-45-days-to-extend-applecare-coverage-after-expiration.2434031/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:21:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/applecare-coverage-extension-period-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AppleCare</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in August increased the period in which customers can extend their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ coverage after it expires. Apple used to allow coverage to be extended for 30 days after the end of the original &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan, but that has now changed to 45 days.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/applecare-apple-care-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1896" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828594" /><br/>
The <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/101560">AppleCare+ extension support document</a> says that customers have 45 days to sign up for a new &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan after existing coverage expires, with options for extending plans by 24 months, 36 months, monthly, or on an annual basis until canceled.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans can be extended for 45 days after expiration in Australia, Austria Canada, Denmark, Finland, France, Germany, Ireland, Italy, Japan, the Netherlands, New Zealand, Norway, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, the United Kingdom, and the United States. In China, there is still a 30-day limit.<br/>
<br/>
An upfront &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Apple Watch is eligible for updated coverage that renews monthly or annually, while upfront &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans for Mac can be enrolled in a new coverage plan that renews on an annual basis.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who want to renew their expired &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans can go to <a href="https://mysupport.apple.com/">Apple's support website</a> to see if their devices are eligible. Apple does not guarantee that &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ can be renewed, and it does not alert customers when &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ is expiring unless required by law.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ expiration dates can be checked in the Settings app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, in the System Settings app on a Mac, or <a href="https://mysupport.apple.com/">on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/applecare-coverage-extension-period-increase/">Apple Now Gives Customers 45 Days to Extend AppleCare+ Coverage After Expiration</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-gives-customers-45-days-to-extend-applecare-coverage-after-expiration.2434031/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OnePlus Buds Pro 3 vs. AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2.2434021/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:58:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>OnePlus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Chinese company OnePlus is debuting new earbuds today, with a feature set that pits them against the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>. The OnePlus Buds Pro 3 look and sound a lot like Apple's AirPods, and while they lack some of the Apple-esque magic integration, they're more affordable at &#36;179.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c4d9oj0Z43o" title="These Headphones Sound BETTER than AirPods Pro!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Design wise, the OnePlus earbuds resemble the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, featuring an in-ear silicone design and a stem. The stem is silver, though, and unlike Samsung's recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a>, you won't mistake these for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; due to the unique case design of the OnePlus Buds Pro 3. Fit is close to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; because of the silicone tips, and they're comfortable to wear. Squeeze gestures can be used on the stem to play/pause music, skip tracks, replay a track, and adjust volume.<br/>
<br/>
The case has an oval shape that's wider and more rounded than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; case, plus it's covered in a faux leather material that gives it a more distinct look.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may have added a USB-C case to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 in 2023, but the initial launch was in 2022, so it's no surprise that other companies are starting to surpass the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; in terms of sound quality. The OnePlus Buds Pro 3 have better out-of-the-box sound than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, even though there's no option for adjusting EQ.<br/>
<br/>
There's a solid balance between bass and higher frequencies with full sound and good separation of tracks. Sound is crisp, and the high-end notes are clear. there are two DACs per earbud, one that's focused on the tweeter and the other on the woofer, which is what gives that balanced sound.<br/>
<br/>
The Active Noise Cancellation works well, and it's on par with ANC from other high-end earbuds. The ANC is adaptive and can adjust based on your surroundings, so ambient sounds can come through when you need them to. The ANC isn't as standout as the sound quality, but it's more than adequate.<br/>
<br/>
Battery lasts for up to 43 hours, which is 13 hours longer than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, and there is ear detection when using the earbuds with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. As for the microphones, call quality is solid.<br/>
<br/>
OnePlus sells Android-based devices, so these earbuds are designed for Android smartphones rather than the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. You're not going to get the useful AirPods features like quick connect and automatic device swapping, and that's a major downside. You also won't get spatial audio unless these are paired with a Google Pixel phone that supports the feature.<br/>
<br/>
For Apple device users, the OnePlus Buds Pro 3 are just standard Bluetooth earbuds, but if that's all you need, you might like what OnePlus has to offer.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oneplus/">OnePlus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2/">OnePlus Buds Pro 3 vs. AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2.2434021/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434012/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:08:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the seventh beta of upcoming an upcoming macOS 15 Sequoia update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-6/">release of the sixth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which allows you to control your locked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac. You can open and use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, interact with notifications, and drag and drop files between your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
There are new options for window tiling, and dragging a window to the edge of the display will suggest a tiled location to make it easier to use multiple apps at once. Apple is adding a Passwords app for managing passwords, Safari can summarize websites, surface key information, and Notes has support for live audio transcription and math equations.<br/>
<br/>
All of the Apple Intelligence features coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> will also be available in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, but Apple does not plan to add these until later in the beta testing process. Apple Intelligence includes Writing Tools for editing, proofreading, and summarizing text in apps, and an Image Playground allows for AI images to be created from prompts.<br/>
<br/>
Custom emoji or "Genmoji" can be created for any situation and used just like emoji, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting much smarter. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do more in apps and will better understand requests, especially those made in regard to on-screen content.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/">Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434012/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:07:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the seventh betas of upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-6-to-developers/">release of the sixth betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;/&zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; Developer Beta setting. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta. The &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; beta track is now separate from the iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1 beta track, with the .1 betas adding support for Apple Intelligence on devices that are able to run the features. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; introduces Apple Intelligence, a set of AI features that are built deeply into the operating system. Apple Intelligence won't be coming until later in the beta testing process, but it includes features for refining and editing writing, generating images and emoji, and most notably, improving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and search. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is gaining a better understanding of natural language, improved contextual awareness, and the personal assistant will integrate with ChatGPT to answer more complex queries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features are limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and iPads with an M-series chip, but there are a number of other features that are coming. Apple is allowing users to rearrange Home screen apps to have open spaces, plus there's a dark mode for app icons and tinting options.<br/>
<br/>
The Control Center is customizable and third-party developers can add controls for their apps, with the Lock Screen Flashlight and Camera icons able to be replaced or removed. Messages is gaining Rich Communication Services support to improve conversations with Android users, the option to schedule texts to be sent later, new text effects, messages over satellite when there's no cellular, and the option to use any emoji for Tapback responses.<br/>
<br/>
There's a dedicated Passwords app for logins, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, and verification codes, and there's now an option to lock and hide apps, which means they can't be opened without secondary <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication even when your phone is unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
Safari has a highlights feature that summarizes articles and surfaces key information on websites, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app interface has been overhauled, and there's a new Tap to Cash feature for privately and securely transferring money using Apple Cash. Other features include equation solving and voice memo transcription in Notes, a game mode for improving game performance, and an option to respond to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on AirPods with head gestures.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will release &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; to the public this fall.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Seventh Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
