<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:03:41 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 20th Anniversary iPhone: What We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/20th-anniversary-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-20th-anniversary-iphone-what-we-know-so-far.2457232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:33:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/20th-anniversary-iphone&#038;post_date=1747449223/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2027 will mark the 20th anniversary of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and Apple is planning to celebrate with an all-new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; design. With the 10th anniversary of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple unveiled the all-display &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X with no bezels at the top or the bottom for the camera or the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> home button. It marked the debut of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, and dictated the next decade of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/All-Screen-iPhone-2027-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001660" /><br/>
For the "&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XX," Apple needs to do even better, and rumors suggest that the company has some big ideas that it's aiming for.<br/>
<br/>
Apple wants to create an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/20th-anniversary-iphone-all-screen-design/">all-glass iPhone</a> that doesn't have cutouts in the display, so there could be a high-end &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 19 Pro model that fulfills that requirement. Apple wants a true <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/20th-anniversary-iphone-all-screen-report/">edge-to-edge display</a><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
The 20th anniversary &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that Apple is planning for 2027 could feature a radical design, offering a display that has no visible frame or bezels. An early rumor suggests that Apple is aiming for a display that curves around all four edges of the device, for a borderless visual experience.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793994" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/Beyond-iPhone-13-Better-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple wants a mostly glass &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a curved display and no cutouts, which would necessitate under-display &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; and an under-display camera.<br/>
<br/>
An all-glass &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a wraparound display that covers all four edges of the device would be less durable than current &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models that have titanium or aluminum frames, so Apple may need to come up with more durable glass before such a device is a possibility.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="battery">Battery</h2><br/>
Apple is developing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/2027-iphone-game-changing-silicon-battery/">new battery technology</a> that could make it into the 2027 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. Apple is looking into using pure silicon anode batteries, which are able to store more lithium ions per gram than current batteries, resulting in significant increases in battery life without major increases in battery size.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ram">RAM</h2><br/>
Apple could use advanced AI memory technology for the 2027 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. Apple is rumored to be considering Mobile High Bandwidth Memory (HBM), a type of DRAM that stacks memory chips vertically and connects them through tiny vertical interconnects to boost signal transmission speeds.<br/>
<br/>
In smartphones, the technology would provide high data throughput while minimizing power consumption and the physical footprint of RAM dies.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="name">Name</h2><br/>
Technically, the 20th anniversary &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup would be the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 19 lineup, but in 2017, Apple released a surprise "&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X" alongside the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8 models. This year, Apple could have similar plans for the high-end device, though what it might be called is unclear.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could decide to call it the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 20, like the decision it made for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X in 2017, or the company could stick with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 19 naming. Alternatively, the all-display device could have an entirely new name, like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-ultra/">iPhone Ultra</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that Apple has planned could be a replacement for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Pro models, or it could be sold alongside them. With plans for a foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in 2026, though, it may not make sense to add yet another phone to the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
The 20th anniversary &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; would presumably come out in the fall of 2027.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/20th-anniversary-iphone/">Apple&#039;s 20th Anniversary iPhone: What We Know So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-20th-anniversary-iphone-what-we-know-so-far.2457232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Even More iPhone Safety Tips You Should Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/more-iphone-safety-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/even-more-iphone-safety-tips-you-should-know.2457229/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:47:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/more-iphone-safety-tips&#038;post_date=1747442861/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last week, we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-safety-tools/">shared a list of iPhone safety tools</a> that every <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owner should know about, from Emergency SOS and Medical ID to Safety Check and Check In. <em>MacRumors</em> readers <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-iphone-safety-tools-you-should-know-about.2456810/post-33900031">had more suggestions</a> on safety information we should highlight, so we have a follow-up.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iPhone-Safety-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001168" /><br/>
<h2 id="you_dont_need_a_sim_to_call_emergency_services">You Don't Need a SIM to Call Emergency Services</h2><br/>
If you have an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with no SIM inside and no cellular service, you can still use it to call emergency services in the United States, Canada, and Australia.<br/>
<br/>
When emergency services are dialed on a smartphone with no SIM, it will automatically connect to any carrier network that's available, no questions asked. If you have an old &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it's worth keeping it charged up and available as a spare in case you ever need it in an emergency.<br/>
<br/>
You'll see "SOS" or "SOS only" in the status bar if you're able to use an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with no SIM for an emergency call.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="you_dont_need_signal_to_call_emergency_services">You Don't Need Signal to Call Emergency Services</h2><br/>
Likewise, if you have no signal and you're in an emergency situation, try dialing emergency services anyway. Even if your carrier doesn't have signal where you are, there could be another carrier that does, and you can automatically use that network.<br/>
<br/>
If you see "SOS" or "SOS only" in the status bar on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it means you don't have a signal with your carrier, but you can still use another carrier to make an emergency call. If your phone says No Service or Searching, there is no nearby cellular network to connect to for an emergency call.<br/>
<br/>
If you're in a remote or rural area with no carrier signal from any carrier, you may be able to use Emergency SOS via satellite on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 or later model to place to get help in an emergency.<br/>
<br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will let you know that a satellite connection is available whenever you're out of cellular or Wi-Fi range. Using Emergency SOS via Satellite typically requires a clear view of the sky for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to establish a connection.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="emergency_services_and_your_location">Emergency Services and Your Location</h2><br/>
When you place an emergency call, your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is able to automatically relay your location to emergency services in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
It does this through a feature called HELO, or Hybridized Emergency Location, which Apple has supported since 2015. HELO uses cell towers and on-device data points like GPS and Wi-Fi to estimate a 911 caller's location.<br/>
<br/>
Location information is relayed through a software system provided by RapidSOS that 911 centers use, and it's how emergency personnel can find you when you call from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="wi-fi_calling">Wi-Fi Calling</h3><br/>
If you're using Wi-Fi calling, you've probably been prompted to enter an Emergency Address. This is so you can be located if you're calling using a Wi-Fi connection. You'll want to make sure your Emergency Address is up to date if Wi-Fi calling is a feature that you use.<br/>
<br/>
You can update your Emergency Address by going to the Settings app, navigating to the Apps section, choosing Phone, tapping on Wi-Fi calling, and then tapping on Update Emergency Address. Apple says you should update your address whenever you change your location.<br/>
<br/>
911 calls will only be placed over Wi-Fi if a cellular network is unavailable, so it's not the default option. When Wi-Fi calling is available, you'll see Wi-Fi in the status bar.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="you_can_text_911">You Can Text 911</h2><br/>
In the United States and some other countries, you can text 911 if making a phone call isn't an option. To do so, open the Messages app, type in your emergency services number, and then type your emergency in the text message field.<br/>
<br/>
When you text 911, your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; goes into an emergency mode for a 30 minute period, and to exit it, you'll need to restart.<br/>
<br/>
Texting 911 is available on iPhones running iOS 13 or later, and you can also text on an Apple Watch with watchOS 6 or later. Texting 911 requires a cellular connection.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="you_can_send_video_to_911">You Can Send Video to 911</h2><br/>
As of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, there is an option to share streaming video and recorded media with 911 operators during emergency calls. When you call 911, emergency dispatchers can send a request to share live video or photos over a secure connection.<br/>
<br/>
The ability to share photos and video with emergency services is available thanks to Apple's partnerships with RapidSOS and Prepared.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="carrier_satellite_services_vs._apple_emergency_sos_via_satellite">Carrier Satellite Services vs. Apple Emergency SOS via Satellite</h2><br/>
On the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 and all later &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, there is a built-in Apple-provided satellite connectivity feature that can be used for emergency situations, texting, and updating your location when Wi-Fi and cellular connectivity are not available.<br/>
<br/>
Separately, some carriers <em>also</em> offer satellite connectivity, and this is distinct from Emergency SOS via Satellite. Apple and cellular carriers haven't done a great job making the distinction between Emergency SOS via Satellite and carrier-provided satellite services, so there can be some confusion.<br/>
<br/>
To use Emergency SOS via Satellite, you need an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 or later, and you need to use Apple's satellite services provided by Globalstar. Emergency SOS via Satellite is the default on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and it will show up when you do not have a cellular or Wi-Fi connection.<br/>
<br/>
With carrier services, what's available varies by carrier, and it comes into play if you have an older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or are in an area where you can't get connectivity through one of Globalstar's satellites. Most carrier satellite services right now are provided through Starlink, and with Starlink, you can text over satellite, but not call.<br/>
<br/>
If you have T-Mobile in the U.S., au in Japan, or One NZ in New Zealand, you have access to Starlink satellite connectivity. In an emergency, if Starlink is what you can connect to, you will need to text emergency services by typing 911 (or your local emergency number) in the Messages app. Starlink may support calls and data in the future, but it does not at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
When you see mentions of Emergency SOS and satellite calls on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in news stories, commercials, and other places, it is referencing the built-in satellite option available on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 and later.<br/>
<br/>
Carrier satellite services are now supported on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 and later, so if you have an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 model, you may be able to text emergency services using carrier satellite services when you have no signal, but you can't use Emergency SOS via Satellite.<br/>
<br/>
Carrier satellite services may be included in some plans or could cost extra in some situations, and it varies from carrier to carrier.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="siri_health_integration">Siri Health Integration</h2><br/>
For a long time now, Apple has partnered with the Suicide Prevention Lifeline to direct customers who may be feeling down to the hotline to get help. If you tell <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> you're thinking of suicide, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will suggest that you call and will offer to dial for you.<br/>
<br/>
Telling &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; you're depressed will prompt &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to offer to call a friend, family member, or NHS.uk.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; also integrates with other services. If you've been sexually assaulted, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will offer to call the National Sexual Assault Hotline. If you've been abused, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will offer to call the National Domestic Abuse Hotline.<br/>
<br/>
You can ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to dial 911 (or your local emergency number) if you're not able to. In the U.S., &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can also dial 988 to reach the National Suicide Prevention and Crisis Hotline.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="add_more">Add More</h2><br/>
Have another tip that you think we should share, safety-related or on another topic entirely? Let us know in the comments or <a href="mailto:guides@macrumors.com">send us an email here</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/more-iphone-safety-tips/">Even More iPhone Safety Tips You Should Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/even-more-iphone-safety-tips-you-should-know.2457229/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an Apple Watch Ultra 2 From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-apple-watch-may/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-apple-watch-ultra-2-from-grid-studio.2457219/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:39:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-apple-watch-may/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://www.gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>. GRID Studio is known for taking non-operational Apple devices that would be cluttering up a landfill and turning them into <a href="https://www.gridstudio.cc/collections/all">stylish art for Apple fans</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/grid-studio-iphone-2g.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002007" /><br/>
GRID Studio takes apart iPhones, iPads, Macs, and other Apple accessories, cleverly displaying each component to provide a look inside Apple's most iconic products. The pieces are arranged in a frame and accompanied by labels and little tidbits of Apple history.<br/>
<br/>
The company is offering a flash sale this weekend, with up to 50 percent off a range of products. The GRID 1, featuring the <a href="https://www.gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">well-known first-generation iPhone</a>, for example, is available for &#36;299, which is a &#36;100 discount off of the typical price.<br/>
<br/>
The original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is one of Apple's most recognizable devices, and it is the ideal piece to get because it was such an important part of Apple's history. The GRID 1 features all of the internal components from the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, from the home button to the chassis.<br/>
<br/>
For something more affordable, the <a href="https://www.gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-6plus">GRID 6 Plus</a>, featuring the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 Plus, is just &#36;99 during the sale. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 Plus was Apple's first larger-sized &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, sold alongside the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6. It is perhaps best known for being the subject of the major "bendgate" controversy because the chassis could become distorted in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/grid-studio-iphone-6-plus.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002008" /><br/>
The GRID 13, <a href="https://www.gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-13">available for &#36;179</a>, features Apple's more modern &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13. The GRID 13 shows off the newer, flat-edged chassis that Apple introduced with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12, a logic board with the A15 chip, and a range of components like the Taptic Engine and the TrueDepth camera system.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/grid-studio-iphone-13.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002009" /><br/>
GRID Studio does accessories too, such as the Magic Mouse. A disassembled version of the Magic Mouse <a href="https://www.gridstudio.cc/products/grid-magic-mouse">is on sale for &#36;99</a>, and it feature's Apple's love it or hate it mouse design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/grid-studio-magic-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002010" /><br/>
We have an (assembled and functional) &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; from GRID Studio to give away to one lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/qQKt9/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow"><br/>
  GRID Studio Giveaway</a><script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (May 16) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on May 23. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after May 23 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-apple-watch-may/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an Apple Watch Ultra 2 From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-apple-watch-ultra-2-from-grid-studio.2457219/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Fortnite for iOS Isn&#039;t Blocked Worldwide, Just the U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-fortnite-ios-not-blocked-worldwide/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-fortnite-for-ios-isnt-blocked-worldwide-just-the-u-s.2457214/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:58:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-fortnite-ios-not-blocked-worldwide/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today clarified that it has not blocked <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> from updating the iOS Fortnite app in the European Union, but it is not planning to allow &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; to offer Fortnite in the United States <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite_apple_featured.jpg" alt="" width="2140" height="1204" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-754674" /><br/>
In a statement to <em><a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1923404412090782109">Bloomberg</a></em>, Apple said that &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; tied its U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; submission to the update that was also being submitted to the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store for iOS in the European Union. Apple told &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; to resubmit the update without the U.S. component.<br/>
<blockquote>We asked that Epic Sweden resubmit the app update without including the US storefront of the App Store so as not to impact Fortnite in other geographies. We did not take any action to remove the live version of Fortnite from alternative distribution marketplaces in the EC.</blockquote><br/>
This morning, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; claimed that Apple blocked its Fortnite submission worldwide. "Apple blocked our Fortnite submission so we cannot release to the US &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; or to the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store for iOS in the European Union," <a href="https://x.com/Fortnite/status/1923293522234356169">Epic Games said</a>. The company went on to claim that Fortnite on iOS will be "offline worldwide until Apple unblocks it."<br/>
<br/>
Given Apple's clarification, it sounds like &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; has decided to take Fortnite offline in the European Union rather than submitting an update that does not include Fortnite for the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. By tying the updates together and suggesting Apple is denying Fortnite's distribution worldwide, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; could rally lawmakers and customers to push back at Apple's attempt to "block" Fortnite in the U.S.<br/>
<br/>
Fortnite gets weekly updates, and the updates need to go out for all platforms at the same time. Apple didn't remove Fortnite from the iOS &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store in the European Union, but by denying the Fortnite submission, the EU version of the game won't get the update on time. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; could remove the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; version of Fortnite from its app submission in order to update the EU version and keep it functional, but it's not yet clear if Epic plans to do so.<br/>
<br/>
Fortnite has been banned from the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; since 2020, and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; does not have a valid U.S. developer account. Last year, to distribute Fortnite in the European Union using an alternative app marketplace, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; created a subsidiary, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Sweden. Because &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; has no U.S. developer account, the company used &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Sweden to submit Fortnite to the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a> lawsuit, Apple was at no point forced to allow Fortnite back in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and it was made clear that Apple does not have an obligation to distribute Fortnite.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; CEO Tim Sweeney said ahead of Apple's decision that he would be "very surprised" if Apple "decided to brave the geopolitical storm of blocking a major app from iOS," but the reality is that Fortnite hasn't been available through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; for the last five years.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was recently ordered to change its &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules to allow developers to direct customers to purchase options outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the U.S., which is why &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; thought it would be able to bring Fortnite back to the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but Apple is upholding the ban. There is nothing in the order that changes the situation with Fortnite.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-fortnite-ios-not-blocked-worldwide/">Apple Says Fortnite for iOS Isn&#039;t Blocked Worldwide, Just the U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-fortnite-for-ios-isnt-blocked-worldwide-just-the-u-s.2457214/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay, Apple Card, Wallet and Apple Cash Currently Experiencing Service Issues [Update: Fixed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-pay-apple-card-wallet-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-apple-card-wallet-and-apple-cash-currently-experiencing-service-issues-update-fixed.2457213/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:45:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-pay-apple-card-wallet-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you're having problems using your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, Apple Cash, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, or the Wallet app, you're not alone. According to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's System Status page</a>, there is an ongoing issue affecting these services.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
Apple says that some users may be experiencing issues with &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;, Apple Cash, &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, or Wallet, and there are multiple complaints on social media sites about &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; and other features not working.<br/>
<br/>
The outage has been ongoing since 11:44 a.m. Eastern Time. We'll update this article when the services are back online.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 2:13 p.m. Eastern Time:</b> Apple says the issues have been addressed. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-pay-apple-card-wallet-outage/">Apple Pay, Apple Card, Wallet and Apple Cash Currently Experiencing Service Issues [Update: Fixed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-apple-card-wallet-and-apple-cash-currently-experiencing-service-issues-update-fixed.2457213/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: CarPlay Ultra and Samsung&#039;s iPhone 17 Air Rival</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/the-macrumors-show-carplay-ultra-and-s25-edge/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-carplay-ultra-and-samsungs-iphone-17-air-rival.2457211/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:28:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/the-macrumors-show-carplay-ultra-and-s25-edge/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the long-awaited rollout of Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> Ultra and Samsung's all-new S25 Edge, which is positioned to rival the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a> later this year. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XkhAPm6eN_o?si=nMAZXJlGIvB1g0Jg" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apples-carplay-ultra-now-available/">announced CarPlay Ultra</a>, its next-generation &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; experience. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; Ultra fully extends across all of the vehicle's displays, including the instrument cluster. It provides access to real-time vehicle data, supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> widgets, theme options, instrument cluster display customizations, and introduces integrations for vehicle functions.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; Ultra is available first in new Aston Martin models in North America. Existing Aston Martin vehicles will also support &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; Ultra through forthcoming software updates. Looking ahead, Apple says it has secured commitments from Hyundai, Kia, and Genesis to bring &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; Ultra to their vehicles in the coming year. Other automakers are expected to follow.<br/>
<br/>
In other news, Samsung this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/samsung-galaxy-s25-edge-2/">announced the Galaxy S25 Edge</a> — a device clearly designed to undercut the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;'s expected appeal, with both smartphones aiming to be the thinnest in their respective ecosystems.<br/>
<br/>
The Galaxy S25 Edge sports a 6.7-inch AMOLED display, a titanium frame, and a remarkably slim 5.8mm profile, weighing in at just 163 grams. It features a dual-lens camera system, including a 200MP wide-angle sensor and a 12MP ultra-wide camera, supported by Qualcomm's Snapdragon 8 Elite chip. Samsung is also pushing its AI credentials with features like Drawing Assist and Audio Eraser.<br/>
<br/>
In contrast, the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; is rumored to be even thinner at just 5.5mm, making it Apple's slimmest &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; ever. It is expected to feature a 6.6-inch OLED display with ProMotion. Apple is said to be removing the ultra-wide camera entirely and opting for a single 48MP wide camera, removing the SIM card tray, and the secondary stereo speaker to save internal space. Other expected specifications include a 24MP front-facing camera, 12GB of RAM, and the A19 chip.<br/>
<br/>
While the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; may win the title of thinnest flagship, it could come with a major compromise: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/09/iphone-17-air-battery-life-rumors/">battery life</a>. According to internal testing leaks, only 60–70% of users are expected to get through a full day on a single charge — a notable drop from the 80–90% seen with other recent &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. Apple is reportedly using a higher-density battery and its custom C1 modem to squeeze as much efficiency as possible into the super-thin design. <br/>
<br/>
To address this, Apple is reportedly developing a new USB-C battery case, designed to extend the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;'s runtime. The accessory could launch alongside the device to help mitigate negative perceptions around longevity. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/09/the-macrumors-show-after-iphone-17-2026-and-beyond/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up to hear our discussion about how the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup is rumored to change after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup later this year, looking at what to expect in 2026, 2027, and beyond.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/18/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-apple-intelligence/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/the-macrumors-show-carplay-ultra-and-s25-edge/">The MacRumors Show: CarPlay Ultra and Samsung&#039;s iPhone 17 Air Rival</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-carplay-ultra-and-samsungs-iphone-17-air-rival.2457211/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Sitewide Sales Hit Anker, Verizon, Samsung, and More, Plus BOGO Apple Watch Band Sale at Woot</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-16-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-sitewide-sales-hit-anker-verizon-samsung-and-more-plus-bogo-apple-watch-band-sale-at-woot.2457207/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:10:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-16-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals include a big sitewide sale at Anker that's exclusive to MacRumors readers, a BOGO Apple Watch band sale at Woot, and a couple of solid discounts on iPhone charging stations and Jackery portable batteries at Amazon. We're also tracking sales at Verizon, T-Mobile, Samsung, and Logitech below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Best-Apple-Deals-Feature-Shelf-Purple-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992236" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Charging Accessories at Amazon</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/new-jackery-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001957" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Find great deals on iPhone charging stations and Jackery batteries</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV4WNKHT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.25OEQTDMMBWFE%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.25OEQTDMMBWFE_1747404472041">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV4WNKHT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.25OEQTDMMBWFE%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.25OEQTDMMBWFE_1747404472041"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Twelve South HiRise 3 Deluxe for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S89SKRQVKWFH%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S89SKRQVKWFH_1747404572767"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;330 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 500 for &#36;469.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week, we're tracking a handful of solid discounts on a collection of iPhone charging stations and portable power stations. Regarding the former accessories, you'll find up to &#36;50 off charging stations from Twelve South and Belkin, with the Belkin devices requiring you to clip an on-page coupon.<br/>
<br/>
For the Jackery accessories, there are big discounts on a trio of the company's portable power stations. We've listed all of these deals below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D6RZT4HH%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3BX4ZGESEVHX2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3BX4ZGESEVHX2_1747404388068">Belkin 3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Station</a> - &#36;89.95 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;99.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL86NC5Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3BX4ZGESEVHX2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3BX4ZGESEVHX2_1747404432387">Belkin 3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Stand</a> - &#36;99.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;119.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV4WNKHT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.25OEQTDMMBWFE%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.25OEQTDMMBWFE_1747404472041">Twelve South HiRise 3 Deluxe</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S89SKRQVKWFH%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S89SKRQVKWFH_1747404572767">Jackery Solar Generator Explorer 500</a> - &#36;469.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ72D53Q%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1CUDE9NG1KCJT%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1CUDE9NG1KCJT_1747404505114">Jackery Solar Generator Explorer 100 Plus</a> - &#36;629.00, down from &#36;929.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZHK1D2P%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ZE6WJ1ZFKCP%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ZE6WJ1ZFKCP_1747404538769">Jackery Solar Generator 3000 Pro</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;3,699.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/anker-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001959" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 20% off sitewide with our exclusive sale</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/anker-offers-macrumors-readers-20-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE 20% OFF</div>Anker Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker is still offering our readers an exclusive 20 percent off this month, and the code works on nearly every accessory sitewide. In order to get this deal, <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">head to Anker's website</a> and add an accessory to your cart, then enter the code <strong>Ankermacrumors2025</strong> at checkout to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Bands at Woot</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/new-braided-loop.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001961" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Buy one Solo/Braided Loop on sale, get up to two free</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-band-discovery-box-buy-1-get-some-free">Woot</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/woots-new-apple-watch-band-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-band-discovery-box-buy-1-get-some-free"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY ONE GET 2 FREE</div>Apple Watch Bands at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot's BOGO sale on Apple Watch Solo Loop and Braided Solo Loop bands is still happening this week, but it is poised to finally end later tonight. If enough stock still remains, Woot could extend the sale again, but now is your best chance to buy one Solo/Braided Loop at a huge discount and get up to two bands for free.<br/>
<br/>
For more information on how this sale works, be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/woots-new-apple-watch-band-sale/">visit our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Verizon</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/verizon-summer-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001962" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on iPhone and iPad cases, smartphones, and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/verizon-and-samsung-new-sales/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Red Hot Deal Days at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Verizon's summer kickoff is back with the carrier's "Red Hot Deal Days" event, offering great deals on iPhone Silicone Cases, iPad Smart Folio, charging accessories, smartphones, wearables, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/viewfinity-samsung-monitor.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001963" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on monitors, storage solutions, and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/uzme1brcsvjpc">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/verizon-and-samsung-new-sales/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/uzme1brcsvjpc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Samsung Spring Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's discount event this week includes solid savings on a collection of monitors, like the <a href="https://howl.link/c9y6squyw01qs">27-inch ViewFinity S9 Smart Monitor</a> for &#36;979.99 (&#36;620 off). You'll also find a few sales on portable SSD devices, TVs, home appliances, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Logitech</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/logitech-keyboard.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001965" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;150 off with select purchase amounts</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://logitech.cfzu.net/kOkKKM">Logitech</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://logitech.cfzu.net/kOkKKM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY MORE, SAVE MORE</div>Logitech Summer Kickoff</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Logitech is kicking off the summer season with a sale that provides &#36;30 off orders worth &#36;150 or more, &#36;70 off orders worth &#36;250 or more, and &#36;150 off orders worth &#36;450 or more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>T-Mobile</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iphone-16-pro-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001969" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get an iPhone 16 Pro at no cost when switching to T-Mobile</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phone/apple-iphone-16-pro">T-Mobile</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phone/apple-iphone-16-pro"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">FREE</div>iPhone 16 Pro at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile is enticing new customers to switch to the carrier with an offer that includes a <a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/news/offers/t-mobile-launches-best-iphone-offer-ever">new iPhone 16 Pro at no cost</a>, plus up to &#36;800 per line to help pay off your current phones from your existing carrier. With this deal, you don't need to trade-in your current device, and the offer is available to up to four people on the Experience Beyond plan.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-16-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Sitewide Sales Hit Anker, Verizon, Samsung, and More, Plus BOGO Apple Watch Band Sale at Woot</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-sitewide-sales-hit-anker-verizon-samsung-and-more-plus-bogo-apple-watch-band-sale-at-woot.2457207/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Air Could Debut Advanced Silicon Battery Tech</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/iphone-17-air-advanced-silicon-battery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-could-debut-advanced-silicon-battery-tech.2457204/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:00:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/iphone-17-air-advanced-silicon-battery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming all-new ultra-thin iPhone 17 Air could become the first Apple smartphone to adopt advanced battery technology, with Japanese supplier TDK preparing to ship its new generation of silicon-anode batteries by the end of June.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Air-Pastel-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999629" /><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20250516VL201/tdk-iphone-silicon-production-component.html">DigiTimes</a></em>, TDK CEO Noboru Saito revealed in a recent interview that the Apple supplier has accelerated its production timeline, moving shipments forward from the originally planned September quarter. That may give smartphone makers enough time to use the cells in thinner models launching this year, he suggested.<br/>
<br/>
"We've made good progress, and we're shipping them very soon," Saito said, adding that "some handset makers might be able to use the new battery in their product one generation early."<br/>
<br/>
The timing could be soon enough for Apple's expected September launch of the iPhone 17 Air, which is rumored to measure just <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">5.5mm at its thinnest point</a>, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
TDK's batteries use silicon for anodes instead of the traditional graphite, allowing them to pack 15% more energy into the same space compared to conventional rechargeable battery packs. This advancement could be key to maintaining adequate battery life in such a slim form factor.<br/>
<br/>
Having said that, reports have been mixed regarding the iPhone 17 Air's potential battery performance. While <em>The Information</em>'s Wayne Ma claimed the device will have "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-17-air-battery-case-report/">worse</a>" battery life compared to previous iPhone models, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman offered a more optimistic outlook, stating that battery life would be "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-price-battery-life-more/">on par with current iPhones</a>" thanks to hardware and software optimizations.<br/>
<br/>
Further supporting the possibility of decent battery life, Kuo recently mentioned in a blog post that the iPhone 17 Air will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/iphone-17-air-high-density-battery-rumor/">"high-density" battery</a>, although he didn't elaborate.<br/>
<br/>
The device is also rumored to incorporate Apple's power-efficient C1 modem and lack an Ultra Wide camera, potentially providing more internal space for a larger battery.<br/>
<br/>
Looking further ahead, a recent report from <em>ETNews</em> has suggested that Apple could adopt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/2027-iphone-game-changing-silicon-battery/">advanced silicon battery technology</a> for its 2027 iPhone, marking the 20th anniversary of the iconic device. The next-generation battery could theoretically use pure silicon anodes, which can store up to 10 times more lithium ions per gram than current materials.<br/>
<br/>
TDK is already working on its fourth-generation silicon batteries, according to the company's CEO. "We plan to introduce fourth-generation silicon batteries sometime in the next fiscal year to widen our lead even further," said Saito, claiming that "mass-producing silicon batteries requires special know-how. It's not like you can do it by just putting the materials together."<br/>
<br/>
The 6.6-inch iPhone 17 Air is expected to replace the Plus model in Apple's 2025 lineup, and is likely to be announced in September, per Apple's typical fall release schedule.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/iphone-17-air-advanced-silicon-battery/">iPhone 17 Air Could Debut Advanced Silicon Battery Tech</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-could-debut-advanced-silicon-battery-tech.2457204/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WSJ: Some Apple Vision Pro Buyers &#039;Feel Total Regret&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/vision-pro-buyers-feel-total-regret/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wsj-some-apple-vision-pro-buyers-feel-total-regret.2457201/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:43:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/vision-pro-buyers-feel-total-regret/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>The Wall Street Journal</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset has left many early adopters expressing dissatisfaction over its weight, limited use cases, and sparse software ecosystem, according to a <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/they-paid-3-500-for-apples-vision-pro-a-year-later-it-still-hurts-496de341">new article from <em>The Wall Street Journal</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/vision-pro-video-recording.jpg" alt="" width="1595" height="897" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898839" /><br/>
In the year following the device's launch, user feedback suggests that it has failed to meet expectations for comfort, software support, and social acceptance. In interviews conducted by <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em>, early buyers of the Vision Pro reported that the device now sits largely unused due to a range of practical issues. Dustin Fox, a real estate agent in Centreville, Virginia, said:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>It's just collecting dust. I think I've probably used it four times in the last year.<br/>
<br/>
It's way too heavy. I can't wear it for more than 20 or 30 minutes without it hurting my neck.</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
He explained that he was initially drawn to the device's novelty and potential productivity benefits, but found the physical experience of wearing the headset unsustainable for extended sessions. The Vision Pro weighs approximately 600 to 650 grams (1.3 to 1.4 pounds), depending on the light seal and headband configuration. This is considerably heavier than typical head-mounted consumer electronics, and the front-heavy distribution has become a recurring complaint.<br/>
<br/>
Tovia Goldstein, a 24-year-old based in New York City, said that his experience watching content on the headset was also limited by discomfort and an insufficient number of apps to make it worthwhile.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>After 60 minutes, you can't, you just have to throw it down. I wouldn't recommend anyone buying it, unless you're really rich and you don't know what to do with your money.</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
When he retrieves the device to investigate any new apps that have been added to the visionOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, he noted the lengthy startup time as a deterrent, citing the need to connect the external battery and wait several minutes before the device is ready to use.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro debuted with high visibility, including a flagship store event in New York City attended by Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>. In the weeks following the launch, users were spotted wearing the headset in public spaces such as malls, restaurants, and sports events, but several buyers said that public enthusiasm quickly diminished.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>People were excited to be wearing it. Then it just died.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
I feel total regret.</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
Fox said that he considered selling his Vision Pro, but resale values had fallen significantly below the original price. <br/>
<br/>
Another early adopter, Anshel Sag, a technology analyst based in San Diego, used the Vision Pro for inflight entertainment but eventually abandoned it due to social discomfort and practicality issues.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>I got pretty dirty looks from people. I don't need that.<br/>
<br/>
It takes up like half of the volume of my carry-on.</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro's travel case, sold separately for &#36;199, is also large; it measures in at roughly 12 inches by 9 inches by 6.5 inches.<br/>
<br/>
Anthony Racaniello, a media studio operator from Philadelphia, attempted to use the headset in the workplace and during air travel but experienced both social alienation and practical challenges. During one nearly six-hour flight, he said a flight attendant ignored him during beverage service.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>You look like you have a sleep mask on. And people are going to treat you that way.<br/>
<br/>
The best compliment I got was a light chuckle and "It looks like you're wearing ski goggles at work."</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
He later sold his Vision Pro for &#36;1,900 — a 46% loss from the original purchase price — and said he did not miss it.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>It's definitely a glimpse at the future. I just think it's a ways away from there. For now, you have to put on what feels like a 500-pound MacBook Pro, strap it to your face and have people laugh at you.</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
Yam Olisker, a 20-year-old YouTuber from Israel, flew to New York to purchase the Vision Pro at launch and obtained &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj;'s signature on both his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the Vision Pro box.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>This is the first time, ever, that I've thought an Apple product was just a bit early, or ahead of its time. I use it much less than I expected.<br/>
</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
That being said, he does not regret the purchase and enjoys watching movies with his Vision Pro, especially 3D films like <em>Metallica</em>, which he said makes it feel "like you're at the concert." Nevertheless, the weight remains an issue, and he has to lie in bed to mitigate its effect when watching movies.<br/>
<br/>
Although Apple's work on a substantially enhanced Vision Pro model has apparently stalled, there are strong indications that the company will release "an incremental update to the product with limited changes to its physical design," such as a chip upgrade, according to <em>The Information</em>. Corroborating this, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> have said that a more iterative second-generation Vision Pro is in active development, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/03/apple-vision-pro-with-m5-chip-rumor/">adding the M5 chip</a> and little else.<br/>
<br/>
This updated model is expected to reuse most of its components from the first-generation Vision Pro to offset the surplus inventory in Apple's supply chain. Gurman said the refreshed device could launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/11/vision-pro-2-with-m5-may-not-launch-until-2026/">between fall 2025 and spring 2026</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-wall-street-journal/">The Wall Street Journal</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/vision-pro-buyers-feel-total-regret/">WSJ: Some Apple Vision Pro Buyers &#039;Feel Total Regret&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wsj-some-apple-vision-pro-buyers-feel-total-regret.2457201/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Again Named the World&#039;s Most Valuable Brand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-again-named-most-valuable-brand/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-again-named-the-worlds-most-valuable-brand.2457185/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:08:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-again-named-most-valuable-brand/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has been named the most valuable global brand for the fourth consecutive year, according to the 2025 edition of Kantar's <a href="https://www.kantar.com/campaigns/brandz/global">BrandZ report</a>, with its brand now valued at &#36;1.29 trillion — a year-over-year increase of 28%.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/apple-park-sunset.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-844498" /><br/>
The latest <a href="https://www.kantar.com/campaigns/brandz/global">Kantar BrandZ Global Top 100 ranking</a> assigns Apple the top position in a comprehensive analysis of brand performance, marking a continued upward trend for the company. Kantar's valuation methodology combines financial performance with brand perception, incorporating insights from over 4.5 million consumer interviews across 522 categories in 54 markets.<br/>
<br/>
According to the report, Apple's dominance reflects sustained consumer trust, premium positioning, and successful diversification across hardware, software, and services. The company's brand value now constitutes approximately 12% of the total value of the BrandZ Global Top 100, which stands at &#36;10.7 trillion in 2025. <br/>
<br/>
Kantar also identifies Apple as representative of two of the fastest-growing categories in the ranking: consumer technology and luxury. According to the report, these sectors grew 46% and 45% respectively, outperforming categories such as finance, automotive, and telecoms. The report cites sustained demand for high-end devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Pro models and the Apple Watch Ultra as indicators of this dual-category positioning.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's lead in the BrandZ ranking places it ahead of other major technology firms including Google (No. 2, &#36;944.1 billion), Microsoft (No. 3, &#36;884.8 billion), Amazon (No. 4, &#36;866.1 billion), and Nvidia (No. 5, &#36;509.4 billion). <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-again-named-most-valuable-brand/">Apple Again Named the World&#039;s Most Valuable Brand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-again-named-the-worlds-most-valuable-brand.2457185/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic: Fortnite Offline Worldwide &#039;Until Apple Unblocks It&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-blocks-fortnite-return-to-ios-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-fortnite-offline-worldwide-until-apple-unblocks-it.2457179/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:50:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-blocks-fortnite-return-to-ios-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Epic Games said today that Apple has blocked its attempt to bring Fortnite back to iOS devices, leaving the popular battle royale game unavailable on iPhones and iPads worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite-apple-logo-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-756080" /><br/>
"Apple has blocked our Fortnite submission so we cannot release to the US App Store or to the Epic Games Store for iOS in the European Union," Epic stated via its <a href="https://x.com/Fortnite/status/1923293522234356169">Fortnite account</a> on X (Twitter). "Now, sadly, Fortnite on iOS will be offline worldwide until Apple unblocks it."<br/>
<br/>
Apple banned the ‌Epic Games‌ developer account back in 2020 when ‌Epic Games‌ violated its ‌App Store‌ rules to add web-based purchases, kicking off a multi-year legal battle. Because the main ‌Epic Games‌ developer account continues to be banned, Epic submitted Fortnite to the U.S. ‌App Store‌ using an account from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/05/epic-games-fortnite-us-app-store/">Epic Games Sweden</a>, a subsidiary that Epic formed to create the ‌Epic Games‌ Store alternative app marketplace in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
The game was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/09/fortnite-submitted-to-us-app-store/">submitted for review</a> on May 9, but after waiting over 120 hours without a response, Epic was forced to pull and resubmit its application to include the latest update.<br/>
<br/>
Epic CEO Tim Sweeney has been vocal about his frustration with the situation, claiming that Apple has not been returning the company's calls and that the review process <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/epic-resubmits-fortnite-to-app-store/">typically moves much faster</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Before submitting Fortnite to the U.S. App Store, Epic CEO Tim Sweeney said the company spoke with Apple about its plans – but never claimed Apple approved them. It remains unclear if Apple will allow Fortnite back, as the Epic v. Apple lawsuit confirmed that Apple has the right to ban Epic's account and isn't required to reinstate it.<br/>
<br/>
It's the latest chapter in the ongoing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">legal battle</a> between the two companies, which began in 2020 when Apple removed Fortnite from the App Store after Epic implemented direct payment options that bypassed Apple's 30% commission.<br/>
<br/>
The game had briefly returned to iOS devices in the EU via the Epic Games Store, but that version has now also gone offline.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-blocks-fortnite-return-to-ios-app-store/">Epic: Fortnite Offline Worldwide &#039;Until Apple Unblocks It&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-fortnite-offline-worldwide-until-apple-unblocks-it.2457179/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sony Announces WH-1000XM6 Noise-Canceling Headphones With Foldable Design</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/sony-wh-1000xm6-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sony-announces-wh-1000xm6-noise-canceling-headphones-with-foldable-design.2457178/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:30:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/sony-wh-1000xm6-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Sony</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sony has <a href="https://www.sony.eu/presscentre/sony-introduces-the-next-evolution-of-noise-cancelling-with-the-wh-1000xm6">announced</a> its new <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-17086682">WH-1000XM6 wireless noise-canceling headphones</a>. The good news is that the company has brought back the foldable design that was absent from its predecessor, the WH-1000XM5. The bad news is that it's stuck with the same naming convention, which sounds less like headphones and more like a dot-matrix printer from the 70s.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/sony-wh-1000xm6-headphones.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001923" /><br/>
The WH-1000XM6 headphones now happily fold up into a redesigned carrying case with a magnetic closure instead of a zipper, making it more compact and travel-friendly than the XM5's. Otherwise, the overall aesthetics remain largely unchanged, but Sony claims the new model delivers significantly improved noise cancellation, a better Ambient Sound (transparency) mode, and enhanced audio quality.<br/>
<br/>
Powering the enhanced noise cancellation is Sony's new HD Noise Cancelling Processor QN3, which works in conjunction with an expanded array of 12 microphones – 1.5 times more than the previous model. The company says this processor is seven times faster than its predecessor, allowing for more precise real-time noise adaptation.<br/>
<br/>
Sony has also introduced several new software features, including Scene-based Listening, which automatically adjusts settings based on your activity and environment. The headphones also support LE Audio with Auracast for broadcast listening capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
Battery life remains unchanged from the WH-1000XM5 at 30 hours, although Sony notes that a quick three-minute charge provides up to three hours of listening time. You can also charge this model and listen to your music at the same time. <br/>
<br/>
Sony says it has collaborated with recording engineers from prestigious studios including Sterling Sound, Battery Studios, and Coast Mastering to fine-tune the improved sound profile.<br/>
<br/>
It sounds promising. The only real downer seems to be the fact that Sony has priced these cans at &#36;449.99 – &#36;50 more than the previous model. Whether the improvements justify the price jump is the main question. These are unashamedly plastic headphones, after all. <em>MacRumors</em> should have a hands-on review of Sony's latest flagship headphones soon. <br/>
<br/>
The WH-1000XM5's come in Black, Platinum Silver, and Midnight Blue, and are available to buy from the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-17086682">Sony website</a> and all the major electronics retailers.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sony/">Sony</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/sony-wh-1000xm6-headphones/">Sony Announces WH-1000XM6 Noise-Canceling Headphones With Foldable Design</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sony-announces-wh-1000xm6-noise-canceling-headphones-with-foldable-design.2457178/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iPadOS 17.7.7 After Reports of App Login Issues [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apple-stops-signing-ipados-17-7-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ipados-17-7-7-after-reports-of-app-login-issues-updated.2457165/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:08:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apple-stops-signing-ipados-17-7-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has stopped signing the iPadOS 17.7.7 update that was released earlier this week for devices unable to run versions of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, meaning that users will not be able to install the update even if they see it available in Software Update. Affected devices include the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, the 10.5-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, and the second-generation 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/ipados-17.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898667" /><br/>
The company has not provided a reason for unsigning the update, but there are a number of reports on the MacRumors forums, Reddit, and elsewhere from users who have experienced issues logging into apps after updating their devices.<br/>
<br/>
From <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/problems-with-apps-after-update.2457073/?post=33905841#post-33905841">MacRumors forums member <em>mrsmith1</em></a>:<blockquote>I have an iPad 6th generation. After the latest update 17.7.7 I’ve been having problems with certain, but not all apps. Wikipedia, Duck Duck Go, Letterboxd and others. Every time I open them it’s like the first time and I have to sign up or do a tour of the app. I can’t seem to do anything about it. Any ideas?</blockquote><br/>
From <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TheSilphRoad/comments/1kl69e3/comment/ms4219m/">Reddit user <em>National_Case748</em></a>:<blockquote>Since updating my iPad to iPadOS 17.7.7 (build 21H433), all apps (such as YouTube, X, etc.) log me out every time I close them. This issue did not happen before the update.<br/>
<br/>
I’ve already tried all of the following:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Checked that Screen Time and Restrictions are disabled.</li><br/>
<li>Verified that no profiles or MDM configurations are installed.</li><br/>
<li>Made sure Safari cookies and password saving are enabled.</li><br/>
<li>Performed a full Reset All Settings.</li><br/>
<li>Finally, I did a complete factory reset and set up the iPad as new (not from backup).</li></ul><br/>
Even after all this, the problem persists. Every time I open an app, it behaves as if it were freshly installed and asks me to log in again.</blockquote>Apple has presumably prevented users from updating to iPadOS 17.7.7 for the time being to address these issues and will release a new update once they have been fixed.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 1:35 pm May 16</b>: Apple has now pulled iPadOS 17.7.7 entirely, meaning it will no longer show up in Software Update at all.<div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apple-stops-signing-ipados-17-7-7/">Apple Stops Signing iPadOS 17.7.7 After Reports of App Login Issues [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ipados-17-7-7-after-reports-of-app-login-issues-updated.2457165/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Says &#039;We&#039;re Faster Than a Mac&#039; in Latest Windows PC Ad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/microsoft-were-faster-than-a-mac-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-says-were-faster-than-a-mac-in-latest-windows-pc-ad.2457150/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:29:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/microsoft-were-faster-than-a-mac-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		<category>Windows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft today shared a new ad on YouTube with the tagline "we're faster than a Mac."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/microsoft-copilot-plus-pc.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1081" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953308" /><br/>
In the video, Microsoft says the top-end Windows PCs with Copilot+ branding are up to 58% faster than the previous-generation MacBook Air with the M3 chip, based on Cinebench 2024 multi-core CPU benchmark results. The ad is citing old figures that were reported on all the way back <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/microsoft-surface-pro-faster-macbook-air/">in May 2024</a>, so take that as you will.<br/>
<br/>
While the ad is using an older MacBook Air for comparison purposes, <a href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/legal/windows/copilotplus-claims?tabs=amd">Microsoft's fine print</a> does say some Copilot+ PCs are still faster than even the latest MacBook Air models with the M4 chip, based on the same Cinebench 2024 benchmark.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="339" height="603" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/k_JsraDdVmQ" title="We’re faster than a Mac. Here’s how much faster. #CopilotPCs #Windows #Windows11" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Some of the Copilot+ PCs that were tested include Lenovo's Yoga Slim 7x with Qualcomm's Snapdragon X Elite processor, Microsoft's Surface Laptop with the Snapdragon X Elite, and HP's OmniBook Ultra 14 with AMD's Ryzen AI 9 HX 375.<br/>
<br/>
While it is true that some PC chips are faster than Apple silicon chips in certain tests, Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/10/apple-introduces-m4-pro-and-m4-max/">said</a> the M4 family of chips continues to offer industry-leading performance per watt. This impressive power efficiency results in the MacBook Air having fast performance, long battery life, and a thin and light design without an internal fan.<br/>
<br/>
In the end, using Windows over macOS remains a dealbreaker for some customers regardless.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/windows/">Windows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/microsoft-were-faster-than-a-mac-ad/">Microsoft Says &#039;We&#039;re Faster Than a Mac&#039; in Latest Windows PC Ad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-says-were-faster-than-a-mac-in-latest-windows-pc-ad.2457150/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the iPad Mini 7 for &#36;399.99 at Amazon This Week (&#36;99 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/get-the-ipad-mini-7-for-399/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-ipad-mini-7-for-399-99-at-amazon-this-week-99-off.2457144/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:24:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/get-the-ipad-mini-7-for-399/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week is providing record low prices on multiple models of the iPad mini 7, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3W6TV6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;499.00. Colors on sale at this price include Purple, Space Gray, and Blue.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-red-and-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972028" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Compared to past sales, this is a match of the best price we've ever tracked on the tablet. You can also get the 512GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3XT3DX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;699.00</strong></a>, which is another &#36;99 discount and available in multiple colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3W6TV6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3XT3DX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>512GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
These deals have been around for a few weeks now, and given that they are the last ones left in the iPad mini 7 lineup, they may soon disappear. This time around, we aren't tracking any deals on the 256GB Wi-Fi model, or any of the cellular tablets.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/get-the-ipad-mini-7-for-399/">Get the iPad Mini 7 for &#36;399.99 at Amazon This Week (&#36;99 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-ipad-mini-7-for-399-99-at-amazon-this-week-99-off.2457144/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights Magnifier on Mac and iPhone Music Haptics in New Videos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apple-videos-accessibility-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-magnifier-on-mac-and-iphone-music-haptics-in-new-videos.2457142/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 09:25:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apple-videos-accessibility-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared new videos that highlight the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-ios-19-accessibility-features/">upcoming Accessibility features</a> that the company plans to introduce with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> and macOS 16. Apple this week debuted a number of new Accessibility options that will be coming later this year to honor Global Accessibility Awareness Day.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Magnifier on Mac Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/R3rBlZGEssw" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The first video, uploaded to Apple's main YouTube channel, shows off the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/macos-16-to-let-your-mac-zoom-with-an-iphone/">Magnifier on Mac feature</a>. We saw this video Tuesday in Apple's newsroom post, but it's now easier to watch over on YouTube. In the spot, a woman uses an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> connected to her Mac in a classroom setting to zoom in on the chalkboard so she can better see the professor's notes and diagrams.<br/>
<br/>
Magnifier on Mac uses the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; camera's zoom feature, beaming the feed to a Mac through Continuity Camera. There are options for creating multiple live session windows for tracking a presentation while also zooming in on a textbook, and each view can be customized with different brightness levels and color and contrast filters to suit individual needs. Magnifier on Mac is an extension of the existing Magnifier option on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which allows the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to be used to zoom in on text and detect objects.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's second video was shared on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> YouTube channel, and it focuses on Music Haptics on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Introduced as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Music Haptics provides taps, textures, and vibrations to the audio of music that's playing, so that users who are deaf or hard of hearing can experience songs.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Music Haptics on iPhone Global Accessibility Awareness Day" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ip3todolKj0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/ios-19-music-haptics-improvements/">plans to expand Music Haptics</a>, adding new customization options. Users will be able to experience haptics for a whole song or for vocals only, and there will be settings to adjust the intensity of taps, textures, and vibrations.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apple-videos-accessibility-features/">Apple Highlights Magnifier on Mac and iPhone Music Haptics in New Videos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-magnifier-on-mac-and-iphone-music-haptics-in-new-videos.2457142/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says These Vehicle Brands Plan to Offer All-New CarPlay Ultra</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/carplay-ultra-committed-automakers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-these-vehicle-brands-plan-to-offer-all-new-carplay-ultra.2457135/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:13:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/carplay-ultra-committed-automakers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>CarPlay Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apples-carplay-ultra-now-available/">announced the launch of CarPlay Ultra</a>, the long-awaited next-generation version of its CarPlay software system for vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/CarPlay-Ultra-Climate-Controls.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001805" /><br/>
CarPlay Ultra features deep integration with a vehicle's instrument cluster and systems, built-in Radio and Climate apps, customizable widgets, and more. The interface is tailored to each vehicle model and automaker's identity, and drivers can also adjust the color scheme. To learn more, read <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apples-carplay-ultra-now-available/">our coverage of Apple's announcement</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Starting today, CarPlay Ultra is available in newly-ordered Aston Martin vehicle models in the U.S. and Canada, and it will be rolling out in select existing Aston Martin vehicle models through a software update in the coming weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, if you cannot afford a &#36;250,000 luxury vehicle from Aston Martin, CarPlay Ultra will eventually be available in more affordable vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said "many" other automakers around the world plan to offer CarPlay Ultra within the next year, including the following three Korean brands:<ul><li>Hyundai</li><br/>
<li>Kia</li><br/>
<li>Genesis</li></ul>Apple first previewed next-generation ‌CarPlay‌ at WWDC 2022, and at the time it shared a long list of automakers that were committed to offering the software system. The list is nearly three years old, however, so it might not be entirely accurate anymore.<br/>
<br/>
The list was as follows:<ul><li>Acura</li><br/>
<li>Audi</li><br/>
<li>Ford</li><br/>
<li>Honda</li><br/>
<li>Infiniti</li><br/>
<li>Jaguar</li><br/>
<li>Land Rover</li><br/>
<li>Lincoln</li><br/>
<li>Mercedes-Benz</li><br/>
<li>Nissan</li><br/>
<li>Polestar</li><br/>
<li>Porsche</li><br/>
<li>Renault</li><br/>
<li>Volvo</li></ul>Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed its next-generation CarPlay instrument cluster design</a> in late 2023, but the automaker has not provided an update since then.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GyTeRyXU1Lk" title="Apple&#39;s &quot;CarPlay Ultra&quot; Officially Here: Everything New In 4 Minutes!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, Mercedes-Benz leadership has <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/4/29/24144356/mercedes-benz-ceo-apple-carplay-next-gen-decoder">since expressed a lack of willingness</a> to let Apple essentially take over its entire software experience.<br/>
<br/>
We will provide coverage of CarPlay Ultra vehicle announcements as they happen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/carplay-ultra/">CarPlay Ultra</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/carplay-ultra-committed-automakers/">Apple Says These Vehicle Brands Plan to Offer All-New CarPlay Ultra</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-these-vehicle-brands-plan-to-offer-all-new-carplay-ultra.2457135/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Verizon and Samsung Kick Off New Sitewide Sales With Savings on iPhone/iPad Cases, Monitors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/verizon-and-samsung-new-sales/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/verizon-and-samsung-kick-off-new-sitewide-sales-with-savings-on-iphone-ipad-cases-monitors-and-more.2457132/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:38:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/verizon-and-samsung-new-sales/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a pair of big sales from <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a> and <a href="https://howl.link/uzme1brcsvjpc">Samsung</a>, which are offering great deals on products including Apple's MagSafe iPhone cases, iPad Smart Folio, computer monitors, storage accessories, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Verizon</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/verizon-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001773" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Verizon today kicked off its annual "Red Hot Deal Days" event, offering deals on everything from smartphones to wearables, headphones, soundbars, and first-party Apple accessories. This includes up to &#36;18 off <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fphone-cases%2Fapple%2F%3Fspecial-offers%3Don-sale">Silicone Cases with MagSafe for iPhone</a> and up to &#36;20 off <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Ftablet-accessories%2Fapple%2F%3Fspecial-offers%3Don-sale">Smart Folio for various iPad models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Red Hot Deal Days at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Verizon is also <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-16-pro%2F">offering the iPhone 16 Pro</a>, Apple Watch Series 10, and iPad all for no cost, with multiple stipulations. You'll need to buy or upgrade to the new iPhone on the Unlimited Ultimate Plan and trade in an existing device from Apple, Google, Motorola, or Samsung. You'll receive promo credits for these devices over the course of 36 months.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fphone-cases%2Fapple%2F%3Fspecial-offers%3Don-sale">Apple Silicone Cases with MagSafe</a> - Get 20% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Ftablet-accessories%2Fapple%2F%3Fspecial-offers%3Don-sale">Apple Smart Folio</a> - Get 20% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fcharging%2Fbelkin%2F%3Fspecial-offers%3Don-sale">Belkin charging accessories</a> - Get 20% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fxbox%2Fsale%2F">Xbox accessories</a> - Get up to 50% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fshop%2Fonline%2Fmeta-bundle%2F">Meta Quest 3S and Ray-Ban Meta glasses</a> - Get &#36;100 off when bought together</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/new-samsung-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001776" /><br/>
<br/>
Over at Samsung, the retailer is hosting a <a href="https://howl.link/k4eldqc3o5634">couple of new special discounts</a> on monitors and various storage devices. For the ViewFinity monitors, if you log in with Samsung's Education Offer Program membership, you can save an extra 10 percent as a teacher.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/uzme1brcsvjpc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Samsung Spring Sale</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/193ep1xa3xgam">Portable 1TB SSD T7</a> - &#36;99.99 (&#36;10 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/16qurhg02x9q3">Portable 4TB SSD T5</a> - &#36;229.99 (&#36;128.99 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/bkh0kqnc44dx9">34-inch ViewFinity S6 Curved Monitor with USB-C</a> - &#36;399.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/i7w09b8vckeum">34-inch ViewFinity S6 Curved Monitor With Thunderbolt 4</a> - &#36;499.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/asp7arvix3z2g">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;849.99 (&#36;450 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/c9y6squyw01qs">27-inch ViewFinity S9 Smart Monitor</a> - &#36;979.99 (&#36;620 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/mbs744aer4c8w">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,149 (&#36;650 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/n07uzko4vl9e5">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Gaming Monitor with 4TB SSD</a> - &#36;1,386.98 (&#36;788 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/verizon-and-samsung-new-sales/">Verizon and Samsung Kick Off New Sitewide Sales With Savings on iPhone/iPad Cases, Monitors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/verizon-and-samsung-kick-off-new-sitewide-sales-with-savings-on-iphone-ipad-cases-monitors-and-more.2457132/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces New Way to Watch MLS Sunday Night Soccer For Free</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/mls-season-pass-now-free-for-xfinity-customers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-new-way-to-watch-mls-sunday-night-soccer-for-free.2457130/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/mls-season-pass-now-free-for-xfinity-customers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MLS Season Pass</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting this weekend, Xfinity customers can watch Apple's weekly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/29/apple-mls-sunday-night-soccer/">Sunday Night Soccer</a> production at no additional cost.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/MLS-Season-Pass-Xfinity.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001766" /><br/>
Sunday Night Soccer consists of a weekly Major League Soccer match every Sunday evening during the 2025 season, with enhanced production and studio programming from Apple. Sunday Night Soccer was already available to Apple TV+ subscribers at no extra cost, and now that perk has been extended to Xfinity X1 and Xfinity Stream customers.<br/>
<br/>
Xfinity customers can find Sunday Night Soccer matches for free via the channel guide, with no Apple TV+ or MLS Season Pass subscriptions required.<br/>
<br/>
2025 marks the third year of a 10-year partnership between Apple and Major League Soccer.<br/>
<br/>
For customers who prefer to watch Sunday Night Soccer via Apple TV+, the streaming service is available through the Apple TV app on a wide variety of devices, and <a href="https://tv.apple.com/">on the web at tv.apple.com</a>. A <a href="https://tv.apple.com/">free seven-day trial is available</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mls-season-pass/">MLS Season Pass</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/mls-season-pass-now-free-for-xfinity-customers/">Apple Announces New Way to Watch MLS Sunday Night Soccer For Free</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-new-way-to-watch-mls-sunday-night-soccer-for-free.2457130/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Lineup Sees &#36;350 Price Drop in China as Sales Decline</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/iphone-16-sees-price-drop-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-sees-350-price-drop-in-china-as-sales-decline.2457129/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:40:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/iphone-16-sees-price-drop-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is now being sold at discounts of over &#36;350 on major Chinese e-commerce platforms, as the company and its retail partners move to stimulate demand in the face of declining sales and intensifying competition in the world's biggest smartphone market (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-e-commerce-sites-offer-discounts-up-351-apples-latest-iphones-2025-05-14/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="3020" height="1698" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-967113" /><br/>
JD.com and Alibaba's Tmall marketplace have introduced significant markdowns on Apple's new devices ahead of China's annual mid-year "618" shopping festival, which runs from June 1 to June 18. JD.com is currently offering the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> with 128GB of storage for 5,469 yuan, down from the official Apple China price of 7,999 yuan — a 2,530 yuan reduction equivalent to approximately &#36;351. Tmall is offering the same model at 5,499 yuan, representing a 2,500 yuan discount when applying platform-specific coupons, some of which include Chinese government subsidies.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple has not openly confirmed its role in the price reductions, the company has employed similar tactics in previous years, particularly around major shopping festivals. In January, Apple issued limited-time discounts of up to 500 yuan on its official website in China.<br/>
<br/>
Smartphones priced below 6,000 yuan qualify for government subsidies of up to 500 yuan, depending on the city or province. These subsidies are part of a national consumption initiative aimed at boosting sales of electronics and other goods amid slowing economic growth. Historically, Apple devices were priced above the subsidy threshold, but the recent discounting has brought certain &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models under the limit, making them eligible for the incentives. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> shipments in China reportedly declined 9% year-over-year in the first quarter of 2025. A separate report placed the year-over-year decline at 49.6%, falling from 3.75 million units in the first quarter of 2024 to 1.89 million in the first quarter of 2025. During the same period, Chinese competitors experienced significant growth, with Xiaomi seeing a 40% increase in shipments and Huawei seeing a 10% increase.<br/>
<br/>
Apple continues to list devices at full price on its own platforms. The tactic of reducing prices with third-party retailers allows the company to offer region-specific price adjustments without undermining its premium positioning globally.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Caution)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/iphone-16-sees-price-drop-in-china/">iPhone 16 Lineup Sees &#36;350 Price Drop in China as Sales Decline</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-sees-350-price-drop-in-china-as-sales-decline.2457129/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
