<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 04:03:17 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Apple Ring&#039; Allegedly in Development to Rival Samsung Galaxy Ring</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development-to-rival-samsung-galaxy-ring.2419922/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:27:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is speeding up development of a smart ring that can be worn on the finger to track users' health biometrics, claims a new report coming out of Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/samsung-galaxy-ring.jpg" alt="" width="940" height="529" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937059" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Teaser image of Samsung Galaxy Ring shown at Galaxy Unpacked in January</em></div><br/>
Apple has toyed with the idea of a ring wearable for several years, as indicated by <a href="https://www.patentlyapple.com/patently-apple/2020/03/apple-wins-patent-for-a-ring-accessory-to-control-content-presented-on-future-virtual-reality-glasses-headset.html">several patents</a>, but with Samsung preparing to bring its own product to market, the time could be ripe for Apple to follow it with something that embodies CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>'s mantra, "be best, not first."<br/>
<br/>
According to the <em><a href="https://www.etnews.com/20240220000215">Electronic Times</a></em>, Apple has been paying close attention to the market for signs that a smart ring would be a popular, less intrusive alternative to a watch, that can be worn for longer and is easier to sleep with. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to be seriously weighing up the idea as a viable expansion of its wearables lineup, and has been increasingly applying for <a href="https://ppubs.uspto.gov/pubwebapp/external.html?q=(11829831).pn.&db=USPAT&type=ids">patents related to an NFC-enabled finger-worn device</a> as it coordinates the timing of the release. <br/>
<br/>
"It seems likely that commercialization is imminent," said an industry insider quoted in the machine-translated report. <br/>
<br/>
The rumor comes as Samsung prepares to unveil a Galaxy Ring at its second Galaxy Unpacked 2024 event, which is likely to take place in the second half of July. The Korean firm teased the product's existence at the end of its first Unpacked event in January, and it is now expected to enter mass production in the second half of the year.<br/>
<br/>
Besides its rumored ability to measure blood flow, the Galaxy Ring is also expected to feature ECG monitoring, sleep tracking, and functionalities for controlling other devices and making wireless payments remotely. The device is expected to come in several sizes. <br/>
<br/>
The emerging smart ring category is currently led by Oura Ring, first released by Finnish health technology company Oura back in 2015. The device collects activity, heart rate, respiratory rate, and sleep data, and transmits it via Bluetooth to the Oura app. Now in its third-generation, the device can also measure body temperature and menstrual cycle, and the battery is said to last for a week on a single charge.<br/>
<br/>
In March 2022, Oura announced that it had sold more than one million rings, but its latest incarnation has come in for criticism after the company introduced a &#36;5.99 monthly subscription fee that put certain aspects of user data behind a paywall. <br/>
<br/>
Would you be interested in an "Apple Ring" as an alternative to Apple Watch? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development/">&#039;Apple Ring&#039; Allegedly in Development to Rival Samsung Galaxy Ring</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development-to-rival-samsung-galaxy-ring.2419922/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Testing Feature That Imports Libraries From Other Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-music-testing-playlist-import-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-testing-feature-that-imports-libraries-from-other-services.2419913/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:55:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-music-testing-playlist-import-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> is testing a new feature that allows users to import songs and playlists into their library from rival streaming services like Spotify. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-music-songshift-transfer.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937053" /><br/>
References to the feature in the latest &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; beta for Android were first spotted by a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AppleMusic/comments/1at8g93/apple_music_470beta_1359_for_android_apple/">Reddit user</a>, and <em>MacRumors</em> has now independently confirmed that the references are indeed in the APK, or Android Package Kit.<br/>
<br/>
The feature appears to be a collaborative effort with <a href="https://www.songshift.com">SongShift</a>, a long-running third-party service that enables users to transfer their music libraries and playlists between different music streaming services. <br/>
<br/>
Images shared on Reddit show new prompts in &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; for Android that offer to "add saved music and playlists you made in other music services to your &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; library." The option also appears in the Android app's settings.<br/>
<br/>
The feature does not yet appear to be fully functional, and the screens are not showing for everyone running the beta, suggesting Apple is at an early stage of A/B testing, or split testing the feature. A/B testing is a method used to compare two versions of the same app, and users are randomly exposed to either version. Statistical analysis is then used to determine which variation performs better for a given conversion goal. <br/>
<br/>
Third-party music transfer services have been available for a few years, but many have limited functionality without a one-off payment or subscription. There's no guarantee that &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; will take the SongShift integration through to full development, but if it does retain the feature, there's a good chance it will eventually appear in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app for Apple devices. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-music-testing-playlist-import-feature/">Apple Music Testing Feature That Imports Libraries From Other Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-testing-feature-that-imports-libraries-from-other-services.2419913/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling Refurbished M3 Pro and M3 Max MacBook Pro Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-m3-pro-and-m3-max-macbook-pro-models.2419890/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 17:04:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began offering <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/refurbished/mac/2023-macbook-pro">refurbished versions</a> of the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3 Pro and M3 Max chip options, offering the machines at a discount for the first time since their October 2023 release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/m3-macbook-pro-14-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937044" /><br/>
The release of M3 Pro and M3 Max models on Apple's refurbished store comes almost two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/apple-refurbished-14-inch-m3-macbook-pro/">entry-level 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro first appeared on the store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Pricing on these latest refurbished MacBook Pro models starts at &#36;1,699 for the 14-inch M3 Pro model with 11-core CPU and 14-core GPU, a &#36;300 discount off of the original &#36;1,999 starting price. The 16-inch MacBook Pro starts at &#36;2,119 for the M3 Pro chip with 12-core CPU and 18-core GPU, offering savings of &#36;380 compared to a brand-new unit priced at &#36;2,499.<br/>
<br/>
Additional configurations with chip, memory, and/or storage space upgrades are also available, although availability will fluctuate over time. Customers looking for a specific configuration should check back often.<br/>
<br/>
All of Apple's refurbished Macs are close to identical to new products. They are subject to a refurbishment process that includes full functionality testing, with any defective modules replaced, as well as a thorough cleaning and inspection. Refurbished products are eligible for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ and have the same 14-day return period as new Apple devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-macbook-pro/">Apple Now Selling Refurbished M3 Pro and M3 Max MacBook Pro Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-m3-pro-and-m3-max-macbook-pro-models.2419890/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Partners With Major League Soccer on New Marketing Campaign</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/beats-major-league-soccer-partnership/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-partners-with-major-league-soccer-on-new-marketing-campaign.2419869/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 10:39:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/beats-major-league-soccer-partnership/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's partnership with <a href="https://www.mlssoccer.com">Major League Soccer (MLS)</a> is expanding with a new agreement that will see Apple's Beats brand become the official consumer audio products partner of MLS. As part of the partnership, Beats will produce exclusive custom headphones for eight MLS clubs, with additional clubs to follow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/beats-mls-custom.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937036" /><br/>
The eight clubs that will initially receive custom Beats headphones include Atlanta United, Columbus Crew, Inter Miami, LAFC, Nashville SC, NYCFC, St. Louis City SC, and Toronto FC, and MLS players will be featured in Beats marketing campaigns through both Beats and MLS.<blockquote>"For more than a decade, Beats headphones have been chosen by the world's top athletes to help them get game ready and heighten their focus, while also allowing them to show off their style and personality," said Chris Thorne, Beats' CMO. "We are extremely excited to join forces with the MLS, one of the fastest growing and most dynamic sports leagues in the world. Beats will be working closely with the MLS clubs and top players to deliver amazing experiences throughout the upcoming season."</blockquote>The announcement comes just a few days ahead of the new MLS season which will see <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> once again serving as the worldwide home for MLS streaming with <a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/channel/tvs.sbd.7000">MLS Season Pass</a>. MLS Season Pass is available in over 100 countries, with pricing in the U.S. set at &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;99 for the full season. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> subscribers receive a discounted price of &#36;12.99 per month or &#36;79 for the full season.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/beats-major-league-soccer-partnership/">Beats Partners With Major League Soccer on New Marketing Campaign</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-partners-with-major-league-soccer-on-new-marketing-campaign.2419869/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Could Come in Two New Color Options</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-16-pro-two-new-color-options/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-could-come-in-two-new-color-options.2419853/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 07:03:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-16-pro-two-new-color-options/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models could come in all-new "Desert Titanium" and "Titanium Gray" color options, according to the leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iphone-16-pro-colors.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-937018" /><em>Mock-up of the alleged new &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; color options shared by Majin Bu.</em></div><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1759581161423044677?s=20">new post</a> on X (formerly Twitter), Majin Bu said that the "Desert Titanium" will be similar to the Gold color option offered on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro in 2022, but deeper and heavier. On the other hand, "Titanium Gray" will apparently be similar to the shade of Space Gray offered on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6 in 2014.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> comes in Black Titanium, White Titanium, Blue Titanium, and Natural Titanium. It is worth noting that there is no ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;‌ with a Gold finish. Gold was available through 2013's ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 5S to 2017's ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 8, and then on 2018's ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ XS to 2022's ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ Pro. The reintroduction of a gold-like shade with the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; seems very plausible as a result.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-color-options/">iPhone 15 Pro Color Options: Which Should You Choose?</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple's "Pro" &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models have always been available in no more than four color options at launch, usually with basic black, white, and gold options alongside a more striking color like green, blue, or purple. This means that while Black Titanium and White Titanium are highly likely to be carried over from the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; to the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, the continuation of Blue Titanium and Natural Titanium is far from certain. It is possible that these color options may be discontinued to make way for "Desert Titanium" and "Titanium Gray," especially since "Titanium Gray" appears to be very similar to Natural Titanium.<br/>
<br/>
This is the first rumor about the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s color options and Majin Bu has a mixed track record for revealing accurate information about Apple's plans. Nevertheless, more information is likely to emerge in the coming months as we approach launch.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-16-pro-two-new-color-options/">iPhone 16 Pro Could Come in Two New Color Options</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-could-come-in-two-new-color-options.2419853/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;300 Off Multiple Apple Studio Display Models, Available From &#36;1,299.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/apple-studio-display-amazon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-300-off-multiple-apple-studio-display-models-available-from-1-299-99.2419852/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 06:54:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/apple-studio-display-amazon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today is matching an all-time low price on the Studio Display, now available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. This is the standard glass version of the Studio Display with the tilt adjustable stand, and it currently has an estimated February 23 delivery date for Prime shipping.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/mac-studio-and-studio-display.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="893" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-838875" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The Studio Display features a 27-inch 5K retina display with a 5120 x 2880 resolution and up to 600 nits of brightness. Discounts on the Studio Display have been very rare over the past few months, and this is only the second time in 2024 that we've tracked a record low price on any version of the monitor.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>Standard Glass Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you want to upgrade to the nano-texture glass option, Amazon also has this model of the Studio Display on sale. It's available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3HP4KL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,599.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,899.99, which is a second-best price on the Studio Display with nano-texture glass.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3HP4KL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>Nano-Texture Glass Studio Display for &#36;1,599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the standard display is engineered for "extremely low reflectivity," but for rooms where there is a lot of glare, Apple suggests the nano-texture glass option with even less reflectivity.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/apple-studio-display-amazon/">Amazon Takes &#36;300 Off Multiple Apple Studio Display Models, Available From &#36;1,299.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-300-off-multiple-apple-studio-display-models-available-from-1-299-99.2419852/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 4 and AirPods Max With USB-C Still Expected Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-4-and-airpods-max-with-usb-c-still-expected-later-this-year.2419850/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 06:33:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple still plans to release multiple new AirPods models later this year, according to the latest information <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-18/apple-vision-pro-returning-3-500-device-over-comfort-lack-of-apps-and-price-lsrk88mq">shared by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/airpods-3-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893120" /><br/>
In an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-25/apple-airpods-plans-4th-generation-low-end-3rd-generation-pro-and-usb-c-max">October 2023 edition</a> of his <em>Power On</em> newsletter, Gurman said Apple planned to release two fourth-generation AirPods models and updated AirPods Max in "late 2024." On Sunday, he confirmed that this plan is "still underway."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman expects the entry-level fourth-generation AirPods to feature a new design with better fit, improved sound quality, and an updated charging case with a USB-C port. He also expects higher-end fourth-generation AirPods with active noise cancellation and a speaker in the charging case that can play a sound for Find My location tracking.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to discontinue the second-generation and third-generation AirPods after launching the two fourth-generation models, he said.<br/>
<br/>
The updated AirPods Max will feature a USB-C port instead of Lightning for charging and wired audio playback, but no other major changes, according to Gurman. He said the over-ear headphones might also be available in new colors. The current color options include Green, Pink, Silver, Sky Blue, and Space Gray.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman expects new AirPods Pro to launch in 2025 with design changes and an "updated chip," which may refer to an H3 chip for improved sound quality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple unveiled the third-generation AirPods during its October 2021 event, while the AirPods Max were announced in a December 2020 press release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/">AirPods 4 and AirPods Max With USB-C Still Expected Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-4-and-airpods-max-with-usb-c-still-expected-later-this-year.2419850/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple Vision Pro 2 at Least 18 Months Away</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away.2419845/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 05:49:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The second-generation version of Apple's Vision Pro headset is at least 18 months away from launch, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Purple-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-929938" /><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-18/apple-vision-pro-returning-3-500-device-over-comfort-lack-of-apps-and-price-lsrk88mq?">latest edition</a> of his "Power On" newsletter, Gurman said that Apple is likely at least a year and a half away from the release of the second-generation Vision Pro headset, placing launch in late August 2025 at the earliest. Gurman noted that Apple is keenly interested in the reasons why customers who choose to return the first-generation Vision Pro headset do so, ultimately passing feedback from retail stores to the company's headquarters to help perfect the next version of the device.<br/>
<br/>
The tidbit effectively rules out the idea of the Vision Pro receiving annual updates like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or Apple Watch, suggesting that it is likely to follow a longer refresh cycle that could even surpass that of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and market research firm Omdia have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/low-cost-vision-pro-canceled/">previously mentioned</a> a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/vision-pro-rumored-to-gain-brighter-displays/">2027 launch time frame</a> for the second-generation Vision Pro headset. It is said that there could be no hardware updates for the Vision Pro until then, meaning that the Vision Pro might go up to 54 months without a refresh from the announcement of the first generation to the second. Meanwhile, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/low-cost-vision-pro-canceled/">could launch a more affordable Vision headset</a> around 2025, according to both <em>The Information</em> and <em>Bloomberg</em>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">Gurman: Apple Vision Pro 2 at Least 18 Months Away</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away.2419845/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Ridley Scott&#039;s Action Epic &#039;Napoleon&#039; Coming to Apple TV+ on March 1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/napoleon-apple-tv-plus-march-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ridley-scotts-action-epic-napoleon-coming-to-apple-tv-on-march-1.2419842/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 05:18:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/napoleon-apple-tv-plus-march-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Original Films' historical action epic "Napoleon" will premiere globally on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> on March 1, 2024, the company has <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-original-films-historical-action-epic-napoleon-from-ridley-scott-to-premiere-globally-on-apple-tv-on-march-1-2024/">announced</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CBmWztLPp9c?si=SgNuTzfhehRm5Zfe" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Directed by Ridley Scott, best known for films including "Alien," "Blade Runner," and "Gladiator," his new biopic stars Joaquin Phoenix as the French emperor and military leader. <br/>
<blockquote>The film is an original and personal look at Napoleon Bonaparte's origins and his swift, ruthless climb to emperor, viewed through the prism of his addictive and often volatile relationship with his wife and one true love, Josephine, played by Vanessa Kirby. The film captures Napoleon's famous battles, relentless ambition and astounding strategic mind as an extraordinary military leader and war visionary.</blockquote>"Napoleon" has received Academy Award nominations for Best Costume Design, Best Production Design, and Best Visual Effects. This year's Oscar winners will be announced at the 96th Academy Awards on March 10.<br/>
<br/>
Scott's film has drawn both praise and criticism from audiences and reviewers. It has been recognized for its technical excellence, epic battle scenes, and some strong performances, including Vanessa Kirby's portrayal of Josephine in particular. But the script has also faced some criticism for its historical accuracy and a somewhat shallow exploration of a complex historical figure. <br/>
<br/>
Scott is also releasing a four-hour-long cut of "Napoleon", exclusive to &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, with extra scenes and the potential to address some of these criticisms, although it's not clear when this will arrive on the streaming service.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; received a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-tv-price-increasing-significantly/">price increase in October</a>, and the service now costs &#36;9.99 per month in the U.S. for new and existing subscribers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/napoleon-apple-tv-plus-march-1/">Ridley Scott&#039;s Action Epic &#039;Napoleon&#039; Coming to Apple TV+ on March 1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ridley-scotts-action-epic-napoleon-coming-to-apple-tv-on-march-1.2419842/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First Alleged iPhone 16 Molds Show Vertical Camera Layout</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/first-iphone-16-molds-vertical-camera-layout/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-alleged-iphone-16-molds-show-vertical-camera-layout.2419835/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 04:14:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/first-iphone-16-molds-vertical-camera-layout/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A photo claiming to show a mold of Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 standard model has appeared online, offering another preview of the rumored new vertical camera arrangement.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iphone-16-mold-majin.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936955" /><br/>
Over the last few months, Apple has been experimenting with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/early-iphone-16-prototypes/">different camera bump designs</a> for the standard iPhone 16 models, all of which have featured a vertical camera arrangement. <br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">latest prototype</a> features the same arrangement with two separate camera rings for the Wide and Ultra Wide cameras, housed within a pill-shaped raised surface, suggesting Apple has drawn inspiration from older iPhone models, such as the ‌iPhone‌ X. <br/>
<br/>
With the vertical camera layout, Apple is expected to bring Spatial Video recording to the standard ‌iPhone 16‌ and ‌iPhone 16‌ Plus models. Current iPhone 15 models have a diagonal camera arrangement and are not able to capture spatial video, a feature that is limited to the iPhone 15 Pro models and the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the updated camera bump design, recent ‌iPhone 16‌ prototypes have also featured a smaller Action Button, similar to the one used on ‌iPhone 15 Pro‌, along with a pressure-sensitive Capture Button for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">shooting horizontal video</a> that sits flush with the frame of the device.<br/>
<br/>
When <em>MacRumors</em> first revealed the latest prototype <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">earlier this month</a>, we cautioned readers that it was sourced from pre-production information, and so may not ultimately reflect the final design that goes into mass production. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iphone-16-molds.jpeg" alt="" width="800" height="617" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936956" /><br/>
Likewise, the existence of case maker molds at this early stage does not necessarily confirm that Apple has settled on this design for the iPhone 16. The molds could simply be being used as test samples based on early schematics. Case makers also often base their initial case designs for upcoming iPhones on leaks and rumors, so the images may not be true representations. <br/>
<br/>
The latest images were <a href="https://x.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1759148932028854647?s=20">shared by Majin Bu</a> on X (formerly Twitter). Bu has a mixed track record for accurate rumors, but schematics and images Bu has <a href="https://twitter.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1754127911202828783">previously leaked</a> show the same design and align with our own information independently sourced from the supply chain.<br/>
<br/>
We should know more when the devices move closer to the Engineering Validation Testing (EVT) phase of development. For additional details on Apple's next-generation 2024 smartphones, check out our dedicated rumor roundups for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/first-iphone-16-molds-vertical-camera-layout/">First Alleged iPhone 16 Molds Show Vertical Camera Layout</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-alleged-iphone-16-molds-show-vertical-camera-layout.2419835/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Be Fined Over &#36;500 Million in EU Music Streaming Probe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/apple-fined-500-million-eu-music-probe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-be-fined-over-500-million-in-eu-music-streaming-probe.2419832/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 03:17:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/apple-fined-500-million-eu-music-probe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>Financial Times</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is set to be hit with a €500 million (&#36;538 million) fine for allegedly breaking EU law over access to music streaming services, according to a <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1e677a7e-9494-4f5b-a724-9e58ef26b34f">Financial Times</a></em> report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/Apple-vs-Spotify-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801789" /><br/>
The focus of the European Commission's investigation has been Apple's policy of preventing streaming music apps from informing iPhone and iPad users within the app that lower subscription prices are available when signing up outside of the App Store. <br/>
<br/>
The investigation began in 2019 after Spotify <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/05/06/eu-to-investigate-apple-over-spotify-complaint/">filed an antitrust complaint against Apple</a>. EU regulators formally charged Apple in the anti-competitive probe in 2021, before the commission last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/28/apple-responds-to-eu-narrowing-antitrust-case/">narrowed the scope of the investigation</a> and dropped a charge of pushing developers to use its own in-app payment system.<br/>
<br/>
According to the paywalled <em>FT</em> report, the Commission will say Apple's actions are illegal and go against the bloc's rules that enforce competition in the single market. Subsequently, it will ban Apple's practice of blocking music services from letting users outside its App Store switch to cheaper alternatives, which has historically given Apple Music an unfair advantage.<br/>
<br/>
The investigation's conclusion will essentially rubber stamp the Commission's preliminary view that Apple's rules equate to "anti-steering" and "unfair trading conditions," in breach of EU antitrust law. The Commission previously said that the rules are "detrimental to users of music streaming services on Apple's mobile devices" given they may end up paying more and "negatively affect the interests of music streaming app developers by limiting effective consumer choice."<br/>
<br/>
Developers are permitted by Apple's <a href="https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/">App Store Review Guidelines</a> to notify users of alternative buying options through external communications, like email. Apps categorized as "reader" apps, including Spotify, have the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/30/reader-apps-account-signups-outside-app-store/">incorporate a link in their app</a> directing users to their website for account management. However, Spotify is still not allowed to promote its reduced subscription rates offered on its website directly from within its iPhone app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has never previously been fined for antitrust infringements by the EU, but it was hit in 2020 with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/03/16/france-fines-apple-1b-euros-anti-competitive/">€1.1 billion (&#36;1.19 billion) fine</a> in France for alleged anti-competitive behaviour. The penalty was revised down to €372 million after Apple appealed.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ft-com/">Financial Times</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/apple-fined-500-million-eu-music-probe/">Apple to Be Fined Over &#36;500 Million in EU Music Streaming Probe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-be-fined-over-500-million-in-eu-music-streaming-probe.2419832/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Sales Arrive at Best Buy With Big Savings on iPad Air, 10th Gen iPad, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/18/ipad-sales-arrive-at-best-buy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-sales-arrive-at-best-buy-with-big-savings-on-ipad-air-10th-gen-ipad-and-more.2419794/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 13:07:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/18/ipad-sales-arrive-at-best-buy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/macbook-pro-air-get-discounts/">great deals on MacBook Pro and MacBook Air</a>, Best Buy this weekend has deep markdowns on a variety of iPads. This includes all-time low prices on the 10th generation iPad and 5th generation iPad Air, as well as a few solid discounts on iPad mini 6 and 9th generation iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipads-yellow-sale-imag.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936880" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-yellow-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936881" /><br/>
The cheapest iPad in this sale is the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clEadOydYiR"><strong>&#36;249.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. For a more recent model, Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi 10th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, which is an all-time low price at &#36;100 off.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEadOydYiR"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi 9th gen iPad for &#36;249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi 10th gen iPad for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKbvh8PEh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi 10th gen iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKduB2Qbr"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular 10th gen iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKdXDXcha"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular 10th gen iPad for &#36;649.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Otherwise, you'll find every model of the 10th generation iPad on sale at a record low price during this sale. This includes all Wi-Fi and cellular tablets, in all colors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/ipad-air-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-842207" /><br/>
Similarly, Best Buy has every model of the 5th generation iPad Air on sale at an all-time low price, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;599.00. These are &#36;150 off across the board, and Best Buy is currently the only retailer online that has every model in every color on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/ipad-mini-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-844773" /><br/>
Lastly, the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 is down to &#36;399.99 this weekend at Best Buy, from &#36;499.00. You can also get the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet for &#36;549.99, which is another &#36;99 discount. These two sales are second-best prices on the iPad mini 6.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEafckZntZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEafXjFS0Q"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/18/ipad-sales-arrive-at-best-buy/">iPad Sales Arrive at Best Buy With Big Savings on iPad Air, 10th Gen iPad, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-sales-arrive-at-best-buy-with-big-savings-on-ipad-air-10th-gen-ipad-and-more.2419794/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s MacBook Pro and MacBook Air Get Major Discounts at Best Buy, Save Up to &#36;300 This Weekend Only</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/macbook-pro-air-get-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-macbook-pro-and-macbook-air-get-major-discounts-at-best-buy-save-up-to-300-this-weekend-only.2419720/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 10:30:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/macbook-pro-air-get-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy has a big <a href="https://howl.me/clD9T1Uiz5Q">Presidents' Day sale</a> happening this weekend, and it includes some of the best prices we've ever seen on Apple's MacBook Air and MacBook Pro. This event will last through the weekend and end on Monday, February 19. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/best-buy-presidents-day-sale/">Our article from yesterday</a> has a deeper dive into everything being discounted during the sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-bb-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935644" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Some of these deals (particularly the MacBook Pro discounts) require a <a href="https://howl.me/clsfFR2NQAO">My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total membership</a>, which start at &#36;49.99/year. In addition to exclusive access to select discounts, you'll get free 2-day shipping, an extended 60-day return window, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-blue-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935647" /><br/>
The highlight of the MacBook Air deals is on the 256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air, priced at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. You can also get the 512GB M2 model on sale at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Both of these &#36;300 discounts are a match for the best prices we've ever seen on the M2 15-inch MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALl0A1vd6"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also find solid discounts on the M2 13-inch MacBook Air and M1 13-inch MacBook Air during Best Buy's new sale. Prices on the M2 models begin at <a href="https://howl.me/clEaauQLFYE"><strong>&#36;949.00</strong></a> and prices on the M1 models begin at <a href="https://howl.me/clD970RKWuk"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a>, both of which are matching previous record low discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-blue-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935646" /><br/>
There are a few more MacBook Pro discounts than MacBook Air discounts, but they will all require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership. If you don't have one, you can still get solid second-best prices on these computers at Best Buy this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: My Best Buy Plus/Total membership required to see final deal price.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALsjD0UdF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 14-inch MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALtdDDDQt"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALuHQfnL8"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;2,149.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Some of the highlights include the 512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/clALsjD0UdF"><strong>&#36;1,399.00</strong></a> and the 512GB M3 Pro model at <a href="https://howl.me/clALtdDDDQt"><strong>&#36;1,749.00</strong></a>. In total, you'll find up to &#36;250 off these computers, and there are also a few 16-inch models on sale this weekend as well.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/macbook-pro-air-get-discounts/">Apple&#039;s MacBook Pro and MacBook Air Get Major Discounts at Best Buy, Save Up to &#36;300 This Weekend Only</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-macbook-pro-and-macbook-air-get-major-discounts-at-best-buy-save-up-to-300-this-weekend-only.2419720/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pencil 2 Falls to New Record Low Price of &#36;79 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/amazon-apple-pencil-2-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-2-falls-to-new-record-low-price-of-79-on-amazon.2419706/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:45:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/amazon-apple-pencil-2-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the Apple Pencil 2 for the new all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. There's an estimated delivery date of Monday, February 19 for Prime members, and no coupon code is required to get this deal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/apple-pencil-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897359" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is the first major discount on the Apple Pencil 2 in 2024, and it beats the low price we tracked during the holidays by about &#36;10. The Apple Pencil 2 is compatible with the following iPads: iPad mini (6th generation), iPad Air (4th generation and later), 12.9-inch iPad Pro (3rd generation and later), and 11-inch iPad Pro (1st generation and later). <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you have the newest iPad Pro models, the second-generation Apple Pencil can now be detected while hovering up to 12mm above the display. This allows users to see a preview of their drawing before they make it, and with Scribble text fields automatically expand when the pencil gets near the screen.<br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for the Apple Pencil with USB-C that launched in 2023, Amazon has a smaller &#36;10 discount on that model. It's available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;69.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;79.00. Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/amazon-apple-pencil-2-low-price/">Apple Pencil 2 Falls to New Record Low Price of &#36;79 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-2-falls-to-new-record-low-price-of-79-on-amazon.2419706/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 16: 15+ Rumored Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16-15-rumored-upgrades-compared.2419705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16&#038;post_date=1708194600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After over a year of reports, there are now over a dozen specific rumors about the features and improvements set to be offered by the two non-Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models later in 2024. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-15-vs-16-Feature-Yellow-Pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-936647" /></div><br/>
All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their direct forerunners are listed below, using information from a range of reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">previously covered</a>. We will update this article as more rumors emerge in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
This guide focuses on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, but to learn about how we are expecting the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> to improve on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">see our other comparison article</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design">Design</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to largely carry over the design of their predecessors, meaning that they will have the same dimensions. The most noticeable alteration that will denote the new models is said to be a vertical rear camera arrangement to facilitate spatial video capture, but the removal of the mute switch in favor of the Action button introduced on last year's Pro models and the introduction of an all-new "Capture" button will also be important changes.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Diagonally arranged rear camera array</td><br/>
 <td>Vertically arranged rear camera array to support spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action Button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>"Capture Button" to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15</strong>: 171g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Plus</strong>: 201g weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 173g weight (+0.01%)<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 203g weight (+0.01%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_memory_and_connectivity">Chip, Memory, and Connectivity</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are rumored to benefit from a moderate improvement in processing power thanks to an all-new A18 chip with a more power Neural Engine to support exclusive generative AI capabilities. We are also expecting 33% more memory and Wi-Fi 6E support.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A16 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N4P" enhanced 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory (+33%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting denser batteries and faster charging capabilities. It is worth noting that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus is rumored to feature a smaller battery than its predecessor, but it is not clear how this will affect actual battery life. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15</strong>: 3,349 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Plus</strong>: 4,383 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 3,561 mAh battery (+6%)<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 4,006 mAh battery (-9%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 27W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging (48% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; (25% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are likely to receive several camera enhancements, such as spatial video capture for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>. While many of Apple's devices are rumored to receive a series of new AI-based features via software updates later this year, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to take these further with exclusive capabilities facilitated by a more powerful Neural Engine in the A18 chip and an upgraded microphone.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Upcoming support for new AI features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></td><br/>
 <td>Upcoming support for new AI features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, plus a suite of device-exclusive AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance, designed to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="release_date">Release Date</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to launch in the fall. Apple usually hosts an event every September to unveil new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, with launch following just over a week later. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/">iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 16: 15+ Rumored Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16-15-rumored-upgrades-compared.2419705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iPhone 16 and iOS 18 Rumors, New Macs and iPads Coming Soon, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/top-stories-iphone-16-ios-18-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-iphone-16-and-ios-18-rumors-new-macs-and-ipads-coming-soon-and-more.2419697/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/top-stories-iphone-16-ios-18-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next set of product releases is likely coming up quickly, with a number of Mac and iPad updates reportedly set for next month. Major changes to iOS are coming to residents of the European Union around the same time, while rumors continue to circulate about a potential HomePod with a full display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/top-stories-17feb2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936792" /><br/>
Other news this week included fresh rumors about the iPhone 16 lineup and iOS 18 coming later in the year, while Apple is investigating reports of screen-related issues on the latest Apple Watch models, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New MacBook Airs and iPads, iOS 17.4, and More Expected Next Month</h2><br/>
Now that Apple has launched its Vision Pro headset, attention has shifted towards <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/12/what-to-expect-from-apple-in-march-2024/">what is next on the company's agenda</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/New-Macs-iPads-iOS-17-4.jpg" alt="" width="3198" height="1798" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936049" /><br/>
As usual, March should be a busy time for Apple, as the company is expected to release new MacBook Air, iPad Pro, and iPad Air models during the month. In a recent press release, Apple also confirmed that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/ios-17-4-new-features-and-changes/">iOS 17.4 update for the iPhone will be released in March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
For more information, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/12/what-to-expect-from-apple-in-march-2024/">recap of what to expect from Apple in March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Rumored to Feature 'Significantly' Upgraded Neural Engine for iOS 18's Generative AI Features</h2><br/>
Apple's next-generation A18 and M4 chips for iPhone 16 models and future Macs will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">feature upgraded Neural Engines with "significantly" more cores</a>, according to Taiwan's <em>Economic Daily News</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-18-Mock-iPhone-16-Feature-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936483" /><br/>
iOS 18 is rumored to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">new generative AI features</a> for Siri, Shortcuts, Messages, Apple Music, and more, and an upgraded Neural Engine would boost performance for AI/machine learning tasks. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/15/apple-xcode-ai-tool-for-coding/">Xcode may also gain an AI tool.</a><br/>
<br/>
<h2>tvOS 17.4 Allegedly Hints at HomePod With Display</h2><br/>
The tvOS 17.4 beta for the Apple TV allegedly includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-homepod-display/">code-level references to an unreleased HomePod with a built-in display</a>, according to <em>9to5Mac</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/HomePod-With-Screen-and-Arm-FaceTime-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801481" /><em>Concepts for HomePod with larger display, based on circulating rumors</em></div><br/>
Last year, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo predicted that Apple would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">release a new HomePod with a 7-inch screen in the first half of 2024</a>, so the device could be nearing launch, barring any delays. Apple often holds its first media event of the year in March.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says Quest 3 is Better Than Apple Vision Pro</h2><br/>
In a video shared on his Instagram page this week, Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg said his company's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/meta-quest-3-apple-vision-pro-zuckerberg/">Quest 3 mixed reality headset is better than Apple's Vision Pro</a> headset for the majority of tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/meta-quest-3.jpg" alt="" width="1385" height="779" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914163" /><br/>
Zuckerberg provided many reasons for his opinion, as outlined <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/meta-quest-3-apple-vision-pro-zuckerberg/">in our coverage</a>. In the U.S., the Quest 3 starts at &#36;499.99, making it a much more affordable option compared to the Vision Pro, which starts at &#36;3,499.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18: All the Rumors and New Features Expected So Far</h2><br/>
iOS 18 is still months away from being unveiled, but there are already rumors and expectations for the software update, as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/15/ios-18-features-and-rumors/">outlined in our recap</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-18-Everything-So-Far-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924581" /><br/>
iOS 18 is rumored to include new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/15/ios-18-features-and-rumors/">ChatGPT-like generative AI features</a> for Siri and select apps, and RCS support in the Messages app for an improved texting experience with Android users. A sketchy rumor claimed that iOS 18 will also have some visionOS-inspired design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Investigating Screen-Related Issue Affecting Some Apple Watches</h2><br/>
In an internal memo shared with Apple Authorized Service Providers last week, Apple said it is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-watch-false-touches-issue/">"investigating" a screen-related issue affecting some Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 displays</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
​"Some customers may report their Apple Watch Series 9 or Apple Watch Ultra 2 is experiencing false touches on their display," the memo says. The issue may cause the screen on affected Apple Watch models to "jump erratically" or exhibit other unexpected behavior, without any user interaction.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/feb-15-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/17/top-stories-iphone-16-ios-18-rumors/">Top Stories: iPhone 16 and iOS 18 Rumors, New Macs and iPads Coming Soon, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-iphone-16-and-ios-18-rumors-new-macs-and-ipads-coming-soon-and-more.2419697/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10 Hidden Messages Features in iOS 17</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/10-hidden-messages-features-in-ios-17/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-hidden-messages-features-in-ios-17.2419693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 04:01:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/10-hidden-messages-features-in-ios-17&#038;post_date=1708182074/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you're an ‌‌iPhone‌‌ user you know how the Messages app works. But when Apple released iOS 17 last year, it introduced an overhauled interface for the Messages app that includes several useful hidden functions and customization options that might not be obvious to the average user. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/iOS-17-Messages-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903379" /><br/>
Below, we've collected 10 of our favorite tips that we hope will make your Messages experience more convenient and enjoyable.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="1._faster_access_to_photo_library">1. Faster Access to Photo Library</h2><br/>
Previously in iOS 16, sharing photos involved tapping the Photos icon in the row of apps below the text input field to access your Camera Roll. But in ‌iOS 17‌ the ‌Photos‌ button is gone, which makes it appear as though you have to tap the + button to the left of the text field to reveal the option.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/1messages-photo-access.jpg" alt="photos messages" width="2738" height="1469" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936912" /><br/>
Thankfully, accessing your photos doesn't have to involve two steps instead of one. If you press and hold the + button, you will be dropped straight into your photo library, ready to select the pictures you want to send.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/2messages-photo-access.jpg" alt="messages photos" width="1338" height="1043" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936913" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2._customize_messages_menu">2. Customize Messages Menu</h2><br/>
When you tap the "+" button in Messages to bring up the column of options, they are arranged in a default order. From the top, there's Camera, Photos, Stickers, Cash (where available), Audio, and Location. At the very bottom is a More button which when tapped reveals any other installed Messages apps (you can also swipe up to reveal this hidden list).<br/>
<br/>
You can reorganize the apps in the list and bring your most-used apps nearer to the top, and even bring up more apps from the "More" section to the first screen of options, in the following way.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/move-imessage-apps.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905326" /><br/>
To move an app within the same screen, press and hold on its icon, then drag it to your preferred location and let go. To move an app up to the first page of icons, simply do the same, but drag it up to the top of the screen and place it where you want.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="3._quicker_replies">3. Quicker Replies</h2><br/>
Before iOS 17, replying to a specific chat bubble in the Messages app involved long pressing on it, then hitting reply. But Apple's swipe to reply feature speeds up the process, and helps you keep track of which message bubble you're replying to with some visual cues.<br/>
<ol><li>Select an iMessage conversation, find the specific message you want to reply to, then swipe right on it.</li><br/>
<li>The selected message will be highlighted and a text box will appear, allowing you to type your reply and hit Send.</li><br/>
<li>To return to the main conversation, tap the blurred background.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/swipe-to-reply.jpg" alt="messages" width="4050" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933820" /><br/>
<br/>
Notice the visual thread that indicates the nested connection between your reply and the original message, which is particularly helpful in group conversations to keep track of who is replying to whom. Remember that everyone in a group conversation can read your inline replies. If you don't want this, start a new conversation with the person you want to reply to. Also, bear in mind that swipe to reply only works on iMessages and not for regular SMS texts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="4._turn_live_photos_into_live_stickers">4. Turn Live Photos into Live Stickers</h2><br/>
In iOS 17, you can take subjects in your Live Photos and turn them into Live Stickers for use in Messages and elsewhere. As the name suggests, Live Stickers are basically looping animated stickers that you can share with family and friends. <br/>
<ol><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>+</strong> button to the left of the text input field, then tap the <strong>Stickers</strong> option.</li><br/>
<li>Select the Stickers icon in the row of sticker apps, then tap the big <strong>+</strong> button in the stickers menu.</li><br/>
<li>Next, tap <strong>Live</strong> below the image search bar, then select a Live Photo.<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/2animate-stickers.jpg" alt="stickers" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936916" /><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Add Sticker</strong> at the bottom of the screen, then tap the sticker you just made to select it, ready for sending. Alternatively, press and hold the sticker, then drag it to an earlier part of the conversation.</li><br/>
<li>You can also long press on the sticker to rearrange it in your collection, add an effect, or delete it. Note that if you add an effect to your creation with the <strong>Add Effect</strong> option, it will cease to be a Live Sticker and instead become a standard static sticker.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/1animate-stickers.jpg" alt="stickers" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936917" /></ol><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="5._use_emoji_as_stickers">5. Use Emoji as Stickers</h2><br/>
In iOS 17, Apple treats all standard emoji as stickers, allowing them to be used in just the same way as actual stickers. What that essentially means is that you aren't limited to inserting them in a conversation. You can also drag them anywhere on a message bubble. You can even layer them on top of one another to create little emoji scenes.<br/>
<ol><li>In a Messages conversation, tap the <strong>Emoji</strong> button in the bottom-left corner of the screen.</li><br/>
<li>Press and hold on an emoji in the list, then drag it up onto the message bubble that you want to react to and release your finger. (Note that you can drag more emoji onto the same message bubble with the same action.)<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/2use-emojis-as-stickers-messages.jpg" alt="" width="2860" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907284" /><br/>
<li>To edit emoji stickers on a message bubble, press and hold the emoji, then tap <strong>Sticker Details</strong> in the popup menu.</li><br/>
<li>To delete an emoji sticker, swipe left on it, then tap the <strong>red Trash button</strong> that appears.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Done</strong> to return to the conversation.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/1use-emojis-as-stickers-messages.jpg" alt="" width="2860" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907283" /></ol><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="6._manage_sticker_apps">6. Manage Sticker Apps</h2><br/>
Standard sticker packs still feature in iOS 17, but the way you access and manage them has changed since iOS 16. The following steps show you how to access, rearrange, and delete installed sticker apps on your iPhone. <br/>
<ol><li>In a conversation thread, tap the <strong>+</strong> button to the left of the text input field.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Stickers</strong> in the vertical menu.</li><br/>
<li>Below the text input field, swipe left across the installed sticker apps all the way to the end of the row, then tap the <strong>Edit</strong> button.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/ios-manage-sticker-apps1.jpg" alt="messages" width="4320" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907146" /><br/>
<li>To rearrange the sticker apps as you want them to appear in the previous row, press the three lines beside an app and drag it up or down to your preferred to location.</li><br/>
<li>To delete a sticker app, tap <strong>Edit</strong> in the top left, then tap the <strong>red delete button</strong> next to the app in question.</li><br/>
<li>To finish, tap <strong>Done</strong> in the top right.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/ios-manage-sticker-apps2.jpg" alt="messages" width="4320" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907147" /></ol><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="7._use_search_filters">7. Use Search Filters</h2><br/>
Previously in iOS 16, you could type a word or phrase in the search field of Apple's Messages app and it would return matching results, but there was no way to filter messages to more easily find what you were looking for. For example, if you were looking for a message from a friend called "John" that had the word "dinner" in it, you would have to search for "dinner" and then scroll through a bunch of messages from anybody and everybody containing that word.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/messages-search-filters.jpg" alt="" width="4137" height="1377" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936926" /><br/>
Thankfully, in iOS 17, Apple improved the search function so that you can combine search queries and narrow down results to quickly find the messages that you're looking for. If you're looking for an image or link from a certain person, for example, first type in the person's name, then tap "Messages with: [person's name]". <br/>
<br/>
Next, select the "Photo" or "Link" filter that appears, and Messages will narrow down the search results further. You can then enter an additional keyword and Messages will show you any links or pictures containing the word. Alternatively, you can start a search with a keyword and then filter the results by person, link, photo, or location.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="8._save_audio_messages">8. Save Audio Messages</h2><br/>
Another smaller improvement in Messages in iOS 17 is that it's a lot clearer where audio messages are kept when you choose to save them. In iOS 16, pressing and holding an audio message brought up a Save option in the pop-up menu, but after tapping it, it was not obvious where to go to locate the file.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/save-to-voice-memos.jpg" alt="" width="1366" height="1388" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904284" /><br/>
‌iOS 17‌, Apple fixed this issue by replacing the "Save" option with "Save to Voice Memos". After tapping it, all you need to do then is open the Voice Memos app, where you'll find the audio message at the top of the list. From there, you can opt to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enhance-voice-memo-recordings-ios/">enhance the recording</a>, skip silences, give the memo an identifying name, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/delete-voice-memo-recordings-iphone-ipad/">delete it</a> when you no longer need it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="9._adjust_audio_message_speed">9. Adjust Audio Message Speed</h2><br/>
When you receive an audio message, you aren't limited to listening to it at the speed it was recorded. If the message includes periodic silences or the person is speaking slowly, you might want to play it back at a faster speed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/audio-message-playback-speed.jpg" alt="audio message" width="2738" height="1709" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936922" /><br/>
Simply long press on the play button to reveal a menu of playback speed options, including 1x, 1.25x, 1.5x, and 2x.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="10._send_audio_messages_faster">10. Send Audio Messages Faster</h2><br/>
If you tend to send lots of audio messages in succession, you don't need to keep tapping the + button to reveal the Audio option to record another one.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/more-audio-recordings.jpg" alt="audio message" width="1338" height="779" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936923" /><br/>
Messages remembers the last kind of message you sent, and will display an audio waveform icon at the right-hand side of the text input field that you can conveniently press and hold to record your next audio message.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/10-hidden-messages-features-in-ios-17/">10 Hidden Messages Features in iOS 17</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-hidden-messages-features-in-ios-17.2419693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Peloton Reverses Course, Will Continue to Support Apple GymKit</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/peloton-apple-gymkit-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/peloton-reverses-course-will-continue-to-support-apple-gymkit.2419666/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 15:17:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/peloton-apple-gymkit-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Peloton</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this week, Peloton said that it would drop support for Apple's GymKit feature that syncs data to the Health app. Customers were unhappy with the decision and complained to the company, leading Peloton to announce a change in plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757966" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/peloton-bike-plus-treadmill-gymkit.jpg" alt="" width="921" height="457" /><br/>
<br/>
Peloton on Thursday said that after listening to member feedback on GymKit, the integration will continue to be offered.<br/>
<br/>
Peloton wanted to stop offering GymKit integration in favor of the Peloton One-Tap tracking feature, but GymKit has been a key feature on the &#36;2,500 Bike+ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/09/08/peloton-announces-bike-gymkit-support/">since its 2020 debut</a>, and other Peloton machines since 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">After listening to Members’ feedback about discontinuing Apple GymKit integration for Bike+, we have decided to continue offering Apple GymKit integration. As a Member-first company, we are always grateful to our Members for sharing their views.</p>&mdash; Peloton (@onepeloton) <a href="https://twitter.com/onepeloton/status/1758588966276870466?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 16, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The One-Tap tracking app does monitor distance, pace, and heart rate metrics, but only basic information is synced to the Apple Health app. With GymKit, data like cadence, average speed, and average power is also available in the Health app for Peloton users.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/peloton/">Peloton</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/peloton-apple-gymkit-support/">Peloton Reverses Course, Will Continue to Support Apple GymKit</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/peloton-reverses-course-will-continue-to-support-apple-gymkit.2419666/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Two Weeks With the Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/vision-pro-2-week-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-weeks-with-the-apple-vision-pro.2419660/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 13:34:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/vision-pro-2-week-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today marks the two-week anniversary of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> launch, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/vision-pro-return-friday/">last day for returns</a> for those who purchased on release day. With plenty of stories going around from those who decided not to keep the &#36;3,500 device, <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera thought he'd share some of the reasons why he'll be keeping his headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lnQld2M8P4A" title="Apple Vision Pro Review: Why I am KEEPIN" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
We need to have a few Vision Pro headsets on hand to write about them here at <em>MacRumors</em>, so that's one of the primary reasons that Dan will be keeping his. Apple is already working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2, and we're interested in seeing what changes and updates are in store. We're also getting new apps on a regular basis, all of which make the Vision Pro a more appealing device.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro is the best way to be immersed in a movie, especially 3D movies, and that's another key reason why Dan won't be bringing his back to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>. The Cinema Environment that shuts out the world is hard to beat because it's basically your own personal movie theater.<br/>
<br/>
Working on the Vision Pro needs some improvement, perhaps with support for multiple Mac displays, but it's useful when traveling with a laptop. It would also be nice to be able to use a mouse, but Magic Keyboard and Trackpad input work well enough.<br/>
<br/>
There are some downsides to the Vision Pro. It's hard to wear for more than about an hour, the battery life is awful, and it doesn't hold a charge at all when not in use. Touch typing with the air keyboard is a poor experience, Personas need a lot of work to be less creepy, there still aren't a whole lot of groundbreaking app experiences, and Guest Mode is awful, so it is fully understandable why we're hearing a lot of return stories.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch Dan's full video to get his thoughts on the Vision Pro after two weeks, and let us know if you kept or returned your Vision Pro in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/vision-pro-2-week-review/">Review: Two Weeks With the Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-weeks-with-the-apple-vision-pro.2419660/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First iPhone 16 Component Leak Reveals Redesigned Camera Chassis</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/iphone-16-camera-component-leak/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-iphone-16-component-leak-reveals-redesigned-camera-chassis.2419647/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 11:12:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/iphone-16-camera-component-leak/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following our previous in-depth coverage of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">various camera bump designs</a> Apple has tested for it, new information has surfaced on social media website X from user Majin Bu. Although this user has a mixed track record, they have occasionally provided accurate information on the design of upcoming iPhones, and their latest post could very well be our first look at a genuine &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; part.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Screenshot-2024-02-16-at-7.05.28 PM.png" alt="" width="2062" height="1160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936878" /><br/>
In <a href="https://twitter.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1758491579067650512">their post</a>, Bu shared an image of what appears to be the main camera chassis for the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, featuring a vertical camera layout. Although the part image was posted upside down, as pointed out by users <a href="https://twitter.com/axoajo/status/1758523318976549339">replying</a> to Bu's post, this does not affect the authenticity of the component itself.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> is able to independently verify the authenticity of the component design pictured above. Through our industry sources, we are able to confirm that the item featured in Bu’s post is the main camera chassis for the I-34 camera project, intended for use in the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; set to be released later this year. <br/>
<br/>
This latest component leak aligns with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/22/iphone-16-vertical-camera-lenses-rumor/">multiple reports</a> concerning the new vertical camera layout Apple has planned for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;. As seen in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/early-iphone-16-prototypes/">our December report on early iPhone 16 prototypes</a>, along with our coverage of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">more recent internal designs</a>, Apple has decided to align the cameras vertically, as opposed to the current diagonal layout found on the base model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus. By employing a vertical camera layout, Apple could bring Spatial Video recording to the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, expanding the feature's overall availability to the entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; range.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the vertical camera layout, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is also expected to receive the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">Action button</a> as a carryover from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and will have an additional <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">Capture button</a> featuring force-sensor technology, located on the right side of the device.<br/>
<br/>
For additional information on what to expect with this year’s new iPhones, check out our dedicated rumor roundup pages for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/iphone-16-camera-component-leak/">First iPhone 16 Component Leak Reveals Redesigned Camera Chassis</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-iphone-16-component-leak-reveals-redesigned-camera-chassis.2419647/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
