<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 02:03:25 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Brings RCS Support to Google Fi, Mint Mobile and Other T-Mobile MVNOs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/ios-18-4-t-mobile-mvno-rcs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-brings-rcs-support-to-google-fi-mint-mobile-and-other-t-mobile-mvnos.2451361/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:04:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/ios-18-4-t-mobile-mvno-rcs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>RCS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The second beta of iOS 18.4 expands <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS messaging support</a> to more carriers in the United States and other countries, according to multiple reports on Reddit, the <em>MacRumors</em> forums, and other social media sites.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-rcs-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2776" height="1562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923042" /><br/>
After installing iOS 18.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/mintmobile/comments/1j2qvcc/rcs_enabled_on_ios_184_beta_2/">with Mint Mobile</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/GoogleFi/comments/1j2wh7l/rcs_on_ios_finally_supported/">Google Fi</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ultramobile/comments/1j2txr4/ultra_has_rcs_on_iphones/">Ultra Mobile</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-beta-2-bug-fixes-changes-and-improvements.2451210/?post=33773459#post-33773459">Tello</a>, and <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/USMobile/comments/1j2sqfi/light_speed_rcs_access_is_in_the_works_184_beta_2/">US Mobile</a> are able to toggle on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a> messaging, and the functionality appears to be rolling out for all T-Mobile Mobile Virtual Network Operators (MVNOs).<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users with a T-Mobile MVNO can be enabled through the Messages section of the Settings app. It appears that &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; access is only available for those running the second iOS 18.4 developer beta, not the public beta.<br/>
<br/>
In France, Orange and Sosh also have &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; available with iOS 18.4 beta 2, according to <em><a href="https://iphonesoft.fr/2025/03/04/rcs-orange-sosh-ios-18-4">iPhoneSoft</a></em>, so &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; may also be rolling out worldwide for other carriers.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; was enabled for major carriers with the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and it stands for Rich Communication Services. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; is a communication protocol that improves messaging between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users, offering support for higher resolution photos and videos, larger file sizes, audio messages, Wi-Fi messaging, real-time typing indicators, read receipts, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/ios-18-4-t-mobile-mvno-rcs/">iOS 18.4 Brings RCS Support to Google Fi, Mint Mobile and Other T-Mobile MVNOs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-brings-rcs-support-to-google-fi-mint-mobile-and-other-t-mobile-mvnos.2451361/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 18.4 Beta Further Hints at Apple&#039;s Work on Smart Home Hub</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/tvos-18-4-smart-home-hub-hints/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-4-beta-further-hints-at-apples-work-on-smart-home-hub.2451359/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 14:50:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/tvos-18-4-smart-home-hub-hints/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the latest beta of tvOS 18.4, there are new hints of Apple's work on a smart home hub accessory that's rumored to be coming as soon as this year. <em>MacRumors</em> found that Apple has added ChatKit framework to the tvOS code, which is curious as there is no Messages app available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> or the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-AI-Command-Center-Concept-Mock-1-Textless.jpg" alt="" width="3000" height="1688" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-987225" /><br/>
The ChatKit framework added to tvOS 18.4 includes reactions and notifications for tapback reactions added to iMessages, like "[person] disliked this" or [person] reacted with [emoji]," which would not be applicable to Apple's current devices that run tvOS.<br/>
<br/>
Both the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; and the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; are built on tvOS, and the upcoming smart home hub will be as well. While the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; and &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; would not work with the ChatKit code features added to tvOS 18.4, Apple's home accessory likely will.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-command-center/">smart home "command center"</a> that Apple is developing is expected to have built-in Apple apps, and it's possible that one of those apps will include Messages.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that there is a shared codebase for tvOS and iOS, so this addition could mean nothing, but these ChatKit features were already included in iOS and have just been added to tvOS with the tvOS 18.4 beta.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's upcoming device will serve as a central hub for smart home management, but it will also support video calls, viewing photos, browsing the web, listening to music, getting news, and more. It is said to look something like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with an all-display design, but it will be smaller, coming in at only six inches square.<br/>
<br/>
Users will likely be able to set it on a table or mount it on a wall, and the expectation is that there would be multiples throughout the house. It will include some sensors for features like sensing the temperature or detecting nearby people.<br/>
<br/>
There is no concrete word on when Apple's smart home hub will launch, but it could come in the second or third quarter of 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/tvos-18-4-smart-home-hub-hints/">tvOS 18.4 Beta Further Hints at Apple&#039;s Work on Smart Home Hub</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-4-beta-further-hints-at-apples-work-on-smart-home-hub.2451359/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M2 iPad Air vs. M3 iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m2-ipad-air-vs-m3-ipad-air-buyers-guide.2451356/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 14:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1741136400/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> arrives just ten months after the previous model. Last year, the biggest change was the introduction of an all-new 13-inch model. With the latest refresh, the most significant upgrade is the move to the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m2-ipad-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954134" /><br/>
The ‌2024 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models have now been discontinued by Apple, but they may still be found refurbished and with third-party resellers for lower prices. As such, some customers may be weighing up whether to buy the 2024 ‌&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; or the new 2025 models. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> Airs from 2024 and 2025 share most of their key features, so should you consider buying or sticking with the older model to save money? <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; (2024)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; (2025)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Introduced in May 2024</td><br/>
 <td>Introduced in March 2025</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip (2022)</td><br/>
 <td>M3 chip (2023)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Made with TSMC's 5nm (N5P) process</td><br/>
 <td>Made with TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> (N3B) process</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>20 billion transistors</td><br/>
 <td>25 billion transistors</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>All-new GPU architecture with dynamic caching, mesh shading, and hardware-accelerated ray tracing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Support for AV1 video decode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Every other aspect of the device is the same between the two models. The upgrade from the 2022 to 2024 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; was more significant, headlining with a larger size option for the first time, bringing it in line with devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, which are available in two sizes. For a deeper dive on the specific differences between the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and M3 chips, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-chip/">see our other guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Given the iterative nature of a single, generation-to-generation chip upgrade, with no enhancements to design, cameras, or display technology, it is almost certainly not worth upgrading from the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; to the M3 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;. Likewise, if the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; can be found at significantly lower price than the M3 model, this device is still a worthwhile buy. The M3 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is primarily aimed at those with an A14-based fourth-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; or older.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-ipad-air/">M2 iPad Air vs. M3 iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m2-ipad-air-vs-m3-ipad-air-buyers-guide.2451356/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 64GB Era is Over</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apples-64gb-era-is-over/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-64gb-era-is-over.2451355/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 13:24:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apples-64gb-era-is-over/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[All of the iPhone and iPad models that are currently part of Apple's lineup now start with at least 128GB of storage, marking the end of the 64GB era. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-Free-Up-Storage-Feature-Redux-1.jpg" alt="" width="2072" height="1166" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-977568" /><br/>
Aside from refurbished devices, the final iPhone and iPad models that Apple offered with 64GB of base storage were the third-generation iPhone SE and the iPad 10. Both of those devices are now discontinued, having been replaced by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/">new iPad with the A16 chip</a>, which are each available with a minimum of 128GB of storage.<br/>
<br/>
This is not the first end of an era for Apple's tech specs in recent months. Since October, all Macs sold by Apple have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/30/entire-mac-lineup-now-at-least-16gb-ram/">configured with at least 16GB of RAM</a>, again with the exception of refurbished models. Previously, the minimum was 8GB.<br/>
<br/>
The first iPhone models with 64GB of base storage were the iPhone 8, iPhone 8 Plus, and iPhone X in 2017, while the first iPad Pro models to be configured with at least 64GB of storage were released in that same year.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apples-64gb-era-is-over/">Apple&#039;s 64GB Era is Over</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-64gb-era-is-over.2451355/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Assassin&#039;s Creed Shadows Coming to Mac on March 20</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/assassins-creed-shadows-mac-march-20/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/assassins-creed-shadows-coming-to-mac-on-march-20.2451351/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 12:57:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/assassins-creed-shadows-mac-march-20/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Assassins's Creed Shadows is set to be released for the Mac on Thursday, March 20, Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=q2zte70j">announced today</a>. The game will launch on Mac at the same time as it is released for PlayStation 5, Windows machines, and the Xbox.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/assassinscreedshadows.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992897" /><br/>
Ubisoft first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/assassins-creed-shadows-mac-november/">announced plans</a> to bring the game to the Mac in May 2024, and at that time, it was supposed to be released in November. The game has been delayed multiple times since then, but it seems it will finally be ready to go later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Set in 16th century Japan, the action roleplaying game is part of the main Assassin's Creed gaming lineup, and it is the successor to Assassin's Creed Mirage. The game focuses on the dispute between the Assassin Brotherhood and the Templar Order, and players can take on the role of Fujibayashi Naoe, a shinobi assassin, or Yasuke, a samurai.<br/>
<br/>
Each character offers different controls and gameplay styles, with separate progression paths, skills, weapon options, and stats. While Naoe uses stealth skills, Yasuke excels at combat.<br/>
<br/>
The game has a vast open world to explore, and players will experience a variety of landscapes with evolving weather and seasons. There are castle towns, bustling ports, pastoral landscapes, and peaceful shrines.<br/>
<br/>
Ubisoft executive producer Marc-Alexis Côté said that Assassin's Creed Shadows is his team's "most ambitious" game to date.<br/>
<br/>
Playing Assassin's Creed Shadows on an Apple device requires a Mac with an Apple silicon chip, with real-time ray tracing available on M3 and M4 Macs. Ubisoft also plans to bring it to iPads with M-series chips.<br/>
<br/>
Assassin's Creed Shadows is priced at &#36;70 and it can be <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/assassins-creed-shadows/id6497794841?mt=12">pre-ordered from the Mac App Store</a> ahead of its March 20 release.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/assassins-creed-shadows-mac-march-20/">Assassin&#039;s Creed Shadows Coming to Mac on March 20</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/assassins-creed-shadows-coming-to-mac-on-march-20.2451351/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are 8 Things to Know About Apple&#039;s New iPad With the A16 Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/a16-ipad-tidbits/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-8-things-to-know-about-apples-new-ipad-with-the-a16-chip.2451346/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 11:55:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/a16-ipad-tidbits/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the headline feature of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/">Apple's new lowest-cost iPad</a> is an A16 chip, the device has some other new features and changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iPad-A16-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992621" /><br/>
Apple's official name for the new entry-level iPad is iPad (A16), but we are referring to the device as the iPad 11 in this article.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we recap eight smaller iPad 11 details you might have missed.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>In the iPad 11, the A16 chip has a 5-core CPU and a 4-core GPU, whereas the A16 Bionic chip in the iPhone 14 Pro, iPhone 14 Pro Max, iPhone 15, and iPhone 15 Plus has a 6-core CPU and a 5-core GPU.</li><br/>
<li>The iPad 11 does not support Apple Intelligence.</li><br/>
<li>The iPad 11 is the first entry-level iPad with a 512GB storage option.</li><br/>
<li>The iPad 11 supports Smart HDR 4, up from Smart HDR 3 on the previous model. Smart HDR 4 makes photos look "even more detailed and vivid."</li><br/>
<li>The iPad 11 supports Bluetooth 5.3, up from Bluetooth 5.2 for the previous model.</li><br/>
<li>While cellular iPad 10 models have a SIM card slot in all countries, the iPad 11 relies entirely on eSIM technology worldwide.</li><br/>
<li>The iPad 11 is still compatible with the first-generation Apple Pencil.</li><br/>
<li>Apple says the iPad 11 has an 11-inch display, while the iPad 10 is listed as having a 10.9-inch display. However, Apple is simply rounding up more with the iPad 11, as both devices actually have a 10.86-inch display.</li><br/>
</ul>Apple makes no mention of the iPad 11 having its custom C1 modem, so cellular models might still have a Qualcomm modem. We await teardowns.<br/>
<br/>
It is also unclear how much RAM is in the iPad 11, but we are working to confirm this detail as soon as possible. iPhones with the A16 Bionic chip have 6GB of RAM, but the iPad 11 has a regular A16 chip with reduced CPU and GPU specifications, so it is unclear if the iPad 11 has 6GB of RAM. The iPad 10 has 4GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad can be pre-ordered now, and it will launch on Wednesday, March 12. In the U.S., the Wi-Fi model starts at &#36;349.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/a16-ipad-tidbits/">Here Are 8 Things to Know About Apple&#039;s New iPad With the A16 Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-8-things-to-know-about-apples-new-ipad-with-the-a16-chip.2451346/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Public Betas of iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and macOS Sequoia 15.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-betas-of-ios-18-4-ipados-18-4-and-macos-sequoia-15-4.2451340/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 10:17:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second public betas of upcoming iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 updates, allowing public beta testers to try out the new features in the software ahead of its public launch. The public betas come a day after Apple provided the beta updates to developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988289" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download the updates from the Settings app on each device after opting into the beta through Apple's public beta testing website.<br/>
<br/>
The new software for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> includes Priority Notifications, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> feature designed to show you your most important notifications first, plus it adds a new Sketch style for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> on all &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; devices. <br/>
<br/>
There is a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ Food section for &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers that aggregates recipes, food stories, and tips for healthy eating, plus an Ambient Music feature for playing chill music from Control Center. On the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Mac, the new updates introduce Mail Categorization, a feature that was previously limited to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
In beta 2, Apple added new emoji characters and debuted the Vision Pro app for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The update also brings <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
An outline of all of the new features in iOS 18.4 can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features/">found in our iOS 18.4 features guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-public-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Public Betas of iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and macOS Sequoia 15.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-betas-of-ios-18-4-ipados-18-4-and-macos-sequoia-15-4.2451340/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Fights UK&#039;s Demand for iCloud Data Backdoor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-legal-complaint-uk-backdoor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fights-uks-demand-for-icloud-data-backdoor.2451339/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 10:07:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-legal-complaint-uk-backdoor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Advanced Data Protection</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today filed a legal complaint with the UK's Investigatory Powers Tribunal in an attempt to quash the UK government's demand for backdoor access to encrypted data, reports <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3d8fe709-f17a-44a6-97ae-f1bbe6d0dccd">Financial Times</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988727" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iCloud-Versus-UK-Key-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Earlier this year, the UK government <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-orders-access-icloud/">ordered Apple</a> to give it secret access to encrypted user data uploaded to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> worldwide, through the creation of a backdoor. The UK used its Investigatory Powers Act to justify the demand, but Apple has not complied.<br/>
<br/>
Instead, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-pulls-encrypted-icloud-security-feature-uk/">removed Advanced Data Protection</a> from the UK so that it would not have to provide the government with access to encrypted data. Advanced Data Protection is designed to provide end-to-end encryption to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac users for data stored in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will undoubtedly fight the UK every step of the way in order to protect user privacy, and the legal challenge that the company filed today could be heard as soon as this month. Apple is not able to discuss the order made by the UK in public due to the terms of the law, so the court case could be heard without public notice.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-deeply-concerned-uk-surveillance-law/">made it clear</a> that it would pull &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; features from the UK rather than compromise its user security, and while that only extends to Advanced Data Protection right now, it could lead to key features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and iMessage being removed in the country. The UK wants backdoor access to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; data to fight terrorism and investigate child sex abuse.<br/>
<br/>
Apple fights vehemently against calls for backdoor access to user data, which we saw in 2016 when the U.S. government demanded that Apple unlock the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; of a shooter in San Bernardino, California. That led to a long legal battle that did not see Apple compromise its security. The U.S. has lately reversed course on encryption, and has been promoting end-to-end encryption for mobile devices to protect against foreign cyber campaigns.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. government is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/27/us-probes-uk-apple-backdoor-treaty-violation/">now looking into</a> whether the UK's demand has violated the CLOUD act, which keeps the UK from asking for data from U.S. citizens, and vice versa.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/advanced-data-protection/">Advanced Data Protection</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-legal-complaint-uk-backdoor/">Apple Fights UK&#039;s Demand for iCloud Data Backdoor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fights-uks-demand-for-icloud-data-backdoor.2451339/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple M2 vs. M3 Chip: How Much Better Is M3?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-m2-vs-m3-chip-how-much-better-is-m3.2451337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:51:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-chip&#038;post_date=1741121503/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> contains the M3 chip, upgraded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip in the previous generation, so how much better really is M3?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Chip-Apple-Event-Slide.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920110" /><br/>
With the introduction of the M3 series in 2023, encompassing the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips, Apple once again set new benchmarks in performance, efficiency, and hardware-accelerated capabilities. The transition from ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ to M3 is marked by Apple's move to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process, among other key architectural improvements such as a completely redesigned GPU.<br/>
<br/>
When unveiling the M3 chips, Apple mainly focused on how they compare to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> series of chips, rather than their direct predecessors from the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ series. Even so, the M3 chip represents an advancement over its predecessor, with the headline upgrade being the transition to a more advanced fabrication process that is just ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ in size, down from 5nm on the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ series of chips. This is evident in the M3's increased transistor count, jumping from 20 billion in the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ to 25 billion, a 25% increase that contributes to its enhanced capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
Benchmark tests underscore this progression, with the M3 outperforming the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ by about 17% in single-core tasks and approximately 21% in multi-core tasks. In GPU performance measured by Metal benchmarks, the M3 exhibits a notable improvement of around 15% over the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip introduces an all-new GPU architecture. This architecture includes Dynamic Caching, a breakthrough feature that optimizes GPU memory allocation and utilization, adapting in real-time to varying task demands. This enhancement not only boosts graphics performance for intensive applications but also bolsters the chip's overall energy efficiency. This is particularly beneficial for graphics-heavy tasks like advanced video editing, 3D rendering, and gaming. It also features support for AV1 video decode to provide more efficient and higher-quality video from streaming services.<br/>
<br/>
Both chips support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>. Despite similarities in the 16-core Neural Engine between the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ and M3, the M3's adoption of a ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ process leads to more efficient execution of machine learning and AI tasks. Additionally, the M3 maintains up to 24GB of unified memory (in Macs only), just like the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌, but leverages the new process for more efficient memory bandwidth utilization.<br/>
<br/>
One other notable difference between the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ and M3 chips is their energy efficiency. The ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ fabrication process enables the M3 to achieve higher performance without a proportional increase in power consumption, making the chip particularly appealing for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users who value a balance between power and battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, the M3 chip is a notable upgrade from the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌, distinguished by its higher transistor count, improved performance in CPU and GPU tasks, and superior energy efficiency. While the M3 offers clear advancements, the extent of its superiority does not necessitate an immediate upgrade for ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ users, especially if their existing workflows are still completed comfortably. For new buyers or those upgrading from older models, the M3's improvements in performance and efficiency will be much more pronounced.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-chip/">Apple M2 vs. M3 Chip: How Much Better Is M3?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-m2-vs-m3-chip-how-much-better-is-m3.2451337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac Studio With M4 Max and M3 Ultra Chips Could Launch This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/mac-studio-coming-this-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-studio-with-m4-max-and-m3-ultra-chips-could-launch-this-week.2451334/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 09:37:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/mac-studio-coming-this-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac Studio</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An updated version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> could launch as soon as this week, reports <a href="https://x.com/markgurman"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. The new machine is expected to be equipped with the M4 Max chip that we first saw in the 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> models, but Apple apparently does not have an M4 Ultra chip ready to go.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Studio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2672" height="1503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946114" /><br/>
Instead, there could be a version of the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; that uses an M3 Ultra chip. Apple didn't release an M3 Ultra chip alongside the M3 chip lineup, so it would be a new chip even though it's not part of the current M4 family. The current &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; has an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Ultra chip, as does the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's "Ultra" chips have historically been two of the "Max" chips linked together, but the M3 Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/m3-max-chip-hidden-change/">does not have</a> the UltraFusion interconnect feature that allows the Max chips to be doubled up. The M3 Ultra would likely be a standalone chip that is a departure from the prior Ultra chips that Apple has come out with.<br/>
<br/>
As the M3 Ultra is not likely to be a doubled up M3 Max chip, it's not entirely clear what we can expect in terms of performance, but Apple has more flexibility to tweak processor cores and add additional GPU power. Gurman suggests that Apple might opt to go with an M3 Ultra in the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; in order to distinguish it from a &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; with a future M4 Ultra chip.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman has faced some difficulty predicting the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;'s launch timeline, perhaps due to Apple's shifting plans. Last year, he said the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; would come out <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-studio-m4-mac-pro-2025/">in mid-2025 around WWDC</a>. He later said that the timing would place it after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, a machine that he suggested <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/">would launch before</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> and the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> teased new product launches with a "There's something in the air" graphic on social media, and Apple has so far updated the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is also rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-macbook-air-tomorrow-says-gurman/">getting a refresh this week</a>, and now we may also get the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; even though it doesn't have "Air" in the name.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac-Studio">Mac Studio (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-studio.237">Mac Studio</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/mac-studio-coming-this-week/">Mac Studio With M4 Max and M3 Ultra Chips Could Launch This Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-studio-with-m4-max-and-m3-ultra-chips-could-launch-this-week.2451334/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expected to Announce New MacBook Air &#039;Tomorrow&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-macbook-air-tomorrow-says-gurman/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expected-to-announce-new-macbook-air-tomorrow.2451330/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:09:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-macbook-air-tomorrow-says-gurman/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO Tim Cook yesterday teased that there was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/tim-cook-theres-something-in-the-air/">"something in the air" this week</a>, and it turns out that could be "things" plural. Following today's announcement of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/">new iPad Air with an M3 chip</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman now says that Apple plans to announce the long-rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/m4-macbook-air-what-to-expect/">MacBook Air with the M4 chip</a> tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/cook-tweet-air-upscale.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992453" /><br/>
"Expect the M4 MacBook Air tomorrow as part of the new product wave," he said, <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1896952051386769851">in a post on X</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman initially said the new MacBook Air <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/">would be announced "earlier" than the iPhone 16e and new iPad Air</a>, but that information was evidently wrong.<br/>
<br/>
As was the case with the new iPad Air, and the iPhone 16e last month, the new MacBook Air should be announced in a press release on the Apple Newsroom website.<br/>
<br/>
Beyond the M4 chip, the new 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models are expected to have Thunderbolt 4 ports, a Center Stage camera, longer battery life, and a few other minor upgrades. No design changes are expected.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-macbook-air-tomorrow-says-gurman/">Apple Expected to Announce New MacBook Air &#039;Tomorrow&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expected-to-announce-new-macbook-air-tomorrow.2451330/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Teams Up With Designer Sandy Liang for Limited-Edition Solo 4 Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-teams-up-with-designer-sandy-liang-for-limited-edition-solo-4-headphones.2451329/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Beats brand is announcing another headphone collaboration today, this time with designer Sandy Liang for <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDF34LL/A/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang-limited-edition">limited-edition Solo 4 headphones</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang-headband.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992508" /><br/>
Beats highlights Liang's "playful, nostalgic aesthetic" and her "signature, whimsical style" that sees Liang's hand-drawn pink ribbon on the headband of metallic silver Solo 4 headphones, as well as matching pink Beats "b" logo buttons on the ear cups.<blockquote>"I've always been drawn to the way nostalgia and modernity can coexist, and working with Beats felt like the perfect way to bring that to life. They're such a cultural icon, I wanted this collaboration to feel personal—something that blends function with a sense of playfulness and personality. I wanted it to feel like more than just headphones, but an accessory that  brings joy,” shared Sandy Liang.</blockquote>A similar pink ribbon is embossed on the wrapper of the custom packaging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992509" /><br/>
The Beats Solo 4 on-ear headphones <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-4-launch/">debuted in April 2024</a> with a number of audio-focused improvements, 50-hour battery life, Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking, three connectivity modes (Bluetooth, USB-C, and 3.5mm), and more.<br/>
<br/>
Beats and Liang partnered with photographer Pia Riverola and model Amelia Gray for a promotional campaign around the launch, and Liang will be <a href="http://apple.co/sandy-liang">sitting down with filmmaker Jeannie Sui Wonders at Apple SoHo</a> this Thursday, March 6, at 6:30 pm for <em>A Conversation on Music + Fashion</em>, part of the Today at Apple programming series in Apple's retail stores.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang-campaign.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992510" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDF34LL/A/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang-limited-edition">Beats Solo 4 — Limited Edition Sandy Liang headphones</a> are available starting today at apple.com in the United States, United Kingdom, and Japan, with limited quantities also available at Apple SoHo and the Sandy Liang flagship store in New York City. They are priced at &#36;199.99 in the U.S.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/beats-solo-4-sandy-liang/">Beats Teams Up With Designer Sandy Liang for Limited-Edition Solo 4 Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-teams-up-with-designer-sandy-liang-for-limited-edition-solo-4-headphones.2451329/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Introduces New Springtime Colors for iPhone 16 Silicone Case and Apple Watch Bands</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-springtime-cases-bands/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-introduces-new-springtime-colors-for-iphone-16-silicone-case-and-apple-watch-bands.2451327/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 07:56:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-springtime-cases-bands/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/">announced</a> the newest additions to its tablet family, the 11th generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>. Alongside these refreshes, the company has introduced a Springtime refresh of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> cases and Apple Watch bands, introducing bright new colorways for the new season.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Silicone Cases</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iphone-16-spring-cases-.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992624" /><br/>
<br/>
The new colors of the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFX4ZM/A/iphone-16-pro-silicone-case-with-magsafe-peony">iPhone 16 Silicone Case</a> (&#36;49.00) include Tangerine, Aquamarine, Peony, and Periwinkle. These are available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Solo Loop</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/spring-colors-solo-loop-watch.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992610" /><br/>
<br/>
The new colors of the Solo Loop (&#36;49.00) include <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDMC4AM/A/40mm-peony-solo-loop-size-0">Peony</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDMP4AM/A/40mm-periwinkle-solo-loop-size-0">Periwinkle</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDN14AM/A/40mm-northern-lights-solo-loop-size-0">Northern Lights</a>. Solo Loop bands come in several sizes, so Apple recommends using its fit guide to find the precise size for your wrist.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Braided Solo Loop</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/braided-solo-loop-spring-colors.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992612" /><br/>
<br/>
The new colors of the Braided Solo Loop (&#36;99.00) include <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDJA4AM/A/42mm-tangerine-braided-solo-loop-size-0">Tangerine</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDJM4AM/A/42mm-aquamarine-braided-solo-loop-size-0">Aquamarine</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDJ04AM/A/42mm-peony-braided-solo-loop-size-0">Peony</a>. Braided Solo Loop bands come in several sizes, so Apple recommends using its fit guide to find the precise size for your wrist.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sport Loop</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/spring-sport-loop-apple-watch.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992604" /><br/>
<br/>
The new colors of the Sport Loop (&#36;49.00) include <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDUX4AM/A/40mm-periwinkle-sport-loop">Periwinkle</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDUW4AM/A/40mm-sage-sport-loop">Sage</a>. These are available for Apple Watch cases sized 40mm, 42mm, and 46mm.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sport Band</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/sport-band-spring-colors.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992606" /><br/>
<br/>
The new colors for the Sport Band (&#36;49.00) include <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDRW4AM/A/40mm-aquamarine-sport-band-s-m">Aquamarine</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDRR4AM/A/40mm-tangerine-sport-band-s-m">Tangerine</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDRU4AM/A/40mm-periwinkle-sport-band-s-m">Periwinkle</a>. These come in both S/M and M/L sizes and are available for Apple Watch cases sized 40mm, 42mm, and 46mm.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hermès Bands</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/hermes-spring-bands-1.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992613" /><br/>
<br/>
There are a few new Hermès bands in this lineup, including the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFU4AM/A/apple-watch-herm%C3%A8s-49mm-bleu-hydra-en-mer">Bleu Hydra En Mer</a> 49mm band for Apple Watch Ultra (&#36;449.00) and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFK4AM/A/apple-watch-herm%C3%A8s-42mm-noir-%C3%A9cru-toile-h-single-tour">Noir/Ecru Toile H Single Tour</a> (&#36;349.00).<br/>
<br/>
Hermès also has a few new color options for the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFN4AM/A/apple-watch-herm%C3%A8s-42mm-rose-sakura-jaune-de-naples-twill-jump-attelage-single-tour">Twill Jump Attelage Single Tour</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFG4AM/A/apple-watch-herm%C3%A8s-46mm-sun-kilim-single-tour">Kilim Single Tour</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFT4AM/A/apple-watch-herm%C3%A8s-46mm-noir-gris-bridon-single-tour">Bridon Single/Double Tour</a> bands.<br/>
<br/>
For more information on today's launches, be sure to read our coverage on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/">new iPad</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/">iPad Air</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-springtime-cases-bands/">Apple Introduces New Springtime Colors for iPhone 16 Silicone Case and Apple Watch Bands</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-introduces-new-springtime-colors-for-iphone-16-silicone-case-and-apple-watch-bands.2451327/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad 11 With A17 Pro Chip and Apple Intelligence Rumor Was Wrong</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-entry-level-ipad-lacks-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-11-with-a17-pro-chip-and-apple-intelligence-rumor-was-wrong.2451325/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 07:47:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-entry-level-ipad-lacks-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/">updated the entry-level iPad with an A16 chip</a>. Unfortunately, however, the device continues to lack support for Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iPad-A16-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992621" /><br/>
Apple Intelligence is not available on the new entry-level iPad, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/ipad/compare/">Apple's tech specs</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In January, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said the new entry-level iPad <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/12/ipad-11-rumored-specs/">would be equipped with an A17 Pro chip, enabling Apple Intelligence</a> on the device:<blockquote>The new entry-level iPads — J481 and J482 — will get faster processors and Apple Intelligence. The current models have the A14 chip and 4 gigabytes of memory. Look for the new versions to have the A17 Pro chip, matching the iPad mini, and a bump to 8 gigabytes of memory. That’s the minimum needed to support the new AI platform.</blockquote>This rumor proved to be wrong.<br/>
<br/>
A private account on X with a proven track record ended up being correct about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/ipad-11-with-a16-chip-identifier-leak/">entry-level iPad getting an A16 chip instead</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The entry-level iPad remains the only iPad model in Apple's current lineup that lacks support for Apple Intelligence. The features are available on any iPad Pro or iPad Air model with the M1 chip or newer, as well as the latest iPad mini with the A17 Pro chip.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-entry-level-ipad-lacks-apple-intelligence/">iPad 11 With A17 Pro Chip and Apple Intelligence Rumor Was Wrong</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-11-with-a17-pro-chip-and-apple-intelligence-rumor-was-wrong.2451325/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;100 Off M4 Mac Mini, Available From &#36;529</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/amazon-100-off-m4-mac-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-100-off-m4-mac-mini-available-from-529.2451322/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 06:56:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/amazon-100-off-m4-mac-mini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a few models of Apple's M4 Mac mini at all-time low prices, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLBTPDCS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;529.00</strong></a> for the model with 16GB RAM/256GB SSD, down from &#36;599.00. Discounts reach up to &#36;100 off in these sales, and include both M4 and M4 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/M4-Mac-mini-Apple-Video.jpg" alt="" width="1508" height="850" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-989831" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the M4 Mac mini with 16GB RAM/512GB SSD for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLBX4B1K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;699.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;799.00, and the model with 24GB RAM/512GB SSD for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLBV145M%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. Most models can be delivered by the middle of March, but we are seeing estimates slip into April in some cases.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLBTPDCS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>M4 Mac mini (256GB) for &#36;529.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple updated the Mac mini back in October 2024, introducing a redesigned computer that's smaller than the previous generation and featuring the M4 and M4 Pro chips. Regarding the M4 Pro model, Amazon also has that device on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLBVHSLD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,294.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,399.00, which is just a few dollars away from the previous all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/amazon-100-off-m4-mac-mini/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;100 Off M4 Mac Mini, Available From &#36;529</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-100-off-m4-mac-mini-available-from-529.2451322/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces Redesigned Magic Keyboard for iPad Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-redesigned-ipad-air-magic-keyboard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-redesigned-magic-keyboard-for-ipad-air.2451321/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 06:36:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-redesigned-ipad-air-magic-keyboard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Magic Keyboard</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/03/apple-introduces-ipad-air-with-powerful-m3-chip-and-new-magic-keyboard/">announced</a> a completely redesigned Magic Keyboard accessory for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ipad-air-magic-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-992578" /><br/>
<br/>
The new keyboard features a larger built-in trackpad, a 14-key function row, and a new aluminum hinge. From Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/03/apple-introduces-ipad-air-with-powerful-m3-chip-and-new-magic-keyboard/">press release</a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>The all-new Magic Keyboard for iPad Air expands what users can do at an even lower price. The larger built-in trackpad brings greater precision for detail-oriented tasks, and a new 14-key function row allows easy access to features like screen brightness and volume controls. The new Magic Keyboard attaches magnetically, and the Smart Connector immediately connects power and data without the need for Bluetooth; a machined aluminum hinge also includes a USB-C connector for charging. Now starting at just &#36;269 for the 11-inch model and &#36;319 for the 13-inch model, the new Magic Keyboard for iPad Air features the magical floating design customers love and comes in white.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
It is compatible with all &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models from the fourth-generation onwards. The new keyboard is more in-line with the Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> that was introduced alongside the M4 models last year, although it still lacks an aluminum top case, backlighting, and haptic feedback.<br/>
<br/>
The new Magic Keyboard for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is only available in white. The 11-inch version is priced at &#36;269 and the 13-inch version costs &#36;319.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-keyboard/">Magic Keyboard</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-redesigned-ipad-air-magic-keyboard/">Apple Announces Redesigned Magic Keyboard for iPad Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-redesigned-magic-keyboard-for-ipad-air.2451321/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Unveils 11th-Gen iPad With A16 Chip and More Storage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-11th-gen-ipad-with-a16-chip-and-more-storage.2451320/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 06:06:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Product Release (Buyer's Guide)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/03/apple-introduces-ipad-air-with-powerful-m3-chip-and-new-magic-keyboard/">announced</a> the 11th-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, now featuring the A16 Bionic chip and more storage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ipad-11-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992618" /><br/>
The announcement came alongside the debut of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/">new iPad Air</a>, which now features the M3 chip. From Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/">press release</a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>The A16 chip provides a jump in performance for everyday tasks and experiences in iPadOS, while still providing all-day battery life. Compared to the previous generation, the updated iPad with A16 is nearly 30 percent faster. In fact, compared to iPad with A13 Bionic, users will see up to a 50 percent improvement in overall performance, and A16 makes the updated iPad up to 6x faster than the best-selling Android tablet.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; starts with 128GB of storage, and is also available in 256GB and a new 512GB configuration. The previous model was only available in 64GB and 256GB configurations.<br/>
<br/>
It is available in blue, pink, yellow, and silver, and continues to start at &#36;349. Customers can pre-order the new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; starting today, with launch scheduled for March 12.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/new-ipad-with-a16-and-more-storage/">Apple Unveils 11th-Gen iPad With A16 Chip and More Storage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-11th-gen-ipad-with-a16-chip-and-more-storage.2451320/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces New iPad Air With M3 Chip, Updated Magic Keyboard</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip-updated-magic-keyboard.2451319/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 06:04:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Product Release (Buyer's Guide)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/03/apple-introduces-ipad-air-with-powerful-m3-chip-and-new-magic-keyboard/">introduced</a> new 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Air models with the M3 chip, along with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-redesigned-ipad-air-magic-keyboard/">updated Magic Keyboard</a> for the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/M3-iPad-Air.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992557" /><br/>
With the M3 chip, the new iPad Air should offer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-chip-benchmark-results/">up to 20% faster performance</a> compared to the previous-generation model with the M2 chip, which was released in May 2024. In addition, the M3 chip brings hardware-accelerated ray tracing to the iPad Air for the first time, providing improved graphics rendering in games. <br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MDFV4LL/A/magic-keyboard-for-ipad-air-11-inch-m3-us-english">new Magic Keyboard for the iPad Air</a> features a larger trackpad, and function keys for easy access to features like display brightness and volume controls. The new Magic Keyboard attaches to the iPad Air magnetically, and the Smart Connector immediately connects power and data without the need for Bluetooth. The keyboard is also equipped with a USB-C port in its hinge for pass-through charging of other accessories.<br/>
<br/>
We have yet to discover any other changes for the new iPad Air beyond the M3 chip and the updated Magic Keyboard. The new 11-inch and 13-inch models continue to have a 12-megapixel Center Stage front camera, 12-megapixel Wide rear camera, Touch ID power button, USB-C port with up to 10 Gbps data transfer speeds, Wi-Fi 6E, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
Storage capacities continue to range between 128GB and 1TB, and battery life is unchanged compared to the previous model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence is available on any iPad Air model with the M1 chip or newer.<br/>
 <br/>
The new iPad Air can be <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-ipad/ipad-air">pre-ordered starting today</a>, and it will launch on March 12. In the U.S., the 11-inch model continues to start at &#36;599, and the 13-inch model continues to start at &#36;799. The device remains available in the same Space Gray, Starlight, Blue, and Purple color options that were offered for the previous model.<br/>
<br/>
The new Magic Keyboard comes in white. In the U.S., it is priced at &#36;269 for the 11-inch iPad Air, and at &#36;319 for the 13-inch iPad Air.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/04/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip/">Apple Announces New iPad Air With M3 Chip, Updated Magic Keyboard</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-new-ipad-air-with-m3-chip-updated-magic-keyboard.2451319/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New MacBook Air Coming This Week: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/m4-macbook-air-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-coming-this-week-what-to-expect.2451247/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:52:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/m4-macbook-air-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> teased a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/tim-cook-theres-something-in-the-air/">new product announcement</a> this week, sharing a short video that says "there's something in the Air." Based on the "Air" wording <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/02/m4-macbook-air-imminent/">and the timing</a> of the launch, it sounds like we're going to get new M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/macbook-air-blue-image.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985914" /><br/>
<h2>Design</h2><br/>
Apple will continue to offer the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; in two sizes, including 13 inches and 15 inches. We are not expecting notable design updates, and there have been no rumors of a new look.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898579" /><br/>
The upcoming M4 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models will likely look identical to the current models, as Apple does not refresh the design of the machines super often. The last &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; design refresh came in 2022, so it's only been three years.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Display</h2><br/>
Apple uses mini-LED display technology for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, but that's likely to stay a premium feature. We're expecting the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; to continue to use the same Liquid Retina Display technology (aka LED) as the current model.<br/>
<br/>
With the recent &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; refresh, Apple added a nano-texture matte display upgrade option. It's possible we could see the same option offered for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, but it's no guarantee because that also might remain a premium option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Chip</h2><br/>
We've already seen the M4 chip in multiple products, including the &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, so it won't be a surprise when it's added to the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/M4-Real-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950311" /><br/>
The M4 chip has up to a 10-core CPU and a 10-core GPU, along with a 16-core Neural Engine. It's built on TSMC's upgraded 3-nanometer process, and was designed with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> in mind. The M4 will outperform the M3 chip, but it won't be a shocking upgrade. We can expect modest improvements in CPU and GPU, with improvements up to 25 percent.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>RAM</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;'s RAM now starts at 16GB instead of 8GB, a change that Apple made last year. We aren't expecting any changes here, and the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; machines will also start with 16GB RAM.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Battery Life</h2><br/>
With the efficiency improvements brought by the M4 chip, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; could see battery life gains. The 14-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/">M4 MacBook Pro</a>, for example, lasts for up to 24 hours when streaming video or 16 hours when browsing the web.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>FaceTime Camera</h2><br/>
Apple updated the &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; with a 12-megapixel front-facing camera, and it's possible we'll get the same update with the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;. The camera supports Center Stage, a feature for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and other video apps that is designed to keep you centered in a video chat even as you move around the room.<br/>
<br/>
The camera will also likely support Desk View, which provides an overhead view of your desk so you can do demonstrations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Thunderbolt Ports</h2><br/>
Current &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models have two Thunderbolt 3 ports, but the next-generation models could get three Thunderbolt 4 ports, which would be an upgrade for both speed and connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; models support up to two external displays when the device's lid is open, and the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; should have the same specifications.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pricing</h2><br/>
The M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;1,099, and there are no pricing changes rumored.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air Discontinuation</h2><br/>
Apple still sells a &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, and it's priced starting at &#36;999. It's possible the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; will get discontinued with an M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; taking its place, though Apple could opt to keep the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; model around if upgrading to M3 chips would make the machine too expensive.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Other "Air" Products?</h2><br/>
It's the M4 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; that's ready to launch imminently, but Apple could also surprise us. There are, after all, multiple Apple products with "Air" in the name, some of which are due for an update.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> is set to be updated this spring, for example, and the AirTags are going to get a refresh at some point in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple's Announcement</h2><br/>
Apple doesn't seem to be planning for a spring event this year, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> was announced via press release and accompanying videos. We're expecting the same release procedure for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, with the device set to come out as soon as tomorrow.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/m4-macbook-air-what-to-expect/">New MacBook Air Coming This Week: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-coming-this-week-what-to-expect.2451247/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Takes Apart iPhone 16e for Closer Look at C1 Modem</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/iphone-16e-teardown-ifixit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-takes-apart-iphone-16e-for-closer-look-at-c1-modem.2451245/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:01:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/iphone-16e-teardown-ifixit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16e</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iFixit today shared one of its traditional teardown videos, taking apart the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> to take a closer look at the internal components.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple's iPhone 16e: A Budget Phone with a BIG Surprise!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dO_0FRZ_WTg" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; has the same quick release battery adhesive as the other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, with the battery adhesive able to be released using a low-voltage electrical charge.<br/>
<br/>
An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/28/iphone-16e-teardown/">earlier teardown revealed</a> a 15.55 Wh battery inside the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj;, which is bigger than the 13.83 Wh battery. iFixit says that Apple was able to place a larger battery in the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; because there is additional space that's available thanks to the single-lens rear-camera.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit's teardown gives us our closest look yet at Apple's new C1 modem. It's on the underside of the RF board, and has the same package structure as the Qualcomm X71M modem, with a 4nm modem and DRAM. The 7nm transceivers are not located in the same package as the modem.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit was not impressed with some of the design decisions that Apple made, due to the repair difficulty. To get to the USB-C port, for example, all of the internal components of the device need to be removed. Still, iFixit said that the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; makes some progress toward repairability thanks to the rollback of parts pairing in iOS and small changes like a metal bracket that protects a flex cable from being sliced when opening up the device.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16e">iPhone 16e (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/iphone-16e-teardown-ifixit/">iFixit Takes Apart iPhone 16e for Closer Look at C1 Modem</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-takes-apart-iphone-16e-for-closer-look-at-c1-modem.2451245/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
