<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:03:25 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Advertised With 72-Hour Battery Life in Low Power Mode, But There&#039;s a Catch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-ultra-2-low-power-mode/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-advertised-with-72-hour-battery-life-in-low-power-mode-but-theres-a-catch.2402020/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 12:30:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-ultra-2-low-power-mode/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the Apple Watch Ultra 2 is <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/09/apple-unveils-apple-watch-ultra-2/">advertised</a> with up to 72 hours of battery life in Low Power Mode, compared to 60 hours for the original Ultra model, there is a catch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-230912.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910333" /><br/>
According to fine print on Apple's website, the testing parameters for the Ultra 2 in Low Power Mode were different than those for the original Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
The fine print for the original Apple Watch Ultra said:<blockquote>Multi-day adventure battery life is based on the following use while in Low Power Mode and with workout settings enabled for fewer GPS and heart rate readings: 15 hours of hiking workout, over 600 time checks, 35 minutes of app use, 3 minutes of talk, and 15 hours of sleep tracking, over the course of 60 hours.</blockquote>The fine print for the Apple Watch Ultra 2 says:<blockquote>Battery life in Low Power Mode is based on the following use: 360 time checks, 360 notifications, 180 minutes of app use, and two 60-minute workouts with music playback from Apple Watch via Bluetooth, over the course of 72 hours.</blockquote>Given these very different testing parameters, customers should keep in mind that the Ultra 2 does not simply offer 12 hours more battery life than the original Ultra in Low Power Mode, which is something that could be easily misconstrued.<br/>
<br/>
It's possible the original Ultra would also get around 72 hours of battery life in Low Power Mode based on the new testing parameters, but this is not proven yet.<br/>
<br/>
We've reached out to Apple for request for comment, and we'll update this story if the company provides a response.<div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-ultra-2-low-power-mode/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Advertised With 72-Hour Battery Life in Low Power Mode, But There&#039;s a Catch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-advertised-with-72-hour-battery-life-in-low-power-mode-but-theres-a-catch.2402020/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Battery Capacities Revealed in Regulatory Database</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-battery-capacities-revealed-in-regulatory-database.2402003/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 11:07:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple does not list battery capacities for the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-unveiled/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-apple-watch-ultra-2/">Ultra 2</a> models, but <em>MacRumors</em> has discovered this information in a Chinese regulatory database today, and we have outlined our findings below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
According to the database, which only provides Apple model numbers instead of product names, the 41mm and 45mm Apple Watch Series 9 models appear to be equipped with 282 mAh and 308 mAh batteries, respectively. These capacities are unchanged compared to the equivalent Apple Watch Series 8 models, which makes sense given that Apple says the Series 9 models have the same 18-hour battery life as Series 8 models.<br/>
<br/>
As for the Apple Watch Ultra 2, it appears to be equipped with a 564 mAh battery, which is approximately 4% larger than the 542 mAh battery in the original Apple Watch Ultra. However, Apple says the Ultra 2 has the same 36-hour battery life as the original Ultra, likely due to it having a brighter display and other new features.<br/>
<br/>
A recap of the Apple Watch battery capacities listed in the database:<p><table class="comparison"><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch</th><br/>
 <th>Battery Capacity</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">282 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 8 (41mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">282 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">308 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 8 (45mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">308 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Ultra 2</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">564 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Ultra</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">542 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><p><br/>
New features for both the Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 include brighter displays, a faster S9 chip, a new "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watches without touching the screen, and more. Both new models have been available to order since Tuesday and will begin arriving to customers and launch in stores on Friday, September 22.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> also found the same battery capacities for what appears to be the iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed/">were reported earlier today</a>. We were unable to find a listing for the regular iPhone 15 battery.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Battery Capacities Revealed in Regulatory Database</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-battery-capacities-revealed-in-regulatory-database.2402003/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 and Accessory Prize Pack From Speck and Best Buy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-speck/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-and-accessory-prize-pack-from-speck-and-best-buy.2401989/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:51:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-speck/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>No AMP</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with accessory maker <a href="https://speckproducts.com">Speck</a> and <a href="https://www.bestbuy.com">Best Buy</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and a set of cases and accessories from <a href="https://speckproducts.com">Speck</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-iphone-15-clicklock-family.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="785" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911299" /><br/>
Speck is well-known for its range of case options for Apple's iPhones, and though the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models have just been announced this week, Speck is ready with a <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/search?q=iphone%2015">whole iPhone 15 case lineup</a> and a selection of <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/clicklock-no-slip-interlock-for-magsafe">ClickLock MagSafe grips and mounts</a> that work with the cases.<br/>
<br/>
If you're not a fan of Apple's new FineWoven cases or don't care for the color options that Apple has available, Speck has debuted <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/search?q=iphone%2015">169 new cases</a> that are available in 17 different designs and 20 colors for all four of the new &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models. The cases are available for purchase now <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/search?q=iphone%2015">from Speck's website</a> and from BestBuy retail locations and <a href="https://www.bestbuy.com/">the BestBuy website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Speck has three types of cases that users can choose from, including standard (with no <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a>), &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, and ClickLock for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, which works with ClickLock accessories. Prices range from &#36;25 to &#36;50, and there are options for every aesthetic. The <a href="https://speckproducts.com/products/presidio2-pro-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-pro-cases">Presido2 Pro</a>, for example, has Speck's Armor Cloud technology and protects the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from drops as high as 13 feet while still looking stylish, plus it works with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-clicklock-clear.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911302" /><br/>
The <a href="https://speckproducts.com/products/presidio2-grip-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases">Presidio2 Grip</a>, one of Speck's most popular options, has the same 13-foot drop protection while also offering no-slip inverted grips. This version is 20 percent slimmer than previous versions of the Grip case, it has &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, and it comes in a range of color options that look great with Apple's new iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-presidio-grip-2.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1212" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911303" /><br/>
If you want protection but don't want to cover up the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s design, Speck has the <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/iphone-15-cases-for-2023/products/presidio-perfect-clear-grip-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases">Presidio Perfect-Clear Grip MagSafe case</a> with no-slip grips, 13-foot drop protection, and stylish grooves at the sides. If you're not a fan of that no-slip look, there's also a <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/iphone-15-cases-for-2023/products/presidio-perfect-clear-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases">Presidio Perfect-Clear case</a> that has a smoother finish.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-perfect-clear-grip.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1209" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911304" /><br/>
These cases all work with ClickLock, a technology Speck has designed to prevent accidental separation of iPhones and &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessories by adding a magnetic interlock mechanism. Speck this week came out with three new ClickLock options that work with its cases and the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models, including the Car Vent Mount, the <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/wallet-for-magsafe-with-clicklock?variant=43285595455619">Wallet</a>, and the StandyGrip.<br/>
<br/>
Priced at &#36;30, <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/wallet-for-magsafe-with-clicklock?variant=43285595455619">Speck's MagSafe Wallet</a> is definitely a product where you want ClickLock because a wallet is the last thing you want to slip off of your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Available in several colors, the Wallet holds 1-3 credit, debit, or ID cards.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-iphone-15-wallet.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1037" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911305" /><br/>
The &#36;30 <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/standygrip-for-magsafe-stand-and-grip-combo-with-clicklock">StandyGrip with MagSafe and ClickLock</a> holds the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; upright in a horizontal or vertical viewing position and it can be used to attach the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to a MacBook so it can serve as a webcam, and that's also a situation where a secure attachment is crucial.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-steadygrip.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911306" /><br/>
Speck also has the &#36;40 <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/car-vent-mount-for-magsafe-with-clicklock">Car Vent Mount for MagSafe with ClickLock</a> that attaches to a car vent and has a built-in cable holder. It uses ClickLock to ensure that your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; isn't going to go flying off of the mount when you hit a bump. To see all of Speck's &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; cases and accessories, make sure to <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/iphone-15-iphone-15-plus-iphone-15-pro-and-iphone-15-pro-max-cases-for-2023">visit the Speck website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-car-vent-mount.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="916" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911307" /><br/>
Speck and Best Buy, the giveaway's sponsors, are providing a 128GB &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and a selection of accessories to go with it, including a Presidio2 Grip Case, a Presidio Perfect Clear Grip Case, and a Presidio Perfect Clear Case, all of which have both &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; and ClickLock. Speck is also adding in its Wallet for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; with ClickLock, its StandyGrip for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Stand, and its Car Vent Mount for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; with ClickLock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-bestbuy-logos.jpg" alt="" width="784" height="197" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911527" /><br/>
To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/fcVMe/speck-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Speck Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (September 15) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on September 22. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after September 22 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-speck/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 and Accessory Prize Pack From Speck and Best Buy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-and-accessory-prize-pack-from-speck-and-best-buy.2401989/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iJustine Talks iPhone 15 and Apple Watch Series 9 First Impressions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15-and-apple-watch-series-9-first-impressions.2401978/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:19:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following Apple's "Wonderlust" event, Justine Ezarik joins us on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/iphone-15-and-apple-watch-series-9-first-impressions/id1602394741?i=1000628022007">The MacRumors Show</a> to talk through our reactions to the announcement of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/X9aU0qMYuT4?si=gyA5OdmwpfeoMJRj" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Justine and Dan attended this week's event at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> and were able to spend some time with the new devices. They talk us through how the new, contoured design and frosted glass of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus feel in the hand and look in-person, as well as just how much smaller and lighter the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max really feel due to their titanium design. We also discuss experiences of using the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s Action button and Double Tap on the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj;, the new selection of color options, some of our favorite new features, and more. See more of Justine's work over on her <a href="https://www.youtube.com/ijustine">YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> in <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvNjk1NTlmZTgtMzMxOC00ZDI5LTkyMmYtYWJlMTAwNjhjYTYzLzg1OTRmODNjLTBkN2QtNDhkOS04OTcxLWFkZmEwMTAzOWEzMS9kODA4NmM5Ni1iNmQ4LTRkNWMtYTZiMy1hZGZhMDEwM2M4NmQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M%3d">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player. Watch a video version of the show <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD8VmuL7qc7ii5uyjzSRk3UM7KI_c4qC5">on the <em>MacRumors</em> YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/the-macrumors-show-mark-gurman-iphone-15-event-expectations/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, take a look back at our discussion with <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> about what we were expecting to see at Apple's event to see what we got right and wrong.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for more episodes, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/20/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-talks-iphone-14/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/09/iphone-14-event-reactions-with-luke-miani/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/15/the-macrumors-show-macbook-air-ijustine/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the show, and let us know what subjects you would like the podcast to cover in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">The MacRumors Show: iJustine Talks iPhone 15 and Apple Watch Series 9 First Impressions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15-and-apple-watch-series-9-first-impressions.2401978/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: First iPhone 15 Promotions Hit Alongside Low Prices on MagSafe Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-15-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-first-iphone-15-promotions-hit-alongside-low-prices-on-magsafe-accessories.2401970/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:48:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-15-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking the first offers for Apple's new line of smartphones, the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro. Additionally, the first discounts have arrived on iPhone 15 accessories like cases and USB-C chargers, and Verizon has all-time low prices on MagSafe chargers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0014.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848005" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911508" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;1,000 off iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2F">AT&T</a>, <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a>, and <a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/devices/new-apple-iphone-15-pro-release?icid=MGPO_MTW_U_23APPLNPI_FU9X6OK5VBCXRCZG35882_HP">T-Mobile</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pre-orders-carrier-deals/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/devices/new-apple-iphone-15-pro-release?icid=MGPO_MTW_U_23APPLNPI_FU9X6OK5VBCXRCZG35882_HP"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro pre-orders are officially up today, and you can get up to &#36;1,000 off the new smartphones at carriers including AT&T, Verizon, and T-Mobile. We go into detail about all of these discounts and more <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pre-orders-carrier-deals/">in our dedicated post</a>, so be sure to check it out if you haven't placed your order yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue-23.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911509" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to 30 percent off iPhone 15 accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1592498&u=63177&m=100061">Casely</a>, <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=J2shFQg6J/U&offerid=592602.5&type=3&subid=0">Hyper</a>, <a href="http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-12147972-1440024949000">OtterBox</a>, and more </li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/deals-iphone-15-accessory-sales/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
We're tracking a list of new iPhone 15 accessory discounts from popular third-party Apple accessory companies like Pad & Quill, Hyper, Satechi, Casely, and more. These sales include discounts on cases, chargers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1592498&u=63177&m=100061">Casely</a> - Take 15 percent off sitewide with code IPHONE15</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=J2shFQg6J/U&offerid=592602.5&type=3&subid=0">Hyper</a> - Take up to 30 percent off charging accessories</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-12147972-1440024949000">OtterBox</a> - Take 25 percent off iPhone 15 cases when buying a screen protector or power product</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?B=695070&U=63177&M=54540&urllink=">Pad & Quill</a> - Take 15 percent off iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max wallet cases</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=&afftrack=">Satechi</a> - Take 20 percent off iPhone 15 accessories with code IPHONE</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/u.cfm?d=1057655&m=80610&u=63177&afftrack=">ESR</a> - Take 20 percent off iPhone 15 accessories with code AFFNEW20, or check out the discounted <a href="https://worlds-1st-apple-certified-6.kckb.st/0b82cd1f">6-in-1 Charging Station</a> in its final days on Kickstarter</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/smart-monitor-m8-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911510" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;120 off Samsung Smart Monitor M8</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4WFFxpJ">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-samsung-monitor-m8-549/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4WFFxpJ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>27-Inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4hg4R0B"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>32-Inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;579.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung this week kicked off a new "Discover Samsung" sale and it has some of the best prices we've seen to date on the updated Smart Monitor M8. You can get the 27-inch model for &#36;549.99 (&#36;100 off) and the 32-inch model for &#36;579.99 (&#36;120 off).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MagSafe</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/magsafe-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911511" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take 25 percent off MagSafe chargers</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fshop%2Fonline%2Fmagsafe-accessories-sale%2F">Verizon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fshop%2Fonline%2Fmagsafe-accessories-sale%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">25% OFF</div>MagSafe Chargers</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Verizon is back with 25 percent off discounts on Apple's trio of MagSafe accessories. You can get the MagSafe Charger for &#36;29.99 (&#36;10 off), the MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;96.74 (&#36;32 off), and the MagSafe Battery Pack for &#36;74.24 (&#36;24 off). These are some of the best prices we've tracked on these accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomePod</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/homepod-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911512" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get a free HomePod when you sign up for Verizon 5G Home Plus</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14568741?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fhome%2Finternet%2F5g%2F">Verizon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14568741?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fhome%2Finternet%2F5g%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">FREE HOMEPOD</div>Verizon 5G Home Plus</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Verizon is offering new customers who purchase its 5G Home Plus service a free HomePod. You'll need to activate and maintain the service for 65 days in order to get the HomePod, and this offer is valid through November 8, 2023. <br/>
<br/>
Verizon 5G Home Plus includes higher-speed downloads and Ultra HD 4K video streaming and starts at &#36;45/month.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-15-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: First iPhone 15 Promotions Hit Alongside Low Prices on MagSafe Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-first-iphone-15-promotions-hit-alongside-low-prices-on-magsafe-accessories.2401970/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: CalDigit&#039;s Thunderbolt Station 4 Offers 18 Ports to Level-Up Mac Connectivity</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/caldigit-thunderbolt-station-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-caldigits-thunderbolt-station-4-offers-18-ports-to-level-up-mac-connectivity.2401966/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:18:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/caldigit-thunderbolt-station-4&#038;post_date=1694801917/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CalDigit</category>
		<category>Thunderbolt</category>
		<category>Thunderbolt 4</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[CalDigit's <a href="https://www.caldigit.com/thunderbolt-station-4/">Thunderbolt Station 4</a> (TS4) is a dock with 98W charging power and an impressive array of 18 ports, ideal for Mac setups with a wide range of connection requirements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/caldigit-ts4-main.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909894" /><br/>
The dock comes with a price tag of &#36;399.99, reflective of its high-speed data transfer, expansive connectivity, and powerful charging abilities. While it may not be the most budget-friendly option on the market, its performance and convenience make a compelling case for professionals with demanding workloads and complex Mac setups. In this review, we delve into the TS4's capabilities to determine whether its cost is justified, and help you understand if it is the right fit for your specific needs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/caldigit-ts4-connected.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909892" /><br/>
The dock comes with a 0.8m Thunderbolt 4 Cable, two rubber feet strips, one power cord, one 230W power supply, and a two-year CalDigit warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Design</h3><br/>
The CalDigit TS4 dock features a high-quality, durable aluminum design. Its overall footprint is reasonably compact, measuring 141mm x 42mm x 113mm, meaning that it avoids taking too much space on a desk. If that is too tall for your desktop, just slide on the included pair of rubber strips for cushioning and tip the dock over on its side. The aluminum casing has a ribbed design that gives it a more industrial look while also offering some extra surface area for effective heat dissipation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/caldigit-ts4-sideways.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909897" /><br/>
The TS4's design, despite its compactness, does not compromise on functionality. It houses an impressive total of 18 ports that are logically divided between the front and rear of the dock. The front features easily accessible USB-C, USB-A, and SD card slots, alongside an audio input and output port. The back, meanwhile, is equipped with the remaining ports, including Thunderbolt 4, USB-C, USB-A, DisplayPort, and Ethernet.<br/>
<br/>
The dock is accompanied by a large power brick that, while necessary for its function, detracts slightly from the portability of the device and is an important consideration in terms of cable management.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>USB Ports</h3><br/>
The dock is outfitted with a total of eight USB ports, split between USB-C and USB-A variants. There are three 10Gb/s USB-C ports (two located conveniently on the front and one at the back), offering high-speed data transfer rates and power delivery. The dock also features five 10Gb/s USB-A ports to accommodate slightly older hardware. Four of these ports are located on the back of the device, and one is placed on the front for easy access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/caldigit-ts4-rear-closeup.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909895" /><br/>
One notable advantage is that the USB ports also deliver power sufficient for charging. One of the front USB-C ports delivers 20W, suitable for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> charger or even a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>. The two rear Thunderbolt ports can supply 15W, while the remaining USB-C and USB-A ports offer 7.5W. This means that even in the absence of the host computer, many of the ports will continue to supply power to your devices, effectively turning the TS4 into a handy charging station.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>SD Card Slots</h3><br/>
Two slots accommodate both full-size SD and microSD cards, with UHS-II support ensuring adequate data transfer rates for photographers or videographers. The positioning of these slots on the front of the TS4 is another thoughtful touch, enabling easy access and the quick swapping of cards.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that these slots are UHS-II and not the latest UHS-III specification, which means they will not offer the absolute highest transfer speeds available on the market for users with UHS-III cards. Despite this, UHS-II is still more than fast enough for the vast majority of users.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Display Support</h3><br/>
The CalDigit TS4 offers comprehensive support for external displays, a feature that is particularly valuable for professionals who require multiple monitors for their workflow. The dock supports up to two 6K, 60Hz screens when connected via the Thunderbolt 4 ports, offering ample screen real estate. Moreover, if your requirements are focused on refresh rates, the TS4 can support up to 240Hz at a 1440p resolution. This makes it a perfect fit for graphic designers, video editors, and others who require high-resolution multi-monitor Mac setups.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/caldigit-ts4-rear.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909896" /><br/>
In addition to the Thunderbolt 4 ports, the TS4 also includes a DisplayPort 1.4 port. DisplayPort 1.4 supports high resolutions and refresh rates, as well as features like HDR, making it an excellent choice for a wide range of displays. However, an HDMI port is noticeably absent on the device, which may be a drawback for those who rely on HDMI for their display setup, such as those using smaller OLED TVs as monitors.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Ethernet</h3><br/>
A 2.5 Gigabit Ethernet port promises substantially faster data transfer rates compared to standard Gigabit Ethernet, offering solid performance. During use of the CalDigit TS4, the Ethernet port provided exceptional performance, delivering the highest speeds observed from the router, even when the other selection of ports were virtually maxed-out. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
The CalDigit TS4 Thunderbolt dock comes equipped with three audio ports, including a 3.5mm audio in port, a 3.5mm audio out port, and a 3.5mm combo jack. This trio of audio ports allows for a versatile set of use cases, catering to both input and output needs.<br/>
<br/>
The 3.5mm combo port on the front is especially handy for quickly connecting headphones. The separate 3.5mm audio input and output ports offer even more flexibility, accommodating for standalone microphones and speakers. For instance, you can connect an external microphone for better voice capture quality during video calls or audio recordings. The dedicated output port allows you to connect speakers without having to frequently unplug your headphones.<br/>
<br/>
During testing, the audio ports on the CalDigit TS4 delivered clear and high-quality sound with no noticeable distortion or noise interference. The ease of access and the quality of the audio signal make these ports an excellent feature for those needing multiple audio connectivity options on their Thunderbolt dock.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Final Thoughts</h3><br/>
Overall, the CalDigit TS4 offers best-in-class connectivity as a Thunderbolt dock with an extremely versatile selection of ports. With its convenient port placement, charging capabilities, and discreet design, it is a standout choice for those seeking a multitude of connection options. The ability to connect a single Thunderbolt cable to a MacBook and instantly activate two external displays and connect to over a dozen peripherals, and even charge devices regardless of whether a computer is attached, is extremely useful.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/caldigit-ts4-upright.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909898" /><br/>
<br/>
While its bulky power supply and the omission of an HDMI port may be off-putting to some users, it still offers a wide variety of features that make it a strong competitor in the market. It is easy to recommend the TS4 to any Mac user looking to level-up their setup and meet a wide range of connectivity needs.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>How to Buy</h3><br/>
The <a href="https://www.caldigit.com/thunderbolt-station-4/">CalDigit Thunderbolt Station 4</a> is available for purchase directly from <a href="https://us.caldigit.com/products/ts4">CalDigit's website</a>, as well as other online retailers like <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FCalDigit-TS4-Thunderbolt-Dock-USB%2Fdp%2FB09GK8LBWS">Amazon</a>. The price at the time writing is &#36;399.99, though prices may vary depending on the retailer and any ongoing promotions or sales.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: CalDigit provided MacRumors with a Thunderbolt Station 4 for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/caldigit/">CalDigit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/thunderbolt/">Thunderbolt</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/thunderbolt-4/">Thunderbolt 4</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/caldigit-thunderbolt-station-4/">Review: CalDigit&#039;s Thunderbolt Station 4 Offers 18 Ports to Level-Up Mac Connectivity</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-caldigits-thunderbolt-station-4-offers-18-ports-to-level-up-mac-connectivity.2401966/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Models Have &#039;Completely Standard&#039; USB-C Port Without Restrictions on Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-usb-c-port-completely-standard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-have-completely-standard-usb-c-port-without-restrictions-on-accessories.2401964/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:10:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-usb-c-port-completely-standard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max are equipped with a "completely standard" USB-C port without any restrictions on cables or accessories, according to <a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/09/contrary-to-rumors-the-iphone-15-has-a-standard-by-the-book-usb-c-port/"><em>Ars Technica</em>'s Andrew Cunningham</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
For previous iPhones with the Lightning connector, Apple limits the functionality of some cables and accessories that are not certified through its <a href="https://mfi.apple.com/">"Made for iPhone" program</a>. It was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/28/iphone-15-usb-c-accessories-limited-without-mfi/">rumored</a> that Apple might apply similar limitations to the USB-C port on iPhone 15 models, but this report confirms that is not the case.<br/>
<br/>
As with iPads and Macs with USB-C ports, the report said all existing USB cables, chargers, and accessories will work normally with the iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
As the report notes, it is still possible that Apple will launch a "Made for iPhone" certification program for iPhone accessories with a USB-C port, but it appears that uncertified accessories will work just fine with the devices.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models are equipped with a USB-C port, but there are differences in data transfer speeds. The lower-end iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-usb-port-limited-to-lightning-speeds/">limited to USB 2.0 data transfer speeds</a> of up to 480 Mbps, which is equal to Lightning, while the iPhone 15 Pro models support USB 3 data transfer speeds of up to 10 Gbps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/">accepting pre-orders</a> for all four iPhone 15 models earlier today. The devices launch on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-usb-c-port-completely-standard/">iPhone 15 Models Have &#039;Completely Standard&#039; USB-C Port Without Restrictions on Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-have-completely-standard-usb-c-port-without-restrictions-on-accessories.2401964/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Color Options: Which Did You Choose?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-color-options/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-color-options-which-did-you-choose.2401950/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 06:31:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-color-options&#038;post_date=1694795500/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are available in an entirely refreshed range of colors thanks to a new titanium design. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; families have different color options, so if you have your heart set on a particular shade, you may not be able to get your preferred model in that color. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are available in four colors, all of which are different from those <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-colors/">available</a> on last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a> models. This year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> color options are quite different from those offered in previous years because the device now features a titanium frame with a brushed texture and contoured edges, as opposed to the polished stainless steel offered since 2017's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max's four available color options are:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Black Titanium</li><br/>
<li>White Titanium</li><br/>
<li>Blue Titanium</li><br/>
<li>Natural Titanium</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The color option that Apple previously called "Silver," encompassing a design with silver metal and white glass, has been available on iPhones for over a decade. This is now "White Titanium" on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. This shade has been tweaked to feature a slightly more beige back glass and softer overall tone.<br/>
<br/>
2022's "Space Black," which was previously "Graphite," is now simply "Black Titanium." It is more of an extremely rich, dark gray tone than deep black. Blue Titanium, on the other hand, appears to be more like navy blue, deeper than previous shades such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12</a> Pro's Pacific Blue. Black and Blue Titanium may be more likely to attract fingerprints on account of their darker finish. Scratches, scuffs, and dents could also be more visible on these finishes than White or Natural Titanium.<br/>
<br/>
"Natural Titanium" is a wholly new shade that showcases the true color of the titanium frame with no color applied to its surface in the PVD process. The rear glass is a matching mid- to-light gray tone. The finish is very similar to that of the Apple Watch Ultra, which also has a titanium casing. It also harks back in some ways to the Space Gray finish of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6S.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-max-camera.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910485" /><br/>
It is worth noting that there is no &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; with a Gold finish. Gold was available through 2013's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5S to 2017's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8, and then on 2018's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS to 2022's &zwnj;iPhone 14 Pro&zwnj;. If you were a fan of this color in previous years, you will now need to look to one of the other options. The warm gray of Natural Titanium may be the best alternative.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="how_to_decide_on_a_color">How to Decide on a Color</h3><br/>
If you use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a case, you may wish to consider which device color will best complement it. You may prefer neutral tones such as White Titanium or Black Titanium and use a more colorful case. Alternatively, you could choose a more striking device color like Blue Titanium and use a more neutral case for an interesting contrast.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-finewoven-cases.jpg" alt="" width="2839" height="1177" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910359" /><br/>
White or Black Titanium may age better over time as new devices are released since they are more neutral, almost monochrome shades that tend to have a more timeless effect. If you do not use a case at all, you may wish to take advantage of a more eye-catching color option such as Natural or Blue Titanium.<br/>
<br/>
If you want an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in a shade that is noticeably brand new, Natural Titanium is the best option. It is most likely to indicate that you have the latest-generation device and could be the most popular color option this year since it is quite different from the offerings in recent years.<br/>
<br/>
Your choice of color may also be dependent on how often you upgrade your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. If you upgrade every year, you may be more confident in buying a more striking new color. If you upgrade more often, it can be a good idea to get a different color every time. A new finish can certainly add some novelty to purchasing a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and make it feel more different from your previous device. Alternatively, if you tend to keep your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; for many years and upgrade less often, it may be wiser to consider a color that is more similar to one you have enjoyed previously.<br/>
<br/>
Customers with multiple Apple devices may also want to get an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; color that complements their other devices. For example, if you have a Midnight <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, Blue Titanium is a good match. The Apple Watch Ultra will be best complimented by Natural Titanium, while Apple Watches with stainless steel casings will be best matched by White Titanium.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-color-options/">iPhone 15 Pro Color Options: Which Did You Choose?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-color-options-which-did-you-choose.2401950/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max Shipping Estimates Extend Into November</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-and-pro-max-shipping-estimates-extend-into-november.2401932/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 05:35:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/">accepting pre-orders</a> for the new iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max today, and shipping estimates for the devices on Apple's online store are already beginning to slip into November for many configurations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
As of 7:15 a.m. Pacific Time in the U.S., the iPhone 15 Pro Max is facing up to a 6-7 week shipping estimate for some configurations on Apple's online store, while the iPhone 15 Pro faces up to a 2-3 week delay for some models. The lower-end iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are largely still available for launch-day delivery.<br/>
<br/>
Inventory will inevitably continue to tighten for both delivery and Apple Store pickup as the day progresses, so order quickly if you are planning to.<br/>
<br/>
As is common when iPhone pre-orders begin, some customers have encountered errors while attempting to place their orders on Apple's website or in the Apple Store app, amid the influx in demand. The issues will likely resolve as the day progresses.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro models have several new features, including a USB-C port, lightweight titanium frame, customizable Action button, faster A17 Pro chip manufactured with a 3nm process, up to 5x optical zoom on the Pro Max model, thinner bezels around the screen, Wi-Fi 6E support, an increased 8GB of RAM, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
The devices will launch in stores and begin arriving to customers on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/">iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max Shipping Estimates Extend Into November</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-and-pro-max-shipping-estimates-extend-into-november.2401932/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Models Now Available for Pre-Order</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-models-now-available-for-pre-order.2401920/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 05:01:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Product Release (Buyer's Guide)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is now accepting pre-orders for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max through <a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone/">its online storefront</a> and the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-store/id375380948">Apple Store app</a>. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> app is typically the quickest way to get a pre-order in as it is often accessible before the website comes up.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-and-15-Pro-Pre-Orders-Live-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911294" /><br/>
Pre-orders are being accepted in more than 40 countries and regions around the world, and those who used Apple's "Get Ready" feature should be able to hit a button to get their orders in without hassle.<br/>
<br/>
Pricing on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; starts at &#36;799 or &#36;33.29 per month in the United States, while pricing on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus starts at &#36;899 or &#36;37.45 per month. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is available starting at &#36;999 or &#36;41.62 per month, and the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max is available starting at &#36;1,199 or &#36;49.95 per month. Pricing will vary depending on country.<br/>
<br/>
The lowest-priced &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, 15 Plus, and 15 Pro models have 128GB of storage, but the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max starts with 256GB of storage. Storage upgrades are available for an increased price, with up to 1TB of storage available. Apple is encouraging customers to use trade-in credits to lower the price of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, and it is also <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-iphone/carrier-offers">promoting carrier deals</a> from AT&T, Verizon, and T-Mobile in the U.S.<br/>
<br/>
All of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models are equipped with USB-C ports, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, a new Ultra Wideband chip, Qualcomm 5G modems, and a range of camera updates. The more affordable &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus have an A16 chip, an aluminum frame, and a frosted glass back, as well as a new 48-megapixel Main camera. There have been updates to Portrait mode, Night mode, and general improvements to image quality thanks to Smart HDR updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Colors.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910250" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models feature a new titanium frame that makes them much lighter than prior-generation models, with titanium also offering increased strength and durability. Apple replaced the mute switch with an Action button that can be customized with a number of functions, and display bezels have been slimmed down.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911148" /><br/>
Pro models are also equipped with a faster A17 Pro chip with major GPU improvements that enable them to play console-level games, and they feature all of the camera improvements from the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models, plus more.<br/>
<br/>
Both models have improved Ultra Wide cameras, and while the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; still has a 3x Telephoto lens, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max has a new tetraprism mechanism for its Telephoto lens, enabling 5x optical zoom.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911150" /><br/>
It's not yet clear on whether there will be shortages of the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, but it is a good idea to pre-order right away just in case. There were rumors of production difficulties with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, so it is possible it will sell out. The 5x zoom lens, the new titanium material, and the A17 Pro chip make it especially enticing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Keynote.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911041" /><br/>
U.S. carriers like Verizon, AT&T, and T-Mobile are accepting preorders for the new devices, as are other carriers worldwide. Big box retailers like Best Buy, Target, and Walmart have pre-orders available too.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who pre-order one of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models can expect to begin receiving their deliveries on Friday, September 22, the official launch date for the new devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/">iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Models Now Available for Pre-Order</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-models-now-available-for-pre-order.2401920/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Battery Capacities Revealed in Regulatory Database</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed-in-regulatory-database.2401911/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 04:15:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple does not advertise battery capacities for its new iPhone 15 lineup, but <em><a href="https://www.mysmartprice.com/gear/apple-iphone-15-series-battery-capacity-wattage-support-revealed-by-chinese-regulatory-database/">MySmartPrice</a></em> has obtained this information from a Chinese regulatory database.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-lineup-store.jpg" alt="" width="2976" height="1538" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911377" /><br/>
The Chinese regulatory listing reveals that the iPhone 15 has a 3,349mAh battery (rated capacity) and a wattage of 12.981Wh, while the iPhone 15 Pro has a 3,274mAh battery and a wattage of 12.70Wh.<br/>
<br/>
Battery capacities for the full iPhone 15 lineup:<br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 15: 3,349mAh</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus: 4,383mAh</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro: 3,274mAh</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max: 4,422mAh</li></ul><br/>
Battery capacities for the 2022 iPhone 14 lineup:<br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 14: 3,279 mAh</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus: 4,325 mAh</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro: 3,200 mAh</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max: 4,323 mAh</li></ul><br/>
The same database accurately revealed battery capacities for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/11/iphone-14-battery-capacities-mah/">all four iPhone 14 models</a> ahead of those devices launching last year. <br/>
<br/>
Despite the incremental increases shown above, Apple did not highlight any battery life improvements for its new iPhone 15 models compared to their direct predecessors, presumably because any difference is negligible in real-world usage. This comes contrary to a multitude of rumors prior to Apple's event, which suggested that the major efficiency improvements of the A17 Pro chip would bring battery life improvements.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the approximate battery life of each of iPhone 15 model is as follows:<br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 15: 20 hours</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus: 26 hours</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro: 23 hours</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max: 29 hours</li><br/>
</ul>This is exactly the same as the iPhone 14, iPhone 14 Plus, iPhone 14 Pro Max, and iPhone 14 Pro Max. Of course, it's possible that efficiency improvements may still result in slightly better real-world performance in Apple's latest models, but we won't know until third-party tests are available.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models were announced by Apple earlier this week and will be available to pre-order on Friday. The devices are set to launch on September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed/">iPhone 15 Battery Capacities Revealed in Regulatory Database</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed-in-regulatory-database.2401911/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Issue iPhone 12 Software Update in France to Address Radiation Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-12-software-update-france-radiation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-issue-iphone-12-software-update-in-france-to-address-radiation-concerns.2401857/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 01:56:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-12-software-update-france-radiation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 12</category>
		<category>France</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple said on Friday it would issue a software update for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12</a> users in France to address <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/france-orders-end-to-iphone-12-sales-radiation/">radiation concerns</a> raised by the country's regulators (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-implement-iphone-12-update-next-few-days-france-minister-2023-09-15/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/iphone-12-preorder-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1213" height="682" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-794852" /><blockquote>"We will issue a software update for users in France to accommodate the protocol used by French regulators. We look forward to iPhone 12 continuing to be available in France," Apple said in a statement.<br/>
<br/>
"This is related to a specific testing protocol used by French regulators and not a safety concern," added the company.</blockquote>The French regulator ANFR said it would test the software update. If it made a difference to the electromagnetic waves the device emitted, the regulator said it would bring the model into compliance with European standards applied in France, and the marketing withdrawal order would be lifted.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, France <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/france-orders-end-to-iphone-12-sales-radiation/">ordered</a> Apple to halt &zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; sales and "fix" existing devices to bring them into electromagnetic radiation compliance with European standards. The increase in emitted electromagnetic radiation observed over time by regulators appears to have been the result of successive software updates issued by Apple, and was not present when the &zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; was launched in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
The ANFR ordered Apple to "remove the &zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; from the French market from September 12 due to the model exceeding the limit" for electromagnetic absorption by the body. The agency also told Apple to recall every &zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; it has ever sold in the country. Ministers later said that though the radiation level was above the accepted standard, it was not dangerous and people were safe to continue using the phones, local media reported. <br/>
<br/>
Following the controversy, Apple <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-14/apple-tech-support-staff-urged-to-stay-mum-on-iphone-12-radiation-issue">reportedly</a> advised its tech-support staff not to volunteer any information when consumers ask about the issue, and tell any concerned customers that that all Apple products go through rigorous testing to ensure that they're safe, according to guidance.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/france/">France</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-12-software-update-france-radiation/">Apple to Issue iPhone 12 Software Update in France to Address Radiation Concerns</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-issue-iphone-12-software-update-in-france-to-address-radiation-concerns.2401857/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Showcases iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Titanium Chassis in New Ad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-showcases-iphone-15-pros-titanium-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-showcases-iphone-15-pros-titanium-chassis-in-new-ad.2401845/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 23:45:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-showcases-iphone-15-pros-titanium-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w_JEezynhrc">shared an ad</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, exclusively highlighting the new titanium finish of the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/w_JEezynhrc?si=Umn0q-DK-7Tep0T-" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The 38-second spot depicts a titanium fragment exploding into view and torpedoing through the Solar System towards the surface of the Earth. "From the edge of the universe... to the palm of your hand," reads the ad's tagline.<br/>
<blockquote>Might meets light. Introducing the new titanium iPhone 15 Pro. Featuring a whole new level of gaming performance with the A17 Pro chip. A more versatile, more advanced Pro camera system. And an aerospace-grade titanium design. iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are our lightest, most powerful Pro models ever.</blockquote>For the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, Apple is using a new titanium frame rather than a stainless steel frame, which cuts down on weight. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are approximately nine percent lighter than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 14 Pro&zwnj; Max, yet the chassis is more durable.<br/>
<br/>
The use of titanium on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; also brings with it a change to the chassis finish. Previously, all Pro iPhones used heavily polished stainless steel with a mirror finish as the chassis material. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; has a brushed finish that is considerably less reflective than the finish of previous Pro iPhones, and is also less prone to fingerprints.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus continue to feature a chassis made from aluminum. Pre-orders for all &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models begin on Friday, September 15, with in-store availability beginning a week later on September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ads/">Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-showcases-iphone-15-pros-titanium-ad/">Apple Showcases iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Titanium Chassis in New Ad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-showcases-iphone-15-pros-titanium-chassis-in-new-ad.2401845/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store Down Ahead of iPhone 15 Pre-Orders</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-store-down-iphone-15-pre-orders/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-ahead-of-iphone-15-pre-orders.2401843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 23:22:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-store-down-iphone-15-pre-orders/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/us/shop/goto/buy_iphone/iphone_15_pro">online store</a> is down ahead of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> pre-orders, which are expected to be available at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/store-down-sept-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862843" /><br/>
"We can't wait either," reads the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>'s message when visiting the U.S. website. "Pre-order begins at 5:00 a.m. PDT. See you then." Apple has been doing 5:00 a.m. pre-orders for the last several years instead of the 12:01 a.m. Pacific Time pre-orders that it used to have.<br/>
<br/>
Customers in more than 40 countries and regions, including Australia, Canada, China, France, Germany, India, Japan, Mexico, the UAE, the U.K., and the U.S., will be able to pre-order &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models when the store comes back online. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus will be available in pink, yellow, green, blue, and black in 128GB, 256GB, and 512GB storage capacities, while the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max will be available in black titanium, white titanium, blue titanium, and natural titanium finishes, in 128GB, 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB storage capacities.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-preorder-times/">Here's When You Can Pre-Order the iPhone 15 in Every Time Zone</a></li></ul><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;799, while the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus is priced starting at &#36;899. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;999, and the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max is priced starting at &#36;1,199. After pre-orders take place, a launch will follow on Friday, September 22.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-store-down-iphone-15-pre-orders/">Apple Store Down Ahead of iPhone 15 Pre-Orders</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-ahead-of-iphone-15-pre-orders.2401843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s When You Can Pre-Order the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max in Every Time Zone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-preorder-times/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-when-you-can-pre-order-the-iphone-15-iphone-15-plus-iphone-15-pro-and-iphone-15-pro-max-in-every-time-zone.2401798/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 15:35:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-preorder-times/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Pre-orders for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are set to begin on Friday, September 15 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time, with the new devices set to become available in multiple countries around the world simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
We've created a list of when pre-orders will take place in various countries so <em>MacRumors</em> readers can be some of the first to place an order. Note that we have not listed every time zone for all countries, nor have we listed all of the available pre-order countries, so you should double check your specific time zone to know when pre-orders are happening where you're located.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div style="width:50%;padding:0 10pt 0 0;float:left;"><ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Australia West</strong> - 8:00 p.m. AWST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Australia East</strong> - 10:00 p.m. AEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Austria</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Belgium</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Canada West</strong> - 5:00 a.m. PDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Canada East</strong> - 8:00 a.m. EDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>China</strong> - 8:00 p.m. CST</li><br/>
  	<li><strong>Denmark</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Finland</strong> - 3:00 p.m. EEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>France</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Germany</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Guernsey</strong> - 1:00 p.m. BST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Hong Kong</strong> - 8:00 p.m. HKT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Ireland</strong> - 1:00 p.m. IST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Isle of Man</strong> - 1:00 p.m. BST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Italy</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Japan</strong> - 9:00 p.m. JST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Jersey</strong> - 1:00 p.m. BST</li><br/>
        <li><strong>Luxembourg</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Netherlands</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
</ul></div><div style="width:50%;padding:0 10pt 0 0;float:right;"><ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>New Zealand</strong> - midnight NZST next day</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Norway</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Portugal</strong> - 1:00 p.m. WEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Puerto Rico</strong> - 8:00 a.m. AST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Saudi Arabia</strong> - 3:00 p.m. AST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Singapore</strong> - 8:00 p.m. SGT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Spain</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Sweden</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Switzerland</strong> - 2:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Taiwan</strong> - 8:00 p.m. CST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>UAE</strong> - 4:00 p.m GST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>United Kingdom</strong> - 1:00 p.m. BST</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>United States West</strong> - 5:00 a.m. PDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>United States Mountain</strong> - 6:00 a.m. MDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>United States Central</strong> - 7:00 a.m. CDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>United States East</strong> - 8:00 a.m. EDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>US Virgin Islands</strong> - 8:00 a.m. AST</li></ul></div><div style="clear:both;"></div><br/>
<br/>
Customers in the United States <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pre-order-setup/">can still "Get Ready"</a> for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; launch with a pre-order setup process that allows them to select an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, confirm it with a carrier, and enter a payment method and shipping address.<br/>
<br/>
Those hoping to get a device on launch day should pre-order right away, as we do not yet know what the available supplies will look like. Popular &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models often sell out quickly, so we could see the new colors disappear within a matter of minutes to hours.<br/>
<br/>
Pricing on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models starts at &#36;799, while pricing on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models starts at &#36;999. Many U.S. carriers are offering discounts, and Apple is offering the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Upgrade Program and trade-in options to drop the price.<br/>
<br/>
After pre-orders on September 15, the first &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; orders will arrive to customers on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-preorder-times/">Here&#039;s When You Can Pre-Order the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max in Every Time Zone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-when-you-can-pre-order-the-iphone-15-iphone-15-plus-iphone-15-pro-and-iphone-15-pro-max-in-every-time-zone.2401798/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 16.6, Downgrading From iOS 16.6.1 No Longer Possible</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-stops-signing-ios-16-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-16-6-downgrading-from-ios-16-6-1-no-longer-possible.2401783/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 14:04:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-stops-signing-ios-16-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/apple-releases-ios-16-6-1/">launch of iOS 16.6.1</a> on September 7, Apple has stopped signing iOS 16.6, the previously available version of iOS. Now that iOS 16.6 is no longer being signed, it is not possible to downgrade to that version of iOS after upgrading to iOS 16.6.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/iOS-16.6-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-892299" /><br/>
Apple routinely stops signing older versions of iOS after new releases come out to encourage customers to keep their operating systems up to date, so it is not unusual that the iOS 16.6 update is no longer being signed.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 16.6.1 is an update that addresses a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/ios-16-6-1-macos-13-5-2-active-vulnerabilities/">zero-day security vulnerability</a> that Apple says was actively exploited in the wild. If you have not updated, it is a good idea to do so.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-16/">iOS 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-16/">iPadOS 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-16.238">iOS 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-stops-signing-ios-16-6/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 16.6, Downgrading From iOS 16.6.1 No Longer Possible</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-16-6-downgrading-from-ios-16-6-1-no-longer-possible.2401783/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Blackmagic Announces New iOS Camera App That Ties Into DaVinci Resolve</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/blackmagic-camera-for-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/blackmagic-announces-new-ios-camera-app-that-ties-into-davinci-resolve.2401774/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 13:40:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/blackmagic-camera-for-ios/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>DaVinci Resolve</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Blackmagic Design today <a href="https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/blackmagiccamera">announced the launch of Blackmagic Camera</a>, a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> app that integrates with Blackmagic Cloud and uploads content directly to the DaVinci Resolve video editing app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/blackmagic-camera-ios.jpg" alt="" width="2007" height="1129" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911286" /><br/>
The app features the same digital film camera controls and image processing functions that are available with Blackmagic Design's cameras. The company says that users can create YouTube, TikTok, and Instagram content with a "Hollywood" cinematic look and feel.<br/>
<br/>
All settings are adjustable, including frame rate, shutter angle, audio levels, tint, shutter speed, lens, white balance, and ISO, with a simple tap-based interface. The interface includes record parameters, histogram, focus peaking, levels, and frame guides, and it can be brought up with a swipe. Focusing can be done by tapping on the screen, and there are options for shooting in 16:9 or vertical aspect ratios.<br/>
<br/>
4K ProRes video can be recorded directly to Blackmagic Cloud and synced directly into DaVinci Resolve. Cloud integration allows video footage to be sent to a post production studio in a matter of minutes for simpler editing, and it is available to all members of a project.<br/>
<br/>
Video can also be recorded to the phone's storage and then exported to an external drive for those who prefer not to use Blackmagic Cloud, or uploaded manually to Blackmagic Cloud. Footage from multiple iPhones can be sent to DaVinci Resolve and lined up using the software's Sync Bin tool.<br/>
<br/>
More information on the Blackmagic Camera app for iOS can be <a href="https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/blackmagiccamera">found on the Blackmagic website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Blackmagic Camera is free to use and can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> as of today. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/blackmagic-camera/id6449580241">Direct Link</a>]<br/>
<br/>
DaVinci Resolve for Mac is <a href="https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/davinciresolve">also free to download</a>, and the DaVinci Resolve Studio version is priced at &#36;295.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/davinci-resolve/">DaVinci Resolve</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/blackmagic-camera-for-ios/">Blackmagic Announces New iOS Camera App That Ties Into DaVinci Resolve</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/blackmagic-announces-new-ios-camera-app-that-ties-into-davinci-resolve.2401774/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Blood Glucose Team Gains New Lead</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-gains-new-lead.2401766/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 12:29:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has done some internal shuffling and appointed Tim Millet, vice president of platform architecture, to lead the team that is working on blood glucose monitoring functionality for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Apple-Watch-Blood-Glucose-Monitoring-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888310" /><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-14/apple-taps-new-chief-for-team-developing-watch-s-glucose-tracker">Bloomberg</a></em>, Millet is now in charge of the Exploratory Design Group or XDG that has been developing noninvasive blood glucose testing for years. The team was previously led by longtime Apple employee Bill Athas, but he unexpectedly died in late 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Millet has been at Apple for almost 20 years, and he reports to Apple chip chief Johny Srouji. <em>Bloomberg</em> says that Millet has played a key role in the transition to Apple silicon, leading several teams that work on the processors.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's work on blood glucose monitoring is being overseen by the semiconductor team rather than a health team because it requires advanced sensors and chips. Apple is exploring a noninvasive monitoring technique that involves shooting a laser underneath the skin to determine the concentration of glucose in the blood.<br/>
<br/>
Noninvasive blood glucose monitoring would allow diabetics to test their blood glucose levels without needing to prick the skin, plus it would likely be able to detect pre-diabetes and other blood glucose issues.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple reached a milestone "proof-of-concept" stage with hardware that is about the size of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but Apple needs to condense the components into a size that can fit into an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
A blood glucose monitoring function for the Apple Watch remains several years away.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-update/">Apple Watch Blood Glucose Team Gains New Lead</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-gains-new-lead.2401766/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Available to Order Tomorrow With These 12 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-tomorrow/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-available-to-order-tomorrow-with-these-12-new-features.2401761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 11:45:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-tomorrow/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will begin accepting pre-orders for the new iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max this Friday, September 15 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time. As usual, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">Pro models</a> have a long list of new features, including a USB-C port, lightweight titanium frame, customizable Action button, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
Below, we have highlighted 12 new features on the iPhone 15 Pro models:<br/>
<ul><li>Lightning has been replaced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">with a <strong>USB-C port</strong></a> for a more universal charging standard and faster data transfer speeds up to 10 Gbps.</li><br/>
<li>All four iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/"><strong>support DisplayPort</strong></a> for up to 4K HDR video mirroring and video output to an external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable, according to Apple's tech specs for the devices.</li><br/>
<li>A new <strong>titanium frame</strong> results in the iPhone 15 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/titanium-iphone-15-pro-weight/">weighing up to 10% less</a> than the iPhone 14 Pro models with a stainless steel frame.</li><br/>
<li>A customizable <strong>Action button</strong> replaces the traditional mute switch on previous iPhones. By default, the button is set to toggle between Ring and Silent modes, but it can also be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-action-button-everything-it-can-do/">assigned to a different action</a> for quick access to the camera, flashlight, Voice Memos, Shortcuts, Focus modes, and more.</li><br/>
<li>The new <strong>A17 Pro chip</strong> enables <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores/">up to 10% faster CPU performance</a> and up to 20% faster GPU performance compared to the A16 Bionic chip.</li><br/>
<li>The devices are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/02/iphone-15-pro-features-specs-rumors/">equipped with <strong>8GB of RAM</strong></a>, up from 6GB in the iPhone 14 Pro models. Along with the new A17 Pro chip, extra RAM benefits overall system performance, particularly for multitasking.</li><br/>
<li>There are <strong>thinner bezels</strong> around the screen compared to the iPhone 14 Pro models.</li><br/>
<li>Like the latest Macs and iPad Pro, the iPhone 15 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-models-wi-fi-6e/">support <strong>Wi-Fi 6E</strong></a> (6GHz) for faster wireless speeds and less signal interference. Remember, you'll need a Wi-Fi 6E router in order to take advantage of this functionality.</li><br/>
<li>The iPhone 15 Pro Max exclusively features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/"><strong>up to 5x optical zoom</strong></a>.</li><br/>
<li>The devices are equipped with a <strong>second-generation Ultra Wideband chip</strong>. Apple says two iPhones with this chip can connect from 3x farther away.</li><br/>
<li>The devices feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-models-more-repairable/"><strong>more repairable internal design</strong></a>, with a redesigned frame that allows for the back glass panel to be easily removed from the devices. This change was first made to the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus last year.</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/new-iphone-15-pro-color-options-no-gold/"><strong>New colors</strong></a>: Natural Titanium, Blue Titanium, White Titanium, and Black Titanium.</li></ul>For more details about the devices, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-tomorrow/">iPhone 15 Pro Available to Order Tomorrow With These 12 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-available-to-order-tomorrow-with-these-12-new-features.2401761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Sells EarPods With USB-C, Lightning, or Headphone Plug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/earpods-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-sells-earpods-with-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug.2401757/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 10:51:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/earpods-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>EarPods</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to updating the AirPods Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">with a USB-C charging case</a>, Apple has made its wired EarPods headphones available with a USB-C connector for use with the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">iPhone 15 models</a>. The earbuds are &#36;19 on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/EarPods-USB-C-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893683" /><br/>
Apple now sells three versions of EarPods, including ones with a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MTJY3AM/A/earpods-usb-c">USB-C connector</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MMTN2AM/A/earpods-lightning-connector">Lightning connector</a>, and a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MNHF2AM/A/earpods-35mm-headphone-plug">3.5mm headphone plug</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Released in 2012, the EarPods have become far less popular since Apple launched wireless AirPods in 2016. Starting with the iPhone 12 series in 2020, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/13/iphone-12-ships-without-earpods-or-charger/">stopped including EarPods</a> and a charger in the box with new iPhones in order to be more environmentally friendly, a decision that was controversial at the time.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/EarPods-Trio.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911208" /><br/>
Apple released its original iconic white earbuds in 2001 alongside the launch of the first iPod, and they received a major redesign and the EarPods name in 2012.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earpods/">EarPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/earpods-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug/">Apple Now Sells EarPods With USB-C, Lightning, or Headphone Plug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-sells-earpods-with-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug.2401757/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
