<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 13:03:26 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 to Include an Additional Capacitive &#039;Capture&#039; Button</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-include-an-additional-capacitive-capture-button.2404661/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:50:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series is expected to gain an additional capacitive button, known internally as the "Capture Button." Codenamed "Project Nova," the button is likely to be one of the main selling points of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, assuming it gets past the initial testing phase. The Capture Button is located on the same side as the Power button, only positioned slightly lower - where the mmWave cutout can be found on more recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. The mmWave cutout has been moved to the opposite side, located under the volume buttons. It is currently unknown what the new capacitive button will be used for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
The Capture Button is expected to be a capacitive button rather than a standard mechanical one. Capacitive buttons, unlike mechanical buttons, do not move when pressed down. Instead, the button detects pressure and touch, providing haptic feedback through the use of haptic engines. The buttons are expected to work similarly to the Home Button on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, which mimics the press of a physical button through the built-in Taptic Engine. According to our sources, the capacitive buttons will feature force sensor functionality. Force sensors detect applied force, and convert the magnitude of force into electrical signals.<br/>
<br/>
Early in the development of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, Apple experimented with capacitive buttons on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in the form of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/#:~:text=Project%20Bongo%2C%20as%20it%20was,do%20not%20move%20when%20pressed.">the since-canceled Bongo project</a>. The Bongo module, unlike the Capture Button, consisted of capacitive Power and Volume buttons, and didn’t bring any additional buttons into the mix. Based on what we’ve heard from our sources, the Bongo module was canceled during the EVT stage of development, after unsatisfactory test results and a significant number of hardware issues. The cancelation left Apple engineers with ample room to reimagine the capacitive buttons for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; series, with an entirely new twist this time around.<br/>
<br/>
Unlike the Bongo project, the Capture Button is set to make its debut across the entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, including the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus. It is worth noting, though, that Apple also created a hardware configuration without the Capture Button button, possibly as a fallback variant in the event of continued hardware failure rates. The Capture Button has appeared on both eSIM-only units and devices with support for physical SIM card slots.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
Along with the new Capture Button, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is expected to gain a capacitive Action Button. Known as "Project Atlas," the haptic Action Button uses a design similar to the Capture Button, using strain gauges and reluctance motor to provide the necessary haptic feedback.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the Capture Button and upgraded Action Button, the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is expected to feature a redesigned camera bump, with vertical camera arrangement akin to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12. The Pro models are also set to feature an increase in screen size, from 6.1" and 6.7" to 6.3" and 6.9", respectively.<br/>
<br/>
It is important to consider that the information presented here is pre-production information. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is still in the early stages of development, and the design has not been finalized. Because of this, there is always a chance that we may not see the Capture Button on the final product.<br/>
<br/>
For more details on what to expect, check out our rumor roundup page for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">iPhone 16 to Include an Additional Capacitive &#039;Capture&#039; Button</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-include-an-additional-capacitive-capture-button.2404661/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 Continue to Be Heavily Criticized</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-finewoven-cases-for-iphone-15-continue-to-be-heavily-criticized.2404651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:05:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new FineWoven cases for iPhone 15 models have been heavily criticized since they were released earlier this month, with some customers and media outlets complaining about the fabric exterior being prone to <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/20/23882255/apple-iphone-15-finewoven-case-wallet-bad">scratches</a> and <a href="https://mastodon.macstories.net/@viticci/111119387802099507">stains</a>. We <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">recapped some of the negative feedback</a> last week, and complaints have continued to surface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913676" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://512pixels.net/2023/09/finewoven-case-letdown/"><em>512 Pixels</em> blog post</a> on Sunday, Relay FM co-founder Stephen Hackett shared a photo of his FineWoven case with a misaligned USB-C port cutout, resulting in the pentalobe screw on the right side of the USB-C port being partially exposed.<br/>
<br/>
"It's one thing for these cases to be a letdown in terms of material, but this is a level of sloppiness that genuinely surprises me from Apple," he wrote. "I know not every example out there is as bad as mine, but the vibes around this case aren't good."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/FineWoven-USB-C-Cutout.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913672" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Photo: Stephen Hackett</em></div><br/>
On social media, some users claimed that the USB-C cutout only appears to be misaligned because of the angle that the photo was taken at, but other users responded with <a href="https://twitter.com/OprahsGift/status/1706087754847666583">straight-on photos</a> of the FineWoven case with the same issue. Not all of the cases have this issue, but multiple customers appear to be affected.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, <a href="https://twitter.com/ParkerOrtolani/status/1705377239850951047">Parker Ortolani</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/HartleyCharlton/status/1706025920648114222"><em>MacRumors</em> editor Hartley Charlton</a> shared photos of FineWoven cases with visible damage on display at Apple Stores. An anonymous, alleged Apple Store employee <a href="https://twitter.com/LindaLominger/status/1706349826093273269">mentioned likewise</a> in a post on X, formerly Twitter.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here you can see FineWoven cases after less than a day on retail shelves. Not great. <a href="https://t.co/9RwCAax7sG">pic.twitter.com/9RwCAax7sG</a></p>&mdash; Parker Ortolani (@ParkerOrtolani) <a href="https://twitter.com/ParkerOrtolani/status/1705377239850951047?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 23, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple describes FineWoven as a "durable micro-twill" material made from 68% post-consumer recycled polyester, and said the material has a significantly lower carbon footprint than leather. Earlier this month, Apple announced that it would no longer use leather in any new products or accessories, as part of its environmental responsibility efforts.<br/>
<br/>
It's hard to measure exactly how much negative feedback there is for the new FineWoven cases, but the material certainly appears to be proving quite unpopular so far. We've reached out to Apple for comment, and we'll update this story if we hear back.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/">Apple&#039;s FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 Continue to Be Heavily Criticized</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-finewoven-cases-for-iphone-15-continue-to-be-heavily-criticized.2404651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>FineWoven Magnetic Link for Apple Watch Now Available to Order</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-magnetic-link-now-available-to-order/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/finewoven-magnetic-link-for-apple-watch-now-available-to-order.2404644/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 11:32:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-magnetic-link-now-available-to-order/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Bands</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new Magnetic Link bands for the Apple Watch are <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MTJ53AM/A/41mm-evergreen-magnetic-link-s-m">now available to order</a> on Apple's online store, as <a href="https://twitter.com/ParkerOrtolani/status/1706366154917245005">spotted by Parker Ortolani</a>. Priced at &#36;99, the bands are made with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">controversial new FineWoven material</a> instead of leather.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-FineWoven-Magnetic-Link.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913658" /><br/>
Apple describes FineWoven as a "durable micro-twill" material with a "soft, suede-like feel." Apple says the material is made from 68% post-consumer recycled polyester, and has a significantly lower carbon footprint than leather, which the company no longer uses for accessories. However, FineWoven cases for iPhone 15 models have been heavily criticized since they were released earlier this month, with some customers and media outlets complaining that the material is very susceptible to visible scratches and stains.<br/>
<br/>
The bands are available in 41mm and 45mm sizes, and they are backwards compatible with other Apple Watch case sizes. Color options include Evergreen, Taupe, and Pacific Blue, and all of the bands are estimated to ship in 4-5 weeks.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-bands/">Apple Watch Bands</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-magnetic-link-now-available-to-order/">FineWoven Magnetic Link for Apple Watch Now Available to Order</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/finewoven-magnetic-link-for-apple-watch-now-available-to-order.2404644/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Apple&#039;s M1 MacBook Air Available for All-Time Low Price of &#36;749.99 (&#36;249 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-available-for-all-time-low-price-of-749-99-249-off.2404638/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:22:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking the return of an all-time low price on the 256GB M1 MacBook Air, which is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;999.00. This deal originally debuted during Prime Day back in July and it remains one of the best MacBook-related discounts of 2023 so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/M1-MacBook-Air-Deals-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2125" height="1195" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850533" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the notebook in Gold and Silver at this price, and there's an estimated delivery date of September 27 to September 30 for the MacBook Air. As of writing, the Space Gray model is not matching this record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are many internal and external differences between the 13.3-inch M1 MacBook Air and the newer 13.6-inch and 15.3-inch M2 MacBook Air models, but as an entry-level computer the M1 device should work great for common tasks, especially at this all-time low pricing. You can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-vs-m2-macbook-air/">read our guide</a> to get a better look at all the similarities and differences between the generations.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-5/">Deals: Apple&#039;s M1 MacBook Air Available for All-Time Low Price of &#36;749.99 (&#36;249 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-available-for-all-time-low-price-of-749-99-249-off.2404638/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 to Feature First A-Series Chip Designed Specifically for Standard Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-feature-first-a-series-chip-designed-specifically-for-standard-models.2404586/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 06:14:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The A17 chip designed for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will be made using a fundamentally different manufacturing process to the A17 Pro in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> to cut costs, according to a rumor that has now been clarified by a reliable source.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/A17-Feature-Dark.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-901448" /><br/>
A <a href="https://weibo.com/u/1833340431">Weibo user</a> who claims to be an integrated circuit expert with 25 years of experience working on Intel's Pentium processors was first to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/23/apple-to-switch-tech-behind-a17-to-cut-costs/">float the rumor in June</a>. Now, the same source has clarified Apple's apparent plan for its standard iPhones' chip in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s A17 Pro chip is fabricated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/15/apple-tsmc-3nm-production-capacity/">using TSMC's N3B process</a>, but Apple reportedly plans to switch to the lower-cost N3E process for next year's standard A17 chip designed for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus. This will mark the first time that Apple has designed a chip specifically for its standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. In previous years, Apple simply gave the entire &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup the same chip before staggering them by one year between the standard and the Pro models starting with 2022's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The A15 Bionic chip in the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and ‌‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌‌ Plus is a higher binned variant with one additional GPU core than the A15 used in the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>‌ and ‌‌&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj;‌‌ mini, so some cross-generational differences despite outwardly featuring the same chip would not be unheard of, but this would effectively be the retention of the same name on a fundamentally different chip.<br/>
<br/>
N3B is TSMC's original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> node created in partnership with Apple. N3E, on the other hand, is the simpler and cheaper node that most other TSMC clients will use. N3E has fewer EUV layers and lower transistor density than N3B, resulting in lower efficiency. N3B has also been ready for mass production for longer than N3E, but it has much lower yield. N3B was effectively designed as a trial node and is not compatible with TSMC's successor processes including N3P, N3X, and N3S, meaning that Apple has to redesign its future chips to take advantage of TSMC's innovations.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was originally believed to be planning to use N3B for the A16 Bionic chip, but had to revert to N4 because it was not ready in time. It is likely the case that Apple is using the N3B CPU and GPU core design <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/iphone-14-pro-setback-removed-graphics-processor/">originally designed for the A16 Bionic</a> in the A17 Pro, before switching to the original A17 designs with N3E later in 2024. This architecture will presumably be iterated on through TSMC's successor nodes for chips like the "A18" and "A19."<br/>
<br/>
The Weibo user was first to say that the standard &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models would retain the A15 Bionic chip, with the A16 being exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro models – a rumor that went on to be widely corroborated and turned out true. Earlier this month, Haitong International Securities analyst Jeff Pu <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-16-rumored-to-feature-enhanced-a17-and-8gb/">corroborated the rumor</a> about 2024's A17 chip being fabricated with N3E, adding that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will also feature 8GB of memory, up from 6GB on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/">iPhone 16 to Feature First A-Series Chip Designed Specifically for Standard Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-feature-first-a-series-chip-designed-specifically-for-standard-models.2404586/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Woot&#039;s Massive Apple Accessory Blowout Has Up to 90% Off iPhone Cases and All-Time Low Price on MagSafe Duo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-woot-apple-accessory/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-woots-massive-apple-accessory-blowout-has-up-to-90-off-iphone-cases-and-all-time-low-price-on-magsafe-duo.2404585/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 06:07:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-woot-apple-accessory/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot today kicked off a <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">new Apple accessory blowout sale</a>, offering as much as 90 percent off select first-party Apple accessories. This includes iPhone cases as recent as the iPhone 14 and MagSafe chargers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/woot-925-sale-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913575" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
All accessories in this sale are in new condition and come with a one year Apple limited warranty. Amazon Prime members can get free standard shipping on Woot, and you'll have until September 30 to shop these deals, but they could disappear faster if stock runs out.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 90% OFF</div>Woot Apple Accessory Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
During this event, Woot has Apple's MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_4"><strong>&#36;94.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.99, which is a new all-time low price on the accessory. You'll also find deals on iPhone leather cases, Beats earbuds, Apple Watch bands, AirTag accessories, and more. The steepest discounts are available on older products, like the iPhone 12 mini Leather Sleeve.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-21%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_17">MagSafe Charger</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;39.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_4">MagSafe Duo Charger</a> - &#36;94.99, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Cases</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-plus-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_5">iPhone 14 Plus Leather Case</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-pro-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3">iPhone 14 Pro Leather Case</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-pro-max-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">iPhone 14 Pro Max Leather Case</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;59.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Audio</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fnew-beats-studio-buds-plus-anc-bluetooth-earbuds-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2">Beats Studio Buds+</a> - &#36;99.95, down from &#36;169.95</li></ul><br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2F1-or-2-pack-apple-airtag-leather-key-ring%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_6">AirTag Leather Key Ring</a> - &#36;12.99, down from &#36;35.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2F1-or-2-pack-apple-airtag-leather-loop%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_8">AirTag Leather Loop</a> - &#36;12.99, down from &#36;35.00</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-woot-apple-accessory/">Deals: Woot&#039;s Massive Apple Accessory Blowout Has Up to 90% Off iPhone Cases and All-Time Low Price on MagSafe Duo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-woots-massive-apple-accessory-blowout-has-up-to-90-off-iphone-cases-and-all-time-low-price-on-magsafe-duo.2404585/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Max Teardown: X70 Modem for Faster 5G, 5x Optical Zoom Lens, A17 Pro Chip, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-15-pro-max-teardown-ifixit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-teardown-x70-modem-for-faster-5g-5x-optical-zoom-lens-a17-pro-chip-and-more.2404576/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 05:39:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-15-pro-max-teardown-ifixit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Repair website iFixit today shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hmQHgWNAg24">video teardown</a> of the new iPhone 15 Pro Max, providing a closer look inside the top-of-the-line device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
While the iPhone 15 Pro Max has a similar internal design as the iPhone 14 Pro Max, the device has a redesigned frame that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-models-more-repairable/">allows the back glass panel to be easily removed</a>, resulting in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/">lower repair fees</a> for cracked glass for customers without AppleCare+ coverage. This change was first made to the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus last year.<br/>
<br/>
The teardown provides a brief glimpse at the iPhone 15 Pro Max's upgraded Telephoto lens with a tetraprism system, which enables 5x optical zoom. iFixit said the Main and Ultra Wide lenses on the device appear to look the same as the ones on the iPhone 14 Pro Max, in line with <a href="https://twitter.com/Tech_Reve/status/1705409878481908094">information shared on social media</a> last week. This suggests camera improvements beyond 5x optical zoom are the result of the A17 Pro chip and software optimizations. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hmQHgWNAg24?si=188W1HfRxEASkBYj" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
iFixit says the iPhone 15 Pro Max has a similar logic board as the iPhone 15 Pro. In addition to the A17 Pro chip, the teardown confirms that the device is equipped with Qualcomm's Snapdragon X70 modem, which <a href="https://speedsmart.net/blog/post/2005/iPhone-15-Pro-up-to-24-Faster-5G-Download-Speeds">reportedly enables faster 5G speeds</a> as expected.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, iFixit gave the iPhone 15 Pro Max a low repairability score of 4/10, in part due to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ifixit-lowers-iphone-14-repairability-score/">Apple's parts pairing requirement</a> that it says harms independent repair shops.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-15-pro-max-teardown-ifixit/">iPhone 15 Pro Max Teardown: X70 Modem for Faster 5G, 5x Optical Zoom Lens, A17 Pro Chip, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-teardown-x70-modem-for-faster-5g-5x-optical-zoom-lens-a17-pro-chip-and-more.2404576/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Launch iPad Mini 7 Later This Year, Industry Report Suggests</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/apple-ipad-mini-7-release-late-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-ipad-mini-7-later-this-year-industry-report-suggests.2404552/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 03:16:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/apple-ipad-mini-7-release-late-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple could be preparing to release a seventh-generation iPad mini before the end of the year, based on a new report by <em><a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20230922VL207/digitimes-research-pc-ce-tablet.html">DigiTimes</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/ipad-mini-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888416" /><br/>
In an article discussing stagnating global tablet demand in the second half of 2023, the Taiwan-based outlet forecasts an uptick in Apple's share of the market owing to orders for a "small-size" iPad in the fourth quarter. From the report (see bold): <blockquote>In the second quarter, iPad shipments had a sequential decline higher than those of non-iPad tablets, resulting in iPads' combined shipment share seeing two consecutive quarters of decline. However, the share will gradually pick up during the second half because of Apple's inventory replenishment needs in the third quarter and <strong>orders for a new small-size iPad in the fourth quarter</strong>, the figures show.</blockquote><em>DigiTimes</em> obtains its information from the suppliers who manufacture parts for iPhones and other Apple products. Its sources often provide reliable information, but the site has a mixed track record when it comes to interpreting that information and accurately deciphering Apple's plans. It is often best to view information from the site with some skepticism until the info is corroborated by additional sources, especially when it comes to rumors.<br/>
<br/>
That said, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman earlier this year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/08/airpods-apple-watch-ipad-apple-tv-2023/">reported</a> that an iPad mini update with a minor "spec bump" is not out of the question. Last month, the leaker known as "ShrimpApplePro" also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/01/ipad-mini-7-could-be-coming-later-this-year/">suggested</a> a seventh-generation iPad mini was in the works at Apple, and said that they had seen evidence that at least one new iPad model is coming this year.<br/>
<br/>
However, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/30/new-ipad-mini-launching-next-year/">January</a> said he believes that the seventh-generation ‌iPad mini‌ is most likely to begin mass production in the first quarter of 2024, and Kuo recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/kuo-new-ipads-unlikely-to-launch-this-year/">said</a> he does not expect any new iPad models this year.<br/>
<br/>
If anything happens before the holidays, a chip upgrade may be the most likely feature of a new ‌iPad mini‌. The ‌sixth-generation iPad mini‌ currently contains the A15 Bionic chip, while the new iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro use the A16 and A17 Pro chip, respectively. A minor spec bump could also include upgrades to the front and rear cameras, potentially bringing features like Photonic Engine to the ‌iPad‌ for the first time. <br/>
<br/>
The latest iPad Pro models brought connectivity upgrades like Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 to the ‌iPad‌ for the first time, so it seems highly likely that these capabilities will also make their way to the ‌iPad mini in the next update‌.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/apple-ipad-mini-7-release-late-2023/">Apple to Launch iPad Mini 7 Later This Year, Industry Report Suggests</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-ipad-mini-7-later-this-year-industry-report-suggests.2404552/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Resident Evil Village for iPhone 15 Pro and iPad Launches October 30</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/resident-evil-village-iphone-15-pro-ipad-oct-30/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/resident-evil-village-for-iphone-15-pro-and-ipad-launches-october-30.2404542/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:51:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/resident-evil-village-iphone-15-pro-ipad-oct-30/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>TouchArcade</category>
		<category>Capcom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em><a href="https://www.capcom-games.com/apple/en-us/">Resident Evil Village</a></em> will be released for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> on October 30, Capcom announced during the Tokyo Game Show over the weekend (via <em><a href="https://toucharcade.com/2023/09/24/resident-evil-village-iphone-ipad-release-date-price-resident-evil-4-remake-unlock-mobile-tgs-2023/">TouchArcade</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/resident-evil-village.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913495" /><br/>
During the event, Capcom also revealed pricing for the mobile ports of <em>Resident Evil 4 Remake</em> and <em>Resident Evil Village</em>. While both games are free to start, they will require &#36;59.99 and &#36;39.99 in-app purchases, respectively, to unlock the full experience. <br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders have since gone live for <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/resident-evil-4/id6462360082"><em>Resident Evil 4 Remake</em> on the App Store</a>, which still lists the game as "Coming Soon – Expected December 31, 2023." Both games will support on screen controls, game controllers, multi-touch, HDR, and more.<br/>
<br/>
For those who haven't been following these games, <em>Resident Evil 4 Remake</em> and <em>Resident Evil Village</em> were showcased during Apple's &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; announcement. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are powered by an A17 Pro chip that features a brand new GPU with hardware-accelerated ray tracing, enabling ported console games to be played on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at near-equivalent performance.<br/>
<br/>
DisplayPort support is built into the USB-C port on all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, meaning that the devices can also output video at up to 4K/60Hz natively to a DisplayPort-equipped external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable. On previous iPhones with a Lightning port, video mirroring is limited to 1080p with Apple's Lightning-to-HDMI or Lightning-to-VGA adapters.<br/>
<br/>
Since Apple's &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; event, Capcom confirmed that <em>Resident Evil 4 Remake</em> will come to macOS and iPadOS devices with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or better. <em>Resident Evil Village</em> is already available on macOS, so the iOS and iPadOS release will be an independent purchase when it arrives just before Halloween with support for &zwnj;M1&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models. As a result, <em>Resident Evil 4 Remake</em> will have cross-progression on iOS, iPadOS, and macOS, while <em>Resident Evil Village</em> will have cross-progression on iPadOS and iOS only. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/toucharcade/">TouchArcade</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/capcom/">Capcom</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/resident-evil-village-iphone-15-pro-ipad-oct-30/">Resident Evil Village for iPhone 15 Pro and iPad Launches October 30</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/resident-evil-village-for-iphone-15-pro-and-ipad-launches-october-30.2404542/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Launch in Over 20 More Countries Later This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-15-pro-launch-over-20-countries-this-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-launch-in-over-20-more-countries-later-this-week.2404534/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:43:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-15-pro-launch-over-20-countries-this-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> series is set to launch in over 20 additional countries and territories on September 29, including Macao, Malaysia, Turkey, Vietnam, and others. Apple has not provided a complete list of the countries.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-lineup-store.jpg" alt="" width="2976" height="1538" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911377" /><br/>
Unlike last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> series, all of the latest &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models were available to order when the first wave of launches took place in over 40 countries and regions on Friday, September 22. <br/>
<br/>
Likewise, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max will all be available to order on day one when the second wave of launches takes place on Friday, September 29. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; introduce over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro/">30 new capabilities and improvements</a>, including USB-C and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> across the lineup, as well as a new titanium design and Action button on the high-end models. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-15-pro-launch-over-20-countries-this-week/">iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Launch in Over 20 More Countries Later This Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-launch-in-over-20-more-countries-later-this-week.2404534/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Teardown Confirms Slightly Larger Battery Capacity</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/apple-watch-ultra-2-and-series-9-teardowns/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-teardown-confirms-slightly-larger-battery-capacity.2404482/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 15:22:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/apple-watch-ultra-2-and-series-9-teardowns/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iFixit today <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fYLLtDxT_sM">shared a video</a> with teardowns of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 and Apple Watch Series 9, providing a closer look inside the watches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
Notably, the video confirms that the Apple Watch Ultra 2 is equipped with a 564 mAh battery, as <em>MacRumors</em> was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/">first to report last week</a> via a regulatory database. This is around a 4% larger capacity than the 542 mAh battery in the original Apple Watch Ultra, but Apple says both models have the same battery life of up to 36 hours.<br/>
<br/>
The video also confirms that the 41mm Series 9's battery capacity is 282 mAh, which is unchanged from the 41mm Series 8.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fYLLtDxT_sM?si=0LUKsK0SIhEVh_bD" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
iFixit did not find any obvious hardware changes related to the new Double Tap gesture <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/watchos-10-1-double-tap/">coming with watchOS 10.1 next month</a>, and overall the Ultra 2 and Series 9 have very similar internal designs as the original Ultra and Series 8.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit has yet to share teardowns of any iPhone 15 models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/apple-watch-ultra-2-and-series-9-teardowns/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Teardown Confirms Slightly Larger Battery Capacity</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-teardown-confirms-slightly-larger-battery-capacity.2404482/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma Launching This Week With These New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/macos-sonoma-launch-date-and-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-launching-this-week-with-these-new-features.2404446/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 12:45:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/macos-sonoma-launch-date-and-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple previously announced that macOS Sonoma will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/macos-sonoma-official-release-date-announced/">released this Tuesday, September 26</a>. The free software update includes many new features and changes for the Mac, including the five that we have highlighted below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-WWDC23-macOS-Sonoma-hero.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900893" /><br/>
In addition to these five features, we have shared the full release notes for macOS Sonoma below for a complete overview of everything new.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Desktop Widgets</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macOS-Sonoma-Widgets.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898329" /><br/>
macOS Sonoma brings widgets to the desktop on the Mac, and they are now fully interactive like on the iPhone. It is even possible to use widgets from your iPhone apps automatically, without having to install the corresponding Mac apps.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Related:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-widgets-work-macos-sonoma/">Here's How Interactive Widgets Work in macOS Sonoma</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Game Mode</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-WWDC23-macOS-Sonoma-gaming-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898499" /><br/>
<br/>
macOS Sonoma <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/macos-14-game-mode/">features a new Game Mode</a> that temporarily prioritizes CPU and GPU performance for gaming on Apple silicon Macs. Game Mode also reduces audio latency for AirPods and input latency for select game controllers connected via Bluetooth.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Web Apps in Dock</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macOS-Sonoma-Web-App-1.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913423" /><br/>
<br/>
On macOS Sonoma, any website can be added to the Dock as a web app for convenient access. To create a web app, load the website in Safari, open the File menu, and select Add to Dock. Web apps offer a simplified toolbar and support push notifications.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Related:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/14/how-web-apps-work-macos-sonoma/">Here's How Web Apps Work in macOS Sonoma</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Screen Savers and Wallpapers</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/macos-sonoma-new-aerial-wallpaper.jpg" alt="" width="2381" height="1339" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908212" /><br/>
macOS Sonoma adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/30/macos-sonoma-beta-7-wallpapers/">new Apple TV-like aerial screen savers</a> that feature slow-motion videos of places around the world, such as Yosemite National Park and Dubai. Each screen saver can transition to a matching desktop wallpaper.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Safari Profiles</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macOS-Sonoma-Safari-Profiles.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913427" /><br/>
The latest version of Safari introduced support for profiles, allowing you to keep your browsing separate for work, personal life, and more. Apple says each profile has separate history, cookies, extensions, Tab Groups, and favorites. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>macOS Sonoma Compatibility</h2>macOS Sonoma is compatible with the following Macs:<ul><li><strong>MacBook Pro:</strong> 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>MacBook Air:</strong> 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac mini:</strong> 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>iMac:</strong> 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>iMac Pro:</strong> 2017</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac Studio:</strong> 2022 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac Pro:</strong> 2019 and later</li></ul><h2>macOS Sonoma Release Notes</h2><blockquote>macOS Sonoma brings all‑new capabilities that elevate your productivity and creativity. Discover even more ways to personalize your Mac with stunning screensavers and widgets that you can add to your desktop. Elevate your presence on video calls with a new way to present your work that keeps you a part of the presentation. Safari profiles and web apps help you organize your browsing in all-new ways. Game Mode boosts your gaming performance. Sonoma also brings big updates to Messages, Keyboard, and Accessibility. And when you upgrade, you get the latest security and privacy protections available for Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Screen Savers</strong><br/>
- Stunning screen savers of locations from around the world seamlessly become your desktop wallpaper when you log-in<br/>
- Shuffle settings for rotating through screensavers by theme including Landscape, Cityscape, Underwater, and Earth<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Widgets</strong><br/>
- Widgets can be placed anywhere on the desktop and adapt to the color of your wallpaper while working in apps<br/>
- iPhone widgets can be added to your Mac when your iPhone is nearby or on the same Wi-Fi network<br/>
- Interactive widgets let you take actions directly from the widget such as running a shortcut, pausing media, and more<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Video Conferencing</strong><br/>
- Presenter Overlay keeps you front and center while sharing your screen in FaceTime or third-party video conferencing apps (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
- Reactions layer 3D effects like hearts, balloons, confetti, and more around you in video calls and can be triggered with gestures (Mac with Apple silicon, Continuity Camera with iPhone 12 and later)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Safari and Passwords</strong><br/>
- Profiles keep your browsing separate for topics like work and personal, separating your history, cookies, extensions, Tab Groups, and favorites<br/>
- Web apps let you use any website like an app, complete with an icon in the Dock for faster access and a simplified toolbar for easier browsing<br/>
- Enhanced Private Browsing locks your private browsing windows when you’re not using them, blocks known trackers from loading, and removes tracking that identifies you from URLs<br/>
- Password and passkey sharing allows you to easily share accounts with trusted contacts<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Messages</strong><br/>
- Live Stickers sync from iOS and iPadOS to macOS, giving you access to the Live Stickers you create on your iPhone and iPad<br/>
- Search filters for people, keywords, and content types like photos or links help you more easily find what you are looking for<br/>
- Swipe to reply inline on any iMessage bubble<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Gaming</strong><br/>
- Game Mode gives games the highest priority on the CPU and GPU, delivering more consistent frame rates and lower latency to wireless controllers and AirPods (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Keyboard</strong><br/>
- Improved autocorrect accuracy makes typing even easier by leveraging a more powerful transformer-based language model<br/>
- Inline predictive text shows single- and multi-word predictions that you can add by pressing the Space bar<br/>
- Improved Dictation experience supports using your voice and keyboard together to enter and edit text<br/>
<br/>
<strong>AirPods</strong><br/>
- Adaptive Audio delivers a new listening mode that dynamically blends Active Noise Cancellation and Transparency to tailor the noise control experience based on the conditions of your environment (AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Personalized Volume adjusts the volume of your media in response to your environment and listening preferences over time (AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Conversation Awareness lowers your media volume and enhances the voices of the people in front of the user, all while reducing background noise (AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Press to mute and unmute your microphone by pressing the AirPods stem or the Digital Crown on AirPods Max when on a call (AirPods (3rd generation), AirPods Pro (1st and 2nd generation), or AirPods Max with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Improved AirPods automatic switching now detects Mac up to 2X faster (AirPods (2nd and 3rd generation), AirPods Pro (1st and 2nd generation), AirPods Max with the latest firmware)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Privacy</strong><br/>
- Sensitive Content Warnings can be enabled to help prevent users from unexpectedly viewing sensitive images in Messages<br/>
- Expanded Communication Safety protections for children now detect videos containing nudity in addition to photos shared through Messages and the system Photos picker<br/>
- Improved sharing permissions let you choose which photos to share and add calendar events without providing access to your entire photo library or calendar<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>
- Live Speech lets you type what you want to say and reads it aloud in FaceTime calls or in-person conversations<br/>
- Personal Voice helps users at risk of speech loss create a voice that sounds like them in a private and secure way using on-device machine learning<br/>
- Made for iPhone compatible hearing devices can be paired and used with Mac (MacBook Pro (2021), Mac Studio (2022), and Mac computers with M2 chip)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This release also includes other features and improvements:</strong><br/>
- One-Time verification code AutoFill from Mail helps you quickly sign into sites in Safari, without leaving the browser<br/>
- Inline PDFs and document scans in Notes are presented full-width making them easy to view<br/>
- Grocery Lists in Reminders automatically group related items into sections as you add them<br/>
- Visual Look Up for recipes helps you find similar dishes from photo<br/>
- Visual Look Up in video helps you learn about objects that appear in paused video frames<br/>
- Pets in the People album in Photos surfaces individual pets just like friends or family members<br/>
- Option to say "Siri" in addition to "Hey Siri" for a more natural way to activate Siri (Mac with Apple silicon, AirPods Pro (2nd generation))<br/>
- High performance mode in Screen Sharing supports color workflows and improves responsiveness while remotely accessing a Mac (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
- Item sharing in Find My allows you to share an AirTag with up to five other people<br/>
- Activity History in Home displays a recent history of events for door locks, garage doors, security systems, and contact sensors<br/>
- Battery health management updated on 13-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip to better optimize long term battery health<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices.</blockquote>macOS Sonoma should be released at approximately 10 a.m. Pacific Time / 1 p.m. Eastern Time on Tuesday. Once the update is available, it can be installed from the System Settings app under General → Software Update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/macos-sonoma-launch-date-and-features/">macOS Sonoma Launching This Week With These New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-launching-this-week-with-these-new-features.2404446/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 17, iPhone 15, and New Apple Watches Released</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/23/top-stories-iphone-15-release/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-17-iphone-15-and-new-apple-watches-released.2404142/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/23/top-stories-iphone-15-release/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There may not have been a media event this week, but that doesn't mean things weren't incredibly busy in the Apple world. The week kicked off with the official release of iOS 17 and related updates, and then there was a daily trickle of media reviews for all of the incoming new hardware.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/top-stories-23sep2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913305" /><br/>
It all culminated with Friday's launch of the iPhone 15 lineup, Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 models, and the tweaked AirPods Pro with USB-C case. There's been lots to unpack with all of this, so read on for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17 Features: The Ultimate Mega Guide</h2><br/>
Following over three months of beta testing, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-ios-17/">iOS 17 was released</a> on Monday for the iPhone XS and newer. The free software update includes a wide range of new features and changes, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-ultimate-guide/">check out our iOS 17 mega guide for our comprehensive coverage of everything new</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17-Ultimate-Guide-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912151" /><br/>
Apple also released iPadOS 17, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-tvos-17/">tvOS 17</a>, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/macos-sonoma-official-release-date-announced/">macOS Sonoma will be released on Tuesday</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Just Install iOS 17? Here's 12 Things to Do First</h2><br/>
After installing iOS 17 on your iPhone, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-things-to-do-first/">check out our list of 12 things to do first</a> in order to take full advantage of the update's key new features and configure some of the new settings that are available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Just-Install-iOS-17-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912098" /><br/>
We've also rounded up some popular iPhone and Apple Watch apps that have already been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/ios-17-interactive-widget-list/">updated with support for interactive Home Screen widgets</a> and some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/ios-17-watchos-10-apps/">other new iOS 17 and watchOS 10 features</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Pro Reviews: Improvements Go Beyond USB-C</h2><br/>
The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/iphone-15-orders-nz-australia/">iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are here</a>! Ahead of Friday's launch, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/iphone-15-pro/">first reviews of the devices were shared</a> by select media outlets and YouTube channels. Make sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-unboxing/">unboxing and early hands-on video</a>, as well as our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/five-reasons-to-buy-iphone-15-pro-max/">top five reasons why you might want to opt for the iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> at the top of the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Max-5-Best-Features-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912998" /><br/>
We've also rounded up early <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/iphone-15/">reviews of the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2</a>, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/airpods-pro-usb-c/">updated AirPods Pro</a> with a USB-C charging case.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Warning: Update Your iPhone 15 to iOS 17.0.2 Before Transferring Data From Another iPhone</h2><br/>
If you are just unboxing an iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, or iPhone 15 Pro Max, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/warning-update-your-iphone-15-to-ios-17-0-2/">make sure to update the device to iOS 17.0.2</a> before transferring data to the device from another iPhone, or else you might encounter issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Update-Your-iPhone-15-to-iOS-17.0.2-Before-Transferring-Data-From-Another-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913145" /><br/>
An update notice screen appears early in the setup process, but don't skip this step or you might find your brand-new iPhone 15 stuck on the Apple logo screen and you'll have to connect it to a computer to restore it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Pro vs. 15 Pro Max Buyer's Guide: 10 Differences Compared</h2><br/>
Over the past week, we have been sharing a series of Buyer's Guides to help customers with their purchasing decisions, including one for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-15-pro-max/">iPhone 15 Pro vs. the iPhone 15 Pro Max that compares 10 major differences</a> between the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-vs-15-Pro-Max-Buyers-Guide.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912383" /><br/>
We've also shared guides for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-ultra-2/">Apple Watch Series 9 vs. Ultra 2</a>, and more, all of which are listed on the <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/">MacRumors Buyer's Guide page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Models Feature New Setting to Strictly Prevent Charging Beyond 80%</h2><br/>
All of the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/iphone-15-80-percent-battery-limit-option/">new battery health setting that prevents the devices from charging beyond 80%</a> at all times.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
This new setting is separate from Apple's pre-existing Optimized Battery Charging feature, which merely delays charging beyond 80% until a better time based on the device's daily charging routine. <br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 models also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-shows-battery-cycle-count/">show the battery's cycle count in the Settings app</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Use All the New AirPods Pro Features in iOS 17</h2><br/>
iOS 17 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-airpods/">adds several features to all second-generation AirPods Pro</a>, including Adaptive Audio, Conversation Awareness, and Personalized Volume, and we've <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/new-airpods-pro-features-ios-17-how-to-use/">explained how to use all of them</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/airpods-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888167" /><br/>
Keep in mind that these software features are also available on the original second-generation AirPods Pro released in September 2022, so there is no need to update to the new USB-C model to use them.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/sep-21-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/23/top-stories-iphone-15-release/">Top Stories: iOS 17, iPhone 15, and New Apple Watches Released</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-17-iphone-15-and-new-apple-watches-released.2404142/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Can Now Repair Bottom Microphone on iPhone 15 and 15 Plus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/apple-can-repair-iphone-15-bottom-microphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-can-now-repair-bottom-microphone-on-iphone-15-and-15-plus.2403993/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 15:56:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/apple-can-repair-iphone-15-bottom-microphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>Apple Authorized Service Providers</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers are able to individually repair the bottom-right microphone on the lower-end iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus, according to information obtained by <em>MacRumors</em> today from multiple sources.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
The new procedure of replacing this microphone on its own should make these repairs cheaper for customers, and also less wasteful, as part of Apple's focus on environmental responsibility. As for the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max, and other iPhone models, repairing this microphone still requires replacing the entire mid-frame chassis. <br/>
<br/>
For repairs of all other microphones on iPhones, including next to the earpiece and rear camera, a mid-frame replacement is still required.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aasp/">Apple Authorized Service Providers</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/apple-can-repair-iphone-15-bottom-microphone/">Apple Can Now Repair Bottom Microphone on iPhone 15 and 15 Plus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-can-now-repair-bottom-microphone-on-iphone-15-and-15-plus.2403993/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Baldur&#039;s Gate 3 Now Available on Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/baldurs-gate-3-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/baldurs-gate-3-now-available-on-mac.2403977/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:41:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/baldurs-gate-3-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular new roleplaying game Baldur's Gate 3 is available to play on the Mac starting today. The title can be downloaded <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/">through the Steam platform</a> and it is playable on Apple silicon Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Baldur's Gate 3: Launch Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XuCfkgaaa08" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The game's minimum requirements include the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> processor and 8GB RAM, but the recommended requirements suggest an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-pro/">M1 Pro</a> or better Apple silicon chip and at least 16GB RAM. With the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip, the game can be run on low to medium settings, but the recommended requirements support high or ultra settings.<br/>
<br/>
Baldur's Gate 3 was initially released on Windows in August, and it is the third game in the Baldur's Gate series. Players can choose one of six pre-made characters or create a custom character to play. The game is set in the Dungeons &amp; Dragons universe, and it uses turn-based combat.<br/>
<br/>
There are 12 classes and 11 races to choose from, along with options to play solo or online with up to four people.<br/>
<blockquote>Gather your party and return to the Forgotten Realms in a tale of fellowship and betrayal, sacrifice and survival, and the lure of absolute power. Mysterious abilities are awakening inside you, drawn from a mind flayer parasite planted in your brain. Resist, and turn darkness against itself. Or embrace corruption, and become ultimate evil.</blockquote><br/>
Baldur's Gate 3 has received almost universally positive reviews, and it is <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/">available from Steam</a> for &#36;60.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/baldurs-gate-3-mac/">Baldur&#039;s Gate 3 Now Available on Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/baldurs-gate-3-now-available-on-mac.2403977/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Models Support USB-C to Ethernet for Faster Internet Speeds</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-usb-c-to-ethernet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-support-usb-c-to-ethernet-for-faster-internet-speeds.2403975/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:26:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-usb-c-to-ethernet/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the launch of the iPhone 15 series today, a few readers of our website have reached out to highlight that the devices support USB-C to Ethernet adapters, allowing for a wired internet connection with faster download speeds than Wi-Fi.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Ethernet.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913342" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>iPhone 15 Pro connected to an Ethernet cable via <a href="https://www.prndlcars.com/">former MacRumors editor turned car reviewer Jordan Golson</a></em></div><br/>
Apple confirmed this information in a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213839">support document</a> last week, with USB to Ethernet adapters listed as compatible with iPhone 15 models. When an iPhone is connected to an Ethernet cable, an otherwise hidden Ethernet menu appears in the Settings app with IP-related information and various configuration options.<br/>
<br/>
One reader informed us that their iPhone 15 Pro connected to Ethernet achieved a peak download speed of over 800 Mbps in a speed test.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Ethernet-Setting.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913346" /><br/>
While this is one of the various clever ways that the USB-C port on the iPhone 15 models can be used, it should be known that previous iPhones with the Lightning connector also supported Ethernet with an adapter. Nevertheless, we have decided to highlight this information as a helpful tip since it is getting attention.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models launched today in the U.S. and more than 40 other countries.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-usb-c-to-ethernet/">iPhone 15 Models Support USB-C to Ethernet for Faster Internet Speeds</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-support-usb-c-to-ethernet-for-faster-internet-speeds.2403975/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Gets Closer Look at Apple&#039;s Maligned FineWoven iPhone 15 Case With Teardown</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/ifixit-finewoven-case-teardown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-gets-closer-look-at-apples-maligned-finewoven-iphone-15-case-with-teardown.2403945/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 12:49:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/ifixit-finewoven-case-teardown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and 15 Pro, Apple introduced a new case material called "FineWoven" as an alternative to leather, and unfortunately, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">it has not proven popular</a> with some customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/ifixit-finewoven-case.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913311" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Image of FineWoven case under microscope from iFixit</div></em><br/>
Given the criticism of the FineWoven case, teardown site <em>iFixit</em> obtained one of the accessories and decided <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/82789/unweaving-the-mystery-apples-finewoven-case-under-the-microscope">to take it apart</a> to get a closer look.<br/>
<br/>
Using a digital microscope, iFixit viewed the FineWoven fabric at 52x and 490x magnification, confirming that it is indeed made up of bundles of tightly woven fibers. Each fiber is much smaller than a strand of hair, measuring in at about six microns thick.<br/>
<br/>
Groups of the individual fibers make up threads that are around 150 microns thick, and iFixit says the microtwill material that Apple is using is not too far off from high-end jackets from companies like Patagonia and Arc'teryx.<br/>
<br/>
When the FineWoven fabric is scratched, the fibers don't break, but the scratch does cause the affected fibers to reflect light irregularly, which means there's a visual mark. The softness of the material also means that items in the pocket with the case can leave an indentation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-finewoven-cases.jpg" alt="" width="2839" height="1177" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910359" /><br/>
Because the FineWoven case is made from fabric, it did stain when exposed to hot sauce and oil, though it was able to resist coffee. When exposed to certain foods or liquids, FineWoven case owners can expect to see the case become stained, and iFixit wasn't able to get the oil or the hot sauce stain out.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit cut the case open to see how it was assembled. The FineWoven fabric is on the outside, with a gray foam inside. Beyond the gray foam, there's a rigid plastic sheet, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> hardware, white foam, another rigid plastic sheet, and an inner layer of FineWoven fabric. All of the layers are thin, and the FineWoven fabric itself is about 0.17mm.<br/>
<br/>
The sides of the case feature the same FineWoven fabric that appears to have been coated in a resin-like material, producing a hard, non-porous surface.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit suggests that those with FineWoven cases protect it with a Durable Water Repellent spray to make the case more resistant to staining and liquid.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/ifixit-finewoven-case-teardown/">iFixit Gets Closer Look at Apple&#039;s Maligned FineWoven iPhone 15 Case With Teardown</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-gets-closer-look-at-apples-maligned-finewoven-iphone-15-case-with-teardown.2403945/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Video: iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Unboxing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-unboxing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-unboxing.2403904/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 11:05:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-unboxing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models are heading out to customers all over the world, including us here at <em>MacRumors</em>. Our videographer Dan Barbera just got his new iPhones in, and over on YouTube, he's unboxed the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ByhrcCcrng4" title="iPhone 15 &amp; iPhone 15 Pro: Unboxing &amp; Hands-On!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The blue and gray titanium models look fantastic with the new brushed finish, and to go along with them, Dan got the black &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. That model also has a sleek new look thanks to the frosted glass back.<br/>
<br/>
The more contoured corners of the new devices make them more comfortable to hold, and the weight reduction for the 15 Pro models is definitely noticeable. As for the display, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; display is brighter than before in the sun, and for the 15 Pro and Pro Max, that slimmed down bezel looks great.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch Dan's video to get a first look at all of the new iPhones, and stay tuned because we'll have device comparisons, deep dives into the camera, and more content coming over the next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/iphone-15-unboxing/">Video: iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Unboxing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-unboxing.2403904/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: New AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Drop to &#36;199.99 Alongside iPhone 15 Accessory Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-22-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-new-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-drop-to-199-99-alongside-iphone-15-accessory-sales.2403898/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:36:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-22-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There were numerous great Apple-related deals over the past week, with our pick of the best being the new AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;199.99 at Amazon. This isn't the only brand new Apple product already getting a discount as you'll find out below, where we're tracking sales on both the Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0005.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847995" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C)</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913276" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;49 off the USB-C AirPods Pro 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/deals-new-airpods-pro-2/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C/MagSafe Case) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One of the biggest deals of the week came from Amazon, which already has &#36;49 off the all-new AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case. It's available for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/verizon-accessories-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913277" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take 23% off iPhone 15 accessory bundles</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fshop%2Fonline%2Fiphone-15-accessory-starter-kit%2F">Verizon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/verizon-20-off-cases-iphone-15/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fshop%2Fonline%2Fiphone-15-accessory-starter-kit%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">23% OFF</div>iPhone 15 Accessory Bundles</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anyone who has a new iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Pro arriving today should take a look at Verizon's accessory bundles. You can get an official Apple-made iPhone 15 case, 35W charger, and USB-C cable for &#36;99.97, down from &#36;127.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 1 & 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-watch-ultra-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913279" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;100 off Apple Watch Ultra (gen 1) and &#36;19 off Apple Watch Ultra 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT6Q8V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/deals-apple-watch-ultra-698/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT6Q8V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra for &#36;698.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;779.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With the launch of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 this week, we're tracking steep discounts on the original model at Amazon. You can get the Apple Watch ultra for as low as &#36;698.99, down from &#36;799.00. If you want the latest model, Amazon has it for &#36;779.99, down from &#36;799.00. For Apple Watch Series 9 shoppers, be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/deals-launch-day-discounts-apple-watch-9-ultra-2/">check out our full post</a> for even more deals.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/anker-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913280" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on USB-C accessories from Anker</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392060864">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/deals-anker-usb-c-batteries-chargers/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
We tracked quite a few Anker discounts this week, starting with ones on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/deals-anker-discounts-accessories/">Eufy Bluetooth trackers and Bluetooth speakers</a>, then focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/deals-anker-usb-c-batteries-chargers/">USB-C accessories for your new iPhone 15</a>. You'll find all of the best Anker discounts listed below, including deals on portable batteries, MagSafe chargers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392060864">3-Port Compact USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;47.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSGH355C%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392107984">6-in-1 USB-C Compact Power Strip</a> - &#36;93.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09VPHVT2Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695391997901">Power Bank 24,000 mAh with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392166960">Power Bank 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;110.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF_1695391752782">MagSafe Charger Stand</a> - &#36;119.96 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.95</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>15-Inch MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/15-inch-macbook-air-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913281" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;250 off 15-inch MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NTC96%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/deals-512gb-15-inch-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We saw a new all-time low price hit the 512GB 15-inch MacBook Air this week, now available for &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00. This is &#36;50 lower than the previous record low that we tracked consistently over the summer.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-22-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: New AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Drop to &#36;199.99 Alongside iPhone 15 Accessory Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-new-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-drop-to-199-99-alongside-iphone-15-accessory-sales.2403898/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iPhone 15 Features We&#039;re Excited About and Should You Upgrade?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-features-were-excited-about-and-should-you-upgrade.2403885/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 09:55:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/our-top-iphone-15-features-should-you-upgrade/id1602394741?i=1000628838273">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's new FineWoven accessories, some of our favorite <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> features, and who should consider upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/D3R79ycZ8xc?si=-aoz69Jj9C2ha3x4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple's FineWoven material replaces leather across <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> cases, AirTag accessories, and Apple Watch bands. Many early reviews of the FineWoven items <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">have been negative</a>, criticizing the material's feel, quality, and durability, so we talk over our early thoughts on the new accessories. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> introduce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro/">over 30 new capabilities and improvements</a>, including USB-C and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> across the lineup, as well as a new titanium design and Action button on the high-end models. We dive into some of our favorite standout features and weigh up who should consider upgrading to the latest devices.<br/>
<br/>
Listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> in <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvNjk1NTlmZTgtMzMxOC00ZDI5LTkyMmYtYWJlMTAwNjhjYTYzLzg1OTRmODNjLTBkN2QtNDhkOS04OTcxLWFkZmEwMTAzOWEzMS9kODA4NmM5Ni1iNmQ4LTRkNWMtYTZiMy1hZGZhMDEwM2M4NmQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M%3d">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player. Watch a video version of the show <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD8VmuL7qc7ii5uyjzSRk3UM7KI_c4qC5">on the <em>MacRumors</em> YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, take a look back at our discussion with iJustine where we talk through our immediate reactions to the announcement of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for more episodes, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/20/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-talks-iphone-14/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/09/iphone-14-event-reactions-with-luke-miani/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the show, and let us know what subjects you would like the podcast to cover in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-features/">The MacRumors Show: iPhone 15 Features We&#039;re Excited About and Should You Upgrade?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-features-were-excited-about-and-should-you-upgrade.2403885/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
