<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:02:40 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple Vision Pro Available Around the World</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/the-macrumors-show-vision-pro-international-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-available-around-the-world.2430285/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:07:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/the-macrumors-show-vision-pro-international-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/apodcast/apple-vision-pro-goes-international/id1602394741?i=1000660560162">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the international rollout of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> and the new Beats Pill Bluetooth speaker.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nHIHVFV6D_c?si=b_0lsCadRx90X6WU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple's Vision Pro headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/">now available</a> to pre-order in Australia, Canada, France, Germany, and the United Kingdom, with availability beginning Friday, July 12. The device also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/">launched today</a> in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore. It has been available in the United States since February. We discuss key considerations when buying the Vision Pro, such as storage configurations and accessories, as well as the significance of the device's long-awaited rollout around the world. We also look to the future with Apple's rumored low-cost Vision headset, which may <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/cheaper-apple-vision-pro-tethered-iphone-mac/">rely on a tethered iPhone</a> for processing power to reduce costs. <br/>
<br/>
In addition, we discuss Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">new Beats Pill Bluetooth speaker</a>, featuring a completely redesigned speaker system consisting of a single tweeter and a single racetrack woofer, a removable lanyard, USB-C and Bluetooth connectivity, 24 hours of battery life, and IP67 water and sweat resistance. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple Intelligence, the apparent suspension of work on the second-generation Vision Pro headset, and Apple's rumored plans to move to thinner device designs.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/the-macrumors-show-vision-pro-international-launch/">The MacRumors Show: Apple Vision Pro Available Around the World</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-available-around-the-world.2430285/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Alogic&#039;s Echelon Series Delivers Budget-Friendly Keyboard and Mouse Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alogics-echelon-series-delivers-budget-friendly-keyboard-and-mouse-accessories.2430283/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:01:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse&#038;post_date=1719604919/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Alogic</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Accessory company <a href="https://alogic.co/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic</a> recently launched a few new input devices with Mac support as part of its Echelon series, and I've been spending some time testing out the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-keyboard-for-macos/?ref=y2uwzwu">USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Keyboard for macOS</a> and the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-mouse-white/?ref=y2uwzwu">USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Mouse</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957182" /><br/>
The Echelon series is a budget-friendly line of accessories, seeking to offer a mid-range feature set at value pricing, and the mouse and keyboard do just that. The keyboard is priced at &#36;59.99 and the mouse at &#36;24.99, with Alogic frequently running promotional discounts of around 20% to bring prices down even further.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Keyboard for macOS</h2><br/>
<a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-keyboard-for-macos/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic's keyboard</a> offers a full-size 109-key layout with function row and number pad. The membrane-style keyboard with chiclet keys has some similarities to Apple's Magic Keyboard for Mac, though you obviously don't have an option for an integrated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> key with Alogic's offering. I've found the keys to be well spaced to allow for smooth typing, and have not experienced any problems with missing keystrokes, double letters, or other issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-keyboard-front.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957186" /><br/>
The Echelon keyboard offers a traditional extended keyboard layout, optimized for Mac with key arrangement and labels such as Command. The function keys in the top row include most of the usual Mac-specific functions such as display brightness controls, Spotlight, Mission Control, Launchpad, media playback controls, mute, volume controls, and even one to jump straight to your home folder when you're in Finder. There's also a dedicated system sleep key in that top row. In the bottom row, there's another dedicated key that will open up your Downloads folder when Finder is active. <br/>
<br/>
At the far right of the keyboard is the number pad, which includes the usual layout of number and arithmetic keys, plus a top row that serves double duty for switching among paired devices and as dedicated keys for select all, cut, copy, and paste.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-keyboard-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957224" /><br/>
Unlike Apple's Magic Keyboard which inexplicably still uses Lightning to charge, Alogic's Echelon keyboard charges over USB-C, and a white braided USB-C to USB-C cable is included in the box. Alogic says the battery lasts "weeks" between charges, but the battery level on my unit has barely dropped at all after several days of heavy usage, so I'm expecting charge intervals to be on the order of a couple of months, similar to what I see with the Magic Keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that Alogic's keyboard goes to sleep within a few minutes of going idle, even if the computer it's connected to remains active, and you'll need to hit a key on it and wait a beat for the keyboard to wake up before you can begin typing. That took a little getting used to for me given my long-term experience with the Magic Keyboard that pretty much always seems to be ready to go.<br/>
<br/>
The Alogic keyboard easily connects to Apple devices over Bluetooth using the standard pairing steps, with support for both Bluetooth 3.0 and Bluetooth 5.0 included. One distinct advantage compared to Apple's Magic Keyboard is that the Echelon supports connections to up to three devices, so you can pair it to your Mac, your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and even another device and easily switch between those devices with a key combo.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, I've found Alogic's Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Keyboard for macOS to be a solid budget keyboard, with a slim profile, a solid typing experience, and a nice set of key functions. The matte white plastic is a clean look that complements the Apple aesthetic, though I'll have to see how well it holds up to picking up dirt and stains over time. I do miss having &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; right on my external keyboard, but if that's not a deal-breaker for you, this keyboard might be worth a look. It's <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-keyboard-for-macos/?ref=y2uwzwu">normally priced at &#36;59.99</a>, but an Independence Day sale going on now knocks the price down to &#36;48.00 with promo code ID20.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Mouse </h2><br/>
<a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-mouse-white/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic's new mouse</a> is a well-matched complement to the Echelon keyboard, coming in the same matte white plastic. It's an ambidextrous mouse, so it's a simple matter of switching between left and right hands in macOS settings, though it's not as ergonomic as a handed mouse.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957183" /><br/>
The Echelon mouse includes the standard left and right mouse buttons and a scroll wheel in between them. The scroll wheel can also be pressed to act as a middle mouse button, but that's it as far as input options on this mouse. There are no additional side or thumb buttons, so if those are something that's become part of your workflow, this mouse isn't for you, at least as an everyday mouse.<br/>
<br/>
The left and right mouse buttons have relatively quiet clicks, which I tend to like, but the middle scroll wheel button is quite loud. Fortunately, that one isn't needed nearly as often so it's not a significant issue. The scroll wheel has well-defined clicks as you scroll to help you feel the movement, but there's no inertial free-spinning capability for quickly scrolling long pages or documents as I have come to appreciate on the Logitech MX Master 3 mouse that has been my daily driver for many years.<br/>
<br/>
At just &#36;24.99 for a wireless mouse, this is definitely a budget pick, and it does show in the overall experience, especially when you're used to a more powerful option. Alogic's Echelon mouse is extremely lightweight, and I find it glides best with some sort of desk pad or mat under it for a better feel, though it is certainly usable on a bare desk surface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-mouse-bottom.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957184" /><br/>
Alogic's Echelon mouse supports both Bluetooth 3.0 and Bluetooth 5.0, and it easily connects to a Mac or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; using the system settings, but the mouse also supports 2.4GHz connections that can deliver improved performance such as lower latency. That 2.4GHz support comes via a small USB-A dongle that conveniently fits into the underside of the mouse when not in use so you don't lose it. Of course, most modern Macs don't include any USB-A ports, but I typically use my MacBook Pro in a desk setup with a Thunderbolt dock that does include some USB-A ports, and the mouse connects fine via the dongle that way. Regardless, most users will likely opt for a Bluetooth connection given the simplicity.<br/>
<br/>
As with the Echelon keyboard, the mouse goes to sleep after just a few minutes of inactivity, which can be a bit disconcerting when returning to my Mac after a short break. I use a total of three displays in my desk setup, so when I sit down at my desk I usually give my mouse a quick shake to locate my pointer. With this Echelon mouse, the pointer doesn't move if the mouse has gone to sleep, so I have to first click once to wake it up before I shake it, which runs the risk of an inadvertent click if it the mouse hadn't been idle long enough to go to sleep. It's possible I'd get used to this over time, but so far I still find it a bit annoying.<br/>
<br/>
As with most sensible wireless mice (sorry, Apple), the Echelon mouse charges via a USB-C port on the front, meaning it can still be used while it's charging. A white braided USB-C to USB-C cable is included in the box for charging purposes. Alogic says a charge should last two to three weeks with typical office usage, although I haven't been using it long enough to fully test those numbers. But given the small drop in charge I've seen in a few days of use, it seems reasonable, and perhaps even conservative, to me. Alogic indicates it takes about an hour to fully recharge the mouse.<br/>
<br/>
The Echelon mouse can be paired with up to three devices simultaneously, two via Bluetooth and one via the 2.4GHz USB dongle. A small connection button on the bottom of the mouse is used for pairing and cycling through the connected devices. There's also an on/off switch on the bottom to conserve battery life and prevent unintended inputs.<br/>
<br/>
Coming from a more powerful Logitech mouse, I can safely say that Alogic's Echelon mouse isn't going to become a full-time part of my setup. But at its budget price, it's potentially a solid option for tossing in a computer bag to use while on the go. While it doesn't include more advanced features, it does offer the basic mouse buttons and a scroll wheel and can pair to multiple devices, and that's all many users may be looking for. The <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-mouse-white/?ref=y2uwzwu">Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Mouse is normally priced at &#36;24.99</a>, but the Independence Day sale with promo code ID20 brings the price down to just &#36;20.00.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: Alogic provided MacRumors with the Echelon keyboard and mouse for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Alogic. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/alogic/">Alogic</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse/">Alogic&#039;s Echelon Series Delivers Budget-Friendly Keyboard and Mouse Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alogics-echelon-series-delivers-budget-friendly-keyboard-and-mouse-accessories.2430283/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-grid-studio-june/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2430280/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 09:32:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-grid-studio-june/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with GRID Studio to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 256GB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>. GRID Studio is well known for transforming old, discarded Apple devices into displayable artwork.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/grid-studio-iphone-2g.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957241" /><br/>
GRID Studio deconstructs Apple devices and artfully arranges the components underneath a glass frame. Each part is labeled and accompanied by relevant historical details. GRID Studio's most iconic piece <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">is the GRID 1</a>, priced at &#36;400.<br/>
<br/>
The GRID 1 features the original Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from 2007, highlighting the parts that made up an important part of Apple's history. The iconic original ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ casing is positioned next to the power button, headphone socket, speaker, logic board, ear piece, and other components, and this is before the days where Apple started making its own chips so there are some unique components to see.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Grid-1st-gen.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934263" /><br/>
iPod fans will be interested in the <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-ipod-photo">&#36;120 GRID iPod Photo</a>, which originally came out in 2004, and was the first iPod featuring a color display. It has the same classic click wheel design, but with a 220x176 LCD display. This model is a fun part of Apple's past because it was the first iPod that really supported storing and showing off photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/grid-studio-ipod-photo.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957243" /><br/>
Most of GRID Studio's pieces are designed to be hung on the wall, but there are also a selection of products that can be displayed on a shelf or tabletop. The &#36;99 <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-3gs-wooden-tabletop-frames">GRID 3GS Wooden Tabletop Frame</a> has an attractive wood backing and acrylic cover that can be hung on the wall or displayed upright on a table with a support rod.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/grid-studio-iphone-3GS.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957244" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 3GS followed the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 3G, and that "S" was meant to represent speed. It had a processor that was twice as fast, and was Apple's first foray into really focusing on blazing fast performance. The GRID 3GS features the classic pre-iPhone 4 design, and it looks great in the wooden frame.<br/>
<br/>
GRID Studio is <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/pages/summersale">hosting a summer sale</a> that will last until July 17, and various GRID pieces are available at up to 50 percent off.<br/>
<br/>
We have one 256GB &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; to give away to a <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/aAdHs/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (June 28) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on July 5. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after July 5 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-grid-studio-june/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2430280/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Planning to Debut New Battery Replacement Method With iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-planning-to-debut-new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16.2430273/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:38:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on technology to simplify <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> battery replacement that could debut later this year, <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-explores-novel-method-for-making-iphone-batteries-more-replaceable"><em>The Information</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-battery-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1333" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-923492" /><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/"><em>Alleged iPhone 16 Pro battery</a> with new metal casing.</em></div><br/>
The move comes in response to a new EU law requiring smartphone manufacturers to ensure batteries can be replaced by owners using easily accessible tools by 2025. According to sources involved in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s manufacturing process, Apple is exploring the use of electrically induced adhesive debonding technology to achieve this.<br/>
<br/>
The current method of replacing an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery is challenging and involves removing adhesive strips with tweezers. If these strips break during the process, additional steps involving heat or solvents are necessary to dislodge the adhesive. After removing the old battery, a tray and specialized machine are required to install a new one securely. <br/>
<br/>
In contrast, the new technology Apple is testing involves encasing the battery in metal rather than black foil. Alleged images of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">iPhone 16 Pro battery with a metal casing</a> leaked earlier this year. By applying a low voltage of electricity, the new battery can be quickly dislodged from the chassis. Despite this advancement, consumers will still need to open the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; themselves, which remains complicated due to the use of adhesives and screws to keep the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s display in place and retain water resistance. <br/>
<br/>
This new battery replacement method is anticipated to debut in at least one <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> model later this year and could be extended to all versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> next year. Apple is expected to continue recommending that users seek professional assistance for battery replacements, given the complexities and potential risks associated with the procedure.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may be exempt from the EU's legislation requiring consumer-friendly battery replacement if its devices meet certain criteria, such as retaining 83% of their capacity after 500 full charges and 80% after 1,000 full charges. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> meets the criteria for 1,000 charges, but earlier models do not meet the 500-charge requirement.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple has a history of offering devices that are challenging to repair due to their tightly sealed designs which enhance water resistance and durability, the company has taken steps to address these concerns by introducing self-repair options and making diagnostic tools available in recent years.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/">Report: Apple Planning to Debut New Battery Replacement Method With iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-planning-to-debut-new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16.2430273/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Best Buy Has Big MacBook Discounts During Its Prime Day-Like Sale, Plus AirTag Deals and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-28-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-best-buy-has-big-macbook-discounts-during-its-prime-day-like-sale-plus-airtag-deals-and-more.2430272/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:30:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-28-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy's Prime Day-like sale is the headline of this week's best Apple deals, featuring up to &#36;400 off the 16-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro and other MacBook discounts. Additionally, this week you'll find great sales on AirTag, Apple Pencil Pro, and Anker accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0007.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847997" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best Buy Member Deals Days</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macbook-pro-16-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957121" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Members can save sitewide at Best Buy this weekend</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/best-buy-member-deals-days/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE SALE</div>Best Buy Member Deals Days</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's "Member Deals Days" sale kicked off this week, and it will run all weekend. Only My Best Buy Plus and Total members can save during this event, which includes notable discounts on Apple products, PCs, smart home products, video games, TVs, and more. In terms of Apple products, the best deals available during this event are on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air and 16-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro, with up to &#36;400 in savings on these computers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bluetooth Trackers</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airtag-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957120" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on AirTag and Eufy SmartTrack Card</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%2Fref%3Dfs_a_md_0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;78.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1719408239814"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Bluetooth tracker discounts were in abundance this week, and you can still get some of the best discounts today on Amazon. The AirTag 1 Pack is on sale for &#36;24.99, down from &#36;29.00, the AirTag 4 Pack is available for &#36;78.99, down from &#36;99.00, and the Eufy SmartTrack Card is discounted to &#36;19.99, down from &#36;29.99.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957118" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;10 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Last week we saw the Apple Pencil Pro drop to a new record low price of &#36;119.00 on Amazon, and this &#36;10 discount is still available this week. Although only a &#36;10 discount, this is still the best deal we've seen to date on the newest Apple Pencil. For more savings, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.99</a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/anker-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957119" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1719241439861">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/amazons-new-sale-anker/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1719241439861"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;15 OFF</div>MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station for &#36;84.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving to Anker's charging accessories, you can get multiple MagSafe-compatible devices at a discount this week on Amazon, like a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1718896305471">portable battery</a> and a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1718896354198">wireless charging station</a>. The highlight of the sale is Anker's 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for &#36;109.99, down from &#36;149.99. Many of these will require you to clip an on-page coupon before you head to the checkout screen in order to see the sales.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1717512554052">MagGo Power Bank 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1717512037932">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;38.24 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;164.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;184.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;84.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1717513024737">MagGo 3-in-1 Folding Charging Station</a> - &#36;93.49, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;129.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/jackery-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957117" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Jackery accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L_1719241793961">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/amazons-new-sale-anker/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L_1719241793961"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Similar to the Anker discounts, Amazon this week introduced a new selection of markdowns on Jackery batteries and other accessories. Jackery is known for its reliable portable battery stations, and the best deal this time around can be found on the Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;229.99.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L_1719241793961">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;199.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3UJLIACLEUQIR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3UJLIACLEUQIR_1719242084580">Solar Generator 300 Plus</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_title">Expansion Battery Pack 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;549.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR_1719241929028">Expansion Battery Pack 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,259.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KGYEKIXRZ05H%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KGYEKIXRZ05H_1719242023321">Explorer 2000 Pro</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CMD7MC6V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1BZ0OGIME7Z68%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1BZ0OGIME7Z68_1719242095491">Explorer 3000 Pro</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR_1719241929027">Solar Generator 2000 Plus + Explorer 2000 Plus + Battery</a> - &#36;3,599.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-28-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Best Buy Has Big MacBook Discounts During Its Prime Day-Like Sale, Plus AirTag Deals and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-best-buy-has-big-macbook-discounts-during-its-prime-day-like-sale-plus-airtag-deals-and-more.2430272/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store Down in UK, Canada, and Other Countries Ahead of Vision Pro Pre-Orders [Update: It&#039;s Back Up]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-in-uk-canada-and-other-countries-ahead-of-vision-pro-pre-orders-update-its-back-up.2430261/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:56:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's online store went down this morning in Germany, France, Australia, the UK, and Canada, as the company prepared to begin taking <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> pre-orders in the five regions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-store-down-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="826" height="519" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957199" /><br/>
Pre-orders begin at 5.00 a.m. Pacific Time, or the following local times. The starting prices given below in local currency are for the 256GB model minus prescription lenses and other accessories.<br/>
<ul><li>Australia – 10:00 pm AEST – &#36;5,999 </li><br/>
<li>Canada – 5.00 a.m. PT – &#36;4,999</li><br/>
<li>France – 2.00 p.m. – €3,999</li><br/>
<li>Germany – 2.00 p.m. – €3,999</li><br/>
<li>United Kingdom – 1.00 p.m. – £3,499</li></ul>&zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; will launch in the five countries on Friday, July 12, and interested customers can currently book a 30-minute demo of the device in their local <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> from launch day up until Thursday, July 18. <br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro is unquestionably Apple's most technically advanced product and a remarkable engineering achievement that impresses at first glance. However, potential buyers should visit an &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; to try it out and thoroughly research its capabilities before making a purchase. Be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">dedicated Vision Pro roundup</a> to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to produce fewer than 400,000 Vision Pro headsets in 2024 due to the complexity of manufacturing, according to analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. However, Apple is said to be already working on a new version of the ‌&zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;‌ for 2025 that will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">priced more affordably</a>. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/">Apple Store Down in UK, Canada, and Other Countries Ahead of Vision Pro Pre-Orders [Update: It&#039;s Back Up]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-in-uk-canada-and-other-countries-ahead-of-vision-pro-pre-orders-update-its-back-up.2430261/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Launches in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-launches-in-china-hong-kong-japan-and-singapore.2430257/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:09:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro spatial computing headset today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/apple-vision-pro-arrives-in-china-mainland-hong-kong-japan-and-singapore/">arrived at Apple Store locations</a> across China mainland, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore. The launches mark the first time the Vision Pro has been officially available outside of the United States, where the device has been on sale since February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-availability-Wangfujing-Beijing-first-purchase.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957191" /><br/>
Consumer interest in the &#36;3,499 headset has reportedly waned at home, where sales are said to have slowed in the five months since its launch. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> is set to launch in the United Kingdom and Canada on July 12. <br/>
<br/>
The headset will also launch on the same day in Australia, France, and Germany, as part of a staggered release in additional markets, which may be just what the company needs to reinvigorate enthusiasm for the device.  <br/>
<br/>
Reviews for the device have been mixed overall. For the most part, users have been impressed with the hardware and the technology introduced by the Vision Pro, but there are questions about the actual function of the device, the intuitiveness of the gesture-based control, the weight and comfort, and VR in general.<br/>
<br/>
During WWDC earlier this month, Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, the first major update to the Vision Pro's operating system. &zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; includes several new features and changes, including a redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app with SharePlay support, the ability to turn existing 2D photos into spatial photos, a larger ultra-wide version of Mac Virtual Display that is equivalent to two 4K monitors side by side, plus support for a physical mouse.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/">Apple Vision Pro Launches in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-launches-in-china-hong-kong-japan-and-singapore.2430257/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung to Begin Rolling Out Hotel Room TVs With AirPlay Support for iPhone and iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/samsung-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-to-begin-rolling-out-hotel-room-tvs-with-airplay-support-for-iphone-and-ipad.2430238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:38:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/samsung-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>AirPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung today <a href="https://news.samsung.com/global/samsung-enhances-hotel-stays-with-apple-airplay-on-hospitality-tvs">announced</a> that it will be rolling out AirPlay support for its series of hotel room TVs, allowing iPhone and iPad users to wirelessly stream videos, music, photos, and more from their device to the TV in their room.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airplay-hotels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898340" /><br/>
The feature allows you to scan a unique QR code on the hotel room TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing you to wirelessly stream content from your iPhone or iPad. After the pairing process, your device will also automatically be connected to the hotel's Wi-Fi network. The device must be updated to iOS 17.3 or iPadOS 17.3 or later.<br/>
<br/>
AirPlay on hotel room TVs works with apps and services like Apple Music, Apple TV+, Apple Arcade for games, Apple Fitness+ for workouts, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung said no personal info is ever stored or saved for this AirPlay feature, and the paired device is automatically removed when you check out of the hotel.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung did not reveal which hotel chains will be offering its AirPlay-enabled TVs. The feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/ios-17-airplay-hotel-feature-now-available/">launched earlier this year</a> on LG hotel room TVs at select IHG Hotels & Resorts properties in the U.S., Canada, and Mexico, with more locations to follow.<br/>
<br/>
Google has long offered a similar Chromecast streaming feature on many hotel room TVs that works with both iPhones and Android devices.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/samsung-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">Samsung to Begin Rolling Out Hotel Room TVs With AirPlay Support for iPhone and iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-to-begin-rolling-out-hotel-room-tvs-with-airplay-support-for-iphone-and-ipad.2430238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the iPad Pro&#039;s Nano-Texture Glass - Is It Worth the Upgrade?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/ipad-nano-texture-glass-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-ipad-pros-nano-texture-glass-is-it-worth-the-upgrade.2430232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:39:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/ipad-nano-texture-glass-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models that Apple released earlier this year have a display upgrade option that allows you to purchase nano-texture display glass, which is supposed to cut down on glare.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gwSnEl4sVa0" title="11&quot; M4 iPad Pro Long Term Review: Nano-Texture Glass Worth it?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
We've already reviewed the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, but we thought we'd revisit the nano-texture glass upgrade to see if it's worth the purchase price.<br/>
<br/>
First introduced with the Pro Display XDR, nano-texture glass is etched at a nanometer scale, which is meant to preserve image quality while scattering ambient light to cut down on glare. It is the most matte display type that Apple makes, and Apple claims that it is useful for high-end, color-managed workflows or demanding ambient lighting environments.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with nano-texture as an option, and it's previously been reserved for the Studio Display and Pro Display XDR. Nano-texture is a premium feature, so it costs an additional &#36;100 over the standard glass. It's also only available on 1TB or 2TB &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, so you do need to shell out at least &#36;1,600 to get it on the 1TB 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Nano-texture on the larger &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will cost at least &#36;1,999, which is the price of the 1TB model plus an extra &#36;100 for the glass upgrade. It is an upgrade targeted at pro users and those with specific needs, and not everyone is going to want to opt for the matte design. The grippier texture of the nano-glass does feel better for writing on with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, but if that's a factor for you, you're better off checking out something like <a href="https://shop.astropad.com/products/rock-paper-pencil">Astropad's Rock Paper Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While nano-texture does a good job cutting down on glare, it does impact the contrast and crispness of the display, so it is serving a specific purpose for select workflows where mitigating light is important.<br/>
<br/>
As with the nano-texture versions of Apple's displays, the nano-texture &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; requires some special care. Apple recommends only cleaning it with the polishing cloth that's included in the box as other cleaning cloths can cause damage.<br/>
<br/>
Given the caveats and the high price tag, the nano-texture display isn't for everyone, but it is a good option for those who know they need extra help addressing glare.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/ipad-nano-texture-glass-hands-on/">Hands-On With the iPad Pro&#039;s Nano-Texture Glass - Is It Worth the Upgrade?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-ipad-pros-nano-texture-glass-is-it-worth-the-upgrade.2430232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s &#039;Member Deals Days&#039; Sale Introduces Low Prices on MacBooks and Much More Exclusively for Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/best-buy-member-deals-days/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-member-deals-days-sale-introduces-low-prices-on-macbooks-and-much-more-exclusively-for-members.2430215/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 07:18:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/best-buy-member-deals-days/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy has opened up a new "<a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2">Member Deals Days</a>" sale, featuring thousands of discounts available exclusively to My Best Buy Plus and Total members. New deals will appear every day of the event, which ends this Sunday, June 30.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macbook-air-and-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957103" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In order to gain access to these deals, you'll need to be a My Best Buy Plus or Total member. These services are <a href="https://howl.me/cmydl3lgN7m">available starting at &#36;49.99 per year</a>, and offer free two-day shipping, an extended 60-day return window on most products, exclusive access to certain sales like Member Deals Days, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE SALE</div>Best Buy Member Deals Days</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In terms of Apple products, the best deals available during this event are on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air. You can get the 256GB model for <a href="https://howl.me/cmydqPtY0P8"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> and the 512GB model for <a href="https://howl.me/cmydqmASWxo"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;150 off original prices and solid second-best discounts.<br/>
<br/>
There are also a few noteworthy 16-inch MacBook Pro discounts at Best Buy this week. The retailer has the 12-Core M3 Pro/18GB RAM/512GB model for <a href="https://howl.me/cmydwcE4wk7"><strong>&#36;2,149.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;2,499.00, and the 12-Core M3 Pro/36GB RAM/512GB model for <a href="https://howl.me/cmydwxr4Noa"><strong>&#36;2,499.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;2,899.00. These are both all-time low prices on the 16-inch MacBook Pro, and although Best Buy has more MacBook Pro discounts during its new sale, these are the best you'll find.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, the <a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2">Member Deals Days sale</a> has many discounts other than Apple products, including TVs, video games, PCs, headphones, home appliances, and more. Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/best-buy-member-deals-days/">Best Buy&#039;s &#039;Member Deals Days&#039; Sale Introduces Low Prices on MacBooks and Much More Exclusively for Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-member-deals-days-sale-introduces-low-prices-on-macbooks-and-much-more-exclusively-for-members.2430215/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>International Roaming Outage Affecting Verizon, AT&amp;T, T-Mobile Customers [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/verizon-international-roaming-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/international-roaming-outage-affecting-verizon-at-t-t-mobile-customers-updated.2430204/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:49:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/verizon-international-roaming-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Verizon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There appears to be an ongoing outage with international roaming across multiple cellular networks, with Verizon, AT&T, and T-Mobile customers abroad complaining about the issue on <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/verizon/">social networks</a> and <a href="https://community.verizon.com">cellular community forums</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/verizon.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957071" /><br/>
Customers traveling internationally have been without service since late Wednesday for hours at a time, with many losing cellular, text, and data. That has left many users unable to call their cellular provider hotline or access online chat help without a Wi-Fi network. <br/>
<br/>
Based on feedback from customers that have managed to contact support, the providers are aware of the issue with international roaming and are actively working on resolving it, although there have been reports that this could take several hours. We'll update this article as soon as we learn more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Does anyone else have <a href="https://twitter.com/Verizon?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Verizon</a> and overseas?? Everyone I’m with phone just fully stopped working… anyone else??</p>&mdash; Patrick Schwarzenegger (@PSchwarzenegger) <a href="https://twitter.com/PSchwarzenegger/status/1806204088205631845?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<strong>Update 1:</strong> There are reports that <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ATT/comments/1dpj9mb/international_data_roaming_not_working/">AT&T</a> and <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tmobile/comments/1dpbdl7/data_roaming_not_working_anymore/">T-Mobile</a> customers abroad are also being affected by the outage, suggesting it could be the result of a wider network problem. We have updated the story headline to reflect the development.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update 2: </strong><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-06-27/verizon-users-abroad-say-they-can-t-connect-to-mobile-network"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports that a Verizon customer service representative who was contacted from the UK on Thursday said that it's an ongoing issue that engineers are working to address.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update 3:</strong> The multi-network outage is related to issues at international connection partner <a href="https://www.syniverse.com">Syniverse</a>, according to a person familiar with the situation. The company says the estimated time of restoration is 12 hours up to 24 hours.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/verizon/">Verizon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/verizon-international-roaming-outage/">International Roaming Outage Affecting Verizon, AT&amp;T, T-Mobile Customers [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/international-roaming-outage-affecting-verizon-at-t-t-mobile-customers-updated.2430204/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Random Apple Pay Charges Affecting iPhone Users in Hungary</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-pay-hungary-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/random-apple-pay-charges-affecting-iphone-users-in-hungary.2430178/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:04:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-pay-hungary-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Hungary</category>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> is malfunctioning in Hungary, according <a href="https://index.hu/gazdasag/2024/06/26/fizetes-elofizetes-otp-bank-hiba-apple-pay-penz/">to reports</a> from several <a href="https://telex.hu/gazdasag/2024/06/26/apple-pay-levonas-fizetes-otp-bank">Hungarian news sites</a>. Apple device owners are seeing surprise, unexpected charges without making purchases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Pay-Canada.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943673" /><br/>
Some users are seeing multiple mistaken transactions, and it is a problem that appears to be affecting most banks in Hungary. Impacted users are being charged small amounts several times in a row. One user saw almost &#36;1,500 USD pulled from his account across 74 rapid fire transactions.<br/>
<br/>
Hungarian news sites say that banks are being slammed with requests for help, and that it appears to be a problem on Apple's end. OTP Bank in Hungary said that "massive, unjustified debits" were made to cards at several banks, with the situation still being analyzed to determine what happened. A statement on <a href="https://www.raiffeisen.hu/fooldal/-/asset_publisher/3yvyD1ghPjYw/content/teves-bankkartya-terhelesek-az-apple-alkalmazasbolt-iranyabol/maximized?_com_liferay_asset_publisher_web_portlet_AssetPublisherPortlet_INSTANCE_3yvyD1ghPjYw_assetEntryId=3734451">Raiffeisen Bank's website</a> says that Apple is working to resolve the problem.<br/>
<blockquote>We inform our customers that due to a technical problem with an external partner, the bank cards of some of our customers may have been incorrectly charged by the Apple App Store. Our colleagues have contacted Apple officials, the problem is being resolved.</blockquote><br/>
Some of the charges appear to be linked to subscriptions that were canceled previously, and some of the amounts match prior transactions. Some customers have been able to have their banks block their cards, preventing further charges.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Lorinc!)</em><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/hungary/">Hungary</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-pay-hungary-issue/">Random Apple Pay Charges Affecting iPhone Users in Hungary</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/random-apple-pay-charges-affecting-iphone-users-in-hungary.2430178/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says iPhones Will Better Support Third-Party Displays and Batteries Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/iphone-third-party-display-battery-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-iphones-will-better-support-third-party-displays-and-batteries-later-this-year.2430156/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 07:55:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/iphone-third-party-display-battery-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today published a <a href="https://support.apple.com/content/dam/edam/applecare/images/en_US/otherassets/programs/Longevity_by_Design.pdf">lengthy whitepaper</a> that highlights the company's approach to device repairability and longevity. In the document, Apple revealed that iPhones will better support third-party displays and batteries later in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912514" /><br/>
First, Apple said True Tone will work with third-party iPhone displays later this year:<blockquote>True Tone requires precise calibration to function properly, and it is not possible to engage a default calibration for third-party displays, which can result in unexpected behavior. For this reason, Apple disables the True Tone feature when third-party displays are used, but enables all other aspects of the display. <strong>In an effort to offer more complete support for third-party parts, starting later in 2024, Apple will allow consumers to activate True Tone with third-party parts to the best performance that can be provided.</strong><br/>
<br/>
They will be able to deactivate True Tone in Settings if the display does not perform to their satisfaction.</blockquote>True Tone automatically adapts the color of the display to match the light in your environment.<br/>
<br/>
Second, Apple said battery health metrics such as maximum capacity and cycle count will work with third-party iPhone batteries later this year:<blockquote>Currently, battery health metrics such as maximum capacity and cycle count are not presented to consumers whose devices have third-party batteries. This is because the accuracy of these metrics cannot be verified by Apple. In fact, an Apple internal analysis has found that some third-party batteries sold as new are actually secondhand, with battery health metrics manipulated to appear as new. <strong>In an effort to improve support for third-party batteries, starting later in 2024, Apple will display battery health metrics with a notification stating that Apple cannot verify the information presented.</strong></blockquote>Apple said the third-party battery metrics are not guaranteed to be accurate.<br/>
<br/>
These changes will presumably be rolled out with iOS 18 updates later this year, but Apple did not provide more specific timing in its document.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/iphone-third-party-display-battery-support/">Apple Says iPhones Will Better Support Third-Party Displays and Batteries Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-iphones-will-better-support-third-party-displays-and-batteries-later-this-year.2430156/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights Accessories With &#039;Colors That Pop&#039; From Nimble, Belkin, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-accessories-colors-that-pop-nimble/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-accessories-with-colors-that-pop-from-nimble-belkin-and-more.2430152/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 07:43:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-accessories-colors-that-pop-nimble/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently created a new section of its online store showcasing accessories with "Colors That Pop," and this week Nimble and Belkin have launched new products as part of this colorful lineup. You can find this section by <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/accessories/all">visiting Apple's accessories page</a> and scrolling down a bit.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Exclusive-Launch_Group-Hero.jpg" alt="" width="6000" height="3500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957012" /><br/>
Starting with Nimble, there's a <a href="https://www.pntra.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple-exclusives">new USB-C charging collection</a> available online, and it's the company's first set of products <a href="https://www.apple.com/us/search/nimble?src=globalnav">released on Apple.com</a> and in Apple retail stores. This collection includes a portable charger and various USB-C cables, all of which you can find below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.gopjn.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple-exclusives%2Fproducts%2Fpowerknit-flex-usb-a-to-usb-c-cable">PowerKnit FLEX USB-A to USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;19.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple-exclusives%2Fproducts%2Fpowerknit-travel-kit-2-pack">PowerKnit Travel Kit 2-Pack USB-C to USB-C Cables</a> - &#36;29.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.pntra.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple-exclusives%2Fproducts%2Fpowerknit-travel-kit-3-pack">PowerKnit Travel Kit 3-Pack USB-C Cables (multiple connectors)</a> - &#36;39.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.pntra.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple-exclusives%2Fproducts%2Fpowerknit-flex-usb-c-to-usb-c-3-pack">PowerKnit FLEX 3-Pack USB-C to USB-C Cables</a> - &#36;59.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.pjtra.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple-exclusives%2Fproducts%2Fchamp-portable-charger-apple-exclusive">CHAMP 10K Portable Charger</a> - &#36;79.95</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Belkin's <a href="https://www.belkin.com/pr-belkin-unveils-colorful-new-lineup-of-qi2-wireless-charging-power-banks.html">product release</a> includes two new MagSafe-compatible portable batteries, both available on Apple.com. First is the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRE72ZM/A/belkin-boost%E2%86%91charge%E2%84%A2-pro-magnetic-power-bank-5k-magsafe-compatible">BoostCharge Pro Magnetic Power Bank 5K</a>, which comes in a range of colors and can fast charge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 models and later up to 15W with Qi2 when the battery pack is plugged in and up to 7.5W when using it wirelessly.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/dlspBTwg.png" alt="" width="1800" height="521" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957011" /><br/>
In total, the power bank provides up to 16 hours of additional battery life, comes with a USB-C port, and includes a USB-C to USB-C cable. This one is priced at &#36;59.95 on Belkin's website and on Apple.com.<br/>
<br/>
Secondly, the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRE52ZM/A/belkin-boostcharge-pro-magnetic-charging-power-bank-10k-cable">BoostCharge Pro Magnetic Power Bank 10K</a> can fast charge &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models and later up to 15W with Qi2, or up to 20W with the integrated USB-C cable. It can provide up to 35 hours of additional battery life, comes in just one color (black), and is priced at &#36;99.95.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Colors That Pop section also features accessories from Tech21, SanDisk, and Herschel. The accessories all share a colorful neon hue and are built for products including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, AirPods, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-accessories-colors-that-pop-nimble/">Apple Highlights Accessories With &#039;Colors That Pop&#039; From Nimble, Belkin, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-accessories-with-colors-that-pop-from-nimble-belkin-and-more.2430152/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 to Bring These 5 New Features to AirPods Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-new-features-airpods-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-to-bring-these-5-new-features-to-airpods-pro.2430153/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:59:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-new-features-airpods-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming iOS 18 software update is packed with features for supported iPhones, but it also promises to make your AirPods Pro experience better with a handful of sophisticated new capabilities that draw from machine learning improvements and AI enhancements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-and-AirPods-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956922" /><br/>
The following five AirPods Pro features are expected to arrive later this year, when iOS 18 is released to the general public in the fall.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Head Gestures</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/f-6805c507f8a4ad4d1cf5bf1383c0c89ad096b3e0.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954464" /><br/>
Apple is set to add new head gestures that allow users to control AirPods Pro handsfree and without saying a word. With the new gestures, you can nod your head up and down, or shake it left to right, in order to answer or decline a call. Siri Interactions will also allow users to answer or dismiss calls, interact with messages, manage notifications, and more — all without speaking.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Voice Isolation</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/voice-isolation-1.jpg" alt="voice" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-889480" /><br/>
Apple's iPhones include a calling feature that can make your voice clearer to the person you're speaking to when on a call, even when you're in a busy environment. Apple in iOS 18 is adding Voice Isolation to the ‌AirPods Pro‌ so that they also cut down on loud background sounds.<br/>
<br/>
When you're on a call, the mics on AirPods Pro usually pick up a wide range of sounds in the environment, like wind around the caller. But with Voice Isolation, machine learning will distinguish these sounds, block out any ambient noise, and prioritize your voice so that it comes through clearly.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Personalized Spatial Audio for Gaming</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Spatial-Audio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1698" height="978" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-787199" /><br/>
Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking will be available for gaming across AirPods (3rd generation), AirPods Pro, and AirPods Max — delivering the immersive audio customers have come to love when listening to music, or watching movies and shows. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says that when using AirPods Pro, gamers will have the best wireless audio latency it has ever delivered for mobile gaming. AirPods Pro users will also enjoy improved voice quality, including 16-bit, 48kHz audio, when chatting with teammates and other players. Game developers will also be able to incorporate spatial audio into their games for a more immersive audio experience.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Granular Adaptive Audio Control</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airpods-adaptive-audio.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955239" /><br/>
Apple's second-generation AirPods Pro have an Adaptive Audio feature called Adaptive Noise Control, which adjusts sound and active noise cancelation in response to changes in your environment. <br/>
<br/>
Right now, Adaptive Audio is an all or nothing setting, but that's set to change in iOS 18. Apple has added a "Customize Adaptive Audio" menu that lets you adjust the setting to allow for more or less noise.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hearing Aid Mode</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/10/airpods-pro-noise-cancellation.jpg" alt="AirPods Pro" width="1212" height="659" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-716249" /><br/>
AirPods Pro will gain a new "hearing aid mode" with the release of iOS 18 later this year, according to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/airpods-pro-to-gain-hearing-aid-mode-ios-18/">March report</a> by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. AirPods Pro already offer a Conversation Boost feature, which boosts the volume and clarity of people directly in front of the wearer, but so far Apple has not advertised the earbuds as a hearing aid device.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-new-features-airpods-pro/">iOS 18 to Bring These 5 New Features to AirPods Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-to-bring-these-5-new-features-to-airpods-pro.2430153/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get an AirTag for Just &#36;24.99 From Amazon, Plus Discounts on Eufy&#039;s SmartTrack Card and Apple Pencil Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-an-airtag-for-just-24-99-from-amazon-plus-discounts-on-eufys-smarttrack-card-and-apple-pencil-pro.2430154/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:46:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Discounts on Apple's AirTag have expanded to include the 1 Pack this week, and also still cover a sale on the 4 Pack of the Bluetooth trackers at Amazon. We're also seeing a record low discount on an AirTag alternative from Eufy, as well as savings on Apple Pencil 2 and Apple Pencil Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airtag-orange-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957000" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the AirTag 1 Pack, Amazon has this accessory on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%2Fref%3Dfs_a_md_0"><strong>&#36;24.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.00. This AirTag 1 Pack isn't on sale as often as the 4 Pack option, so even at just &#36;4 off it's still a solid discount at its second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%2Fref%3Dfs_a_md_0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;78.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the AirTag 4 Pack available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"><strong>&#36;78.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. This is another second-best price, and just about &#36;4 higher than the all-time low price. As of writing, the AirTag 4 Pack can be delivered as soon as June 28 for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/eufy-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956999" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want to save more money, Eufy's SmartTrack Card Bluetooth tracker is on sale right now on Amazon. This accessory is designed to fit in your wallet and is priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1719408239814"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;29.99. The SmartTrack Card is compatible with Apple's Find My app, allowing you to track the device within the app and receive left behind alerts and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1719408239814"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956283" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon today has the Apple Pencil Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a>, down from the regular price of &#36;129.00. Although this is only a &#36;10 discount, it's the lowest price we've tracked on the brand new Apple Pencil Pro among the major online retailers. The Apple Pencil 2 is also at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Pencil Pro launched last month alongside the new 2024 iPad lineup, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/09/apple-pencil-pro-features/">new gestures and capabilities</a> into the stylus. The Apple Pencil Pro is compatible with the M4 iPad Pro and the M2 iPad Air, and marks the first update to the Apple Pencil since the Apple Pencil 2 in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/">Get an AirTag for Just &#36;24.99 From Amazon, Plus Discounts on Eufy&#039;s SmartTrack Card and Apple Pencil Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-an-airtag-for-just-24-99-from-amazon-plus-discounts-on-eufys-smarttrack-card-and-apple-pencil-pro.2430154/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expands Diagnostics Tool for Self-Service Repairs to Europe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-diagnostics-self-service-repairs-europe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-diagnostics-tool-for-self-service-repairs-to-europe.2430155/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:11:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-diagnostics-self-service-repairs-europe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Self Service Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/apple-expands-self-service-repair-diagnostics-support-to-europe/">announced</a> that it now offers a diagnostics tool for self-service iPhone, Mac, and Studio Display repairs in Europe. This software lets customers complete the System Configuration process following <a href="https://support.apple.com/self-service-repair">self-service repairs</a> by placing the device into Diagnostics Mode and following the on-screen prompts, without needing to contact Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Self-Service-Repair-MacBook.jpeg" alt="" width="3920" height="2205" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938858" /><br/>
Apple says the diagnostics tool is now available in 32 countries in Europe, including the U.K., France, Germany, the Netherlands, and others. The tool, which was previously limited to technicians at Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers, first became available for self-service repairs in the U.S. last year.<br/>
<br/>
Launched in 2022, the self-service program provides customers with access to genuine Apple parts, tools, and manuals to repair select iPhone, Mac, and Studio Display models, allowing for some do-it-yourself repairs.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/apple-diagnostics-self-service-repairs-europe/">Apple Expands Diagnostics Tool for Self-Service Repairs to Europe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-diagnostics-tool-for-self-service-repairs-to-europe.2430155/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Scraps Continuous Scrolling in Search Results</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/google-scraps-continuous-scrolling-search-results/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-scraps-continuous-scrolling-in-search-results.2430151/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:49:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/google-scraps-continuous-scrolling-search-results/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google is reportedly scrapping continuous scrolling of search results on desktop and mobile, with the company returning to the old method of dividing results into several pages (via <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/6/25/24185727/google-search-continuous-scrolling-doomscrolling-graveyard">The Verge</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/Google-Logo-Feature-Slack.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-837104" /><br/>
Google <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/google-search-continous-scrolling-us-desktop/">introduced continuous scrolling</a> on mobile and desktop in 2021 and 2022, respectively. The change was reminiscent of a social media feed, although Google's version was never quite the "infinite scroll" that social network users will be familiar with. Search has typically returned the equivalent of six pages of results in a single scroll, before offering users a "More results" button that keeps the scroll going.<br/>
<br/>
Google originally claimed that continuous scroll would make browsing results quicker and easier, although some users likely missed how the old pagination system often acted as a natural breaker that allowed them to consider whether they had all the information they needed.<br/>
<br/>
A Google spokesperson reportedly told <em><a href="https://searchengineland.com/google-dropping-continuous-scroll-in-search-results-443529">Search Engine Land</a></em> that continuous scroll would be removed from desktop search results from June 25, while the feature will be removed from mobile results "in the coming months." Google said that the change is needed to allow it to serve search results faster, instead of automatically loading results that users haven't explicitly requested.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/google-scraps-continuous-scrolling-search-results/">Google Scraps Continuous Scrolling in Search Results</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-scraps-continuous-scrolling-in-search-results.2430151/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Podcasts App Now Shows Chapter Segments When Scrubbing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-podcasts-scrubbing-chapters/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-podcasts-app-now-shows-chapter-segments-when-scrubbing.2430148/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:17:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-podcasts-scrubbing-chapters/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple's Podcasts app now shows chapter segments of a podcast when you scrub through a currently playing episode, making it easier to browse through the audio content.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/podcasts-scrubbing-chapters-ios-18.jpeg" alt="" width="1170" height="714" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956975" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image credit: <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iOSBeta/comments/1do9pg8/ios_18_db2_podcasts_now_shows_chapters_segments/">Reddit user Wristnut</a></em></div><br/>
As spotted by Redditor "Wristnut," navigating the timeline across the chapter segments shows the chapter name above the line. Note that this behavior appears in the Podcasts app proper, and it is not currently reproducible on the Lock Screen media controls in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta 2.<br/>
<br/>
While the ability to scrub through chapter segments is new, chapters themselves are not. Some podcast listeners may not be familiar with them because creators have to manually add chapters, and many shows have not adopted them. Creators must specify chapters in the header of an MP4 file or by modifying the ID3 tags of MP3 or AAC files using third-party tools.<br/>
<br/>
When creators do support chapters, listeners can find them by swiping up on the Now Playing screen on iOS and iPadOS or by clicking the Chapters button located in the top-right corner of the Podcasts app for macOS. Creators can also provide chapter-specific artwork that is displayed on the Now Playing screen and on the Lock Screen on iOS and iPadOS, providing a timely visual supplement to the podcast.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> supports chapters for MP4, MP3, and AAC files, whether they are available from the directory or manually added to the Library via an RSS feed. Some of the tools used to add chapters include Ferrite on iOS and iPadOS, Forecast by Overcast, Podcasts Chapters on macOS, and Vizzy on the web.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is currently in its second developer beta, with a public beta expected in July, followed by a general release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-podcasts-scrubbing-chapters/">iOS 18: Podcasts App Now Shows Chapter Segments When Scrubbing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-podcasts-app-now-shows-chapter-segments-when-scrubbing.2430148/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iCloud &#039;Keep Downloaded&#039; Option Included in iOS 18 and macOS Sequoia</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-ios-18-macos-sequoia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-included-in-ios-18-and-macos-sequoia.2430145/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 04:23:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-ios-18-macos-sequoia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, Apple has added a new "Keep Downloaded" option when browsing items in iCloud, allowing users to designate which files and folders should remain permanently available locally on their device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-15-keep-downloaded.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956964" /><br/>
In previous versions of iOS and macOS, users had limited control over which files and folders were kept offline. iCloud's automatic management system would offload files from the device to free up space, potentially removing files that you might want to keep available at all times. <br/>
<br/>
Apple offered no straightforward way to prevent this – until now. In macOS Sequoia, when browsing iCloud Drive in Finder, right-clicking a file or folder reveals the new "Keep Downloaded" option. When enabled, the cloud symbol next to the item is opaque instead of transparent, indicating that it will remain on the device. <br/>
<br/>
In iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, the same option can be found in the Files app when a file or folder is long pressed to bring up the contextual menu. Users can now explicitly mark files to remain on their device, regardless of how much storage they take up.<br/>
<br/>
The ability to prevent iCloud items from being offloaded should be particularly welcomed by users who need to frequently access documents or files during travel or in areas with poor connectivity. macOS Sequoia, iOS 18, and iPadOS 18 are available in a beta capacity right now, and are limited to developers. The new option should be available to all users when the software launches to the public this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-ios-18-macos-sequoia/">iCloud &#039;Keep Downloaded&#039; Option Included in iOS 18 and macOS Sequoia</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-included-in-ios-18-and-macos-sequoia.2430145/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
