<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:03:20 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>What&#039;s Next for the Apple Watch Ultra 3 and Apple Watch SE 3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-watch-ultra-se-whats-next/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-next-for-the-apple-watch-ultra-3-and-apple-watch-se-3.2455954/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:44:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-watch-ultra-se-whats-next/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week marks <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-watch-launched-10-years-ago-today/">the 10th anniversary</a> of the Apple Watch, which launched on April 24, 2015. Yesterday, we recapped features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-11/">rumored for the Apple Watch Series 11</a>, but since 2015, the Apple Watch has also branched out into the Apple Watch Ultra and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, so we thought we'd take a look at what's next for those product lines, too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-watch-ultra-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891517" /><br/>
<h2>2025 Apple Watch Ultra 3</h2><br/>
Apple didn't update the Apple Watch Ultra in 2024, opting only to introduce a new color, so it's due for a refresh. There are some exclusive features that are rumored for the Apple Watch Ultra that will further distinguish it from the standard Apple Watch lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>5G and Satellite Connectivity</h3><br/>
Like the Apple Watch Series 11, the Apple Watch Ultra is likely to get a new MediaTek modem that will enable 5G connectivity for the first time, but it is also rumored to be getting satellite connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, satellite connectivity is limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 14 and later, but by adding it to the Apple Watch Ultra, Apple will be able to better compete with companies like Garmin that offer dedicated satellite hardware for off-grid emergency use. The Apple Watch Ultra is aimed at hikers, scuba divers, and others who often partake in activities in remote areas, so a backup connection would definitely increase its appeal with the device's target audience.<br/>
<br/>
With satellite integration, the Apple Watch Ultra would be able to connect to available Globalstar satellites to send texts and location information when cellular networks and Wi-Fi aren't available. It could either be limited to emergency situations, or available for texting like satellite connectivity on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Satellite connectivity is expected to be a feature exclusive to the Apple Watch Ultra, and it's not something we expect to see added to the Apple Watch Series 11.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Design and Display</h3><br/>
With the Apple Watch Series 10, Apple introduced an LTPO3 OLED display that's bigger and brighter than the Apple Watch Ultra display, with faster refresh rates that enable a live ticking seconds hand on some watch faces.<br/>
<br/>
This year, Apple could bring those same display improvements to the Apple Watch Ultra, so it's possible the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will feature the same wide-angle OLED that's up to 40 percent brighter at certain viewing angles, and the faster refresh rate for the seconds hand.<br/>
<br/>
Similarly, Apple redesigned the back of the Apple Watch Series 10, and it's now made of metal instead of ceramic. It's also got a larger charging coil and integrated antenna, and we could see all of these changes come to the Apple Watch Ultra 3.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Health Features</h3><br/>
Apple is working on a blood pressure monitoring feature, and there is a chance that it could launch in the 2025 Apple Watch Series 11 and Apple Watch Ultra 3, but it's not guaranteed because there have been some development problems that could delay it.<br/>
<br/>
If we do get blood pressure monitoring, it <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-01/apple-plans-hypertension-sleep-apnea-detection-for-next-watch">won't provide</a> exact systolic and diastolic measurements, instead monitoring for hypertension and providing an alert if the condition is detected over time.<br/>
<br/>
After receiving a hypertension alert, an Apple Watch user could provide that information to a medical professional for additional testing, similar to how the existing atrial fibrillation features work in the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>watchOS 12</h3><br/>
watchOS 12, set to launch in September, is expected to have some design changes that will be applicable to the Apple Watch Ultra 3. We could get <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/apple-watch-watchos-12-visionos-design-changes/">visionOS-like design changes</a> that will match the changes coming in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>, but there's not going to be a complete overhaul.<br/>
<br/>
We could see new interface elements that are inspired by visionOS, with an emphasis on translucency, glass-like finishes, rounded buttons, and subtle lighting effects.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could also introduce a new set of features "powered" by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>. These capabilities won't run directly on the Apple Watch because it does not have enough RAM or storage space to support it, but a connected &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will be able to supply enough power for Apple Watch &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features.<br/>
<br/>
There are also rumors that Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/ios-19-4-revamped-health-app-rumor/">new version of the Health app</a> that has personalized health recommendations to help users lead a healthier lifestyle, and that functionality would likely have an Apple Watch component.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2025 Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
Apple doesn't update the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; very often, and it's actually been three years since we last got a refresh. It's overdue for an update, and 2025 is expected to be the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-watch-se-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941419" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; hasn't had an update since 2022, so a new model will have an updated chip that's faster and more capable, and there's a possibility that there could be design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Design</h3><br/>
There were rumors that Apple was working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/apple-watch-se-plastic/">colorful, hard plastic casing</a> for the next &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, but it may have been scrapped. Apple's design team <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/23/plastic-apple-watch-se-in-jeopardy/">didn't like the look</a> of the plastic watch and the casing is not cheaper than aluminum to make, so Apple might have nixed it.<br/>
<br/>
If that's the case, the next &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; could continue to use aluminum and it will look similar to the current model, but it is probably going to get a larger display and slimmed down bezels. The current &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; is available in 40mm and 44mm size options and it was modeled after the Apple Watch Series 6, but Apple has made two sizing updates since then. The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; will either get the 41mm and 45mm size options introduced with the Apple Watch Series 7, or the 42mm and 46mm size options Apple added with the Series 10. The 41mm/45mm size option is most probable because it distinguishes the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; from the Series 11 without making the third-generation SE look too outdated.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Display</h3><br/>
Larger display sizes are a possibility as mentioned above, and so is always-on display technology. This is an Apple Watch staple that hasn't ever been introduced for the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; line, but it's now been around so long that it's probably affordable enough for Apple to add.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Faster Chip</h3><br/>
The current &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; has an S8 chip that's based on the A13 Bionic chip, but the Apple Watch Series 10 uses an S10 chip. The Series 11 could get an even faster chip, and Apple could use the current S10 for the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
A faster chip would improve speeds for things like using apps on the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, and it would allow for some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> requests to be processed on-device for quicker response times and more accurate dictation. Right now, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; isn't able to access health info on the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, but that could change if the third-generation model gets a new chip.<br/>
<br/>
It's also possible that Apple will add an Ultra Wideband chip to the next &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, allowing for Precision Finding and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> integration.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Health Features</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; does not have ECG or temperature sensing capabilities, nor does it offer sleep apnea detection. It's possible at least one of these features will expand to Apple's more affordable watch line this year, with sleep apnea being the most likely because it doesn't require any additional hardware.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 11</h2><br/>
If you want to know what's rumored for the Apple Watch Series 11, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-11/">we have a dedicated guide</a> that aggregates all of the rumors that we've heard so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Launch Date</h2><br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3, Apple Watch Series 11, and &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; 3 are expected in September 2025, and they will likely launch alongside the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> models.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-watch-ultra-se-whats-next/">What&#039;s Next for the Apple Watch Ultra 3 and Apple Watch SE 3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-next-for-the-apple-watch-ultra-3-and-apple-watch-se-3.2455954/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 13-Inch iPad Air and Mount From Lululook</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/macrumors-giveaway-13-inch-ipad-air-lululook/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-13-inch-ipad-air-and-mount-from-lululook.2455948/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 10:50:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/macrumors-giveaway-13-inch-ipad-air-lululook/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2FLULULOOK%2Fpage%2FBC05BD56-06BF-47EE-9FD3-23478F234266">Lululook</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 13-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLULULOOK-Pro-iPad-13-M4%2Fdp%2FB0DTKJ6DJT%2F%3Fth%3D1">Lululook Foldable Magnetic Charging Mount</a> to go along with it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lululook-angled-arm-ipad-stand.jpg" alt="" width="1787" height="1005" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999816" /><br/>
Lululook makes all kinds of stands and accessories for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and other Apple products, and its &#36;100 Foldable Magnetic Charging Mount is not quite like other stands you've seen. It's a desk stand that clamps on to the edge of a desk or a table, with an adjustable arm that can be tilted and angled to get the perfect viewing position.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lululook-ipad-stand-arm.jpg" alt="" width="788" height="443" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999813" /><br/>
An &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; connects directly to the mount using magnets that hold it securely in place, while the other end clamps to a desk. There are actually 88 small magnets to ensure that your &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; isn't going to go anywhere. A joint on the clamp allows it to be rotated 360 degrees, and there's also another joint at the top, so it's easy to reposition.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lululook-ipad-stand-arm-3.jpg" alt="" width="1063" height="599" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999815" /><br/>
A USB-C cable provides power, and the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is able to charge through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-connector/">Smart Connector</a>. With the three section arm, it can be shifted around on a desk, so it's perfect for setting up an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; as a second monitor, or attaching one to a worktable where you want to be able to watch video content while the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is out of your workspace. You can use it in either landscape or portrait mode. There are versions of the stand for the 13-inch 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-ipad-air/">2025 iPad Air</a> models, plus it works with some older iPads too, including the 2018 and later 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lululook-ipad-stand-arm-2.jpg" alt="" width="1124" height="631" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999814" /><br/>
Lululook has plenty of other stand options too, if you don't need the clamp design. The <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FiPad-Pro-12-9-Air-13%2Fdp%2FB0DZXGHZGM%2F%3Fth%3D1">Magnetic Wireless Charging Stand</a> for the 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and Air is &#36;90, and it has a clean, Mac-like look. It charges an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; via &zwnj;Smart Connector&zwnj;, and it has two 360-degree pivot points for adjustability. The stand is made from aluminum alloy so it has a sleek look that blends well with Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lululook-magnetic-ipad-charging-stand.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999810" /><br/>
There's also the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLULULOOK-Magnetic-Spinning-Foldable-12-9%2Fdp%2FB0C3H3721R%2F">&#36;80 Magnetic iPad Stand</a> for the 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which is a good option if you don't need included charging. It has a 360-degree rotating base, and it is height and angle adjustable so you can get it into just the right position. It rotates into portrait or landscape mode, and magnets hold it securely in place.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lululook-magnetic-ipad-stand.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999812" /><br/>
We've got a 128GB 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and a Lululook Foldable Magnetic Charging Mount for one lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/GMYYk/lululook-giveaway" rel="nofollow"><br/>
  Lululook Giveaway</a><script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (April 25) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on May 2. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after May 2 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/macrumors-giveaway-13-inch-ipad-air-lululook/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 13-Inch iPad Air and Mount From Lululook</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-13-inch-ipad-air-and-mount-from-lululook.2455948/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Latest iPadOS 19 and iPhone 17 Air Rumors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/the-macrumors-show-ipados-19-and-iphone-17-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-latest-ipados-19-and-iphone-17-air-rumors.2455943/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:50:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/the-macrumors-show-ipados-19-and-iphone-17-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/ipados-19-will-be-more-macos-like-iphone-17-air-leaks/id1602394741?i=1000704919401">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the rumored look of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> "Air" and iPadOS 19's major productivity update.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DSMst_fo7Gg?si=-u_-NHqVYfjO2o07" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We take a closer look at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-thin-as-buttons/">rumored design</a> of the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; "Air," which is expected to introduce a radically thinner design. It is rumored to be as thin as 5.5mm, versus the 8.725mm thickness of the Pro models. It has now emerged that even the buttons will need to be thinner than those used on the other models to simply fit on the device.<br/>
<br/>
We also discuss the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/iphone-17-pro-sky-blue-color/">rumored "Sky Blue" color option</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; Max, which bears a resemblance to the "Sierra Blue" of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 13 Pro. Sky Blue was first introduced on the M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> earlier this year. Moreover, we talk through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/17/images-of-apple-vision-air-cable/">purported "Midnight" colorway</a> for the Apple Vision "Air."<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, iPadOS 19 is expected to bring a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/13/ipados-19-more-like-macos/">major software upgrade</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. The update is expected to make the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; more "macOS-like," with improved productivity, multitasking, and window management. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> also has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/18/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-apple-intelligence/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up to hear our discussion with <em>Daring Fireball</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/john-gruber/">John Gruber</a> about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> and the future of the company.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/the-macrumors-show-ipados-19-and-iphone-17-air/">The MacRumors Show: Latest iPadOS 19 and iPhone 17 Air Rumors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-latest-ipados-19-and-iphone-17-air-rumors.2455943/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Woot&#039;s Blind Box Apple Watch Band Sale, Plus Steep Discounts on MacBook Air and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-25-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-woots-blind-box-apple-watch-band-sale-plus-steep-discounts-on-macbook-air-and-more.2455941/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 07:47:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-25-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Multiple Apple products hit all-time low prices this week, including the M4 MacBook Air, 11th generation iPad, and M3 iPad Air. We're also still tracking a sale on Apple Watch Solo Loop and Braided Solo Loop bands at Woot, which can net you up to two free bands when you buy one at a discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Best-Apple-Deals-Feature-Shelf-0004.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-999835" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Bands</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/new-apple-watch-solo-loop-yellow.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999755" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Buy one Apple Watch band, get up to two free</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-band-discovery-box-buy-1-get-some-free">Woot</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/woots-new-apple-watch-band-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-band-discovery-box-buy-1-get-some-free"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY ONE GET 2 FREE</div>Apple Watch Bands at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week, Woot brought back its popular sale on Apple Watch Solo Loop and Braided Solo Loop bands, but there is a change. This time, when you buy any Solo Loop or Braided Solo Loop at a discount on Woot, you'll get up to two extra bands for free. You can find more information on the sale in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/woots-new-apple-watch-band-sale/">original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/m4-macbook-air-orange.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999756" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;150 off M4 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9S5GC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/23/m4-macbook-air-to-switch-2-pre-orders/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9S5GC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9NV7L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;108 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,092.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBHQPQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,269.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week kicked off a sale on M4 MacBook Air models, and these prices have only gotten better as the week continued. You can now find up to &#36;130 off 13-inch models and up to &#36;150 off 15-inch models on Amazon right now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/apple-watch-se-orange.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999757" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;79 off Apple Watch SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZJVYY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/amazon-apple-watch-se/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZJVYY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.97</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ2NM9S%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get &#36;79 off the Apple Watch SE this week on Amazon, starting at just &#36;169.97 for the 40mm GPS model. Overall, these are both just a few cents away from the best prices we've seen so far this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/11th-gen-ipad-orange.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999758" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;48 off 11th generation iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75TN5F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/11-gen-ipad-record-low-price/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75TN5F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;319.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76LW4J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;419.80</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ77SG5C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;48 OFF</div>512GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;601.67</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has a few discounts on Apple's 11th generation iPad this week, including a return of the all-time low price on the entry level model. Prices start at &#36;319.99 for the 128GB Wi-Fi iPad, down from &#36;349.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/ipad-air-orange.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999759" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;69 off M3 iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/21/m3-ipad-air-70-off-amazon/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;729.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Early in the week, Amazon introduced a few discounts on the M3 iPad Air, and many of these have now been discounted even further. Prices start at &#36;549.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air, which is an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-25-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Woot&#039;s Blind Box Apple Watch Band Sale, Plus Steep Discounts on MacBook Air and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-woots-blind-box-apple-watch-band-sale-plus-steep-discounts-on-macbook-air-and-more.2455941/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Send Web Links That Jump to the Exact Text You Mean</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/send-web-links-jump-to-exact-text/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/send-web-links-that-jump-to-the-exact-text-you-mean.2455939/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:48:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/send-web-links-jump-to-exact-text&#038;post_date=1745596122/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sometimes when you share a webpage link with someone, you just want to bring their attention to a specific passage or sentence to make your point, rather than have them read through the entire article.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/safari-icon-blue-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833485" /><br/>
In 2020, Google added a function to its Chrome browser called Scroll to Text Fragment (STTF) that helps you achieve this. It allows URLs to link directly to any visible text on a page. You may have seen it work in Google Search, where clicking on a link in your returned results takes you to a highlighted passage of text further down the page.<br/>
<br/>
Since then, Google has built the feature into the open source Chromium code, so most other popular Chromium browsers like Edge, Opera, and Vivaldi also have it these days. (Brave is an exception, citing <a href="https://github.com/WICG/scroll-to-text-fragment/issues/76">some privacy risks</a> of STTF.)<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Copy Link With Highlight in Safari</h2><br/>
Late last year, Apple joined the club, and brought full support to Safari 18.2. To use the feature, visit a web page and simply highlight the text you want to create a link to, then right-click and choose <strong>Copy Link with Highlight</strong> from the dropdown menu.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/copy-link-with-highlight1.jpg" alt="" width="2276" height="728" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999741" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The "Copy Link to Highlight" option</em></div><br/>
This will generate a special URL that includes a hash (#) symbol and "text" element, followed by a few words that bookend the selected text. All you need to do is share the link with someone, and when they click it they'll be sent directly to that part of the webpage with the specific passage highlighted, as shown below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/copy-link-with-highlight2.jpg" alt="" width="2034" height="712" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999742" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The shared link as the recipient sees it</em></div><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. The Copy Link to Highlight option is also available in Safari on the iPhone and iPad, and indeed in any browser that uses WebKit on iOS and iPadOS. Hopefully that makes it easier for you to direct the recipient of the link to the content you actually want them to focus on. <br/>
<br/>
Bear in mind that the look of highlighted text can differ depending on whether the page author has styled it to look a certain way. Also, text fragment linking does not work in PDFs. Firefox users: You'll need to install Thomas Steiner's <a href="https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/link-to-text-fragment/">Link to Text Fragment</a> extension, which will add a <strong>Copy Link to Selected Text</strong> option to the contextual menu.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/send-web-links-jump-to-exact-text/">Send Web Links That Jump to the Exact Text You Mean</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/send-web-links-that-jump-to-the-exact-text-you-mean.2455939/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Arlo Rolls Out Apple Home Support for 2nd-Gen Essential Camera Lineup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/arlo-apple-home-support-2nd-gen-essential-cameras/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/arlo-rolls-out-apple-home-support-for-2nd-gen-essential-camera-lineup.2455933/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:38:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/arlo-apple-home-support-2nd-gen-essential-cameras/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Arlo</category>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.arlo.com/en-us/">Arlo</a> has begun rolling out Apple Home integration for its Essential Second-Generation camera lineup, reports <a href="https://www.the-ambient.com/news/arlo-finally-adds-apple-home-support-to-its-latest-cameras/"><em>The-Ambient</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/arlo-indoor-essential-camera.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786222" /><br/>
The integration allows devices like the Arlo <a href="https://www.arlo.com/en-us/doorbell/video/arlo-doorbell.html">Essential 2K Video Doorbell</a>, <a href="https://www.arlo.com/en-us/cameras/VMC2060-100NAS.html">2K Indoor Camera</a>, and <a href="https://www.arlo.com/en-us/cameras/VMC3052-100NAS.html">2K Outdoor XL Camera</a> (all second-gen models) to be added to the Apple Home app. That's provided they are connected to a compatible Arlo Base Station or SmartHub.<br/>
<br/>
When properly connected, users will be able to view live feeds and screenshots, receive motion and audio notifications, and use two-way audio directly from the Apple Home app. The update also brings Siri voice control functionality and the ability to view camera feeds on Apple TV, making it convenient to check who's at the door without reaching for your phone.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em>The-Ambient</em>, this update should prove a big improvement for Apple Home households, where third-party camera support has traditionally been inconsistent at best. While Arlo still hasn't implemented HomeKit Secure Video support (something many users have been clamoring for), standard HomeKit integration is a meaningful step toward a more unified smart home experience.<br/>
<br/>
The rollout appears to be specifically for second-generation Essential devices, so owners of first-gen or other Arlo camera lines might need to wait a bit longer (or invest in newer hardware) to enjoy the same Apple Home integration.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/arlo/">Arlo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/arlo-apple-home-support-2nd-gen-essential-cameras/">Arlo Rolls Out Apple Home Support for 2nd-Gen Essential Camera Lineup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/arlo-rolls-out-apple-home-support-for-2nd-gen-essential-camera-lineup.2455933/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Plans to Source All US-Bound iPhones From India by 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-source-us-bound-iphones-india-2026/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-plans-to-source-all-us-bound-iphones-from-india-by-2026.2455932/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 01:36:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-source-us-bound-iphones-india-2026/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>India</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is accelerating its manufacturing shift away from China, with plans to assemble all U.S.-bound iPhones in India by the end of 2026, according to a new <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c2be45b8-cfad-4cbb-9a1a-bfd0626be372">Financial Times</a></em> report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/iPhone-12-Made-in-India.jpg" alt="" width="2715" height="1527" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-755211" /><br/>
The ambitious timeline would require Apple to double its current iPhone production capacity in India. It marks a major acceleration of Apple's supply chain diversification strategy, which has been gradually expanding in recent years.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, the majority of iPhones are manufactured in China through partners like Foxconn. The U.S. market accounts for approximately 28 percent of Apple's global iPhone shipments, which totaled 232.1 million units in 2024, according to International Data Corporation.<br/>
<br/>
The shift comes amid renewed trade tensions between the US and China. President Trump recently implemented substantial tariffs on Chinese imports, causing Apple's market value to drop by approximately &#36;700 billion. In response, Apple reportedly rushed existing Indian-manufactured iPhones to the U.S. to avoid higher tariffs imposed on Chinese goods.<br/>
<br/>
The timing isn't coincidental. CEO Tim Cook has reportedly been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/apple-tariff-exemptions/">working diligently</a> behind the scenes to protect Apple from the full impact of Trump's tariffs. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/17/tim-cook-trump-apple-tariff-exemption/">As reported last week</a>, Cook secured a temporary exemption for iPhones, Macs, Apple Watches, and iPads from the bulk of Trump's 145 percent tariffs on Chinese imports after phone calls with Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick and other senior White House officials.<br/>
<br/>
The exemption might be short-lived, however. Trump later indicated that "no one would be getting off the hook" and that electronics companies would be "moving to a different tariff bucket" as his administration reviews semiconductors and the electronics supply chain.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been gradually building manufacturing capacity in India with partners Tata Electronics and Foxconn. The company's relationship with the Indian government may prove helpful, as India is currently working toward a bilateral trade agreement with the U.S., which could provide more favorable trade conditions.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the assembly pivot, Apple still relies heavily on Chinese suppliers for hundreds of iPhone components. The company has pledged a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/24/apple-announces-500b-us-investment-plan/">&#36;500 billion investment</a> in the United States but has not announced plans to bring iPhone manufacturing to American soil.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is scheduled to report quarterly earnings next week, where investors will be watching closely for any comments on how these tariffs and supply chain shifts might impact the company's future performance.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/india/">India</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-source-us-bound-iphones-india-2026/">Report: Apple Plans to Source All US-Bound iPhones From India by 2026</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-plans-to-source-all-us-bound-iphones-from-india-by-2026.2455932/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything Rumored for the 2025 Apple Watch Series 11</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-11/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-rumored-for-the-2025-apple-watch-series-11.2455919/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:52:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-11&#038;post_date=1745549546/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we celebrate <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-watch-launched-10-years-ago-today/">the 10th anniversary</a> of the Apple Watch today, we thought we'd take a look at what Apple has in store for the next-generation version of the device that's coming this fall. The Apple Watch Series 11 doesn't sound like it's going to be a groundbreaking anniversary device, but Apple could surprise us.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/apple-watch-series-10-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996975" /><br/>
<h2 id="new_modem_technology">New Modem Technology</h2><br/>
Right now, the Apple Watch uses Intel cellular modems that are limited to LTE connectivity, but Apple is planning to instead adopt technology from MediaTek for future Apple Watch models. MediaTek's modem chip supports 5G RedCap, which is a 5G service specifically designed for wearables that don't need standard 5G speeds.<br/>
<br/>
5G RedCap could bring 5G connectivity to the Apple Watch, which would likely be an improvement over the existing LTE connectivity options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="chip_improvements">Chip Improvements</h2><br/>
We could get an updated S11 chip for the Apple Watch this year, which would have a more compact, efficient design. There could be optimizations in battery life, along with additional space for a larger battery or other components.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="health_features">Health Features</h2><br/>
Apple is working on a blood pressure monitoring feature, and there is a chance that it could launch in 2025 models, though there have been rumors of development issues that could push it back.<br/>
<br/>
When blood pressure monitoring comes to the Apple Watch, it <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-01/apple-plans-hypertension-sleep-apnea-detection-for-next-watch">won't provide</a> exact systolic and diastolic measurements, instead simply monitoring for hypertension and providing an alert if the condition is detected over time. Hypertension is a serious issue where a person's blood pressure stays high over time, and it is a risk factor for heart disease, stroke, and other health issues.<br/>
<br/>
After receiving a hypertension alert, an Apple Watch user could provide that information to a medical professional for additional testing, similar to how the existing atrial fibrillation features work in the Apple Watch. Apple has been running into problems with accuracy and reliability that could cause delays.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="watchos_revamp">watchOS Revamp</h2><br/>
watchOS 12, set to launch in September, will bring some watchOS design changes to the Apple Watch Series 11 along with existing Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that it will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/apple-watch-watchos-12-visionos-design-changes/">visionOS-like design changes</a> that will match the changes coming in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>, but it won't be a complete design overhaul. We could see new interface elements that are inspired by visionOS, with an emphasis on translucency, glass-like finishes, rounded buttons, and subtle lighting effects.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could also introduce a new set of features "powered" by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>. These capabilities won't run directly on the Apple Watch because it does not have enough RAM or storage space to support it, but a connected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will be able to supply enough power for Apple Watch &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ai-powered_health_coaching">AI-Powered Health Coaching</h2><br/>
In an update to &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, Apple could introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/ios-19-4-revamped-health-app-rumor/">new version of the Health app</a> that would feature personalized health recommendations to help users lead a healthier lifestyle. This would naturally have an Apple Watch component, using data gathered by the watch and providing on-device guidance.<br/>
<br/>
Food tracking features could also be introduced in the future, with Apple set to compete with apps like MyFitnessPal.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_happened_to_redesign_rumors">What Happened to Redesign Rumors?</h2><br/>
Ahead of when the Apple Watch Series 10 launched, there were rumors that Apple was working on a special anniversary version of the device, or an "Apple Watch X" with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">major design overhaul</a>. That redesign was said to include a thinner casing and a new way for bands to attach to the device using a magnetic connection, which would have meant that existing bands <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/your-apple-watch-bands-may-not-work-with-new-model/">would not be compatible</a> with new Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
With the Series 10, we did get a thinner casing, but there was no new band attachment system. It's not clear if that's been scrapped entirely, but it's not a rumor that has popped back up for the Series 11.<br/>
<br/>
Apple didn't acknowledge the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch last year, so that could be something that will come up with the Series 11 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_about_blood_oxygen_monitoring">What About Blood Oxygen Monitoring?</h2><br/>
Since early 2024, Apple Watch models sold in the United States <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/">have not had</a> blood oxygen monitoring capabilities after Apple was forced to remove the feature or face an import ban <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">for patent violations</a>. No Apple Watch Series 10 models in the U.S. have a functioning blood oxygen monitoring feature, and it's looking like the Apple Watch 11 won't either.<br/>
<br/>
There have been no signs as of late that hint at whether and when blood oxygen monitoring is coming back. Apple has the ability to re-enable blood oxygen monitoring via a software update because the hardware is still there, but so far, Apple doesn't seem willing to settle with Masimo, the company that sued it, nor have we heard rumors of an alternative solution.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could win an appeal of the case, settle, or create a new method for blood oxygen sensing that doesn't use Masimo technology, but if none of those things happen, it will be years before blood oxygen sensing comes back. Masimo's patents are set to expire in 2028, so at least there's hope for a blood oxygen sensing before the end of the decade.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="pricing">Pricing</h2><br/>
If new tariffs are introduced on semiconductors and Apple's products aren't exempted, there is a possibility that the Series 11 models could get more expensive. As of now, though, we're still expecting a &#36;399 starting point.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="future_apple_watch_updates">Future Apple Watch Updates</h2><br/>
Apple is working on some much more exciting updates for future versions of the Apple Watch, but we're still several years away from most of them.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/23/apple-watches-with-cameras-rumored/">Built-in cameras</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a>.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-watch-glucose-monitoring-feature/">Non-invasive blood glucose monitoring</a>, a feature Apple has been working on for years for diabetes prevention.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
We're expecting the Apple Watch Series 11 to be announced in September alongside new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> models.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-11/">Everything Rumored for the 2025 Apple Watch Series 11</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-rumored-for-the-2025-apple-watch-series-11.2455919/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube Tests AI Overviews in Search Results</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/youtube-search-results-ai-overviews/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-tests-ai-overviews-in-search-results.2455918/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:23:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/youtube-search-results-ai-overviews/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>YouTube</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google-owned YouTube <a href="https://support.google.com/youtube/thread/18138167?hl=en&amp;msgid=340138072">this week said</a> it is "experimenting" with a new video search results carousel that appears after searches for select keywords.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/General-YouTube-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983782" /><br/>
According to YouTube, the video results carousel will use AI to highlight clips from videos that "will be most helpful for your search query," which essentially means that it will take clips from videos and play them right in results, so people may not need to click into a video to find the information they're looking for.<br/>
<br/>
Google uses AI overviews for Google Search, but the YouTube version will differ. AI won't summarize videos, and will simply pull clips from them. It is not clear the AI-selected clips will encourage users to watch a full video, or cause fewer people to engage with videos, but AI integration into Google Search has <a href="https://searchengineland.com/google-ai-overviews-hurt-click-through-rates-454428">impacted traffic to websites</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, the feature is being tested with a small number of YouTube Premium users for English search queries, and the AI-generated results are most likely to surface when users search for information about products, or for locations and things to do in those locations. Two example searches provided include "best noise cancelling headphones" and "museums to visit in San Francisco."<br/>
<br/>
YouTube has not provided details on what the AI will prioritize, so video creators may have another metric to optimize for in the future should this functionality see a wider rollout.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube/">YouTube</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/youtube-search-results-ai-overviews/">YouTube Tests AI Overviews in Search Results</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-tests-ai-overviews-in-search-results.2455918/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta Officially Changes Threads Domain Name, Adds New Web Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/threads-web-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-officially-changes-threads-domain-name-adds-new-web-features.2455916/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:02:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/threads-web-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Meta <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2025/04/new-features-threads-web-experience/">today announced</a> that it is adding several new web features to the Threads social network, as well as officially relocating the website to a new domain. Threads is migrating from Threads.net to Threads.com, and Threads.com will be the new default domain name.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/threads-web-improvements.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999712" /><br/>
When Threads launched in 2023, Meta did not own Threads.com, so it was located at Threads.net. Meta acquired Threads.com in September 2024, and since then, the Threads.com domain forwarded to Threads.net. Going forward, users who type Threads.net into a browser window will be forwarded to Threads.com.<br/>
<br/>
To accompany the name change, Threads on the web is getting several interface updates to make browsing through posts on the social network easier.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>When using a single column view, custom feeds will be shown on the top of the web page in the same order they appear in mobile.</li><br/>
 	<li>Liked and saved posts can be accessed through the main menu icon.</li><br/>
 	<li>A column can be added by clicking on the column icon on the right-hand side of the screen.</li><br/>
 	<li>A Threads post can be copied as an image instead of being captured in a screenshot, which allows posts to be shared on Instagram and other social networks.</li><br/>
 	<li>Clicking the "+" button at the bottom of the screen shows a pop up composer that follows your cursor as you scroll through feeds.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Meta is also testing a feature that allows users to upload the list of people they follow on other apps to Threads, starting with X.<br/>
<br/>
Meta says that it plans to continue to provide updates to the Threads web experience, with more web updates coming in the near future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/threads-web-features/">Meta Officially Changes Threads Domain Name, Adds New Web Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-officially-changes-threads-domain-name-adds-new-web-features.2455916/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Debuts Dialogue-Only Subtitles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/netflix-debuts-dialogue-only-subtitles/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-debuts-dialogue-only-subtitles.2455913/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:24:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/netflix-debuts-dialogue-only-subtitles/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix <a href="https://about.netflix.com/en/news/introducing-a-new-way-to-experience-subtitles">today announced</a> that it is introducing a new subtitle option that only shows subtitles for spoken dialogue, aimed at those who don't need captions, but prefer to watch movies and TV shows with the subtitles turned on.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884791" /><br/>
According to Netflix, nearly half of all viewing hours on the streaming service in the U.S. happen with the subtitles or captions on, which is why it is debuting the new setting.<br/>
<br/>
The new option will show subtitles for dialogue, but no audio cues such as [phone buzzing], [door slams], or [fireplace crackling], which are normally shown when closed captioning is turned on. Netflix says the option will be available on new titles that are coming to Netflix, starting with the final season of YOU that launched today.<br/>
<br/>
The dialogue-only subtitle setting can be selected by opening up the language picker when watching a Netflix show and choosing the "English" option. "English CC" will have both dialogue and audio cues as normal.<br/>
<br/>
Going forward, dialogue-only subtitles will be available for all new Netflix originals in every language that Netflix offers in addition to the SDH and CC options.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/netflix-debuts-dialogue-only-subtitles/">Netflix Debuts Dialogue-Only Subtitles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-debuts-dialogue-only-subtitles.2455913/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Secret Robotics Team Gets New Leadership</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-robotics-team-leadership-change/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-secret-robotics-team-gets-new-leadership.2455906/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 13:25:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-robotics-team-leadership-change/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Robot</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>John Giannandrea</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is removing another project from AI chief John Giannandrea, and he will no longer oversee Apple's secret robotics division, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-04-24/apple-to-strip-secret-robotics-unit-from-ai-chief-weeks-after-moving-siri">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-Robot-Emoji-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990175" /><br/>
After Apple failed to deliver promised <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features on time under Giannandrea's leadership, Apple asked <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/20/siri-leadership-shakeup/">Vision Pro chief Mike Rockwell</a> to oversee the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; team and future &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; development instead.<br/>
<br/>
Now the robotics team will make a similar move, transitioning to the hardware division where robotics development will be overseen by Apple senior vice president John Ternus instead of Giannandrea. Giannandrea continues to head up Apple's AI and machine learning efforts, and changing the robotics team leadership will give his team more time to focus on new artificial intelligence features. Giannandrea has hundreds fewer engineers to manage, and the shift is a clear indication that Apple leadership does not feel that he can lead multiple teams.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is making major management changes in order to further prioritize &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;, as it needs to catch up with Google, OpenAI, Perplexity, and other AI companies that are leagues ahead in AI development.<br/>
<br/>
Kevin Lynch, who oversaw the development of the Apple Watch and Apple's now-canceled car, is leading the robotics team. Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-robot/">several robotics projects</a> in the works, and a tabletop robot with an arm that can move around an iPad-style display could be the first device to come from the robot team. Apple is also planning for a more mobile robot that would be more like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> on wheels able to carry out simple tasks, place calls, and answer queries.<br/>
<br/>
Ternus is a top Apple exec and he has worked on some of Apple's biggest products, overseeing the hardware engineering of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Mac, and other devices. He already oversees another hardware engineering team working on robotics and smart home technologies, and <em>Bloomberg</em> suggests that Apple's move to merge the two robotics teams could indicate that Apple is ramping up robot development.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-robot/">Apple Robot</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/john-giannandrea/">John Giannandrea</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-robotics-team-leadership-change/">Apple&#039;s Secret Robotics Team Gets New Leadership</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-secret-robotics-team-gets-new-leadership.2455906/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains How AI-Generated App Store Review Summaries Work in iOS 18.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-ai-generated-review-summaries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-ai-generated-app-store-review-summaries-work-in-ios-18-4.2455904/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 12:54:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-ai-generated-review-summaries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of iOS 18.4, Apple introduced a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> feature that summarizes multiple user reviews to provide an at-a-glance summary of what people think of an app or a game. In a new blog post on its <a href="https://machinelearning.apple.com/research/app-store-review">Machine Learning Research blog</a>, Apple provides some detail on how &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; review summaries work.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/app-store-review-summaries.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993504" /><br/>
Apple is using a multi-step large language model (LLM) system to generate the summaries, with the aim of creating overviews that are inclusive, balanced, and accurately reflect the user's voice. Apple says that it prioritizes "safety, fairness, truthfulness, and helpfulness" in its summaries, while outlining some of the challenges in aggregating &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; reviews.<br/>
<br/>
With new app releases, features, and bug fixes, reviews can change, so Apple's summarizations have to dynamically adapt to stay relevant, while also being able to aggregate both short and long reviews. Some reviews also include off-topic comments or noise, which the LLM needs to filter out.<br/>
<br/>
To begin with, Apple's LLM ignores reviews that have spam, profanity, or fraud. Remaining reviews are then processed through a sequence of LLM-powered modules that extract key insights from each review, aggregating themes that reoccur, balancing positive and negative takes, and then generating a summary that's around 100 to 300 characters in length.<br/>
<br/>
Apple uses specially trained LLMs for each step in the process, ensuring that the summaries are an accurate reflection of user sentiment. During the development of the feature, thousands of summaries were reviewed by human raters to assess factors like helpfulness, composition, and safety.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://machinelearning.apple.com/research/app-store-review">full blog post</a> goes into more detail on each step of the summary generation process, and it is worth checking out for those who are interested in the way that Apple is approaching LLMs.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-ai-generated-review-summaries/">Apple Explains How AI-Generated App Store Review Summaries Work in iOS 18.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-ai-generated-app-store-review-summaries-work-in-ios-18-4.2455904/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPadOS 19 Rumored to Show Mac-Like Menu Bar When Connected to Magic Keyboard</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ipados-19-mac-like-menu-bar-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-19-rumored-to-show-mac-like-menu-bar-when-connected-to-magic-keyboard.2455902/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 12:09:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ipados-19-mac-like-menu-bar-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Magic Keyboard</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When an iPad running iPadOS 19 is connected to a Magic Keyboard, a macOS-like menu bar will appear on the screen, <a href="https://majinbuofficial.com/ipados-19-and-ios-19-new-features/">according to the leaker Majin Bu</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ipad-air-magic-keyboard-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992623" /><br/>
This change would further blur the lines between the iPad and the Mac. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman previously claimed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/13/ipados-19-more-like-macos/">iPadOS 19 will be "more like macOS,"</a> with unspecified improvements to productivity, multitasking, and app window management, and the addition of a macOS-like menu bar would certainly align with that overall plan.<br/>
<br/>
In a blog post today, the leaker also claimed that iPadOS 19 will enhance Stage Manager, the feature that lets you use multiple apps at once on an external display. The leaker said that Stage Manager will work more seamlessly, but they did not provide any specific details about the alleged improvements. They also said that iOS 19 will enable at least a basic version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ios-19-iphone-stage-manager-rumor/">Stage Manager on iPhone models with a USB-C port</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The first beta of iPadOS 19 should be available after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">WWDC 2025 keynote on June 9</a>, but some new features are not enabled until later betas.<br/>
<br/>
Majin Bu has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">mixed track record with Apple rumors</a>, with some hits and some misses.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-keyboard/">Magic Keyboard</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ipados-19-mac-like-menu-bar-rumor/">iPadOS 19 Rumored to Show Mac-Like Menu Bar When Connected to Magic Keyboard</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-19-rumored-to-show-mac-like-menu-bar-when-connected-to-magic-keyboard.2455902/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Rumored to Add Stage Manager Support to USB-C iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ios-19-iphone-stage-manager-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-rumored-to-add-stage-manager-support-to-usb-c-iphones.2455901/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 11:49:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ios-19-iphone-stage-manager-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		<category>Stage Manager</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A leaker known as <a href="https://x.com/majinbuofficial">Majin Bu</a> today claimed that iOS 19 will enable support for at least a limited version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a> on iPhone models with a USB-C port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/ipados-16-stage-manager.jpg" alt="" width="3574" height="2006" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849728" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://majinbuofficial.com/ipados-19-and-ios-19-new-features/">blog post</a> citing sources, the leaker said that when an iPhone with a USB-C port is connected to an external display, users will be able to take advantage of a Stage Manager-like interface with multiple apps open at once on the screen. However, he said that there might be more limitations compared to Stage Manager on iPads.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone models with a USB-C port include all iPhone 15 models and newer.<br/>
<br/>
iPhones with both Lightning and USB-C ports can already be connected to external displays, but only for basic screen mirroring.<br/>
<br/>
The first developer beta of iOS 19 should be available immediately after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">WWDC 2025 keynote on June 9</a>, and the software update is expected to be released to the general public in September. It is unclear if Stage Manager support on USB-C iPhones would be available in the first beta, or enabled later in the iOS 19 software cycle.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung offers a similar feature called DeX on its Galaxy smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
Majin Bu has a mixed track record with Apple rumors, with some hits and some misses. They were one of the sources who accurately claimed that the device succeeding the iPhone SE <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/18/iphone-16e-name-is-likely/">would be named the iPhone 16e</a>, but they also inaccurately claimed that the device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/iphone-se-dynamic-island-rumor/">would have a Dynamic Island</a> instead of a notch. They also accurately leaked the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-may-introduce-redesigned-milanese-loop/">redesigned Milanese Loop for the Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/iphone-16-pro-color-desert-titanium/">Desert Titanium color name for iPhone 16 Pro models</a>, several iPhone cases, and much more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ios-19-iphone-stage-manager-rumor/">iOS 19 Rumored to Add Stage Manager Support to USB-C iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-rumored-to-add-stage-manager-support-to-usb-c-iphones.2455901/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stores Giving Away a Limited-Edition Pin For Free Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-stores-to-give-away-special-pin/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-giving-away-a-limited-edition-pin-for-free-today.2455897/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 10:15:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-stores-to-give-away-special-pin/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting today, April 24, Apple Stores around the world are giving away a special pin for free to customers who request one, while supplies last.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Global-Close-Your-Rings-Day-Pin.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999653" /><em>Photo Credit: <a href="https://choreographics.me/">Filip Chudzinski</a></em></div><br/>
The enamel pin's design is inspired by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/apple-celebrates-10-years-of-activity-rings/">Global Close Your Rings Day award</a> in the Activity app, which Apple Watch users can receive by closing all three Activity rings today. The limited-edition pin is the physical counterpart to that digital award.<br/>
<br/>
To receive the pin, simply visit an Apple Store and ask an employee about it. We were able to receive the pin without having our Activity rings closed yet today, so that does not appear to be a requirement, but your mileage may vary.<br/>
<br/>
Given that Apple says the pin is only available while supplies last, keep in mind that some stores might already be out of them.<br/>
<br/>
Here is what Apple said about the pin in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/04/get-active-with-apple-watch/">press release</a>:<blockquote>To celebrate Global Close Your Rings Day, customers can obtain a special pin inspired by the award. Customers can pick up a pin at Apple Store locations worldwide starting April 24, while supplies last.</blockquote>The original Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-watch-launched-10-years-ago-today/">launched 10 years ago today</a>, on April 24, 2015, so the pin is a tiny momento of the anniversary.<br/>
<br/>
Here is what Apple Watch chief Jeff Williams said about the 10-year anniversary:<blockquote>Apple Watch has changed the way people think about, monitor, and engage with their fitness and health. A decade ago, we introduced Activity rings  and since then, Apple Watch has grown to offer an extensive set of features designed to empower every user. People write to us almost every day sharing how Apple Watch has made a difference in their life, from motivating them to move more throughout the day, to changing the trajectory of their health.</blockquote>If you received the pin, feel free to share a photo in our forums.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-stores-to-give-away-special-pin/">Apple Stores Giving Away a Limited-Edition Pin For Free Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-giving-away-a-limited-edition-pin-for-free-today.2455897/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Ad Highlights a Key Advantage Over Android Smartphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-16-trust-issues-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-ad-highlights-a-key-advantage-over-android-smartphones.2455895/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:55:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-16-trust-issues-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Ceramic Shield</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gdR32VJQ6aE">shared a new ad</a> that highlights a key advantage that iPhone 16 models have over Android smartphones: the Ceramic Shield.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gdR32VJQ6aE?si=itLlgheWt0fqR26E" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Apple says the iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max displays are all protected by the latest-generation Ceramic Shield material, which is advertised as being "2x tougher than glass on any other smartphone."<br/>
<br/>
In the new "Trust Issues" ad, a father hands his iPhone to a stranger and asks them to take a photo of his family at a carnival. Unfortunately, the stranger drops the iPhone, leading to a moment of suspense given the device might have been damaged. However, the display glass remains intact due to the Ceramic Shield.<br/>
<br/>
"Relax, it's iPhone 16," the video description concludes.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, your mileage may vary.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the Ceramic Shield on all iPhone 12 models, and it has continued to improve the glass-ceramic material's formulation over the years.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ceramic-shield/">Ceramic Shield</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-16-trust-issues-ad/">iPhone 16 Ad Highlights a Key Advantage Over Android Smartphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-ad-highlights-a-key-advantage-over-android-smartphones.2455895/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Air Launching Later This Year With These 16 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-16-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-launching-later-this-year-with-these-16-new-features.2455888/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:24:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-16-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the so-called "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>" is not expected to launch until September, there are already plenty of rumors about the ultra-thin device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Air-Pastel-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999629" /><br/>
Overall, the iPhone 17 Air sounds like a mixed bag. While the device is expected to have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/iphone-17-air-thinness-video/">impressively thin and light design</a>, rumors indicate it will have some compromises compared to iPhone 17 Pro models, including only a single rear camera, a single speaker, and an A19 chip instead of a more powerful A19 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DawhWztSaI0?si=1WqzCEvZIpAB8PW2" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
While there have been some concerns that the iPhone 17 Air's thin design could result in limited battery life, the device might end up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-price-battery-life-more/">beating expectations</a>. There are three rumored features for the iPhone 17 Air that could contribute to longer battery life than one might imagine, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/iphone-17-air-high-density-battery-rumor/">a higher-density battery</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/iphone-16e-battery-life/">Apple's power-efficient C1 modem</a>, and the lack of an Ultra Wide camera providing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/28/iphone-16e-teardown/">more internal space for a larger battery</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we recap 16 key rumors for the iPhone 17 Air as of April 2025:<ul><li>The thinnest iPhone ever, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">measuring just 5.5mm at its thinnest point</a>, but possibly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/iphone-17-air-9-5mm-thick-including-camera/">up to 9.5mm with the rear camera bump included</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">6.6-inch OLED display</a> with Face ID <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">and a Dynamic Island</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/ltpo-for-all-iphone-17-models-report/">ProMotion support</a> for up to a 120Hz refresh rate</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">A19 chip</a> instead of A19 Pro chip</li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">single 48-megapixel rear camera</a> on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/17/iphone-17-air-front-page-tech-renders/">all-new elongated camera bar</a></li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">24-megapixel front camera</a></li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">single speaker</a> in the earpiece, no bottom speaker</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/">Apple-designed Wi-Fi 7 chip</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apples-c1-modem-iphone-17-air-lack-mmwave/">Apple-designed C1 modem for cellular connectivity</a></li><br/>
<li>eSIM only, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">no physical SIM card slot</a> worldwide</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/slimmer-iphones-without-usb-c-ports/">USB-C port</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/iphone-17-air-high-density-battery-rumor/">High-density battery</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-price-battery-life-more/">Camera Control button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-magsafe-action-button/">Action button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-magsafe-action-button/">MagSafe</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Newly reported today:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">12GB of RAM</a>, exceeding the minimum for Apple Intelligence</li></ul>Bookmark our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air roundup</a> to stay up to date with more rumors in the coming months.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-16-new-features/">iPhone 17 Air Launching Later This Year With These 16 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-launching-later-this-year-with-these-16-new-features.2455888/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Air Now Rumored to Feature 12GB of RAM Like the Pro Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-now-rumored-to-feature-12gb-of-ram-like-the-pro-models.2455885/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:41:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The rumored ultra-thin "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>" model will be equipped with 12GB of RAM, according to the latest word from Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iPhone-17-Air-Size-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993585" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/luXVWtplQ9Bokb">blog post</a> today, the well-known Apple supply chain analyst said that the iPhone 17 Air, iPhone 17 Pro, and iPhone 17 Pro Max will all be equipped with 12GB of RAM. He previously only expected the iPhone 17 Pro Max to have 12GB of RAM, so this is good news for customers who will be purchasing the other models.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said even the base-model iPhone 17 might be equipped with 12GB of RAM, but only if supply chain shortages can be overcome. He said that Apple will make a final decision on the amount of RAM it will offer in this device by May.<br/>
<br/>
All of the models in the iPhone 16 lineup are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/all-iphone-16-models-have-8gb-ram/">equipped with 8GB of RAM</a>, so the jump to 12GB would be a significant increase. Increased RAM can contribute to improved performance for Apple Intelligence and multitasking.<br/>
<br/>
Even if the base-model iPhone 17 sticks with 8GB of RAM, Kuo said he expects all models in the iPhone 18 lineup to have 12GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said the increased RAM will primarily benefit Apple suppliers Micron and SK Hynix.<br/>
<br/>
Apple should announce the iPhone 17 series in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">iPhone 17 Air Now Rumored to Feature 12GB of RAM Like the Pro Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-now-rumored-to-feature-12gb-of-ram-like-the-pro-models.2455885/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch SE Hits &#36;169.97 Low Price on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/amazon-apple-watch-se/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-hits-169-97-low-price-on-amazon.2455883/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:28:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/amazon-apple-watch-se/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is discounting the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.97</strong></a> today, down from &#36;249.00. This is just a few cents away from the best price we've tracked so far in 2025, and it's available in Starlight, Silver, and Midnight Aluminum color options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/new-apple-watch-se-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998411" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has four 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE at this price, including multiple sizes of the Sport Band model. Most are in stock and available to be delivered by the end of April.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, you can get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE at the low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ2NM9S%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;199.97</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This one is available in Midnight and Starlight Aluminum colors, and in both Sport Loop and Sport Band options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ2NM9S%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/amazon-apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE Hits &#36;169.97 Low Price on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-hits-169-97-low-price-on-amazon.2455883/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
