<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:03:03 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C Hit Best-Ever Price of &#36;189.99 for All Your New Year&#039;s Resolution Fitness Needs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/02/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-new-years/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-hit-best-ever-price-of-189-99-for-all-your-new-years-resolution-fitness-needs.2415242/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 08:04:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/02/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-new-years/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is kicking off the new year with an all-time low price on Apple's AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. There's an estimated delivery date of January 7 for most residences in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-Pro-Case-With-USB-C.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909509" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
We haven't tracked an all-time low price on this model of the AirPods Pro 2 since around early December. This is largely the same model as the AirPods Pro 2 from 2022, with the addition of a USB-C port on the MagSafe Charging Case, instead of Lightning.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
A few other noteworthy AirPods deals include the AirPods 3 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;149.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00, and the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. Stock on the AirPods 3 has begun to dwindle with delivery into mid January, but the AirPods 2 has the same estimates as the AirPods Pro 2.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/02/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-new-years/">Apple&#039;s AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C Hit Best-Ever Price of &#36;189.99 for All Your New Year&#039;s Resolution Fitness Needs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-hit-best-ever-price-of-189-99-for-all-your-new-years-resolution-fitness-needs.2415242/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sketchy Rumor Says Vision Pro Will Launch in Final Week of January</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/02/vision-pro-could-launch-in-last-week-of-january/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sketchy-rumor-says-vision-pro-will-launch-in-final-week-of-january.2415237/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:09:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/02/vision-pro-could-launch-in-last-week-of-january/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset will launch in the last week of January, a sketchy online report coming out of China claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
The information comes from <a href="https://wallstreetcn.com/livenews/2603883"><em>Wall Street Insights</em></a>, a Chinese investor news service with an unproven track record for Apple rumors. The website claims to have obtained exclusive information suggesting that the Vision Pro will launch on Saturday, January 27 in the United States. While the report clearly says that the launch is set to occur on a date that falls on a Saturday in the United States, there is a chance that the website is actually referring to January 27 in China, which falls on Friday, January 26 in the United States – a much more likely date for the launch of the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has rarely launched any of its hardware products on Saturdays, so it seems very unlikely that the Vision Pro headset would be the first. The company likely prefers to launch products on weekdays to align with normal business hours, ensuring maximum media coverage and stock market reaction. Friday, January 26 is likely also a more accurate interpretation since Apple overwhelmingly chooses Fridays to launch its new devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple simply says that the Vision Pro headset will launch "early" this year and has not yet announced any specific time frame for pre-orders and the product's launch. Oft-accurate Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/">recently said</a> that he expects the Vision Pro to hit shelves in late January or early February, which effectively lines up with this latest report from China. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, on the other hand, has been firmer in saying that Apple is planning the device's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/vision-pro-february-launch/">retail launch for February</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/02/vision-pro-could-launch-in-last-week-of-january/">Sketchy Rumor Says Vision Pro Will Launch in Final Week of January</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sketchy-rumor-says-vision-pro-will-launch-in-final-week-of-january.2415237/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What Do You Want to See From Apple in 2024?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-in-2024.2415161/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 08:03:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-2024&#038;post_date=1704135821/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last Friday, we shared our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-what-to-expect-2024/">annual What to Expect Guide</a> that covers everything we're expecting to see from Apple in 2024, based on current rumors and historical product release information.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/What-to-Expect-from-Apple-in-2024-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928304" /><br/>
We're going to see the launch of the Vision Pro early in the year, followed by new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a> models, a new version of the AirPods, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> in a new size, an Apple Watch that has blood pressure monitoring and sleep detection, and of course, refreshed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models with a host of new features.<br/>
<br/>
While we know what we're expecting to see from Apple in 2024, we want to hear from the <em>MacRumors</em> community. What are you hoping to see Apple release this year?<br/>
<br/>
Are you looking forward to generative AI? Crossing your fingers for new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> features? What would you like to see in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>? Will you buy Apple's Vision Pro headset?<br/>
<br/>
Let us know your thoughts in the comments, and take a look at our What to Expect Guide to see an overview of the current rumors. We'll be hearing a lot more about Apple's 2024 product plans in the coming months, and we'll have in-depth coverage at MacRumors.com.<br/>
<br/>
If you want to discuss Apple's upcoming products, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com">our <em>MacRumors</em> forums</a> are an excellent resource, plus they're a great place to get help on current Apple products, software, and so much more.<br/>
<br/>
We'd like to thank our readers and our forum members for making <em>MacRumors</em> the number one source for Apple news, rumors, and advice. <em>MacRumors</em> celebrated its 23rd birthday this year, and that's thanks to our dedicated supporters. We are looking forward to another year of rumors and product launches in 2024. Happy New Year!<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-2024/">What Do You Want to See From Apple in 2024?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-do-you-want-to-see-from-apple-in-2024.2415161/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Products We&#039;re NOT Expecting to Launch in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/apple-products-were-not-expecting-to-launch-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-products-were-not-expecting-to-launch-in-2024.2415157/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 07:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/apple-products-were-not-expecting-to-launch-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2024 is shaping up to be a busy year for Apple with a large number of important new releases due across the company's product lines, but there are some noticeable absences from its rumored plans. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-Logo-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-924188" /><br/>
Using information from various analysts and reliable sources, here's everything we're no longer expecting Apple to release this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPhone SE 4</h3><br/>
While Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/06/iphone-se-4-canceled-kuo/">previously rumored</a> to be planning the launch of the fourth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> for 2024, the company is now widely expected to release the device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/12/iphone-se-5g-modem-2025-launch-rumor/">in 2025</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/iphone-se-4-modified-flag-edges.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-886982" /><br/>
The current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; launched in March 2022, meaning that it will be at least 33 months old by the time its successor arrives. The next-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is expected to feature a design <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/">based on the iPhone 14</a>, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/11/suppliers-bidding-on-iphone-se-4-displays/">OLED display</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-se-4-reuse-iphone-14-battery/">larger battery</a>, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/iphone-se-4-to-feature-action-button-and-more/">Action Button, USB-C port, Face ID</a>, and potentially Apple's first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/27/kuo-iphone-se-4-oled-display/">custom 5G cellular modem</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>AirTag 2</h3><br/>
Production of the second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> tracker was apparently due to kick off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/02/kuo-new-airtag-production-late-2024/">in the fourth quarter of 2024</a>, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/airtag-2-postponed-until-2025/">latest forecast</a> from Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> claims that the accessory will not reach mass production and be released until 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/AirTag-2-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-917578" /><br/>
According to Kuo, the second-generation &zwnj;AirTag&zwnj; will be part of a new spatial computing ecosystem that Apple is building, with the Vision Pro serving as the core to integrate other devices. A new &zwnj;AirTag&zwnj; would likely incorporate Apple's second-generation Ultra Wideband chip that debuted in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, allowing for even more precise tracking at longer distances.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MicroLED Apple Watch Ultra</h3><br/>
The first Apple device to offer a microLED display will apparently be an upcoming Apple Watch Ultra model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/microled-apple-watch-still-on-track-for-2025/">released in late 2025</a> or 2026. In fact, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-3-in-2024-odds-decreasing/">may not update</a> the Apple Watch Ultra in 2024 and hold off for the significant display upgrade the following year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/Apple-Watch-Ultra-Black-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-905396" /><br/>
Apple's plan to bring a microLED display to the Apple Watch Ultra is very widely corroborated, starting with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/10/microled-apple-watch-2025/">report</a> from display analyst Ross Young in January 2023. The microLED display is expected to be 2.12-inches in size, a 10% increase over the display of the current Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
The advanced display technology offers improved brightness, color reproduction, dynamic range, viewing angles, and efficiency, making images look more like they are "painted" atop the display glass. The project is part of Apple's plan to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/06/apple-microled-struggle-led-to-reliance-on-samsung/">reduce its reliance on Samsung</a> as a supplier while yielding benefits from engineering its own displays in-house, just like its chip technology.<br/>
<br/>
While <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/02/cheaper-airpods-and-micro-led-apple-watch-rumors/">initial reports</a> distinctively placed the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a> Ultra in 2024, the latest reports point to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/10/microled-apple-watch-2025/">late 2025</a> or potentially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-to-launch-in-2026/">even 2026</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iMac Pro</h3><br/>
Apple is still rumored to be working on a high-end "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> Pro" model with a 32-inch mini-LED display and a larger <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/10/30/imac-pro-2022-rumors/">selection of ports</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iMac-Pro-2022-27-and-24-iMac.jpg" alt="" width="1626" height="914" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833952" /><br/>
Despite the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/19/imac-pro-officially-discontinued/">discontinuation of the iMac Pro</a> and any &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; models larger than 24-inches in 2021, Apple is still said to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/26/imac-with-over-30-inch-display/">plans to launch</a> a substantially bigger and more powerful &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; model.<br/>
<br/>
While <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/new-32-inch-imac-pro-expected-2024-or-2025/">floated the possibility</a> of the machine launching in late 2024, 2025 may be a more likely time frame.   &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj; has similarly said that the new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">launch in 2025</a>, so the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; may well continue to be the only Apple all-in-one desktop available this year. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Foldable iPhone and iPad</h3><br/>
Apple has been known to be working on foldable display technology for many years, filing multiple patents related to the technology, but a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> still seems to be quite some time away.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1458" height="820" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-797663" /><br/>
Rumors in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/09/10/apple-orders-samsung-foldable-display-samples/">September 2020</a> indicated that Samsung was providing foldable display samples to Apple for a future foldable ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌, but there had been no strong indication that Apple was planning to use Samsung's technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-foldable-panels-samsung-display/">until recently</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In 2021, <em>Bloomberg</em> claimed that Apple had started "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/15/iphone-13-in-display-fingerprint-sensor/">early work</a>" on an ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ with a foldable display, but that it had not committed to releasing a foldable device at that time. Development in 2021 had not expanded beyond a display, and Apple did not have full foldable ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ prototypes. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj; initially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/20/kuo-iphones-with-under-screen-touch-id-now-coming-in-2023-foldable-iphone-in-2024/">said</a> that Apple would introduce a foldable ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ in 2024, but in 2022, he revised his prediction and said that Apple is unlikely to unveil a foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; until <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/01/apple-testing-9-inch-foldable/">2025 or later</a>. Display analyst Ross Young has also suggested <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/21/apple-exploring-20-inch-foldable-macbook/">2025</a> is the earliest that we might see a foldable ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to bring a foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to market before a foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but for the time being, the company is said to be focused on expanding OLED displays throughout the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Mac lineups and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/apple-focusing-on-oled-rather-than-foldable-ipad/">considering the potential</a> of offering a foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; even further in the future.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/apple-products-were-not-expecting-to-launch-in-2024/">Apple Products We&#039;re NOT Expecting to Launch in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-products-were-not-expecting-to-launch-in-2024.2415157/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Five Productivity Apps to Kick-Start the New Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/five-apps-to-start-the-new-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/five-productivity-apps-to-kick-start-the-new-year.2415079/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 02:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/five-apps-to-start-the-new-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac Apps</category>
		<category>Top iOS Apps</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apps can play a pivotal role in helping to reach new goals, form habits, or simply improve personal productivity –  here's five you should consider adopting going into 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Sqaure-Complement.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833993" /><br/>
Each app we've chosen for this list has a unique ability to aid Apple device users in various aspects of personal and professional development. From sophisticated task management to habit formation, these apps offer a wide range of functionalities tailored to meet the diverse needs of users seeking to make the most out of the upcoming year. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/things-3/id904237743">Things 3</a></strong> (&#36;9.99 for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch, &#36;19.99 for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and &#36;49.99 for Mac): Things 3 is a popular task manager designed for Apple devices, offering a more robust feature set compared to Apple's default Reminders app. It stands out for its elegant and user-friendly interface and powerful features like project planning, deadlines, Markdown support, and more. These capabilities make it an outstanding tool for anyone looking to bring more structure to the tasks in their personal and professional life at the start of the new year.</li><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/obsidian-connected-notes/id1557175442">Obsidian</a></strong> (free): Obsidian is a versatile Markdown note-taking application that surpasses the capabilities of Apple Notes with its distinctive approach to personal knowledge management and plug-ins. Unlike most note-taking apps, Obsidian specializes in linking thoughts and ideas through a network of interconnected notes, creating a personal knowledge base that grows and evolves over time. Obsidian's ability to map out and visually connect goals, plans, and ideas could be incredibly valuable going into the new year.</li><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/streaks/id963034692">Streaks</a></strong> (&#36;4.99): Streaks is a habit-forming app designed to help users establish and maintain good habits by leveraging the psychological power of "streaks" or consecutive days of completing a specific task. What sets Streaks apart is its focus on consistency and incremental progress, encouraging users to build small, daily habits of their choosing that lead to significant long-term changes in behavior – perfect for sticking to those tricky New Year's resolutions.</li><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fantastical-calendar/id718043190">Fantastical</a></strong> (free, "Premium" subscription available): Fantastical is a calendar application known for its superior functionality and user-friendly interface, distinguishing it from the default Calendar app. It offers a range of features that enhance scheduling and time management, such as natural language parsing and a highly customizable view that integrates tasks and reminders alongside calendar events. This makes Fantastical a perfect tool for anyone seeking to start the new year with better time management.</li><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/chatgpt/id6448311069">ChatGPT</a></strong> (free, "Plus" subscription available): ChatGPT is a conversational AI tool that offers users an interactive platform for various tasks and queries. It can provide assistance across a wide range of areas, such as generating creative ideas, offering productivity tips, helping with language learning, or even providing motivation and mental wellness advice. ChatGPT's capacity to provide instant, informed responses on a diverse range of topics makes it an excellent tool for anyone seeking a reliable and intelligent digital assistant to enhance their daily productivity or learning.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Are there any other productivity apps that you'd recommend to start the new year? Let us know in the comments. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-apps/">Mac Apps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-ios-apps/">Top iOS Apps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/five-apps-to-start-the-new-year/">Five Productivity Apps to Kick-Start the New Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/five-productivity-apps-to-kick-start-the-new-year.2415079/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Just Broke a Tradition It Held for 12 Years</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/apple-just-broke-a-tradition-it-held-for-12-years/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-just-broke-a-tradition-it-held-for-12-years.2415136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/apple-just-broke-a-tradition-it-held-for-12-years/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has broken a tradition it maintained for 12 years, releasing no new iPads in 2023 – the first time that the company has chosen to not launch a new tablet in an entire calendar year since the introduction of the product line.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/aapl-logo-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="890" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-776656" /><br/>
From its debut in 2010, the iPad has been an important product for Apple and the clear tablet market leader, releasing at least one new model every year. In recent times, the company has released as many as four new iPad models per year. Before 2023, 2009 was the last year with no new iPads, simply because the product line had not yet launched. <br/>
<br/>
The most recent iPad launches took place in October 2022. The only iPad-adjacent hardware released in 2023 was the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">Apple Pencil with USB-C</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>2010</strong>: iPad (1st generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2011</strong>: iPad 2</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2012</strong>: iPad (3rd generation), iPad (4th generation), and iPad mini (1st generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2013</strong>: iPad Air (1st generation) and iPad mini 2</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2014</strong>: iPad Air 2 and iPad mini 3</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2015</strong>: iPad mini 4 and iPad Pro 12.9-inch (1st generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2016</strong>: iPad Pro 9.7-inch</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2017</strong>: iPad (5th generation), iPad Pro 12.9-inch (2nd generation), and iPad Pro 10.5-inch</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2018</strong>: iPad (6th generation), iPad Pro 11-inch (1st generation), and iPad Pro 12.9-inch (3rd generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2019</strong>: iPad (7th generation), iPad Air (3rd generation), and iPad mini (5th generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2020</strong>: iPad (8th generation), iPad Air (4th generation), iPad Pro 11-inch (2nd generation), and iPad Pro 12.9-inch (4th generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2021</strong>: iPad (9th generation), iPad mini (6th generation), iPad Pro 11-inch (3rd generation), and iPad Pro 12.9-inch (5th generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2022</strong>: iPad (10th generation), iPad Air (5th generation), iPad Pro 11-inch (4th generation), and iPad Pro 12.9-inch (6th generation)</li><br/>
    <li><strong>2023</strong>: <em>None</em></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
This hiatus in new iPad releases is noteworthy considering the history of the product line and could signal a moment of reflection about the direction of the device. As the iPad has become more advanced and widely adopted, the urgency for frequent upgrades has diminished for many potential customers. This shift in consumer behavior could have prompted Apple to reevaluate its tablet strategy, focusing on more impactful and less frequent hardware updates.<br/>
<br/>
Another aspect to consider is the criticism Apple has faced regarding the increasing complexity of the iPad lineup and questions around the direction of iPadOS. By taking a year off from new releases, Apple may be planning to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/what-the-2024-ipad-lineup-could-look-like/">reshape the lineup</a> with a clearer sense of purpose going forward.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors and analyst forecasts suggest that 2024 will be a much more significant year for the iPad lineup, with every model, encompassing the entry-level iPad, iPad mini, iPad Air, and iPad Pro, expected to receive a hardware refresh. With the rumored introduction of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">12.9-inch iPad Air</a> model, 2024 could see Apple launch an unprecedented six iPad models in a single calendar year. The flagship iPad Pro is expected to introduce at least <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/2024-ipad-pro-what-to-expect/">a dozen new features</a>, including OLED display technology, the M3 chip, and a new, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/27/new-ipad-pro-and-redesigned-magic-keyboard/">"laptop-like" keyboard accessory</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/01/apple-just-broke-a-tradition-it-held-for-12-years/">Apple Just Broke a Tradition It Held for 12 Years</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-just-broke-a-tradition-it-held-for-12-years.2415136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Watch Sales Resume, iOS Features Coming in 2024, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/30/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-resume/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-resume-ios-features-coming-in-2024-and-more.2415023/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/30/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-resume/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2023 is quickly drawing to close, so it's a traditional time for us to look back at everything that happened in the Apple world over the past year and look forward to what we're expecting to see in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/top-stories-30dec2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928492" /><br/>
While the news and rumor cycle largely slows down at this time of year, the past couple of weeks have been dominated by developments in a patent dispute that saw Apple forced to briefly halt U.S. sales of the latest Apple Watch models before a court paused the ban. Make sure to read on below for the latest developments in this case and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Once Again Available to Purchase From Apple's Online Store</h2><br/>
Last week, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-pausing-series-9-ultra-2-sales-in-us/">paused sales of the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 in the U.S.</a> due to a patent dispute with medical tech company Masimo related to blood oxygen sensing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-watch-ultra-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913279" /><br/>
In January, the U.S. International Trade Commission ruled that Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/11/apple-watch-masimo-patent-infringement/">infringed on a Masimo patent</a> related to blood oxygen sensing, and it ordered an import and sales ban for Apple Watch models offering the feature. However, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">Apple appealed the decision</a> in court and was granted a temporary stay, so the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">ban is lifted</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-online/">sales have resumed</a> for now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What to Expect From Apple in 2024: Vision Pro, iPhone 16 Models, Revamped iPad Pro and More</h2><br/>
Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset is expected to be the company's most important product of 2024, but there are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-what-to-expect-2024/">many other products to look forward to next year</a>, including the first iPad Pro models with OLED displays, a redesigned Apple Watch, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/What-to-Expect-from-Apple-in-2024-Feature-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928302" /><br/>
Check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-what-to-expect-2024/">complete guide to what we're expecting in 2024</a> to learn more about some of the most interesting devices and updates expected to launch next year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple in 2023: The Biggest Stories and Surprises of the Year</h2><br/>
2023 was a relatively iterative year for Apple product releases, but there were still <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/the-biggest-apple-news-stories-of-2023/">several notable announcements and surprises</a> throughout the year. Apple previewed its upcoming Vision Pro headset, the full-sized HomePod made a comeback, the iPhone finally switched to USB-C, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-in-2023-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928075" /><br/>
This week, we recapped the 10 biggest Apple news stories and surprises of the year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The MacRumors Show: 2023 Year in Review</h2><br/>
On the final episode of the year for The MacRumors Show podcast, hosts Dan Barbera and Hartley Charlton <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-2023-year-in-review/">took a look back at Apple's year</a>, which included a number of product launches and software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/The-MacRumors-Show-2023-Year-In-Review-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928482" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-qa/">Last week's episode</a> saw Dan and Hartley answer listener questions about Apple heading into 2024. Topics discussed include the Vision Pro, upcoming iPad models, app sideloading in the EU, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The MacRumors Show now has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, and you can also listen on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcast platform.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iOS Features Coming in 2024 for Messages, Apple Music, and More</h2><br/>
2024 is just a few days away, and there are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/new-ios-features-launching-in-2024/">many iOS 17 and iOS 18 features</a> that are expected to launch throughout the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912514" /><br/>
In a recent article, we listed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/new-ios-features-launching-in-2024/">eight new iOS features that are expected to launch on iPhones next year</a>, including Stolen Device Protection, collaborative Apple Music playlists, RCS support in the Messages app, generative AI functionality for Siri, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Kuo: Vision Pro Likely to Launch by Early February</h2><br/>
Apple will likely <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/">begin selling the Vision Pro in the U.S. in late January or early February</a>, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898552" /><br/>
Apple first announced the Vision Pro at WWDC in June, and said it would launch in the U.S. in early 2024, followed by more countries later in the year. Kuo estimates that Vision Pro shipments in 2024 will reach approximately 500,000 units, which would make it a low-volume product.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/dec-28-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/30/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-resume/">Top Stories: Apple Watch Sales Resume, iOS Features Coming in 2024, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-resume-ios-features-coming-in-2024-and-more.2415023/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sizes to Change Next Year: What to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/30/iphone-sizes-to-change-next-year-what-to-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sizes-to-change-next-year-what-to-know.2415015/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 04:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/30/iphone-sizes-to-change-next-year-what-to-know/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has not significantly tweaked <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> screen sizes since the introduction of the ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 12 models in 2020, but that's set to change with the 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models will have notably larger display sizes than the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models. Here's what we know.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">multiple sources</a>, the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;‌ and ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;‌ Max will feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/iphone-16-display-sizes/">increase in display size</a> compared to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;‌ Max, measuring roughly 6.3 inches and 6.9 inches, respectively. To be more precise, the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;‌ will have a 6.27-inch display (159.31 mm), while the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;‌ Max will feature a 6.85-inch (174.06 mm) screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="iphone_16_pro">iPhone 16 Pro</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Thickness</th><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>149.6 mm</td><br/>
 <td>146.6 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>71.45 mm</td><br/>
 <td>70.60 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Display</th><br/>
 <td>6.3" (159.31 mm)</td><br/>
 <td>6.1" (155.38 mm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>194 grams</td><br/>
 <td>187 grams</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><p></p><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="iphone_16_pro_max">iPhone 16 Pro Max</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Thickness</th><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>163.0 mm</td><br/>
 <td>159.9 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>77.58 mm</td><br/>
 <td>76.70 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Display</th><br/>
 <td>6.9" (174.06 mm)</td><br/>
 <td>6.7" (169.98 mm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>225 grams</td><br/>
 <td>221 grams</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><p></p><br/>
With the increase in display size, the dimensions of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s body will also increase. The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;‌ and 16 Pro Max will be slightly taller than their predecessors, while also being somewhat wider. <br/>
<br/>
The larger form factor of the devices will give Apple more internal space for components. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models could get larger, longer-lasting batteries for example. The display itself could see improvements, too (see below). Besides that, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/iphone-16-series-16-rumored-new-features/">plenty of additional features are rumored</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Display Technology</h2><br/>
Apple is weighing up the use of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">micro-lens technology</a> to maintain or increase the brightness of OLED displays on next year's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models while potentially reducing their power consumption. Micro-lens arrays or MLA uses a uniform pattern of billions of lenses inside the panel to reduce internal reflection. The reflected light increases perceived brightness without increasing power consumption.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/iPhone-14-Pro-Display-Two-Times-Brighter-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2504" height="1408" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862901" /><br/>
Next year's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; could feature a more power-efficient display thanks to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/iphone-16-more-efficient-oled-display/">new OLED material set</a> that is reportedly being developed by Samsung specifically for Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus</h2><br/>
We are not expecting size changes for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, and these devices will be the same size as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus. However, with the ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 17 and ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 17 Plus in 2025, Apple is expected to also bring the larger 6.27- and 6.86-inch display sizes to its two standard ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ models. As a result, expect the entire &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 lineup to use a taller aspect ratio of 19.6:9. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone Sizes: A Brief History</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>The Original iPhone to iPhone 4S (2007-2011):</strong> The first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, launched in 2007, featured a 3.5-inch screen, a size that Apple maintained up to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4S. This screen size was considered quite large at the time compared to many contemporary phones.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone 5 to iPhone 5S/SE (2012-2016):</strong> With the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5, Apple increased the screen size to 4 inches. This change addressed the growing consumer trend towards larger screens, allowing for an improved viewing experience while maintaining a comfortable grip.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone 6 and 6 Plus (2014):</strong> A significant change came with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 and 6 Plus, featuring screen sizes of 4.7 inches and 5.5 inches respectively. This move was a response to the burgeoning market of larger smartphones or "phablets." It marked Apple's foray into a segment that competitors like Samsung had been capitalizing on.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone 6S to iPhone 8 (2015-2017):</strong> The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6S, 7, and 8 series continued with the same size variants as their predecessors, 4.7 inches for the regular models and 5.5 inches for the Plus models.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone X and Beyond (2017-present):</strong> With the introduction of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X in 2017, Apple shifted to a new design paradigm, reducing bezels and introducing notch-based displays. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X had a 5.8-inch screen, which was a middle ground between the two previous sizes. Subsequent models expanded on this concept, with screen sizes increasing further in variants like the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS Max, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-11-pro/">iPhone 11 Pro Max</a>, and later models.</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 12 mini & iPhone 13 mini (2020-2021):</strong> The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a> was introduced in 2020, and marked the first time since the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> that Apple released a new model specifically designed to be smaller and more compact. Featuring a 5.4-inch screen, it catered to users who preferred smaller, more manageable phones that could be easily used with one hand. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> mini continued the trend, however reports and market analysis indicated that the overall demand for such a device was relatively low compared to Apple's larger models, and Apple has not replicated the option in &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineups since. </li><br/>
</ul>What do you think about Apple's expected &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; size changes? Share your thoughts in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/30/iphone-sizes-to-change-next-year-what-to-know/">iPhone Sizes to Change Next Year: What to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sizes-to-change-next-year-what-to-know.2415015/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple in 2024: Vision Pro, iPhone 16 Models, Revamped iPad Pro and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-what-to-expect-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apple-in-2024-vision-pro-iphone-16-models-revamped-ipad-pro-and-more.2414978/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:56:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-what-to-expect-2024&#038;post_date=1703890561/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2024 is going to start off strong with the launch of the Vision Pro, Apple's first major new product since the 2015 Apple Watch, and new iPads, Macs, AirPods, and iPhones are set to follow.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OVkawPHKLdw" title="Apple&#39;s New Products for 2024: Vision Pro, OLED iPad Pro, iPhone 16 &amp; More!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
There are some exciting products in the works, including a larger version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a>, updated iPhones, an Apple Watch with new health features, and more. In this guide, we've outlined everything that we know about the new products that are coming from Apple in 2024, based on current rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_vision_pro_february_2024">Apple Vision Pro (February 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">the Vision Pro headset</a> at WWDC in June 2023, but it's finally almost ready to launch. Apple introduced the Vision Pro early to give developers time to create apps for the device, and since then, Apple has been working on finalizing the hardware and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> operating system. The most recent rumors have suggested Apple will debut the Vision Pro in February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
At launch, the Vision Pro is only going to be available in the United States, and it sounds like Apple may require customers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-to-push-vision-pro-customers-to-pick-up/">to purchase in store</a> or pick up online orders in a store in order for Apple employees to provide the right Light Seal and knitted headband for a good fit, plus Zeiss prescription lens inserts for those who need them.<br/>
<br/>
The headset is similar to other virtual reality headsets like the Oculus, though it is made from glass and aluminum for a premium feel. Some early testers have said that the headset can be heavy on the head, but Apple may introduce an extra strap to mitigate some of the weight. The Vision Pro is using two 4K micro-OLED displays, and the technology is both more advanced and more expensive than the displays used by Apple's competitors.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is not expecting to sell many Vision Pro headsets, and rumors suggest it'll manufacture around 400,000 units. At a &#36;3,500 price point, it's not too surprising that interest may be limited.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro headset is a mixed reality device that transitions between virtual and augmented reality using a Digital Crown on the side. Content can be displayed in a full virtual environment, or in the real world around you using the augmented reality capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
There are more than a dozen cameras in the Vision Pro headset, and it's controlled using subtle hand gestures and eye movements. Audio Straps provide spatial audio, and there's a somewhat weird external display that projects an image of your eyes so people can tell whether you're using the headset in VR or AR mode.<br/>
<br/>
While the headset isn't particularly affordable for most people, it's an exciting launch because it's using cutting-edge technology and it is an entirely new device that's going to evolve and become sleeker and more affordable over the next decade. The Vision Pro has been likened to the Apple Watch, which was also expensive and clunky when it launched, but Apple made updates at a rapid pace and by the third generation, it was much improved.<br/>
<br/>
Much more information about the Vision Pro <strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">can be found in our Vision Pro roundup</a></strong>, and we also have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">details on visionOS in that roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="oled_ipad_pro_march_2024">OLED iPad Pro (March 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple didn't update the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup in 2023, but 2024 will be the year of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models are set to get upgraded OLED displays for the first time, so &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; screens will be as impressive as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> screens.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/OLED-iPad-Air.jpg" alt="" width="2363" height="1329" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-806474" /><br/>
This will be the first time that Apple has used OLED for such a large display, and OLED technology will bring deeper blacks, faster refresh rates, better contrast, and improved efficiency for less battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
OLED displays are thinner, so Apple may be planning to cut down on the thickness of the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. A design update is expected to accompany the OLED transition, and the new iPads will come in 11.1-inch and 13-inch sizes, up from the current 11-inch and 12.9-inch sizes. The size increase may come from a change in bezel width, so physical size could remain roughly the same.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will adopt the faster M3 chip that was first introduced in the MacBook Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>. Built on a 3-nanometer process, the M3 offers up to 21 percent faster CPU speeds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-much-better-really-is-m3/">compared to the M2</a>, and 15 percent faster GPU speeds. The GPU is also using a new architecture that optimizes memory allocation and utilization for improved performance and efficiency, plus it includes hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading.<br/>
<br/>
GPU improvements will result in better gaming graphics and capabilities, plus the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will be more efficient at tasks like video editing.<br/>
<br/>
Other possible features include up to 4TB of storage, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> charging capabilities, and a higher price tag due to the OLED display technology. More on what we are expecting from the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/"><strong>our dedicated OLED iPad Pro guide</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="two_ipad_air_models_march_2024">Two iPad Air Models (March 2024)</h2><br/>
To offer consumers more choice at a variety of price points, Apple is expanding the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; lineup in 2024. For the first time, there will be two &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models, just like there are two &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
Sizes will be similar to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, coming in at 10.9 inches and 12.9 inches. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models won't have OLED displays, ProMotion, or other high-end &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; features, but they will be cheaper than the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
Since Apple updated the design of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; in 2021, we're not expecting a major overhaul to the look of the device, but it's possible there will be some refinements to accommodate the new screen size.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ios_18_june_2024">iOS 18 (June 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple introduces new software updates on an annual basis at its Worldwide Developers Conference, and this year, we're expecting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; should be one of the most interesting updates we've had in years because rumors so far suggest that we're going to see Apple getting into generative AI in a big way.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909207" /><br/>
AI and machine learning will be used in multiple ways in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, with a range of new AI integrations in apps. In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, for example, we might see auto-generated playlists, and in apps like Pages and Keynote, we may see AI-assisted writing and slide deck creation.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is expected to get features powered by large language models (LLMs), which are the driving force behind chatbots like chatGPT. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will include deeper integration with the Shortcuts app for automating complex tasks, and there will be improved interactions between &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
Speaking of Messages, &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will see Apple adopting Rich Communication Services (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>) as an alternative to SMS/MMS. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; will be used for conversations between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users and Android users, and it will improve cross-platform messaging.<br/>
<br/>
Higher-resolution photos and videos will be supported, as will audio messages, cross-platform emoji reactions, read receipts, real-time typing indicators, and more. Basically, texting with someone on Android will feel a lot more like chatting with another &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user.<br/>
<br/>
Blue and green bubbles aren't going away, though. iMessage to iMessage chats will be blue, and Android to iMessage chats will still be green.<br/>
<br/>
More information on what to expect from the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/"><strong>can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="macos_15_watchos_11_and_tvos_18">macOS 15, watchOS 11, and tvOS 18</h3><br/>
Along with &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, we'll also get new versions of macOS, watchOS, and tvOS. We haven't heard much about these updates, but we can expect some of the same AI improvements.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="visionos_2">visionOS 2</h3><br/>
Alongside the Vision Pro headset, Apple will introduce &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;, the operating system that's designed to run on the device. It has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a>, a dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, virtual reality environments, and Apple apps tailored to the Vision Pro Display. While the first iteration of &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; will come out alongside the headset, &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 2 will likely be previewed in June. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/visionos-home-screen-mt-hood.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900011" /><br/>
<h2 id="apple_tv_first_half_of_2024">Apple TV (First Half of 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple is working on a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K, but it is not yet clear when it's going to launch. Rumored features include a faster A16 processor and support for Wi-Fi 6E or Wi-Fi 7.<br/>
<br/>
More on the next-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv/"><strong>found in our Apple TV guide</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_16_september_2024">iPhone 16 (September 2024)</h2><br/>
The standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models are expected to look similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models with no size or design changes, but there will be some notable improvements. Apple is planning for a vertical camera arrangement to support spatial video capture, doing away with the diagonal lens setup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-With-Dynamic-Island.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912423" /><br/>
Right now, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models are the only devices able to record spatial video that can be viewed on the Vision Pro, but that is expected to change in 2024. There's also going to be a new Capture Button on all four &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, with the button situated on the right side of the device under the power button.<br/>
<br/>
It'll be in roughly the same spot as the mmWave antenna on U.S. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, with the mmWave antenna set to move to the left side. As the name suggests, the Capture Button will provide users with a quick way to take videos. The Capture Button will be capacitive, offering haptic feedback when pressed, plus rumors suggest it supports multiple pressure levels.<br/>
<br/>
The Action Button introduced with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is expected to expand to the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, so it will be available across the 2024 lineup. The Action Button can be assigned to do things like mute/unmute, activate translate, turn on the flashlight, set a Focus mode, activate a custom Shortcut, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The Action Button on the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models could be upgraded to use capacitive technology, which would provide haptic feedback when pressed.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup, Apple limited the 3-nanometer A17 Pro to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max, but in 2024, all four &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models will get 3-nanometer A-series chips. A new thermal design to combat overheating is a possibility as well.<br/>
<br/>
We have more on all of the features rumored for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/"><strong>in our iPhone 16 roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_16_pro_september_2024">iPhone 16 Pro (September 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple's flagship lineup consists of four phones, two standard models and two Pro models. This year, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models are going to get a size update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Pro-Mock-Header-Updated.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924442" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to have a 6.3-inch display, up from 6.1 inches, while the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max is expected to have a 6.9-inch display, up from 6.7 inches. To accommodate the larger displays, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max will be slightly taller and wider than the equivalent &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
All of the features coming to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup are expected for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, including the capacitive Capture Button on the right side and an updated capacitive Action Button, both of which will feature haptic feedback.<br/>
<br/>
A faster A-series chip is rumored, likely the A18 Pro, and there are some pretty major camera updates planned. Apple may add a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, which will join the 48-megapixel Wide lens. The Ultra Wide camera will offer better low-light performance, and it will facilitate better spatial videos for the Vision Pro headset too.<br/>
<br/>
Both the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will get the 5x tetraprism lens that was limited to the 15 Pro Max in 2023, and there's one rumor about an even better periscope camera with "super zoom" capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
Faster 5G modem chips from Qualcomm are expected, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models may also get the next-generation Wi-Fi 7 technology that offers up to 2.4x faster speeds than Wi-Fi 6.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch_x_september_2024">Apple Watch X (September 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple is planning a major update for the Apple Watch this year, perhaps in celebration of the 10th anniversary of the device. The Apple Watch was announced in 2014, but didn't come out until 2015, so technically it's not clear whether the anniversary will fall in 2024 or 2025. 2024 will, however, be the year that we're expected to get the "Apple Watch 10" or "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>" as rumors have called it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-watch-ultra-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913279" /><br/>
Rumors suggest there will be a new design and new health features for the 2024 Apple Watch. The next Apple Watch could be slimmer, and Apple may implement a magnetic band attachment system, changing how bands connect to the Apple Watch for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
The new band system would mean that current bands would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/your-apple-watch-bands-may-not-work-with-new-model/">not likely be compatible</a> with the new version of the Apple Watch, but swapping over to a magnetic system would free up space in the Apple Watch either to make the casing slimmer or to add bigger batteries or other new internal components.<br/>
<br/>
Apple hasn't added new health features to the watch for some time, but in 2024, we could see sleep apnea detection and blood pressure monitoring. Rumors suggest the Apple Watch will be able to detect hypertension, monitoring whether a user's blood pressure is trending upward. The first iteration of blood pressure monitoring won't give specific systolic and diastolic readings, but a future version might.<br/>
<br/>
Sleep apnea detection will be done through sleep measurements and the tracking of breathing patterns. The Apple Watch will be able to inform users if the condition might be present, allowing them to contact their doctor for more information.<br/>
<br/>
More on changes expected for the 2024 Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">can be found in our Apple Watch X guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="airpods_4_september_2024">AirPods 4 (September 2024)</h2><br/>
Fourth-generation AirPods are coming in 2024, and as with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, Apple is going for a two-model launch. Two versions of the AirPods will be available at different price points, with the higher-end version to gain Active Noise Cancellation, a feature that has previously been limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/airpodsd-3-purple-4.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-855069" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a> will have an updated design that's a cross between the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a> and the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, with shorter stems. Fit is expected to be improved, as is sound quality, but it is unclear if Apple will add silicone tips.<br/>
<br/>
A redesigned case is set to feature speakers for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> alerts and a USB-C charging port, and with a software update coming later in 2024, Apple will add hearing aid functionality that will let the AirPods serve as an over-the-counter alternative to traditional hearing aids.<br/>
<br/>
New &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; are in the works too, but a refresh isn't expected until 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="usb-c_airpods_max_september_2024">USB-C AirPods Max (September 2024)</h2><br/>
Apple hasn't updated the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; since launch, and in 2024, they'll get a minor refresh. Apple is expected to add a USB-C port for charging and new color options, but nothing else will change.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airpods-max-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875245" /><br/>
<h2 id="ipad_mini_7_october_2024">iPad Mini 7 (October 2024)</h2><br/>
There's a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> coming, but no design changes are planned. We can expect an upgraded A-series chip, likely the A16, along with upgraded front and rear cameras.<br/>
<br/>
The display assembly may be installed in a different way in order to minimize "jelly scrolling" or screen tearing, which can cause images and text on one side of the display to be tilted downward due to mismatched refresh rates.<br/>
<br/>
New colors are likely, and Apple will probably add Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3, improvements it has been making to all of its &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="refreshed_low-cost_ipad_october_2024">Refreshed Low-Cost iPad (October 2024)</h2><br/>
Alongside the new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; 7, we could see a refreshed low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. Apple typically updates the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; on an annual basis, but the company skipped 2023, so we're due for a refresh.<br/>
<br/>
No design changes are coming, but the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will get a faster chip (likely the A16), and it could be updated with support for Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mac_mini_late_2024">Mac mini (Late 2024)</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> is due for an update, as it was last refreshed with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chips in January 2023. A 2024 version of the desktop machine will include Apple's M3 and M3 Pro chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/mac-mini-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909563" /><br/>
<h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
<h3 id="magic_keyboard">Magic Keyboard</h3><br/>
Alongside the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, Apple is expected to debut an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/magic-keyboard-apple-pencil-rumors/">updated version of the Magic Keyboard</a>. The new Magic Keyboard will feature a sturdier frame made from aluminum, giving it a more Mac-like look.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/2021-Magic-Keyboard-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2226" height="1252" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-797122" /><br/>
The keyboard will be made of aluminum as well, and Apple is planning to add a larger trackpad that more closely resembles the trackpad of the MacBook.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_pencil_3">Apple Pencil 3</h3><br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/magic-keyboard-apple-pencil-rumors/">refreshed version of the Apple Pencil</a> is in the works, with the new device set to be a followup to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> 2. It will be a higher-end &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; able to work with Apple's next-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/apple-pencil-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897359" /><br/>
We don't yet know a lot about what we can expect from a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_possibilities">Other Possibilities</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>MacBook Pro</strong> - The MacBook Pro was updated with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips in late 2023. Apple sometimes refreshes the MacBook Pro annually, but so far there's no word of M4 chips or whether we'll see a MacBook Pro update in 2024.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Mac Studio</strong> - The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> was updated with &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chips in June 2023, so it could get an update with M3 chips at some point in 2024. Apple has not yet unveiled an M3 Ultra chip.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Mac Pro</strong> - Like the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> was refreshed in June 2023 with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra. There's no word on when we'll see it updated again as of yet.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Home Hub Device</strong> - Rumors suggest Apple is working on a smart home display that would serve as a central hub for controlling smart home products, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-smart-home-ipad-display/">it could launch</a> as soon as 2024.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>New Display</strong> - There have been multiple rumors of a Pro Display XDR successor, but there's no word on when an update might come. It could be 2024, or it could be later.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="wrap_up">Wrap Up</h2><br/>
Based on what we're hearing so far, 2024 is going to be a monumental year for Apple. Along with the Vision Pro, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lineup is set to get an overhaul, and the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models have some exciting features. We're also counting on a suite of new AI features in the software updates that are coming this year.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to follow MacRumors.com and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/">the MacRumors roundups</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/">guides</a> over the course of 2024 to keep up with all of the rumors we're hearing. Bookmark our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/upcoming-apple-products/">What to Expect Guide</a> and our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-event/">Events Guide</a> to see a continually updated overview of what's on the horizon.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-what-to-expect-2024/">What to Expect From Apple in 2024: Vision Pro, iPhone 16 Models, Revamped iPad Pro and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apple-in-2024-vision-pro-iphone-16-models-revamped-ipad-pro-and-more.2414978/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple&#039;s 2023 Year in Review</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-2023-year-in-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apples-2023-year-in-review.2414970/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:28:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-2023-year-in-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the final episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/dk/podcast/apples-2023-year-in-review/id1602394741?i=1000640026919">The MacRumors Show</a> for 2023, we take a look back and evaluate Apple's year as a whole.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7HvIWv903eo?si=S12qLcXCH1mwxuMi" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
The year kicked off in January with an unusual array of hardware releases consisting of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-announces-new-homepod/">relaunch of the HomePod</a> alongside the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/apple-announces-m2-pro-macbook-pro/">M2 Pro and M2 Max MacBook Pros</a>, as well as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/new-m2-m2-pro-mac-mini/">M2 and M2 Pro Mac mini</a>. In May, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/09/apple-announces-final-cut-pro-and-logic-pro-for-ipad/">Apple announced</a> Final Cut Pro and Logic Pro for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, extending its own professional-grade creative tools to its tablet users for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
June was particularly eventful with the announcement of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, tvOS 17, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> at WWDC. Apple simultaneously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/apple-reveals-vision-pro-headset/">unveiled the Vision Pro</a> mixed-reality headset, a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/apple-new-15-inch-macbook-air/">15-inch MacBook Air model</a>, and updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> lines with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/apple-unveils-m2-ultra-chip-as-most-powerful-apple-silicon-chip-yet/">M2 Ultra</a> chip.<br/>
<br/>
September marked the official release of the new operating systems and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">debut</a> of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> series, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-finewoven/">introduction</a> of FineWoven as a new material for accessories, and the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 with USB-C. In October, Apple continued by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">introducing</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> with USB-C, and somewhat unexpectedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-m3-macbook-pros/">announced</a> the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max MacBook Pros, as well as the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, at the end of the month.<br/>
<br/>
November saw Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">announce support</a> for Rich Communication Services (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>). The year concluded with the release of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-releases-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2/">iOS 17.2</a>, Aston Martin and Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewing</a> the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, and a notable legal development where sales of the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; were briefly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">banned in the United States</a>.<br/>
<br/>
How do you think 2023 was for Apple? Let us know in the comments. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so head over and subscribe to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-qa/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion where we take your questions about Apple rumors and more.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-2023-year-in-review/">The MacRumors Show: Apple&#039;s 2023 Year in Review</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apples-2023-year-in-review.2414970/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-from-grid-studio.2414965/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:04:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>No AMP</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with GRID Studio to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 13-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>. GRID Studio turns key devices from Apple history into art that can be displayed in the home or office.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/GRID-1.jpg" alt="" width="1348" height="759" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919076" /><br/>
GRID's art pieces feature a deconstructed Apple device with the components laid out underneath a glass frame. Each part is clearly labeled, and interesting historical facts are included. GRID Studio has a range of different products available, with prices that start at &#36;40 and go up based on the complexity and rarity of the original device.<br/>
<br/>
The GRID 1, <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">priced at &#36;400</a>, features Apple's first-ever <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that came out in 2007. It includes all of the components from the original &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, from the curved shell to the power button, headphone socket, and logic board.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/GRID-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928286" /><br/>
GRID's <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE4s">&#36;139 GRID 4s</a> showcases the successor to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4s initially came out in 2011, and it was Apple's fifth-ever &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The 4s was notable because the "s" represented <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, a smart personal assistant that was, at the time, exclusive to the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/GRID_4S.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928287" /><br/>
GRID Studio doesn't just do iPhones. The <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/apple-watch-series-0">&#36;200 GRID Watch 1</a> includes the original 2015 Apple Watch, which was the first wrist-worn wearable that Apple came out with. The GRID piece includes the S1 chip, Apple's first system-on-a-chip, along with the original Apple Watch casing and the other internal components of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/GRID-WATCH.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928288" /><br/>
Apple silicon fans will appreciate the <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AEm1-chip">&#36;199 GRID M1</a> that celebrates Apple's first in-house Mac chip. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> is an important part of Apple's history, and the GRID piece encases it in resin and provides a rundown on all of the features, including the 8-core CPU, 8-core GPU, and dedicated Neural Engine.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/GRID-M1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928289" /><br/>
For Mac fans, GRID Studio also sells the <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid-macbook-air-1st-generation">GRID MacBook Air</a> for &#36;599. This piece highlights the first-generation 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; that came out in 2008, which Apple called the world's thinnest notebook and marketed as an ultraportable computer. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; had an aluminum casing and a white bezel around the display, and it was equipped with a custom Intel chip, a full-size keyboard, and a multi-touch trackpad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/GRID-MacBook-Air.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928290" /><br/>
GRID Studio is having a holiday sale right now, with a promo code on the site offering 15 percent off. Some devices are also discounted by as much as 50 percent, with details <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">available on the website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
GRID Studio is providing one winner with a 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; equipped with an &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, 512GB SSD, and 8GB Unified Memory. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/nqV01/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (December 29, 2023) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on January 5, 2024. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after January 5 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-macbook-air/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-from-grid-studio.2414965/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker&#039;s End-of-the-Year Sale Has Low Prices on Power Banks, USB-C Chargers, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/ankers-end-of-the-year-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-end-of-the-year-sale-has-low-prices-on-power-banks-usb-c-chargers-and-more.2414964/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 08:55:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/ankers-end-of-the-year-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anker is sending off 2023 with a <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fnew-year-sale%3Fref%3DmasterBanner1">sale on its most popular charging accessories of the year</a>, including portable batteries, MagSafe-compatible devices, USB-C cables, and more. Anker is also throwing in a surprise gift on orders over &#36;100 through January 8, 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/anker-new-gold.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922736" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up all of the accessories in this sale below. You'll find a good collection of Anker's best multi-port wall chargers, as well as a pair of portable batteries with smart digital displays. These deals will be automatically applied when you head to the checkout screen on Anker's website.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fnew-year-sale%3Fref%3DmasterBanner1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Anker's End-of-the-Year Sale</div></a></div><h2>Portable Batteries</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1335-130w-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D42691850797206%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023">Prime 12,000 mAh</a> - &#36;76.50, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1336-20000mah-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D42691854925974%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023">Prime 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;104.00, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Wall Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2045%3Fvariant%3D37438397841558%26ref%3Dnew-year-sale">65W Charging Hub</a> - &#36;34.50, down from &#36;45.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2668%3Fvariant%3D41974350315670%26ref%3Dnew-year-sale">65W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;37.97, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2148%3Fvariant%3D41974285172886%26ref%3Dnew-year-sale">120W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;59.98, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2343-100w-usb-c-charger%3Fvariant%3D42691851911318%26ref%3Dnew-year-sale">100W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;69.60, down from &#36;86.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Charging Stations</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa9129-charging-station-67w%3Fvariant%3D42733234454678%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023">Nano 6-in-1 Charging Station</a> - &#36;49.50, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa9128-6-in-1-charging-station%3Fvariant%3D42691854336150%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023">Prime 6-in-1 Charging Station</a> - &#36;88.00, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fy1811%3Fvariant%3D42206465327254%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023">3-in-1 Cube with MagSafe</a> - &#36;127.46, down from &#36;149.95</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Cable + Charger Bundles</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fbundle-a2668111-a88660a1%3Fvariant%3D42461886775446%26ref%3Dnew-year-sale">65W 3-Port Charger + USB-C to USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;85.48, down from &#36;94.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fbundle-a2148111-a88660a1%3Fvariant%3D42462302732438%26ref%3Dnew-year-sale">120W 3-Port Charger + USB-C to USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;116.99, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/ankers-end-of-the-year-sale/">Anker&#039;s End-of-the-Year Sale Has Low Prices on Power Banks, USB-C Chargers, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-end-of-the-year-sale-has-low-prices-on-power-banks-usb-c-chargers-and-more.2414964/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Apple Stores Planned Near Los Angeles, Toronto, and Atlanta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/new-apple-stores-planned-near-la-toronto-atlanta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-stores-planned-near-los-angeles-toronto-and-atlanta.2414961/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 08:30:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/new-apple-stores-planned-near-la-toronto-atlanta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning new retail stores in the Los Angeles, Toronto, and Atlanta metropolitan areas, according to building permits viewed by <em>MacRumors</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-Store-Waterside-Shops.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928471" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple Waterside Shops in Naples, Florida</em></div><br/>
Apple is preparing to open a new store at the Del Amo Fashion Center shopping mall in Torrance, California, per building permits filed with the city in October. Torrance is located in the South Bay region of Los Angeles County.<br/>
<br/>
The permits reveal that Apple will be located on the main level of the mall, between Lululemon and Madewell. The store will be taking over the combined space of two side-by-side units previously occupied by J.Crew and Chico's.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman was first to report on Apple's plans for the store in June, after obtaining the company's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/01/apple-store-update-plans/">internal roadmap for retail expansion</a>. Apple estimated that the store would open in March 2024, per the roadmap, but this timeframe is subject to change based  on completion of construction, hiring, and other factors.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also moving forward with plans to relocate its store at the Square One shopping mall in Mississauga, Ontario, west of Toronto in Canada. Apple will be taking over a space previously occupied by Massimo Dutti on the second floor of the mall, above the food court, according to a building permit filed with the city in June.<br/>
<br/>
Last, a building permit filed with Gwinnett County in May confirms that Apple plans to relocate its store at the Mall of Georgia in Buford, northeast of Atlanta. The new store will remain in the mall, but the permit did not reveal a specific location.<br/>
<br/>
Apple estimated that the new Square One and Mall of Georgia stores would open in late 2023, based on the roadmap, but the projects are taking longer.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, Apple confirmed that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apples-infinite-loop-store-closing-next-month/">permanently closing its Infinite Loop store</a> in Cupertino, California on January 20. Apple will also be shuttering its Royal Hawaiian store in Honolulu on the same day. Apple said all affected employees at both locations will be given the opportunity to continue working for the company.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/29/new-apple-stores-planned-near-la-toronto-atlanta/">New Apple Stores Planned Near Los Angeles, Toronto, and Atlanta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-stores-planned-near-los-angeles-toronto-and-atlanta.2414961/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>8 Tips to Extend Your iPhone&#039;s Battery Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/8-battery-life-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8-tips-to-extend-your-iphones-battery-life.2414908/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 14:25:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/8-battery-life-tips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With New Year's Eve and New Year's Day approaching, many <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users may need to get the most out of their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery life for extended parties and other festivities. We've rounded up some helpful battery tips that you might want to put into action to ensure your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; keeps working long into the night.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-early-black-friday-iphone-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920873" /><br/>
<h2>1. Disable Haptic Keyboard Feedback</h2><br/>
If you've turned on the keyboard option that provides haptic feedback when you tap the on-screen keys, you might want to turn it off temporarily because it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/20/ios-16-haptic-keyboard-battery-life/">can affect battery life</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872406" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/haptic-keyboard-feedback.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1961" /><br/>
Here's how to turn it off:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on Sounds & Haptics.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on Keyboard Feedback.</li><br/>
 	<li>Toggle off Haptic.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
<h2>2. Turn Off Proximity AirDrop Sharing</h2><br/>
When you hold two iPhones running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> together, or an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; running &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; and an Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 or later, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; initiates a proximity-based AirDrop or contact transfer protocol. If you're continually triggering this, it can drain battery, so if your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is near many other iPhones and you're getting the AirDrop interface over and over again, you should turn it off.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905665" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/airdrop-proximity-sharing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1327" /><br/>
To do so, go to Settings &gt; General &gt; AirDrop and toggle off "Bringing Devices Together."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>3. Use Offline Maps</h2><br/>
If you're traveling somewhere, you can save some battery life if you download <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> for offline usage, a feature available on iPhones running &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; or later. Offline maps are especially useful if you're going somewhere with poor cellular connectivity because you can get turn-by-turn directions without the battery drain. Just make sure to turn cellular off in spotty areas.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899235" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Maps-Offline.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Downloading a map is as simple as searching for a location, tapping on the download button, and selecting the area of the map to download. We have a dedicated how-to that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/download-offline-maps-ios-apple-maps/">walks you through all of the steps</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>4. Turn Off Live Activities</h2><br/>
Live Activities let apps keep an ongoing notification on the Lock Screen or in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, which can cause noticeable battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849710" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/ios-16-live-activities-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Live Activities can be disabled by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Go to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> &amp; Passcode.</li><br/>
 	<li>Enter your passcode to unlock the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 	<li>Scroll down and toggle off Live Activities.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
This will prevent Live Activities from showing up on the Lock Screen, but you'll want to take this one step further. In the individual app sections in the Settings app, you can disable Live Activities on an app-by-app basis, or avoid using Live Activities features within apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>5. Turn Off Always-On Display</h2><br/>
If you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, the always-on display leaves the time, your wallpaper, widgets, and Live Activities visible on the Lock Screen even when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864733" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/turn-off-always-on-display.jpg" alt="settings" width="640" height="408" /><br/>
The display uses a 1Hz refresh rate to preserve battery, and the display turns off when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in a pocket, but always-on display still drains battery faster than no always-on display.<br/>
<br/>
You can turn off the Always-On display by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on Display &amp; Brightness.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on Always On Display.</li><br/>
 	<li>Toggle off Always On Display.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
It's not entirely clear just how much battery life the always-on display drains because it's going to vary from use case to use case, but even if it's only a few percent, it can be worth turning off.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6. Use Focus Modes</h2><br/>
Apple's built-in Focus option can cut down on the number of notifications that you're receiving, and fewer notifications means less opportunity for apps to wake up your display and cause battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850799" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/ios-16-lock-screen-focus.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" /><br/>
Focus modes let you choose which apps and people can send you notifications and when, so during work hours you can make sure you're only getting work notifications, and during personal time, you can limit your work notifications. You can limit notifications when driving, when you're asleep, when you're working out, and in any other scenario you can think of.<br/>
<br/>
You'll still get all of your notifications when the Focus mode ends, but all in one alert rather than multiple. Turning off unwanted notifications from apps is still the best method for saving battery life, but Focus modes let you keep your notifications while still cutting down on the number that you receive.<br/>
<br/>
Apple made Focus modes relatively easy to set up, but it still takes some work to get everything running, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-16-focus/">we have a dedicated Focus guide</a>. You can find all of the Focus features in the Focus section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>7. Limit When and How Often Apps Can Access Location</h2><br/>
It's always good to check in on privacy and access settings to make sure apps and services aren't doing things you don't want them to be doing.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872415" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/ios-16-location-services.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1299" /><br/>
Limiting the apps that have access to your location and how often apps can access that data can save battery life.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Choose Privacy &amp; Security.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap Location Services.</li><br/>
 	<li>Review the list and edit settings by tapping on the name of each app in the list.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
You have four possible choices for location settings for each app, though not all four choices will always be available for every app depending on what it does. You can select the following: Never, Ask Next Time Or When I Share, While Using the App, and Always.<br/>
<br/>
Never will prevent an app from ever accessing your location, and unless there's a specific need for an app to know where you are, such as a mapping app, setting location access to Never is the best choice. While Using the App allows the app to detect your location only when the app is open and being actively used. If you close the app or switch over to another app, location access ends. This is the second best setting to use.<br/>
<br/>
Ask Next Time Or When I Share will prompt an app to ask you with a pop-up the next time that it wants your location, so you can temporarily approve it. With this setting, location access is off until expressly allowed via the pop-up. Always lets an app to have access to your location at all times, regardless of whether it's open or closed. This will result in the most battery drain and should be limited to only the apps that you need the most.<br/>
<br/>
Many apps ask for location information that don't really need it to function (for example, a banking app might want location access to show nearby ATMs, which is also available through entering a zip code), so clearing the cruft will ensure no apps are accessing your location without express permission.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="13._use_low_power_mode">8. Use Low Power Mode</h2><br/>
Turning on Low Power Mode is an obvious choice for maintaining battery without having to hassle with a lot of settings, and you can toggle it on from Control Center, the Battery section of the Settings app, or using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205234">Low Power Mode</a> cuts down on background activity, turns off your display after inactivity more quickly, limits display refresh rate, limits email fetch, cuts down on visual effects, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-858449" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/ios-16-beta-6-battery-percent-low-power.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Low Power Mode can be set to turn on at a certain battery percentage using Shortcuts, which is a handy way to have it automatically turn on when you need it, and it's the best option if you're someone who doesn't often remember to toggle on Low Power Mode.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Tips</h2><br/>
Have favorite tips for prolonging your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery life? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/8-battery-life-tips/">8 Tips to Extend Your iPhone&#039;s Battery Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8-tips-to-extend-your-iphones-battery-life.2414908/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Use These iPhone Features to Stay Safer</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-safety-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/use-these-iphone-features-to-stay-safer.2414902/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 13:03:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-safety-features&#038;post_date=1703808194/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> has quite a few built-in safety features that are designed to help keep you safe, and with New Year's Eve parties approaching, it may be worth a refresher on what your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can do and the options you can enable to protect yourself.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/FindMy-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-779341" /><br/>
<h2 id="stolen_device_protection">Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-stolen-device-protection-feature/">Stolen Device Protection keeps</a> your data safe in case someone steals your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and also happens to know your passcode. Earlier this year, there were reports about thieves spying on a victim's passcode before stealing an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, giving them access to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain passwords, banking accounts, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ios-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926120" /><br/>
With Stolen Device Protection, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication is required to view passwords in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain, turn off Lost Mode, erase content and settings, use saved Safari payment methods, and apply for or view an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>. Authentication <em>and</em> an hour-long waiting period is required for changing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> password, changing an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; passcode, removing &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;/&zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;, and turning off &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Stolen Device Protection is actually an iOS 17.3 feature, so there are some extra steps to use it. You'll need to download and install the iOS 17.3 public beta <a href="https://beta.apple.com">from Apple's beta software website</a> and follow the instructions. It's a little bit of a hassle, but if you're going to be out in public and drinking, Stolen Device Protection is worth the effort just in case.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Note:</b> Apple does not recommend installing beta software on a primary device, and there is a chance that the install could cause issues with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. We have not seen reports of iOS 17.3 causing problems, but it is worth weighing the benefits and downsides before opting for a beta. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_check_in">Messages Check In</h2><br/>
If you're going out somewhere, you can use the Check In feature in Messages to let a trusted friend or family member know where you're going and when you should arrive.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/messages-check-in.jpg" alt="" width="4320" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909078" /><br/>
When you head out, turn on Check In, and it will keep track of your progress. If you stop along the way, Messages will ping you to see what's going on, and if you do not respond, helpful information like your battery level, location, route traveled, location of last &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; unlock, and cellular status will be shared with the trusted person.<br/>
<br/>
Check In is a feature that ensures someone is keeping an eye on you from afar, and if you're in an accident, accosted, or otherwise in trouble, it gives detailed information that can be used to find you.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="use_find_my">Use Find My</h2><br/>
You can also give a trusted friend or family member access to your location through the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app. Go to &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, choose the People tab, and tap Share My Location.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/find-my-friends-precision-finding.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1690" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911341" /><br/>
With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip, &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; can be used to track down your friends in a crowd if you're in a place like a concert venue. Note that both people need to have an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="medical_id">Medical ID</h2><br/>
Make sure your medical information is up to date in the Health app. Tap on your profile and then go to Medical ID to update your information.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iphone-medical-id.jpg" alt="" width="1316" height="740" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928279" /><br/>
This is a quick way for someone to see your name, age, allergies, and emergency contacts, and it's data that can be viewed when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="safety_check">Safety Check</h2><br/>
It's a good idea to use the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Safety Check feature every now and then to see who you're sharing data with and who can track you. Open up the Settings app, go to Privacy and Security, scroll down, and tap on Safety Check.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/ios-16-manage-sharing-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1299" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856675" /><br/>
In an emergency, you can use the Emergency Reset option, but for a check up, you'll want to tap on Manage Sharing &amp; Access. It will show you who can see your location, which apps have access to your location data, who you share photo albums with, who you share notes with, all devices logged in to your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="features_to_know_about">Features to Know About</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Emergency SOS</strong> - If you press and hold on the side button and either volume button on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, you can call emergency services surreptitiously. There's also an option to press five times on the side button to call, which is an even easier method. Adjust your SOS settings by going to Settings &gt; Emergency SOS.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Emergency SOS on Apple Watch</strong> - To contact emergency services on the Apple Watch, hold down the side button until the emergency call slider appears, and then drag it to make the call.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Crash Detection</strong> - Crash Detection contacts local emergency services if a crash is detected. It's on by default, but double check that it's enabled under Settings > Emergency SOS > Call After Severe Crash.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Satellite SOS</strong> - In a remote area where you don't have signal, you can use satellite connectivity to get help in an emergency. It's a feature available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and 15 models, and note that you will need to be outside and have a line of sight to the sky for the best connectivity.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Use Siri</strong> - You can ask <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> to call 911 (or your local emergency number).</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Text 911</strong> - Need to get help while staying quiet? You can text 911 in the United States by opening up the Messages app and typing 911 in the "To" field. This works on Apple Watch too.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="other_safety_tips">Other Safety Tips</h2><br/>
Know of other safety tips &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users should be aware of? Share them in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-safety-features/">Use These iPhone Features to Stay Safer</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/use-these-iphone-features-to-stay-safer.2414902/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Keep Listening to YouTube in the Background or With iPhone Locked</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/listen-youtube-background-iphone-free/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-keep-listening-to-youtube-in-the-background-or-with-iphone-locked.2414883/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/listen-youtube-background-iphone-free&#038;post_date=1703793600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, listening to YouTube audio in the background usually requires paying for a YouTube Premium subscription, but there is a simple workaround that allows you to keep listening to a video when you are doing other things on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or when your device is locked. Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/General-YouTube-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-814336" /><br/>
As YouTube has grown in popularity over the years, Google has opted to park several features of the video hosting service behind a paywall, such as ad-free viewing, SharePlay on iOS, and the ability to listen to YouTube audio on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; when the app is closed.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, YouTube Premium costs &#36;13.99 a month to access these features. But if all you want to do is listen to YouTube-hosted audio like podcasts, music, or lectures when you are in other apps or when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked and in your pocket, there is a way to achieve this without paying for the subscription. <br/>
<br/>
The following steps show you how it's done. <br/>
<ol><li>Launch Safari on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and visit <a href="https://www.youtube.com">youtube.com</a>, then search for the video whose audio you want to listen to.</li><br/>
<li>Next, tap the <strong>aA</strong> button in Safari's address bar, then select <strong>Request Desktop Website</strong> from the popup menu.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/youtube-safari.jpg" alt="safari" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927791" /><br/>
<li>Tap the play button or tap the video to begin playback, while ignoring or dismissing any popups encouraging you to open the YouTube mobile app. (You will need to watch or skip a few ads before video playback begins.)</li><br/>
<li>Now, lock your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with the device's <strong>Side</strong> button. The audio will pause, but you can just tap the <strong>Play</strong> button in the Lock Screen playback controls widget to resume listening. <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/youtube-locked-iphone.jpg" alt="Lock Screen" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927792" /></ol>After following the above steps, the audio from YouTube will continue to play on your locked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; for as long as the video lasts, leaving you free to pocket your device and listen on headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/youtube-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1339" height="738" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927793" /><br/>
<br/>
Alternatively, if you want to use other apps while listening, simply swipe up from the bottom of the screen to exit out of Safari, and then use the media controls in your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> or Control Center to resume playback when it automatically stops.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/listen-youtube-background-iphone-free/">How to Keep Listening to YouTube in the Background or With iPhone Locked</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-keep-listening-to-youtube-in-the-background-or-with-iphone-locked.2414883/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Once Again Available to Purchase From Apple&#039;s Online Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-online/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-once-again-available-to-purchase-from-apples-online-store.2414879/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 07:58:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-online/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>ITC</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following a ruling from the U.S. Court of Appeals <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">staying the Apple Watch import ban</a>, Apple has returned the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-watch/apple-watch">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-watch/apple-watch-ultra/49mm-cellular-titanium-white-ocean-band-onesize">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> to its online stores in the U.S., and they should also be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-available-in-stores-today/">available in some Apple retail stores</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/apple-watch-ultra-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-885160" /><br/>
Apple on Tuesday filed an emergency request asking for the import ban to be paused while an appeal is under way. The appeals court implemented an interim stay while it decides whether it will grant Apple's request for a stay for the entire length of the appeal, and as a result, Apple can once again sell Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing technology.<br/>
<br/>
The International Trade Commission (ITC) has until January 10 to file a response to Apple's request for a stay, and other parties have until January 15 to submit letters supporting or opposing the import ban. Apple should be able to continue to sell the watch at least until the appeals court makes a final ruling on the stay, which will happen at some point after January 15.<br/>
<br/>
If the appeals court rules in Apple's favor, the import ban on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and Ultra 2 will be paused for the entire duration of the appeals process. If the court does not rule in Apple's favor, the import ban will be reinstated. The appeals process could last for many months, so Apple may get a significant reprieve as it argues against the ITC's decision.<br/>
<br/>
The ITC in October decided that Apple had infringed on blood oxygen sensing technology patented by Masimo, and put in place a U.S. import ban that went into effect on December 26. In preparation for the ban, Apple actually <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">stopped sales online</a> on December 21, and ended in-store sales after December 24.<br/>
<br/>
The Biden administration had the opportunity to veto the import ban, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">opted not to do so</a>, making the import ban official. To get around the Apple Watch legal issues, Apple will need to win its appeal against Masimo, settle with Masimo, or remove the infringing blood oxygen sensing technology from the Apple Watch lineup.<br/>
<br/>
The import ban only affected &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> models sold in Apple retail stores and the online store in the United States. Sales in other countries have not been affected, and the Apple Watch models have continued to be available in the U.S. in stores like Target, Walmart, and Best Buy.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itc/">ITC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-online/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Once Again Available to Purchase From Apple&#039;s Online Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-once-again-available-to-purchase-from-apples-online-store.2414879/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iOS Features Coming in 2024 for Messages, Apple Music, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/new-ios-features-launching-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ios-features-coming-in-2024-for-messages-apple-music-and-more.2414878/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 07:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/new-ios-features-launching-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2024 is just a few days away, and there are many iOS 17 and iOS 18 features that are expected to launch throughout the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912514" /><br/>
Below, we have recapped new iOS features expected in 2024, including Stolen Device Protection, collaborative Apple Music playlists, AirPlay on hotel room TVs, app sideloading in the EU, next-generation CarPlay, roadside assistance via satellite outside of the U.S., RCS support in the Messages app, and generative AI for Siri.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ios-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926120" /><br/>
Earlier this year, <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> reported about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/19/apple-responds-to-iphone-theft-recovery-key-report/">thieves spying on an iPhone user's passcode</a> before stealing the device, often in public places like bars. With knowledge of the passcode, the thief can then change the victim's Apple ID password, turn off Find My, and more to gain full control of the device. The thief can also use the passcode to gain access to passwords stored in iCloud Keychain and other sensitive information.<br/>
<br/>
Stolen Device Protection is Apple's hopeful solution to the problem. Apple says the feature is designed to add an additional layer of security in the event someone has stolen your iPhone and also obtained the device's passcode.<br/>
<br/>
When the feature is turned on, Face ID or Touch ID authentication is strictly required for the following actions, with a passcode fallback no longer available:<ul><li>Accessing passwords or passkeys saved in iCloud Keychain</li><br/>
<li>Applying for a new Apple Card or viewing an Apple Card's virtual number</li><br/>
<li>Turning off Lost Mode</li><br/>
<li>Erasing all content and settings</li><br/>
<li>Taking certain Apple Cash and Apple Card Savings actions in the Wallet app</li><br/>
<li>Using payment methods saved in Safari</li><br/>
<li>Using your iPhone to set up a new device</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For especially sensitive actions, including changing the password of the Apple ID account associated with the iPhone, the feature adds a one-hour security delay on top of biometric authentication. In these cases, the user must authenticate with Face ID or Touch ID, wait one hour, and authenticate with Face ID or Touch ID again. However, Apple says there is no delay when the iPhone is in familiar locations, such as at home or work.<br/>
<br/>
Actions that require Face ID or Touch ID authentication, and have a one-hour security delay, when the feature is turned on:<ul><li>Changing your Apple ID password</li><br/>
<li>Updating select Apple ID security settings, including adding or removing a trusted device, trusted phone number, Recovery Key, or Recovery Contact</li><br/>
<li>Changing your iPhone passcode</li><br/>
<li>Adding or removing Face ID or Touch ID</li><br/>
<li>Turning off Find My</li><br/>
<li>Turning off Stolen Device Protection</li></ul>Stolen Device Protection is an opt-in feature that can be found in the Settings app under Face ID & Passcode, and it is available for all iPhones that are compatible with iOS 17. iPhone users who update to the iOS 17.3 beta are able to preview the feature.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to share additional information about the feature once iOS 17.3 is released widely.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music Collaborative Playlists</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-music-collaborative-playlist.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898803" /><br/>
A new Collaborative Playlists option for Apple Music subscribers allows multiple people to add, reorder, and remove songs in a shared playlist. Users are able to leave <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-17-3-collaborative-playlist-emoji/">animated emoji reactions</a> next to songs in the playlist.<br/>
<br/>
This feature was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">initially expected to launch with iOS 17.2</a>, but it was removed from that update towards the end of the beta testing period. The feature was re-added in iOS 17.3, and Apple's website confirms that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-collaborative-playlists-2024/">will return in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPlay on Hotel Room TVs</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airplay-hotels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898340" /><br/>
Following the release of iOS 17.2, Apple updated its website to indicate that an AirPlay feature for hotel room TVs has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-delays-airplay-in-hotel-rooms/">delayed until next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple originally said the feature was "coming later this year," but it now says it will be "coming in an update in 2024." Apple did not provide a more specific timeframe, but the feature should be added in an iOS 17 update in the first half of next year.<br/>
<br/>
The feature will allow iPhone users to scan a QR code on their hotel room TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing them to wirelessly stream videos, photos, and music from their iPhone to the TV. Google already offers a similar feature on some hotel TVs, allowing guests to stream content from their smartphone via Chromecast.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in June said Holiday Inn parent company IHG Hotels & Resorts would be one of the first hotel chains to adopt the feature.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>App Sideloading in EU</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman last year reported that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/13/apple-europe-alternate-app-store-support/">preparing to allow app sideloading on the iPhone</a> in order to comply with the European Union's Digital Markets Act. This would allow users to install apps outside of Apple's App Store, but the change is only expected to be made in European Union countries, at least initially.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman recently said that he expects app sideloading in the EU to roll out in an iOS 17 update released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/">in the first half of 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Next-Generation CarPlay</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><br/>
Apple said that the first vehicles with support for its next-generation CarPlay system would be announced in late 2023, and it delivered on that promise with just days to spare. Earlier this month, Aston Martin and Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed what the next-generation CarPlay experience will look like</a> in some of their upcoming vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
Aston Martin confirmed that it will release its first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay in 2024, but there is no specific timeframe, and details remain slim.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first previewed the next-generation CarPlay experience in June 2022, promising deeper integration with the instrument cluster and climate controls, support for multiple displays across the dashboard, a dedicated FM radio app, widgets, and more. The interface can be tailored to each specific vehicle model and automaker's brand identity.<br/>
<br/>
When first unveiling next-generation CarPlay last year, Apple said committed automakers included Acura, Audi, Ford, Honda, Infiniti, Jaguar, Land Rover, Lincoln, Mercedes-Benz, Nissan, Polestar, Porsche, Renault, and Volvo. Beyond the addition of Aston Martin, it's unclear if this list has changed since that initial announcement.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Roadside Assistance via Satellite Outside U.S.</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-roadside-assistance.jpg" alt="" width="1596" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910510" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 17, all iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 models offer a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-roadside-assistance-feature-tested/">roadside assistance via satellite feature</a> that allows users in the U.S. to contact roadside assistance company AAA for vehicle service when outside of cellular and Wi-Fi coverage.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said the feature is available "beginning" in the U.S., so it will likely expand to some additional countries starting in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>RCS Support</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
In November, Apple announced that it will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">support the cross-platform messaging standard RCS</a> in the Messages app on the iPhone starting "later next year," so it will likely be an iOS 18 feature based on that timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
RCS support should result in the following improvements to the default messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices:<ul><br/>
 <li>Higher-resolution photos and videos</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages</li><br/>
 <li>Typing indicators</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts</li><br/>
 <li>Wi-Fi messaging between iPhones and Android devices</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats, including the ability for iPhone users to leave a conversation that includes Android users</li><br/>
 <li>Improved encryption compared to SMS</li><br/>
</ul>These modern features are already available for iPhone-to-iPhone conversations with blue bubbles, via iMessage, and many of the features are also available in third-party messaging apps, such as WhatsApp and Telegram. RCS support on the iPhone will extend the features to green bubbles in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smarter Siri</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman expects <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">iOS 18 to feature generative AI technology</a> that "should improve how both Siri and the Messages app can field questions and auto-complete sentences." He said Apple has also explored generative AI features for other apps across its platforms, including Apple Music, Pages, Keynote, and Xcode.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The Information</em> reported that Apple plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">incorporate large language models into Siri</a> to let users automate complex tasks, a feature that would involve deeper integration with the Shortcuts app. The report said this feature is expected to be released in an iPhone software update coming next year, which would likely be iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
Generative AI surged in popularity last year when OpenAI released ChatGPT, a chatbot that can respond to questions and other prompts. Google and Microsoft released similar chatbots earlier this year, as more companies race into the space. The chatbots are trained on large language models, allowing them to respond like a human.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/new-ios-features-launching-in-2024/">New iOS Features Coming in 2024 for Messages, Apple Music, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ios-features-coming-in-2024-for-messages-apple-music-and-more.2414878/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Has Some of the Last Deals of the Year on Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Pro (Up to &#36;300 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/amazon-last-deals-year-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-some-of-the-last-deals-of-the-year-on-apples-m3-macbook-pro-up-to-300-off.2414877/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 07:15:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/amazon-last-deals-year-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a collection of M3 MacBook Pro models on sale at all-time low prices, including both 14-inch and 16-inch notebooks. Most of the MacBook Pros will arrive in the second week of January at this point.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-bb-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924141" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the 8-Core M3, 1TB 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KC8X7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,549.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,799.00. This is a record low price on the 14-inch MacBook Pro, and it's only available in Space Gray.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KC8X7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (8-Core M3, 1TB) for &#36;1,549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KB9M3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M3 Pro, 1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GX9MF%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (14-Core M3 Max, 1TB) for &#36;2,899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For the larger display, Amazon has the 12-Core M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB 16-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXB2B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;2,599.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;2,899.00. This, along with a pair of deals on other M3 Pro and M3 Max models, represent all-time low prices on the 16-inch MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB) for &#36;2,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXB2B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB) for &#36;2,599.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5J4X7W%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (16-Core M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB) for &#36;3,749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/amazon-last-deals-year-macbook-pro/">Amazon Has Some of the Last Deals of the Year on Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Pro (Up to &#36;300 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-some-of-the-last-deals-of-the-year-on-apples-m3-macbook-pro-up-to-300-off.2414877/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discusses Push Towards High-End Mac Gaming in New Interview</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-silicon-mac-gaming-interview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discusses-push-towards-high-end-mac-gaming-in-new-interview.2414872/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 06:19:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-silicon-mac-gaming-interview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac Gaming</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>Inverse</em>'s Raymond Wong today published an in-depth <a href="https://www.inverse.com/tech/mac-gaming-apple-silicon-interview">overview of Apple's increasing push towards high-end gaming on the Mac</a>. The story includes commentary from Apple marketing managers Gordon Keppel and Leland Martin.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Mac-Gaming.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899793" /><br/>
One of the biggest reasons that gaming has improved on the Mac in recent years is the switch from Intel processors to Apple silicon, resulting in MacBooks providing industry-leading performance-per-watt. In addition, the latest M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips for the Mac feature hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for improved graphics rendering, which is especially beneficial for high-end AAA games.<br/>
<br/>
"Now, every Mac that ships with Apple silicon can play AAA games pretty fantastically," said Keppel. "Apple silicon has been transformative of our mainstream systems that got tremendous boosts in graphics with M1, M2, and now with M3."<br/>
<br/>
Apple silicon also results in the Mac having the same underlying hardware architecture as the iPhone and iPad, simplifying the development process.<br/>
<br/>
"If you look at the Mac lineup just a few years ago, there was a mix of both integrated and discrete GPUs," said Martin. "That can add complexity when you're developing games. Because you have multiple different hardware permutations to consider. Today, we've effectively eliminated that completely with Apple silicon, creating a unified gaming platform now across iPhone, iPad, and Mac. Once a game is designed for one platform, it's a straightforward process to bring it to the other two. We're seeing this play out with games like Resident Evil Village that launched first [on Mac] followed by iPhone and iPad."<br/>
<br/>
A new technology built into the M3 family of chips is Dynamic Caching, which allows the GPU to allocate memory usage in real time. Apple says this capability "dramatically increases GPU utilization and performance" for demanding apps and games.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has made gaming-related improvements on the software side, too. macOS Sonoma <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/macos-14-game-mode/">features a new Game Mode</a> that temporarily prioritizes CPU and GPU performance for gaming. Game Mode also lowers AirPods audio latency, and reduces input latency with popular third-party game controllers by doubling the Bluetooth sampling rate.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/10/apple-releases-mac-game-porting-toolkit/">released a new toolkit</a> that makes it easier for game developers to port Windows games to the Mac. The toolkit provides an emulation environment that allows developers to run their existing, unmodified Windows game on the Mac and quickly evaluate how well the game could run on macOS before writing any code.<br/>
<br/>
"We've definitely seen interest from developers and publishers like Kojima Productions and Annapurna Interactive Games on how to take advantage of both parts of the Game Porting Toolkit," Martin said. "When you download the toolkit, there's really two parts to it. There's that emulation environment and that's helped demonstrate today's game — you drop in an existing Windows game and see how well it could run on the Mac. The second part is the Metal shader converter and that's there to help developers convert their tens of thousands of shader code into Metal. And they've praised how incredibly useful this is and how it's saved them a bunch of time in their development timeline."<br/>
<br/>
Several high-profile games launched on the Mac this year, including a <em>Resident Evil 4</em> remake, <em>Resident Evil Village</em>, <em>Stray</em>, and <em>Baldur's Gate 3</em>. <em>Death Stranding Director's Cut</em> and <em>Assassin's Creed Mirage</em> are also expected to launch on the Mac next year.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.inverse.com/tech/mac-gaming-apple-silicon-interview">full interview at <em>Inverse</em></a> is a worthwhile read for those interested in gaming on the Mac.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-gaming/">Mac Gaming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/apple-silicon-mac-gaming-interview/">Apple Discusses Push Towards High-End Mac Gaming in New Interview</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discusses-push-towards-high-end-mac-gaming-in-new-interview.2414872/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
