<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 03:00:52 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Five New Features in the iOS 18 Phone App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-phone-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/five-new-features-in-the-ios-18-phone-app.2434190/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 15:46:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-phone-app&#038;post_date=1724377617/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Phone app doesn't often get updated, but with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and Apple Intelligence, it's getting a major overhaul that includes one of the best new features in the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-Phone-App-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962140" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything new with the Phone app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="record_phone_calls_apple_intelligence">Record Phone Calls (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
After placing or answering a call on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can initiate a recording that gives you an audio copy of the call.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-call-recording-1.jpg" alt="" width="5416" height="3047" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960199" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open the Phone app.</li><br/>
 <li>Make a call.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the record button in the top left corner to start a recording.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
When you tap on the record button, everyone on the call is informed that the call is being recorded through an audible message. The message repeats for each person that is recording, so if two &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users are on a call and both record, the message will play twice.<br/>
<br/>
There is no confirmation dialogue when a call is being recorded, so someone who does not want to be recorded would need to hang up the call as there is no opt out.<br/>
<br/>
While the call is in progress, audio is recorded and saved to the Notes app for later access. When you open up the Notes app, you'll see a Call Recording labeled with the date and the time with an option to tap on Play to repeat the call or to tap into the note for more information.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="transcribe_and_summarize_phone_calls_apple_intelligence">Transcribe and Summarize Phone Calls (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
Calls that are saved in the Notes app are automatically transcribed, so you can see a full transcription of what was said on the call. You can get to a transcription by tapping into a Call Recording note.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-call-recording-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1289" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960200" /><br/>
As you listen to the call, the transcript will update so you can read along with what's being said.<br/>
<br/>
Transcriptions have a "Summary" button so you can get a quick summary of what was said in the call, plus there is a search option for searching for key words and phrases.<br/>
<br/>
Transcripts can be added to a different note, or copied, and the audio can be saved to the Files app or shared.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="search_call_history">Search Call History</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, Apple added a search feature for the Recents tab, which means you can now search through all of your incoming and outgoing calls and voicemails.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-phone-app-call-history-search.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962170" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Phone app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the Recents tab.</li><br/>
 <li>Search for the person or number you're looking for with the search bar at the top of the interface.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
You can type in phone numbers or names to see calls that have been placed, received, or missed, and contacts that have the name or phone number you're searching for.<br/>
<br/>
Along with name or phone number, you can search for the date of a call, the type of call (such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>), or use multiple search parameters. If you wanted to see all calls from Eric in June, for example, you could type in "Eric" tap the name when it comes up to set the parameter, and then add in "June" to the search bar.<br/>
<br/>
There are options to "See All" calls and voicemails when conducting a search to view more results.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="swap_sim_cards">Swap SIM cards</h2><br/>
If you have two SIMs on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, such as for personal and work purposes, you can swap between them using a Control Center toggle. In prior versions of iOS, you had to change numbers using the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
To swap numbers, open up Control Center, navigate to the connectivity controls, and long press on Cellular Data.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="contact_suggestions">Contact Suggestions</h2><br/>
When you start typing in a number with the Keypad in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you'll see a list of contacts so you can quickly get to who you want to call.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-auto-fill-phone-app-dialing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962169" /><br/>
Type in the first digit or two of a number and then tap on the "More" icon to see all of your options. You can tap one from there to dial.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="t9_dialing">T9 Dialing</h2><br/>
Related to the contact suggestion feature, you can actually search for names instead of numbers using T9 characters. If you have a contact in your phone under "Eric," you can type in 3 for E, 7 for R, 4 for I, and 2 for C, and the contact card for Eric will pop up.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-phone-app-t9-dialing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962168" /><br/>
T9 dialing dates back to the days before touchscreens, allowing smartphone users to type using predictive text that associated numbers with letters. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has not supported T9 dialing until now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_release_info">Apple Intelligence Release Info</h2><br/>
Call recording, transcribing, and summarizing are Apple Intelligence features that will be available in iOS 18.1. Recording phone calls won't be available in the initial &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update that comes out alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, but it should be introduced to the public in an October update.<br/>
<br/>
Using Apple Intelligence will require an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, or an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
Additional information on new features that Apple has added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-phone-app/">Five New Features in the iOS 18 Phone App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/five-new-features-in-the-ios-18-phone-app.2434190/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Slated to Launch in Mid-September Alongside iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/macos-sequoia-mid-september-launch-date/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-slated-to-launch-in-mid-september-alongside-ios-18.2434189/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:51:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/macos-sequoia-mid-september-launch-date/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, the newest version of the operating system that runs on the Mac, is set to launch in mid-September, <em>MacRumors</em> has learned. While Apple's iOS updates are consistently introduced in September, macOS launch dates vary, and new Mac updates have been released in September, October, and November in recent years.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macOS-Sequoia-Night-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961501" /><br/>
This year, Apple plans to release &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; around the same time as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> rather than holding it until October. Introducing both updates at the same time will ensure that cross-platform features are functional and working as intended, such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring. A key new feature, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring allows an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; to be controlled using a Mac running &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features coming to &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; include refreshed window tiling capabilities, a dedicated Passwords app, and updates to Safari, Messages, Maps, Notes, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features will not be in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; or &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; at launch, with Apple instead introducing the functionality in subsequent iOS 18.1 and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 updates. We expect to see those updates released in October.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is in the final stages of beta testing &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; and &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; ahead of its annual fall iPhone-focused event. If Apple sticks with the timing that it has used for the last several years, the most likely event date is September 10. If that's the event date, new iPhones could launch a week later on September 20. New iOS updates typically come out on the Wednesday before new iPhones launch, so with that timeline, we could see &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; on September 18.<br/>
<br/>
There is some wiggle room with dates, though, and Apple could opt to hold the event later in September, which would change the software launch date guesstimate. Apple could announce its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; event as soon as next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/macos-sequoia-mid-september-launch-date/">macOS Sequoia Slated to Launch in Mid-September Alongside iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-slated-to-launch-in-mid-september-alongside-ios-18.2434189/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nintendo Shutting Down Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp App, Plans to Release Paid Offline Version</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/nintendo-shutting-down-animal-crossing-pocket-camp/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nintendo-shutting-down-animal-crossing-pocket-camp-app-plans-to-release-paid-offline-version.2434185/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:06:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/nintendo-shutting-down-animal-crossing-pocket-camp/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nintendo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nintendo <a href="https://faq.ac-pocketcamp.com/hc/en-us/articles/36349494591001-What-will-happen-when-the-Animal-Crossing-Pocket-Camp-online-service-ends">today announced</a> that it will shut down the Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp app for iOS on November 29, seven years after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/11/21/animal-crossing-pocket-camp-launches/">the game originally launched</a>. Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp is a freemium app that Nintendo has regularly been adding new content to through ongoing events, so there are players with money invested in the game.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2017/10/animalcrossingpocketcamp.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="514" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-598832" /><br/>
There will be no more events or updates with the Pocket Camp service being discontinued, but Nintendo will release a paid version of Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp so that existing users can continue to play an offline version of the game. The paid version will allow saves to be transferred over, but it will not support visiting and interacting with other players or receiving gifts. It will not have in-app purchases nor will it require an online connection.<br/>
<br/>
Pocket Camp users who have purchased Leaf Tickets, the in-game currency, can redeem them through November 28. Leaf Tickets not used by that date will expire. Pocket Camp Club subscriptions will be ending on October 28, but Nintendo will continue providing the associated benefits until Pocket Camp shuts down.<br/>
<br/>
Nintendo plans to release the paid version of the app when the existing freemium version is shut down, but pricing has not yet been announced. Transferring a Pocket Camp save to the new app requires linking to a Nintendo Account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nintendo/">Nintendo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/nintendo-shutting-down-animal-crossing-pocket-camp/">Nintendo Shutting Down Animal Crossing: Pocket Camp App, Plans to Release Paid Offline Version</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nintendo-shutting-down-animal-crossing-pocket-camp-app-plans-to-release-paid-offline-version.2434185/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2434184/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 13:31:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, including both the Lightning and USB-C versions. The firmware has a build number of 7A5290a, up from 7A5266c, and it is available to developers at the current time. This is the fourth firmware update that Apple has released since announcing new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 features in June.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803705" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/AirPods-Pro-Beta-Firmware.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1081" /><br/>
There are multiple features that are coming to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and these features are included in the firmware update.<br/>
<br/>
With head gestures, users can control <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with a shake or a nod of the head. If you get a phone call, for example, you can shake your head no if you don't want to answer it, or nod to accept the call. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interactions can be used for responding to incoming messages, calls, and notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is adding Voice Isolation to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to cut down on loud background sounds to make you easier to hear, and there is a new Personalized Spatial Audio feature specific to gaming. Game developers will be able to incorporate spatial audio into their games for a more immersive audio experience.<br/>
<br/>
The new firmware is limited to developers at the current time, but it will be available to all &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; users following the public launch of the new software.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-4/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2434184/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Require Identity Verification for Sending &#36;500+ in Apple Cash Starting in October</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-cash-identity-verification-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-require-identity-verification-for-sending-500-in-apple-cash-starting-in-october.2434173/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 10:17:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-cash-identity-verification-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Cash</category>
		<category>Tap to Cash</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began sending out emails to customers letting them know about upcoming changes that are being made to the Apple Cash Terms and Conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-tap-to-cash.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957059" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> introduce Tap to Cash, a feature that allows users to exchange Apple Cash in person by holding an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or Apple Watch near another &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or Apple Watch. As part of this feature implementation, Apple is changing the identity verification rules surrounding Apple Cash.<br/>
<br/>
Starting on October 4, Apple will require that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch users verify their identity to send more than a total of &#36;500 in peer-to-peer transfers, which includes sending Apple Cash via Messages and making Tap to Cash payments. Identity verification is required whether sending money from an Apple Cash balance or from a supported card in the Wallet app. Prior transactions will count toward the limit that will trigger identity verification.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109312">already requires</a> identity verification for Apple Cash for those who use the feature frequently. <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109312">Apple's support document</a> says that users cannot add or receive &#36;500 or more in total without identity verification, so it sounds like verification will also be required when sending large amounts of money as of October.<br/>
<br/>
Identify verification for Apple Cash involves taking photos of a driver's license or ID card, as well as answering personal history questions and providing information like home address, date of birth, and social security number.<br/>
<br/>
Identity verification for sending payments makes sense as Tap to Cash will allow money to be exchanged without being accompanied by personal information like phone number. Tap to Cash is designed for private in-person transactions where Apple Cash is exchanged. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's email to customers also says that it is adding the Vision Pro as a supported device for Apple Cash and that weekly peer-to-peer transfer limits will apply to transfers that are sent as well as received. Apple allows users to send or receive a maximum of &#36;10,000 <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109305">within a 7-day period</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-cash/">Apple Cash</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-cash/">Tap to Cash</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-cash-identity-verification-october/">Apple to Require Identity Verification for Sending &#36;500+ in Apple Cash Starting in October</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-require-identity-verification-for-sending-500-in-apple-cash-starting-in-october.2434173/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Lineup to Introduce Wave of Camera Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/iphone-16-lineup-wave-of-camera-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-to-introduce-wave-of-camera-improvements.2434167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:30:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/iphone-16-lineup-wave-of-camera-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>AppleInsider</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup will feature a significant number of new camera features and capabilities, <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/08/22/exclusive-every-iphone-16-iphone-16-pro-camera-spec-capture-button-detail-revealed"><em>AppleInsider</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
Both the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models are rumored to step up the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s photography and videography functions, including upgraded hardware such as 48-megapixel sensor on the Pro models' ultra wide camera and software such as macro photography for the standard models and an all-new image format. Reiterating some previous rumors, the report claims that:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;'s main camera will remain the same as that of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> with a 48-megapixel sensor and a f/1.6 aperture, and there are unlikely to be changes to the unit on subsequent generations through to 2026.</li><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;'s ultra wide camera will gain a f/2.2 aperture, up from the f/2.4 aperture on the previous generation, to improve low-light performance.</li><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus may support macro photography for the first time. The feature is currently exclusive to the Pro models. </li><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will continue to feature a 48-megapixel main camera with an f/1.78 aperture.</li><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will gain the 5x tetraprism telephoto camera introduced on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max last year, replacing the current 3x telephoto camera. </li><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will feature an upgraded ultra wide camera with a 48-megapixel sensor, with the same pixel-binning feature as the main camera. It will have an f/2.2 aperture, up from f/2.4, for significantly improved low-light performance and support 48-megapixel ProRaw photography.</li><br/>
	<li>Apple will introduce a new image format called "JPEG-XL," sitting alongside HEIF, JPEG, HEIF Max, ProRaw, and ProRAW Max.</li><br/>
	<li>The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will support 3K video at 120 frames per second with Dolby Vision.</li><br/>
	<li>A new capacitive "Capture" button will be introduced on all four models, designed to be used exclusively by camera apps. Users will apparently be able to select which camera app the button opens, including third-party ones.</li><br/>
	<li>The Capture button offers a force-sensitive half-press tied to a developer API that could, for example, lock exposure and focus, before fully depressing the button to take a photo.</li><br/>
	<li>Sliding along the capacitive button will also perform different actions. This gesture will tout a developer API.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is expected to be announced in just a matter of weeks. The Pro models are expected to feature larger display sizes and a faster chip, while the standard models are set to offer the Action button and a redesigned rear camera array. See <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">our comprehensive roundup</a> for more information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/appleinsider-com/">AppleInsider</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/iphone-16-lineup-wave-of-camera-improvements/">iPhone 16 Lineup to Introduce Wave of Camera Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-to-introduce-wave-of-camera-improvements.2434167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Promotes Final Cut Pro for Mac and iPad in New Ad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-final-cut-pro-for-mac-and-ipad-in-new-ad.2434166/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:12:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Final Cut Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared new ads focusing on <a href="https://www.apple.com/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro 10.8</a>, the latest version of the Apple-designed app for professional video editing. The first ad highlights Final Cut Pro for the Mac, while the second covers Final Cut Pro for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Final Cut Pro 10.8 Apple Pro Apps" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dy3k9M8kqu0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Final Cut Pro for iPad 2 Apple Pro Apps" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5IshJoOuIJQ" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Both videos walk through the different features that are available in Final Cut Pro on the Mac and the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. The Mac video walks through different tools for adding effects and organizing footage, while the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; ad shows off the touch-based gestures and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> integration.<br/>
<br/>
With Final Cut Pro 10.8, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/final-cut-pro-major-update/">came out in June</a>, Apple added Enhance Light and Color, an feature that improves color, color balance, contrast, and brightness in one step. Slo-Mo, another AI feature, blends the frames of video intelligently to provide higher-quality movement.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also introduced Final Cut Camera, an app that can capture video from multiple iOS devices and feed it into Final Cut Pro for a multicam experience.<br/>
<br/>
Final Cut Pro is priced at &#36;300 for the Mac version, and &#36;49 per year or &#36;4.99 per month for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; version. Apple offers a free 90-day trial.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-ad/">Apple Promotes Final Cut Pro for Mac and iPad in New Ad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-final-cut-pro-for-mac-and-ipad-in-new-ad.2434166/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Let EU Users Set New Defaults for Multiple Apps, Delete App Store, Photos, Messages and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-eu-default-app-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-let-eu-users-set-new-defaults-for-multiple-apps-delete-app-store-photos-messages-and-more.2434165/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-eu-default-app-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/">making additional changes</a> to its app ecosystem in the European Union to comply with the terms of the Digital Markets Act. The default browser selection experience that's already in place will be updated, Apple will allow EU users to set defaults for more types of apps, and core iOS apps like Messages and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> will also be deletable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owners in the EU can already set different defaults for the browser, mail app, app marketplace, and contactless payments, but Apple is going to allow users to select new defaults for phone calls, messaging, password managers, keyboards, call spam filters, navigation, and translation. That means, for example, that EU users will be able to choose an app like WhatsApp instead of Messages to be their default texting app, or a mapping app like Waze to be the default instead of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet provided insight into just how setting a new default will work for messaging apps, navigation, password managers, and more, and the company plans to provide more information as the launch date for these features approaches. New defaults for phone calls, messaging, password managers, spam call filters, and keyboards will be able to be set starting with an update to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> coming later this year, while the option to set different navigation and translation defaults will be implemented in spring 2025.<br/>
<br/>
To handle the multitude of new default apps that can be set, Apple is adding a Default Apps section to the Settings app. It will list all of the defaults available to each user for easy management.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/eu-ios-18-default-apps-settings.jpg" alt="" width="1432" height="606" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962200" /><br/>
Along with setting new apps as defaults, Apple will let users delete core apps. The &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, Messages, Camera, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, and Safari apps will be able to be deleted, so it's essentially just the Settings and Phone apps that will not be able to be removed in the EU. If a user deletes the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; app, it will be able to be reinstalled from the Settings app if desired, while the other apps can be reinstalled from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.4, EU users were able to select a default browser from a randomized list of the top 12 browsers in their country. In a future update to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, the browser choice window will pop up again if a user has Safari set as their default. The new browser selection experience will include a descriptive line about the browser, as well as the option to set a default browser right from the choice window. If a user selects a browser that is already installed on their device, it will open automatically, otherwise there will be a downloading icon and the browser will open after it's downloaded. Users will also need to scroll through the full list of available browser options before being able to make a selection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/eu-ios-18-default-browser-choice.jpg" alt="" width="1928" height="882" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962201" /><br/>
Note that the option to set a default browser will only show up again for users who have Safari as the default, so if an EU user has already selected Chrome, the choice window will not pop up again with the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update coming later in the year. Users will also see the selection interface on all of their devices rather than just one, and it will show up when Safari is opened for the first time after updating. Setting a new default when Safari is on the user's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or Dock will see the new default browser replace the Safari icon.<br/>
<br/>
The browser default popup will also be displayed when migrating to a new device if the user previously had Safari set as the default.<br/>
<br/>
The changes that Apple is making are applicable for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users in the European Union with updates to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and will not be available in other countries like the United States.<br/>
<br/>
More information on the changes <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/browser-choice-screen/">can be found on Apple's developer site</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-eu-default-app-update/">Apple to Let EU Users Set New Defaults for Multiple Apps, Delete App Store, Photos, Messages and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-let-eu-users-set-new-defaults-for-multiple-apps-delete-app-store-photos-messages-and-more.2434165/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Studio Display Available for Record Low Price of &#36;1,299.99 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-studio-display-low-discounts-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-studio-display-available-for-record-low-price-of-1-299-99-on-amazon.2434157/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 08:23:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-studio-display-low-discounts-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the Apple Studio Display for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.00, which is a match of the all-time low price on the monitor. This is the standard glass version of the Studio Display with the tilt adjustable stand, and Amazon also has a few other models on sale as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/studio-display-april.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948662" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the standard glass model with the VESA Mount Adapter for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3HGN6Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.00, but there isn't currently a sale on the tilt- and height-adjustable stand model. In regards to the VESA model, this is a match of the all-time low price on the display.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Standard Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you want to upgrade to the nano-texture glass option, Amazon also has this model of the Studio Display on sale. It's available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3HP4KL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,599.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,899.00, which is a second-best price on the Studio Display with nano-texture glass.<br/>
<br/>
The Studio Display features a 27-inch 5K retina display with a 5120 x 2880 resolution and up to 600 nits of brightness. Apple says that the standard display is engineered for "extremely low reflectivity," but for rooms where there is a lot of glare, Apple suggests the nano-texture glass option with even less reflectivity.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/apple-studio-display-low-discounts-2/">Apple Studio Display Available for Record Low Price of &#36;1,299.99 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-studio-display-available-for-record-low-price-of-1-299-99-on-amazon.2434157/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Folding All-Screen MacBook Delayed Until Late 2027 At the Earliest</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/kuo-foldable-macbook-delayed-2027/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-folding-all-screen-macbook-delayed-until-late-2027-at-the-earliest.2434144/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 03:50:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/kuo-foldable-macbook-delayed-2027/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Foldable MacBook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's rumored foldable MacBook won't arrive until the end of 2027 or 2028 at the earliest because of technical challenges, according to the latest prediction by <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1826460677604786478">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/foldable-macbook-astropad.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="768" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-837701" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Concept by <a href="https://astropad.com/foldable-mac-screen/">Astropad</a></em></div><br/>
Previous reports from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">display industry analyst Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/first-apple-foldable-coming-in-2025/">Haitong analyst Jeff Pu</a>, Korean website <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/apple-20-inch-display-future-macbook-pro/">The Elec</a></em>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-foldable-ipad-delays/">Kuo himself</a> suggested that Apple is developing an all-display foldable laptop that will feature a 20.2-inch or an 18.8-inch screen. <br/>
<br/>
When folded, the laptop was rumored to be a full-size on-screen keyboard that seamlessly integrates the typing experience into the display itself. When completely unfolded, the device was said to function as a standard monitor. Paired with an external keyboard, it would essentially transform into a large-screen desktop setup. <br/>
<br/>
Kuo in May said that LG Display was aiming to begin mass production of display panels for a MacBook with a 20.2-inch or an 18.8-inch foldable screen in the fourth quarter of 2025. However, his <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1826460677604786478">latest post on X (Twitter)</a> claims that Apple has canceled the 20-inch design and has now settled on a display size of 18.8 inches.<br/>
<br/>
"Some market participants previously expected Apple to launch the foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in 2025," said Kuo in his latest post. "But the current supply chain survey indicates that the foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; has no visibility. This may also be because some call this foldable MacBook a foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been experimenting with various devices with foldable displays, including a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-foldable-ipad-delays/">foldable iPad</a> and MacBook. Obviously the MacBook is already foldable, but Apple has reportedly been exploring an all-display MacBook form factor that has no standard keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
Display analyst Ross Young said in July 2022 that Apple could bring some kind of foldable laptop to market in 2026 or 2027, and it remains unclear if such a device would be classified as a Mac, an ‌&zwnj;iPad&zwnj;‌, or something in between. <br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/first-apple-foldable-coming-in-2025/">May report</a>, Haitong analyst Jeff Pu said Apple's first foldable devices would reach mass production in 2025 and 2026, following increasing evidence of foldable devices in Apple's supply chain. At the time, the analyst said Apple would likely release a large-screen foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or MacBook in that timeframe before launching a higher-volume foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in late 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Pu had claimed one Apple foldable with a 20.3-inch display would start production in late 2025, which was sooner than previously expected. However, Pu later said he believed Apple would join the foldable market in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-foldable-ipad-delays/">second quarter of 2026</a> due to "display durability issues," reflecting Apple's intention to perfect a foldable design. It seems Apple is still in the prototyping stage of a foldable device. Would you be interested in such a product? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-macbook/">Foldable MacBook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/kuo-foldable-macbook-delayed-2027/">Kuo: Folding All-Screen MacBook Delayed Until Late 2027 At the Earliest</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-folding-all-screen-macbook-delayed-until-late-2027-at-the-earliest.2434144/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card Turns 5, Still U.S. Only</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-card-turns-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-turns-5-still-u-s-only.2434116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-card-turns-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yesterday marked the fifth anniversary of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/20/apple-card-launches-widely-in-us/">saw an official release</a> on August 20, 2019. The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; is Apple's first and only Apple-branded credit card, made available in partnership with Goldman Sachs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/apple-card-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="1144" height="644" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-735877" /><br/>
At launch, the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; was only available in the United States, and today, five years later, it is still limited to the United States and has not expanded to additional countries. Just a month after the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;'s debut, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/09/30/tim-cook-visits-germany/">interested in expanding</a> the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; to multiple countries, but that it would take time due to various regulations around the world.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors of &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; talks in Europe, and Apple trademarked &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; in Europe, Hong Kong, and Canada, but no deals have emerged. &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; expanding to additional countries is even more up in the air with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">upcoming decoupling</a> from Goldman Sachs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning to end its partnership with Goldman Sachs in 2025, and it will need to find a new &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; provider in the United States. Apple and Goldman Sachs ran into trouble with customer service issues for disputed &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions, as well as complaints with wait times for Apple Savings account withdrawals.<br/>
<br/>
Goldman Sachs even ended up <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-fed-probes-goldman-sachs-consumer-business-wsj-2023-01-20/">being investigated</a> by the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau because of customer complaints, which led to a souring of the bank's relationship with Apple. Goldman Sachs now plans to get out of consumer banking entirely.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; is a no-fee credit card with no annual fees, no international fees, no fees for making a late payment, and no fees for exceeding a credit limit. There aren't consumer protections like one might get with an American Express card, but there is deep integration with the Wallet app for tracking spending.<br/>
<br/>
Apple provides 1 percent Daily Cash back on all purchases, 2 percent for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> purchases, and 3 percent for &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; purchases from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>. Daily Cash is sent to customers each day, hence the name.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not commented on the possibility of expanding &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; to additional countries in some time, and there is no word on whether that's still the plan.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-card-turns-5/">Apple Card Turns 5, Still U.S. Only</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-turns-5-still-u-s-only.2434116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google&#039;s Pixel AI Image Creation and Editing Tools Are Kind of Terrifying</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/googles-pixel-ai-image-creation-and-editing-tools-are-kind-of-terrifying.2434114/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:19:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google last week introduced the Pixel 9 smartphone lineup, with a selection of new devices that are focused on AI. All of the Pixel 9 phones support Gemini AI, and Google has also added AI-based image generation and editing tools. Reviewers have been testing the new smartphone features, and the AI image generation is probably going to turn into a PR nightmare for Google based on what's come out so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/google-pixel-9.jpg" alt="" width="2050" height="1153" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962164" /><br/>
Google introduced an AI image generation app for the Pixel phones, called Pixel Studio. It's designed to create stickers and images using text-based prompts, and it looks and sounds a lot like Apple's planned Image Playground. So far, reviewers have been able to create all manner of questionable images with Pixel Studio, ranging from a Nazi version of Spongebob to Elmo with an AK47.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/pixel-studio-digital-trends.jpg" alt="" width="3240" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962163" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Image via Digital Trends</div></em><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.digitaltrends.com/mobile/i-tried-google-pixel-studio-app-image-generator-problems-concerns/">Digital Trends</a></em> had no trouble getting Pixel Studio to make images of beloved cartoon characters doing questionable activities. Guns, drugs, and alcohol were not off-limits, nor were offensive situations like school shootings. Pixel Studio did not generate these kinds of images unless asked, but that's most likely what people will immediately do with the feature rather than generating images of cute cats and bunnies.<br/>
<br/>
Google said that there were "safety checks" in place to keep Pixel Studio from being "used nefariously," and there are some. Pixel Studio will not create images of humans, and Google is tweaking the AI in response to reviews. After speaking with Google, <em>Digital Trends</em> was no longer able to get Pixel Studio to create cartoon characters using cocaine or dressed as German soldiers.<br/>
<br/>
Even more concerning than Pixel Studio is Google's "Reimagine" tool, which can add objects to photos that you've already taken. <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/21/24224084/google-pixel-9-reimagine-ai-photos">The Verge</a></em> used it to add corpses, bombs, drugs, and disasters to images, and objects included in photos look so realistic that it's difficult to tell when an image has been edited. Google is able to do a pretty good job matching lighting and perspective to the original photo, and there are no watermarks or flags on social media. Google does add a metadata tag, but that's easy enough to eliminate with a screenshot.<br/>
<br/>
You can, of course, use Reimagine for adding sunsets and rainbows to your image, just like you can use Pixel Studio for creating fun pictures, and both AI features work great, so these tools aren't all bad. <em><a href="https://www.androidauthority.com/30-pixel-studio-creations-3473158/">Android Authority</a></em> shared a post with Oreo pizza, a giraffe surfing, and kittens playing basketball, for example. As <em>The Verge</em> points out, you could always add a body to an image or create a picture of Elmo with a gun, but it would take some Photoshop skill and time to do so. With the Pixel phones, it takes just a thought and a few seconds to create that kind of image, and it's right there on the smartphone for anyone to use.<br/>
<br/>
In statements to <em>The Verge</em> and <em>Digital Trends</em>, Google said that it designed its generative AI tools to "respect the intent of user prompts" which can lead to the creation of content "that may offend" when the user asks for it. But Google claims that there are "Terms of Service" on what content is not allowed, and that safeguards will be continually refined.<br/>
<br/>
Apple hasn't yet introduced its image generation tools, Image Playground or Genmoji, and the media surrounding the Pixel 9 launch gives us some insight into what the response might be like if Apple doesn't get it just right. With AI, it's likely that people are going to be able to find workarounds even if Apple puts numerous safeguards in place. Apple so far has shied away from photorealistic AI images, but Google is going all in, and it's going to be much harder to trust photos on social media and the internet going forward.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/">Google&#039;s Pixel AI Image Creation and Editing Tools Are Kind of Terrifying</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/googles-pixel-ai-image-creation-and-editing-tools-are-kind-of-terrifying.2434114/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>App Store VP Departs as Apple Prepares for Organizational Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/app-store-organizational-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-vp-departs-as-apple-prepares-for-organizational-changes.2434107/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:11:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/app-store-organizational-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> vice president Matt Fischer is set to leave the company as Apple prepares for an &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; reorganization to deal with regulatory changes, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-21/apple-s-app-store-head-to-leave-in-reorganization-amid-global-scrutiny">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
Apple plans to split its &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; group into two teams, one that handles the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and a second team that oversees alternative app distribution. As of earlier this year, Apple has supported iOS app downloads from alternative app stores and from websites in the European Union, a change that the company had to make to comply with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
To handle ongoing compliance with EU regulations for app distribution and alternative payment methods, &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; chief <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phil-schiller/">Phil Schiller</a> is changing the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s hierarchy.<br/>
<br/>
Fischer joined Apple in 2003 to oversee iTunes marketing, but he has served as the vice president of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; since 2010. In an email to Apple employees today, Fischer said that he had been thinking about leaving Apple for some time, and the reorganization provided the right opportunity.<br/>
<br/>
With Fischer leaving, &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; senior director Carson Oliver will oversee the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and Ann Thai, a director who oversees &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; features, will head up the team that handles alternative app distribution.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/app-store-organizational-changes/">App Store VP Departs as Apple Prepares for Organizational Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-vp-departs-as-apple-prepares-for-organizational-changes.2434107/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PSA: There&#039;s a New Character Bug That Can Cause iPhones to Crash</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-character-bug-respring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-theres-a-new-character-bug-that-can-cause-iphones-to-crash.2434102/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:25:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-character-bug-respring/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There is a new character bug that can result in a respring on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, reports <em><a href="https://infosec.exchange/@kpwn/113000348717635390">TechCrunch</a></em>. Typing "":: in the search field after swiping over to the App Library will cause the Springboard to reset, dropping you back at the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Lock Screen. A respring is not a full reset, and it only takes a few seconds for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to be functional again.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
Typing the same characters into the Settings app search interface will cause the Settings app to crash, but putting it in a Spotlight search doesn't seem to impact anything. The respring seemed to only happen on devices running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> when we tested, but putting those characters into a search interface on a device running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> does result in some odd behavior, such as the characters disappearing and the Settings app crashing.<br/>
<br/>
You can actually type in just "": and any other character to cause the respring to happen, so it's something related to the first three symbols in a four character sequence.<br/>
<br/>
Character bugs have in the past spread though Messages and have allowed users to crash the iPhones of others, but this is a much more insignificant issue because the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; owner needs to manually type (or paste) the characters into a search interface. There does not appear to be a way to affect an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; through Messages or another texting platform.<br/>
<br/>
It's likely Apple will address the issue with an iOS update in the near future.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-character-bug-respring/">PSA: There&#039;s a New Character Bug That Can Cause iPhones to Crash</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-theres-a-new-character-bug-that-can-cause-iphones-to-crash.2434102/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Max: One Year Review</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review.2434095/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:53:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been almost a year since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models were released, so <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera decided to do a one-year check-in review on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max to see how it's performed over the last 12 months.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vSX-9cRPZx4" title="iPhone 15 Pro Max: One Year Later Review" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Unsurprisingly, Dan has seen some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> battery degradation, and it's dropped to 89 percent. That's with regular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> usage, running betas, and standard day-to-day use. Even at 89 percent, the battery can still last for a full day without needing a charge.<br/>
<br/>
As for the titanium chassis, it's held up well. There are a few nicks due to minor drops, but the display has seen a lot more damage with several scratches, some of which are deep.<br/>
<br/>
The transition to USB-C has been a little tough just because there are still people with Lightning iPhones. If someone wants to borrow your charger, you may not have the right cable if you've switched to USB-C and they're still on Lightning.<br/>
<br/>
Dan uses the Action Button for opening up the Camera app, but there's so much more that the Action Button can do in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and it's going to get a lot more useful in the future. You can set Control Center controls to the Action Button, and developers can make new controls for apps that you can use.<br/>
<br/>
There's not too much to say about the triple-lens camera setup, which is great. The 5x zoom lens is excellent for taking portrait pictures of people, and it's been a solid improvement. Otherwise, the cameras are fantastic with a lot of focal length versatility thanks to the new zoom option.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max has held up well, and if you have one (or a Pro), there's no real need to upgrade to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. The A17 Pro in the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is incredibly fast and there's no way most people are even reaching the limits of its capabilities at this time, and Apple isn't adding too much more than an extra Capture Button and a slightly larger display in 2024. You can already use Apple Intelligence if you have an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; model, so there's not a lot to get out of a year-over-year upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
If you have an older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it's worth looking at the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, or even an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; when prices drop and they're discontinued. All of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have a chip compatible with Apple Intelligence, a Capture Button, and an Action Button, so there's a lot to gain coming from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> or earlier.<br/>
<br/>
How has your &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; held up if you have one? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review/">iPhone 15 Pro Max: One Year Review</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-one-year-review.2434095/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Fifth watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-fifth-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2434094/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:50:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the fourth beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to give the new features a try ahead of when the software launches this fall. The fifth beta comes a week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-4/">after the fourth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957264" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-vitals.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; can be downloaded after signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's beta software website</a> and upgrading your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to the public beta version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. You'll need to open up the Watch app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, go to General, select Software Update, and choose the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Public Beta option under Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, Apple added a new Vitals app that can be used to give you a daily overview of your health metrics, letting you know if anything is out of the ordinary. It compares information collected at night like heart rate, sleep, respiratory rate, and oxygen level to your levels over the previous weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Smart Stack has new widgets like Translate and Shazam, plus it's smarter because it is able to suggest widgets based on time, date, location, and daily routine. Interactive widgets let you access app features from the Smart Stack, and it also supports Live Activities.<br/>
<br/>
Training Load is a new way of measuring how the intensity and duration of workouts impact the body over time, with Apple providing an effort level for cardio-based workouts to help you know when to rest and when to push harder.<br/>
<br/>
You can now customize your Activity Ring requirements for different days of the week, and Apple added support for rest days. Taking a break from activity will no longer ruin a streak because you can pause for a day, a week, a month, or more.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include more workout types, Check In for Messages, a revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face, improvements to Double Tap, and more, with additional information <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">available in our watchOS 11 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-5/">Apple Releases Fifth watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-fifth-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2434094/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Launches Stand One Max Qi2 Charging Hub for iPhone, Apple Watch and AirPods</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-stand-one-max-qi2-charging-hub-for-iphone-apple-watch-and-airpods.2434088/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nomad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nomad today introduced its latest multi-device charger, debuting a new version of the Stand One Max with Qi2 support. Rather than continuing to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a>, Nomad is transitioning to Qi2, the latest Qi charging standard that is able to charge iPhones at &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nomad-stand-one-max-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962082" /><br/>
The Stand One Max can charge an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at up to 15W, and we were able to test the charger out ahead of launch. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max charged from 0 to 39 percent in an hour, which is essentially identical to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging speeds.<br/>
<br/>
The Stand One Max features an upright charging base for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a small charging arm for the Apple Watch and a Qi-based platform for charging the AirPods. It's a compact design that takes up little room on a desk, and as with all Nomad products, it is well-made. Nomad had a prior version of the Stand One Max, but the new version moves the Apple Watch charger lower to allow for compatibility with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s StandBy mode.<br/>
<br/>
The Stand One Max is crafted from solid metal and it has a shiny glass cover panel. It can be purchased in silver or carbide colors, and the close to 2 pound weight adds stability, as does the rubber bottom. An &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be positioned on the magnetic base in portrait or landscape mode, so StandBy is supported. The angle of the charging base cannot be adjusted, but it is tilted back slightly for a comfortable viewing position on a desktop or nightstand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nomad-stand-one-max-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962083" /><br/>
In addition to charging a MagSafe-compatible &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at up to 15W, the Stand One Max has an Apple Watch fast charger so that it can charge the Series 7 or later at the fastest possible speed. The position of the Apple Watch charger allows for Night Stand mode to be used, which also wasn't possible with the prior iteration. The AirPods charger charges at 5W, and there is a small indentation to guide positioning.<br/>
<br/>
The relocated position of the Apple Watch charger is convenient because it no longer prevents the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from charging in landscape mode, and there is no loss of functionality. The AirPods charger is pushed back behind the Apple Watch charger, and the overall footprint is about the same. It is a better design than the prior Stand One Max, and it is less expensive with the transition to Qi2.<br/>
<br/>
The new Stand One Max is priced at &#36;150, which is &#36;30 lower than the price of the prior &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; version. You will need to supply your own 30W power adapter, but a USB-C power cable is included. The Stand One Max can be <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/stand-one-max-carbide-3rd-gen">purchased from the Nomad website</a> as of today.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad is also offering a flash sale on its <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/base-one-max-3-in-1-silver">Base One Max chargers</a> this week, discounting them by 30 percent with the promo code BM130. The Base One Max has a flat charging base so it can charge non-MagSafe smartphones.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nomad/">Nomad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/nomad-qi2-stand-one-max/">Nomad Launches Stand One Max Qi2 Charging Hub for iPhone, Apple Watch and AirPods</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-stand-one-max-qi2-charging-hub-for-iphone-apple-watch-and-airpods.2434088/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon&#039;s New Accessory Sale Includes Deals on AirTag, Eufy SmartTrack, and Jackery Power Stations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/amazon-airtag-eufy-jackery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-new-accessory-sale-includes-deals-on-airtag-eufy-smarttrack-and-jackery-power-stations.2434084/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 08:17:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/amazon-airtag-eufy-jackery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a big collection of discounts on Bluetooth trackers and portable power stations, including Apple's own AirTag, Anker's more affordable brand of Eufy SmartTrack accessories, and power stations from Jackery. All of these deals can be found on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airtag-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940079" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the AirTag, you can get the 1 Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;24.99</strong></a> and the 4 Pack of trackers for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;99.00. These are both solid second-best prices on the AirTag.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/eufy-smartrack-link.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955367" /><br/>
<br/>
Anyone who needs a Bluetooth tracker but wants to save a bit of money should look at Anker's Eufy brand of trackers, which are on sale on Amazon right now and compatible with Find My on Apple devices. These start at just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214586794"><strong>&#36;15.99</strong></a> for one tracker and raise to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"><strong>&#36;48.99</strong></a> for a 4 Pack. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214586794"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 1 Pack for &#36;15.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 2 Pack for &#36;29.88</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1723214604243"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;21 OFF</div>SmartTrack Link 4 Pack for &#36;48.99 (Prime members only)</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you want a tracker that you can fit in a wallet, Eufy's SmartTrack Card is a great solution at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1723214719490"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.99. Most of Eufy's trackers can be delivered between August 22 and August 27, and none of these deals require a coupon code in order to see the final sale prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1723214719490"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962136" /><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Jackery has a large collection of discounts on its best portable power stations on Amazon this week, starting at &#36;199.99 for the Explorer 100 Plus Power Station, down from &#36;229.00. Most of these deals require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.WAQNA1RIZWIZ_1723559358185">Explorer 100 Plus Power Station with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;199.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.FK2BIIO8032Y%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.FK2BIIO8032Y_1723559560854">Solar Generator 240 with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;269.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1S26WFMTGKTLG%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1S26WFMTGKTLG_1723559487405">Explorer 1000 Power Station (version 2)</a> - &#36;629.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.399U48EASRUZ2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.399U48EASRUZ2_1723559529144">Explorer 2000 Pro Power Station</a> - &#36;1,499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.35XLU54M76H6P%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.35XLU54M76H6P_1723559651126">Explorer 3000 Pro Power Station</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/amazon-airtag-eufy-jackery/">Amazon&#039;s New Accessory Sale Includes Deals on AirTag, Eufy SmartTrack, and Jackery Power Stations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-new-accessory-sale-includes-deals-on-airtag-eufy-smarttrack-and-jackery-power-stations.2434084/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: iCloud Is the Most Popular Apple Subscription Service in the US</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/icloud-storage-most-popular-apple-service/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-icloud-is-the-most-popular-apple-subscription-service-in-the-us.2434083/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 08:04:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/icloud-storage-most-popular-apple-service/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Paid <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> storage overwhelmingly remains the most popular Apple service in the United States, according to a <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/icloud-storage-remains-apples-most">new report</a> from Consumer Intelligence Research Partners (CIRP).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iCloud-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-803318" /><br/>
Nearly two-thirds of Apple customers in the United States opt for paid &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage, surpassing other services like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> in terms of user adoption. In comparison, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; have achieved moderate penetration rates among Apple customers, with 42% and 32% adoption, respectively. &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;, the company's extended warranty service, sees even lower adoption, with only 17% of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> buyers opting for the additional coverage. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-services-cirp.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="934" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-962128" /><br/>
These other services, while significant contributors to Apple's Services revenue, operate in highly competitive markets, unlike the cloud storage market where no service is able to offer such a deeply integrated experience with Apple devices as &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;. Many users opt for just one music service and multiple video subscriptions, which limits the growth potential for Apple's subscription offerings. As Apple's hardware sales growth slows, the company has increasingly turned to its services segment as a source of revenue.<br/>
<br/>
Paid &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; subscriptions start at &#36;0.99 per month for 50GB of storage, &#36;2.99 per month for 200GB, and &#36;9.99 per month for 2TB. These standalone &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage plans can also be bundled with other Apple services through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a>, which offers three tiers: the Individual plan at &#36;16.95 per month includes 50GB of &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>; the Family plan at &#36;22.95 per month includes 200GB of &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage and extends those services to up to six family members; and the Premier plan at &#36;32.95 per month includes 2TB of &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage and adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>+ and Apple Fitness+.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/icloud-storage-most-popular-apple-service/">Report: iCloud Is the Most Popular Apple Subscription Service in the US</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-icloud-is-the-most-popular-apple-subscription-service-in-the-us.2434083/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s September Event: New Products to Expect Beyond the iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-september-event-new-products-to-expect-beyond-the-iphone-16.2434080/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:53:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will hold its annual iPhone event next month, with some signs pointing to September 10 as the date that the company will announce its new flagship iPhone 16 lineup. But it's worth noting that there are a few more products expected to be unveiled as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Event-October-2023.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919098" /><br/>
Keep reading to learn everything we know about what else Apple is expected to announce at the event beyond the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
Apple is expected to release a thinner version of the Apple Watch in 2024, but it likely won't look significantly different from current models, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Larger display sizes are anticipated, and Apple plans to continue offering two models.<br/>
<br/>
The larger of the two standard Apple Watch casing sizes, the 45mm model, is expected to become the smallest option, while an all-new 49mm casing size, matching the current Apple Watch Ultra, is expected to be introduced as the new larger option.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> also predicts that the 2024 Apple Watch Series 10 will feature a slimmer design with larger screens. Kuo expects the Series 10 to come in 45mm and 49mm sizes, an increase from the current 41mm and 45mm options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-9-display.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913380" /><br/>
The next-generation Apple Watch is expected to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/next-apple-watch-thinner-logic-board-rumor/">resin-coated copper</a>, which will allow for a thinner logic board and enhance durability and water resistance. A thinner logic board would create additional internal space for other components.<br/>
<br/>
Previously, Mark Gurman mentioned that Apple was considering a magnetic band attachment system that could free up more space inside the Apple Watch, but his latest reports do not mention this feature. If implemented, the magnetic band system might make existing bands incompatible with new models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also been working on features for hypertension and sleep apnea detection in the Series 10, but Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">indicates</a> these may not be ready for launch. Apple is reportedly facing reliability issues with the hypertension feature, which could cause delays, and the sleep apnea detection relies on blood oxygen monitoring, a feature Apple has temporarily removed from the Apple Watch due to patent concerns.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 3</h2><br/>
When Apple Watch Ultra 2 debuted last year, key new features included a 50% brighter display, a faster S9 chip, a "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watch without touching the screen, on-device Siri, and increased internal storage. This year's iteration could be much more modest, though.<br/>
<br/>
Initially, it was believed that Apple was working on an Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display, which would provide increased brightness, better contrast, and improved battery efficiency. However, these plans appear to have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">postponed indefinitely</a>. <br/>
<br/>
As a result, the design of the Apple Watch Ultra 3 is likely to remain largely unchanged. Reporter Mark Gurman recently said that this year's third-generation Apple Watch Ultra will have "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">roughly the same look as the original,</a>." He has previously suggested a totally redesigned "Apple Watch X" with a thinner case and magnetic bands is coming, but this is likely to be a different model to the Ultra, and he said it would be released "in 2024 or 2025."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
According to Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, the Apple Watch Ultra 3 is expected to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/">"almost no" new hardware upgrades</a> compared to the Apple Watch Ultra 2. His phrasing would seem to suggest that the rumored blood pressure and sleep apnea detection features will be machine learning / software-based, relying on existing sensors. However, Mark Gurman says the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will feature a new processor that succeeds last year's S9 chip, and that this could "lay the groundwork for some AI enhancements down the road."<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 was expected to include improved health tracking capabilities such as blood pressure monitoring and sleep apnea detection, aligning with the rumored features of the Apple Watch Series 10, but those features could be further out, as mentioned above.<br/>
<br/>
On the flip side, Apple is rumored to be adopting new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/09/2024-apple-watch-more-power-efficient-display/">low-energy OLED panel technology</a> in new Apple Watch models to further reduce the power consumption of its always-on display. If that's the case, it's unlikely that Apple would use the technology in its latest Series model without also bringing it to its latest Apple Watch Ultra model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE 3</h2><br/>
Apple's third-generation Apple Watch SE may feature significant changes according to recent reports. Research analyst David Hsieh suggests the new model will have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/08/apple-watch-series-x-larger-display-rumor/">larger display</a>, matching the Apple Watch Series 8 with 41mm and 45mm case sizes. This represents an increase from the current 40mm and 44mm options, potentially offering about 12% more screen area.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Watch-SE-3-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918243" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reports that Apple is likely to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/apple-watch-se-plastic/">rigid plastic</a> instead of aluminum for the watch's body. This material change could lower production costs and appeal to parents buying for children. These updates indicate Apple's strategy to create a more accessible smartwatch option, balancing modern features with affordability and durability.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4 (Possibly)</h2><br/>
The fourth-generation AirPods are anticipated to launch in either September or October, with Apple planning to offer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">two versions at different price points</a>, so there's a decent chance we could see them next month during Apple's iPhone 16 event. Both models will sport a redesigned look, featuring a USB-C port instead of the Lightning port, shorter stems similar to the AirPods Pro, an improved fit, and enhanced audio quality.<br/>
<br/>
The higher-end version is expected to include Active Noise Cancellation (ANC), introducing ANC at a more affordable price point for the first time. This version is also likely to feature a speaker in the charging case for Find My location tracking. While it will be less expensive than the AirPods Pro (&#36;249), it won’t include features like silicone ear tips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/AirPods-Fourth-Generation-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905655" /><br/>
The next-generation AirPods are expected to inherit the H2 chip from the second-generation AirPods Pro. Currently, the second- and third-generation AirPods use the H1 chip. The H2 chip brings Bluetooth 5.3 connectivity, which offers faster and more reliable connections with Bluetooth accessories, as well as improved power efficiency that can lead to longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple claims that the H2 chip delivers an "exceptional acoustic experience" when paired with a new low-distortion audio driver and custom amplifier in the AirPods Pro. This combination results in richer bass and clearer sound across a wider range of frequencies, thanks to computational audio enhancements enabled by the H2 chip. It's highly likely that similar improvements will be featured in the fourth-generation AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max 2 (Possibly)</h2><br/>
Apple could release second-generation AirPods Max at its September event, but like AirPods 4, these could appear later in October, with rumors only pointing to a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/">late 2024</a>" release. The AirPods Max are currently the oldest model in Apple's AirPods lineup, having been released in December 2020. Over three years later, rumors have started to surface about a new-generation model expected to arrive later this year.<br/>
<br/>
One significant change will be the replacement of the Lightning port with a USB-C port, aligning with European regulations and creating uniformity across Apple's AirPods lineup. As a result, the AirPods Max 2 will include a USB-C to USB-C charging cable instead of the previous Lightning to USB-C cable. Additionally, Apple will need to offer a USB-C to 3.5mm audio cable so users can connect the AirPods Max 2 to devices with 3.5mm audio ports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Black-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877635" /><br/>
The Bluetooth 5.3 specification, already present in the AirPods Pro 2, iPhone 15 lineup, and the latest Apple Watch models, is almost certain to be included in the second-generation AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release the new AirPods Max in fresh colors, though the exact shades are unknown. Currently, they are available in Space Gray, Silver, Green, Sky Blue, and Pink, with interchangeable ear cushions for custom color combinations.<br/>
<br/>
Although there are no specific rumors about the H2 chip in AirPods Max 2, it seems likely they will include it. The H2 chip, designed for Apple’s earbuds and headphones, enhances audio quality, improves battery life, and supports features like Personalized Volume and Conversation Awareness.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iPhone Cases and Apple Watch Bands</h2><br/>
As is typical of September Apple events, it's likely that new iPhone cases and Apple Watch bands will be released in a variety of fresh colors. The new cases and bands sometimes become available to order on Apple's online store just minutes after the event ends.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/march-2023-apple-watch-bands.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888020" /><br/>
Notably, this year the larger of the two standard Apple Watch casing sizes in the Apple Watch Series models, the 45mm size, is expected to become the smallest option. An all-new 49mm casing size, matching the current Apple Watch Ultra, is expected to be introduced as the new larger option. Given that the 49mm Apple Watch Ultra is compatible with bands designed for the 45mm Apple Watch Series models, it is possible that Apple Watch bands could be compatible across both Series 10 models and the Apple Watch Ultra for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Software for Apple Products</h2><br/>
iOS 18 for the iPhone, iPadOS 18 for iPad, watchOS 11 for the Apple Watch, and tvOS 18 for the Apple TV are all expected to be released in September following several months of beta testing, and Apple will likely provide release dates for these software updates. Sometimes the updates are released within days of the event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Public-Beta-Thumb-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958424" /><br/>
For all the details on the new software features you can expect, check out our dedicated roundups for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/#tvos_and_the_tv_app">tvOS 18</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/">Apple&#039;s September Event: New Products to Expect Beyond the iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-september-event-new-products-to-expect-beyond-the-iphone-16.2434080/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
