<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 09:03:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Hit With &#36;5 Billion Class Action Lawsuit Over eBooks Availability</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-books-licensing-lawsuit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hit-with-5-billion-class-action-lawsuit-over-ebooks-availability.2454529/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 07:22:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-books-licensing-lawsuit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Books</category>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A lawsuit filed against Apple in California this week accuses the company of violating the state's false advertising law and other consumer laws, by intentionally misleading customers into thinking that they are purchasing digital e-books from the Apple Books app in perpetuity, when instead they are only purchasing revokable licenses to the books.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/General-Books-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-831769" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/845533211/Morehouse-et-al-v-Apple-Inc">proposed class action complaint</a> explains that Apple is required to pull a digital book or audiobook from the Apple Books app if and when it loses a license to that content, resulting in the content no longer being available in the app's store. As a result, the complaint alleges that some customers have unexpectedly found that digital books they previously purchased were no longer available to re-download, despite having paid for them. Apple removes books without warning, and without providing refunds, the complaint adds.<br/>
<br/>
As noted in the complaint, the purchase screen in the Apple Books app does not include a link to any terms of service or licensing information. However, in order to set up and use an iPhone, iPad, Mac, or other Apple device, users are required to agree to Apple's various <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/sla/docs/iOS18_iPadOS18.pdf">software license agreements</a>, which all state the following:<blockquote>By using this software in connection with an Apple Account, or other Apple Services, you agree to the applicable terms of service, such as the latest Apple Media Services Terms and Conditions […]</blockquote>In the <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/us/terms.html">Apple Media Services Terms and Conditions</a>, Apple states the following:<blockquote>Purchased Content will generally remain available for you to download, redownload, or otherwise access from Apple. Though it is unlikely, subsequent to your purchase, Content may be removed from the Services and become unavailable for further download or access from Apple (for instance, because Apple loses its right from the Content provider to make it available). To ensure your ability to continue enjoying Content, we encourage you to download all purchased Content to a device in your possession and to back it up.</blockquote>The lawsuit, <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/845533211/Morehouse-et-al-v-Apple-Inc">Morehouse et al v. Apple, Inc.</a>, was filed in a U.S. district court in San Jose on Tuesday. The plaintiffs are seeking up to &#36;5 billion in damages, with the proposed class being all individuals who purchased a digital book or audiobook from the Apple Books store within the to-be-determined class period. A judge has yet to be assigned to the case, and it remains to be seen if the class action lawsuit is certified and proceeds to trial.<br/>
<br/>
The complaint was filed by law firm Siri & Glimstad LLP.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-books/">Apple Books</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-books-licensing-lawsuit/">Apple Hit With &#36;5 Billion Class Action Lawsuit Over eBooks Availability</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hit-with-5-billion-class-action-lawsuit-over-ebooks-availability.2454529/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air for the Low Price of &#36;749</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/m2-macbook-air-749/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-for-the-low-price-of-749.2454528/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 07:00:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/m2-macbook-air-749/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLJ4JKHB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.link/o2iokizxm136a">Best Buy</a> are discounting Apple's 13-inch M2 MacBook Air with 16GB of RAM and 256GB SSD storage down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLJ4JKHB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;749.00</strong></a> in a few colors. This is a &#36;250 discount on the previous generation M2 MacBook Air, and a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/m2-macbook-air-dark-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970552" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon and Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon currently has this deal available only in Silver, while Best Buy has the computer at this price in Silver, Space Gray, Midnight, and Starlight. Each discount has been applied automatically and does not require any coupon codes or memberships in order to see the final deal price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DLJ4JKHB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (16GB/256GB) for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Although this is a previous generation device, it will work great for anyone who doesn't need the performance gains introduced with the newer Apple silicon chips, especially at this discounted price. Apple just announced the new M4 MacBook Air, and anyone shopping for those models can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/new-m4-macbook-air-50-discounts/">get up to &#36;60 off</a> a few configurations on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/m2-macbook-air-749/">Get the 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air for the Low Price of &#36;749</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-for-the-low-price-of-749.2454528/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Hasn&#039;t Given Up on Haptic Buttons for a Future iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons-for-a-future-iphone.2454523/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 06:27:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is still exploring solid-state buttons with haptic feedback for a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, according to a new report from a known Weibo leaker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/iPhone-15-Pro-Multi-Purpose-button-Mute-Switch-Feature-Green-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-890432" /><br/>
In a new post, the leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a>" said that Apple's work on solid-state buttons for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is ongoing. They said that production cost is not the project's main issue, but rather "mistouches," since a correct response is apparently not "perfectly guaranteed." <br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to currently be adjusting the "tactile design" of its solid-state buttons and working on their long-term reliability, especially for mass production. Apple's current button design is integrated directly into the frame, with no rebound when clicked, but the company is apparently seeking to more closely replicate the experience of a traditional mechanical button.<br/>
<br/>
The advantages of the design are simplicity and reducing mechanical wear, while enabling users to differentiate between a light press and a firm press to trigger different functions. The project is purportedly now "on hold," with the company determining that the current market is more interested in display and battery technology advancements. <br/>
<br/>
It was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/kuo-iphone-15-pro-models-solid-state-buttons/">widely reported</a> that Apple was intending to bring solid-state buttons to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro in 2023 as part of "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/">Project Bongo</a>," but it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/11/kuo-iphone-15-pro-no-solid-state-buttons-after-all/">canceled the plan</a> at a late stage. They were then <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/12/iphone-16-pro-solid-state-buttons/">rumored</a> to come to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, before being shelved indefinitely. The feature is not expected to arrive in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup, but the latest report suggests that they're likely to appear someday in the future. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons/">Apple Reportedly Hasn&#039;t Given Up on Haptic Buttons for a Future iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons-for-a-future-iphone.2454523/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Plex Mobile App With Streamlined Interface Rolling Out to Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/new-plex-mobile-app-now-rolling-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-plex-mobile-app-with-streamlined-interface-rolling-out-to-users.2454516/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 04:59:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/new-plex-mobile-app-now-rolling-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Plex</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Plex is rolling out a new version of its mobile app, and it's a fairly major redesign that features expanded artwork, streamlined navigation, and a dedicated tab for centralized media libraries designed for "personal media pros."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/plex-mobile-update.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997401" /><br/>
Plex said in a <a href="https://forums.plex.tv/t/the-new-experience-is-coming-to-mobile-what-to-expect/909623">forum post</a> that the updated app is being fully deployed over the course of the week, and introduces several key improvements based on user feedback received during its preview testing phase. If you installed the beta version of the app, which was made available via TestFlight in November, then you'll know what to expect. <br/>
<br/>
Among the changes, users will notice new title artwork for movies and shows, a dedicated spot for the Watchlist feature in the top navigation, and a simplified user menu. Performance enhancements include improved load times, better scrolling performance, and added support for portrait mode, according to Plex.<br/>
<br/>
For those who use Plex to manage personal media collections, the update adds TV show shuffle options, improved library reordering, and enhanced access to item context menus via a long press.<br/>
<br/>
Several other changes have been made that Plex wants existing users to be made aware of. The company says pre-existing downloads will lack some metadata after updating, which can be fixed by re-downloading content. The new version also removes music and photo functionality from the main app, as Plex has developed dedicated companion apps – Plexamp and Plex Photos – for these media types.<br/>
<br/>
The mobile update arrives just weeks before Plex implements its previously announced subscription price changes. Starting April 29, the company will increase the cost of its Plex Pass to &#36;6.99 monthly or &#36;69.99 annually, up from &#36;4.99 and &#36;39.99 respectively, marking its first price hike in a decade.<br/>
<br/>
Plex also noted that a new app for TV platforms, including Apple TV, will follow the mobile update "soon," continuing the company's refresh of its entire app ecosystem. The redesigned app is still in beta, but it is already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/plex-previews-redesigned-apple-tv-app/">available for testing on the Apple TV</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/plex/">Plex</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/new-plex-mobile-app-now-rolling-out/">New Plex Mobile App With Streamlined Interface Rolling Out to Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-plex-mobile-app-with-streamlined-interface-rolling-out-to-users.2454516/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New AirPods Max Firmware Unavailable Due to iOS 18.4 Bug, Apple Says Update &#039;Coming Soon&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/new-airpods-max-firmware-unavailable/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-airpods-max-firmware-unavailable-due-to-ios-18-4-bug-apple-says-update-coming-soon.2454511/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 03:59:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/new-airpods-max-firmware-unavailable/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AirPods Max users have been left unable to download Apple's new firmware update bringing lossless and low-latency audio support to the headphones, owing to a software bug with iOS 18.4, <em>MacRumors</em> can confirm.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18.4-airpods-max-2024-colors-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996305" /><br/>
Apple officially announced the new feature support for AirPods Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/airpods-max-lossless-audio-coming-april/">last week</a>. Then on Monday, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-airpods-max-firmware-7e99/">released</a> an AirPods Max (USB-C) firmware update version 7E99 in tandem with the rollout of iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and macOS Sequoia 15.4 software updates for iPhone, iPad, and Mac. However, since then, AirPods Max owners have not been able to successfully update their devices due to an unspecified conflict with the firmware and Apple's latest software.<br/>
<br/>
The AirPods Max firmware was supposed to enable lossless and low-latency audio support as part of the broader software releases. "With this update, AirPods Max will unlock 24-bit, 48 kHz lossless audio, preserving the integrity of original recordings and allowing listeners to experience music the way the artist created it in the studio," said Apple in a press release. "Lossless audio and ultra-low latency audio enable music creators to fully utilize AirPods Max throughout their entire professional workflow on Logic Pro and other music creation apps."<br/>
<br/>
However, after Apple indicated the firmware was available for download, user reports of problems slowly began to trickle in. As it stands, there's no sign that anyone has been able to install the firmware.<br/>
<br/>
It's still not clear what Apple has done in iOS/iPadOS 18.4 and macOS Sequoia 15.4 to cause the issue, but all the indications are that Apple will need to release a point update to its platforms to correct the bug. On its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106340">AirPods firmware support page</a>, Apple currently lists the unobtainable firmware version 7E99 for AirPods Max as "coming soon."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/new-airpods-max-firmware-unavailable/">New AirPods Max Firmware Unavailable Due to iOS 18.4 Bug, Apple Says Update &#039;Coming Soon&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-airpods-max-firmware-unavailable-due-to-ios-18-4-bug-apple-says-update-coming-soon.2454511/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Is Still Obsessed With the Idea of an All-Glass iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-idea-of-an-all-glass-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-is-still-obsessed-with-the-idea-of-an-all-glass-iphone.2454510/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 03:20:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-idea-of-an-all-glass-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Patent</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you think the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/ios-19-visionos-redesign-rumors/">glassy redesign of iOS 19</a> could be a game-changer, check out Apple's latest granted U.S. patent detailing all-glass enclosures for future devices including the iPhone, Apple Watch, and even Mac Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-glass-enclosures-patent-main.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826169" /><br/>
The patent envisions devices where all external surfaces (front, back, and sides) are made of glass, creating a seamless, transparent appearance with a roving interface that can be used from any angle. <br/>
<br/>
Beyond aesthetics, the glass enclosures would introduce new interactive capabilities, according to the patent. Apple describes touch- and force-sensitive areas extending to the sides and back of devices, essentially creating multi-sided interfaces that could adapt based on how the user holds or orients the device. The embodiments also include mechanisms to take apart the devices for repairs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-glass-enclosures-patent-second.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826172" /><br/>
For iPhones, the patent illustrates a six-sided glass design where displays could appear on any surface, with accommodations for components such as speakers and microphones. The user interface would dynamically shift depending on the device's orientation, allowing for contextual interactions regardless of which side faces the user.<br/>
<br/>
The filing also includes concepts for other Apple products, including a glass Mac Pro tower with an octagonal prism shape, and an Apple Watch constructed almost entirely from transparent glass (a concept that we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/28/all-glass-apple-watch-before-glass-iphone/">resurfaced last week</a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-glass-enclosures-patent-dyanmic-software.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826167" /><br/>
Some designs feature deformable sides, enabling users to trigger actions by applying pressure, such as squeezing the sides of an iPhone to control media playback or adjust volume. Certain ideas also have echoes of Apple's previous experimentation with force-sensitive inputs like 3D Touch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's exploration of glass enclosures isn't exactly new. The company has been investigating this technology for over a decade – and former design chief Jony Ive famously wanted to create an iPhone out of a single seamless slab of glass. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-glass-enclosures-patent-other-devices.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826171" /><br/>
Of course, patents don't guarantee we will actually see the products as consumer devices, but they do offer an insight into Apple's potential long-term vision for more immersive, interactive device designs across its product lines. <br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://www.patentlyapple.com/2025/04/apple-won-a-patent-for-all-glass-device-embodiments-for-apple-watch-mac-an-iphone-that-allows-imagery-on-both-front-and-ba.html">Patently Apple</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent/">Patent</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-idea-of-an-all-glass-iphone/">Apple Is Still Obsessed With the Idea of an All-Glass iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-is-still-obsessed-with-the-idea-of-an-all-glass-iphone.2454510/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Bug Seemingly Resurrects Previously Deleted iPhone Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/ios-18-4-update-deleted-apps-returning/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-bug-seemingly-resurrects-previously-deleted-iphone-apps.2454506/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 01:26:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/ios-18-4-update-deleted-apps-returning/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest iOS 18.4 software update appears to be causing long-deleted apps to reappear on some users' iPhones, based on corroborating reports on forums and social media.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Generic-iOS-18.4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984205" /><br/>
Several Reddit threads (<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/s/MwYoHRvTUy">1</a>,<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/s/7BCTZDM56x">2</a>,<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/s/4J2gl2nDUg">3</a>,<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/s/LhDkeudJnn">4</a>) and posts on <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/256029403?sortBy=rank">Apple's Community Support</a> pages over the last 24 hours are filled with reports from users who, after having updated to iOS 18.4, immediately discovered third-party apps and/or games installed on their device that were not there before. <br/>
<br/>
Going on the reports, the iOS 18.4 update has manifested a bug that is causing apps to reappear – since in most cases it appears that the apps had been deleted by the users months or even years ago and long forgotten. Apple released iOS 18.4 on Monday.<br/>
<br/>
The behavior doesn't seem to be related to Apple's Automatic Downloads option either. The setting enables automatic downloads of apps purchased on other Apple devices. However, many affected users say they do not own another Apple device.<br/>
<br/>
Likewise, the bug is impacting users with devices that have never been jailbroken and have never used an alternative marketplace outside of the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
It's not clear how prevalent the glitch is, but not everyone is affected, suggesting it could be related to location or device model. As it stands, the current solution for affected users is just to re-delete the reappearing app while we await further details around the issue. <br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Tanner!)</em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/ios-18-4-update-deleted-apps-returning/">iOS 18.4 Bug Seemingly Resurrects Previously Deleted iPhone Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-bug-seemingly-resurrects-previously-deleted-iphone-apps.2454506/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Visa and American Express Vying to Win Apple Card Deal in &#039;Fierce&#039; Fight</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/visa-american-express-apple-card-deal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/visa-and-american-express-vying-to-win-apple-card-deal-in-fierce-fight.2454482/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:50:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/visa-american-express-apple-card-deal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Visa wants to pay Apple approximately &#36;100 million to be the new payment network for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, reports <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/finance/banking/apple-card-visa-mastercard-deal-3ce762da">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>. As of right now, the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; is on the Mastercard payment network, but that is set to change because Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/15/goldman-sachs-apple-card-partnership-end-early/">ending its partnership</a> with Goldman Sachs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Card-iPhone-16-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2049" height="1153" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985779" /><br/>
Both American Express and Visa are vying to replace Mastercard as Apple's card services provider, while Mastercard is aiming to retain its position. Apple apparently plans to choose a new &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; network before it selects a partner to replace Goldman Sachs as the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;'s issuing bank, and competition is intense. Visa is offering Apple a &#36;100 million upfront payment, while American Express is "in the mix" and Mastercard is "fiercely trying" to retain its role.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Goldman Sachs have been working to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">dissolve their partnership</a> since 2023, with Goldman Sachs planning to exit the consumer banking market. JPMorgan Chase and Synchrony Financial are in talks with Apple to take over for Goldman Sachs, but American Express has also been aiming to become the issuer and network of the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;. Apple needs both an issuing bank for the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; and a payment network that facilitates transactions.<br/>
<br/>
Goldman Sachs and Apple have worked together on the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; since its 2019 launch, and have also teamed up for the high-yield Apple Savings account. Apple has not been happy with Goldman Sachs because of customer service issues caused by long wait times for disputed &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions and savings account withdrawals.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau even <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-fed-probes-goldman-sachs-consumer-business-wsj-2023-01-20/">launched an investigation</a> into Goldman Sachs due to the customer complaints, which led to tension, so both companies are eager to end their relationship.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; has over 12 million users in the United States, with approximately &#36;20 billion in balances.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/visa-american-express-apple-card-deal/">Visa and American Express Vying to Win Apple Card Deal in &#039;Fierce&#039; Fight</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/visa-and-american-express-vying-to-win-apple-card-deal-in-fierce-fight.2454482/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 11.4 With Sleep Alarm Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/apple-releases-watchos-11-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-11-4-with-sleep-alarm-update.2454468/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 10:34:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/apple-releases-watchos-11-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 11.4, the fourth major update to the operating system that runs on the Apple Watch. watchOS 11.4 is compatible with the Apple Watch Series 6 and later, all Apple Watch Ultra models, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> 2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Thumb-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955941" /><br/>
watchOS 11.4 can be downloaded on a connected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> by opening up the Apple Watch app and going to General &gt; Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
With watchOS 11.4, Apple has added an option for a Sleep Wake Up alarm to break through Silent Mode, so you can have your Apple Watch make a sound in addition to haptic tapping when a morning alarm goes off. There's also support for Matter-compatible robot vacuum cleaners in the Home app.<br/>
<blockquote>This update includes new features, improvements, and bug fixes, including:<br/>
- Matter-compatible robot vacuum cleaners can be added to the Home app as well as used in scenes, automations, or simply say "Siri, clean the living room."<br/>
- An option to allow Sleep Wake Up alarm to break through Silent Mode<br/>
- An issue where face selection may become unresponsive when switching faces<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/100100</blockquote><br/>
More of the features available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">can be found in our watchOS 11 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/apple-releases-watchos-11-update/">Apple Releases watchOS 11.4 With Sleep Alarm Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-11-4-with-sleep-alarm-update.2454468/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;60 Off New M4 MacBook Air, Available From &#36;949</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/new-m4-macbook-air-50-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-60-off-new-m4-macbook-air-available-from-949.2454467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 10:24:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/new-m4-macbook-air-50-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">all-time low prices on the new M4 MacBook Air</a>, with up to &#36;60 off the 13-inch and 15-inch versions of the computer. Right now these discounts are only available on Amazon, and most of them have estimated delivery windows of early April.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/M4-MacBook-Air-13-and-15-inch-Feature-Pink-and-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994261" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon and Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This time around, there is one 13-inch configuration on sale and one 15-inch configuration on sale, reaching up to &#36;60 off the original price. You can get the 256GB 13-inch M4 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;949.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00, and the 256GB 15-inch M4 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBDCFH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,139.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,199.00. Both of these deals are available in two colors on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBDCFH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,139.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We aren't currently tracking any notable deals on the 512GB models of the M4 MacBook Air. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/new-m4-macbook-air-50-discounts/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;60 Off New M4 MacBook Air, Available From &#36;949</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-60-off-new-m4-macbook-air-available-from-949.2454467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac Studio Buyer&#039;s Guide: All Models Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-studio-generations-compared/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-studio-buyers-guide-all-models-compared.2392337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 08:15:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-studio-generations-compared&#038;post_date=1743531300/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Mac Studio</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has now refreshed the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> twice since its introduction in 2022, so should you upgrade your unit and is an older model still worth buying?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Mac-Studio-Desk.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-899968" /><br/>
The new &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;'s main upgrade is its chip, moving from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Max and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra to the M4 Max and M3 Ultra. Compared to its predecessor, the new &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; is up to 75% faster with 2x faster graphics. It also now features up to 512GB of memory of 16GB of storage, as well as Thunderbolt 5 connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
See the breakdown below for each new feature, change, and improvement that was added with the latest &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; compared to its predecessors:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2022)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2023)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2025)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-max/">M1 Max</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-ultra/">M1 Ultra</a> chip</td><br/>
 <td>Apple &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max or &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chip</td><br/>
 <td>Apple M4 Max or M3 Ultra chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: 10-core CPU (8 performance cores, 2 efficiency cores)<br/>
 <strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: 20-core CPU (16 performance cores, 4 efficiency cores)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: 12-core CPU (8 performance cores, 4 efficiency cores)<br/>
 <strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: 24-core CPU (16 performance cores, 8 efficiency cores)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Up to 16-core CPU (12 performance cores, 4 efficiency cores)<br/>
 <strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: Up to 32-core CPU (24 performance cores, 8 efficiency cores)<br/>
 </td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: Up to 32-core GPU<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: Up to 64-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: Up to 38-core GPU<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: Up to 76-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Up to 40-core GPU<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: Up to 80-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hardware-accelerated ray tracing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>AV1 decode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: 16-core Neural Engine (11 TOPS)<br/>
 <strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: 32-core Neural Engine (22 TOPS)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td> <strong>M2 Max</strong>: 16-core Neural Engine (15.8 TOPS)<br/>
 <strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: 32-core Neural Engine (31.6 TOPS)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td> <strong>M4 Max</strong>: 16-core Neural Engine (38 TOPS)<br/>
 <strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: 32-core Neural Engine (76 TOPS)<br/>
 </td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: Video decode engine<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: Two video decode engines</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: Video decode engine<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: Two video decode engines</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Video decode engine<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: Two video decode engines</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: Two video encode engines<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: Four video encode engines</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: Two video encode engines<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: Four video encode engines</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Two video encode engines<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: Four video encode engines</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: Two ProRes encode and decode engines<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: Four ProRes encode and decode engines</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: Two ProRes encode and decode engines<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: Four ProRes encode and decode engines</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Two ProRes encode and decode engines<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: Four ProRes encode and decode engines</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: 32GB or 64GB memory<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: 64GB or 128GB memory</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: 32GB, 64GB, or 96GB memory<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: 64GB, 128GB, or 192GB memory </td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: 36GB, 48GB, 64GB, 128GB memory<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: 96GB, 256GB, or 512GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: 400GB/s memory bandwidth<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: 800GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: 400GB/s memory bandwidth<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: 800GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Up to 546GB/s memory bandwidth<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: 819GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>512GB, 1TB, 2TB, 4TB, or 8TB SSD storage</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: 512GB, 1TB, 2TB, 4TB, or 8TB SSD storage<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: 1TB, 2TB, 4TB, or 8TB SSD storage</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: 512GB, 1TB, 2TB, 4TB, or 8TB SSD storage<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: 1TB, 2TB, 4TB, 8TB, or 16TB SSD storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M1 Max</strong>: Four Thunderbolt 4 ports and two USB-C ports<br/>
<strong>M1 Ultra</strong>: Six Thunderbolt 4 ports</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 Max</strong>: Four Thunderbolt 4 ports and two USB-C ports<br/>
<strong>M2 Ultra</strong>: Six Thunderbolt 4 ports</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M4 Max</strong>: Four Thunderbolt 5 ports and two USB-C ports<br/>
<strong>M3 Ultra</strong>: Six Thunderbolt 5 ports</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>HDMI 2.0 port</td><br/>
 <td>HDMI 2.1 port</td><br/>
 <td>HDMI 2.1 port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Support for up to four Pro Display XDRs and one 4K display</td><br/>
 <td>Support for up to eight 4K displays, six 6K displays, or three 8K displays</td><br/>
 <td>Support for up to eight 4K displays, eight 6K displays or four 8K displays</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>3.5mm headphone jack</td><br/>
 <td>3.5mm headphone jack with advanced support for high-impedance headphones</td><br/>
 <td>3.5mm headphone jack with advanced support for high-impedance headphones</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>802.11ax Wi‑Fi 6</td><br/>
 <td>802.11ax Wi‑Fi 6E</td><br/>
 <td>802.11ax Wi‑Fi 6E</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Bluetooth 5.0</td><br/>
 <td>Bluetooth 5.3</td><br/>
 <td>Bluetooth 5.3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Released March 2022</td><br/>
 <td>Released June 2023</td><br/>
 <td>Released March 2025</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Only those 2022 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; users who consistently push their machines to the limit with tasks like 3D rendering, video editing in high resolutions, machine learning workflows, or large-scale software development should consider upgrading to the 2025 model. The 2025 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; introduces a considerable leap in performance, particularly with the M4 Max and M3 Ultra chips, offering substantially better GPU performance, more powerful GPUs with hardware-accelerated ray tracing, a significantly faster Neural Engine, and support for up to 512GB of memory and Thunderbolt 5. These improvements dramatically improve workflows that demand extreme parallel processing, faster memory access, or broader external display setups. If your current 2022 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; ever feels like a bottleneck, or if you are preparing to work with increasingly complex projects over the next few years, the upgrade is likely to be worth it. However, for users whose workloads remain well within the capabilities of the &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj; or &zwnj;M1 Ultra&zwnj;, especially those focused on less GPU-intensive tasks, the gains may not justify the cost at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Upgrading from the 2023 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; to the 2025 model is likely to be worth it for far fewer users, simply because the performance gains, while significant on paper, will make less of a real-world difference for most professionals already using the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max or &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chip because the 2023 model is still exceptionally capable. However, there are a few edge cases where the upgrade may be justified—particularly for users working with local large language models or intensive AI workloads, where the vastly improved Neural Engine in the M4 Max or M3 Ultra can offer major benefits. Similarly, users who rely on extremely high memory capacity or bandwidth, or those building systems around Thunderbolt 5 and AV1 decode support, might see tangible improvements that justify the cost. Still, for the vast majority of users, especially those in video production, app development, or general pro workflows, the 2023 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; remains more than sufficient for the foreseeable future, making the 2025 upgrade more of a luxury than a necessity.<br/>
<br/>
The 2022 and 2023 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; models are still very much worth buying, especially if found refurbished or second-hand at a good price. Both models offer excellent performance that remains highly competitive even in 2025, with the &zwnj;M1 Ultra&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra still delivering substantial CPU and GPU power, high memory bandwidth, and dedicated media engines that easily handle demanding tasks like video editing, music production, 3D rendering, and software development. While they lack newer features like Thunderbolt 5, hardware-accelerated ray tracing, or the enhanced Neural Engine performance found in the 2025 models, those are largely beneficial only to users with very specific, future-facing workloads. For most professionals and power users, especially those upgrading from Intel Macs or base <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> systems, the 2022 and 2023 models remain an outstanding value—and often represent the best balance between performance and cost when purchased refurbished or pre-owned.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac-Studio">Mac Studio (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-studio.237">Mac Studio</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-studio-generations-compared/">Mac Studio Buyer&#039;s Guide: All Models Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-studio-buyers-guide-all-models-compared.2392337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Delta Emulator Gains Online Multiplayer for Nintendo DS Games</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/delta-emulator-online-multiplayer-nintendo-ds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/delta-emulator-gains-online-multiplayer-for-nintendo-ds-games.2454450/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 04:47:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/delta-emulator-online-multiplayer-nintendo-ds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The popular iOS game emulator <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/delta-game-emulator/id1048524688">Delta</a> has received a major update that adds online multiplayer functionality for Nintendo DS games. Version 1.7 of the app now allows players to compete against each other in classic DS titles like <em>Mario Kart DS</em>, <em>Bomberman</em>, and <em>Animal Crossing</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Delta-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946979" /><br/>
Nintendo officially shut down the original DS online services back in 2014, so Delta relies on alternative Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection servers maintained by the community. The way it works is very straightforward – simply select your preferred server within the emulator settings. No complex DNS or network configuration is required.  A list of supported games can be found on <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Nintendo_DS_Wi-Fi_Connection_games">Wikipedia</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Beyond online multiplayer, version 1.7 also introduces several other notable improvements. Nintendo 64 emulation has been enhanced, with new options to upscale resolution and use custom texture packs for improved visuals. A quick screenshot feature has also been added, alongside various bug fixes and performance optimizations.<br/>
<br/>
Delta is regarded as one of the most polished game emulators available on iOS, supporting multiple Nintendo platforms including NES, SNES, N64, Game Boy, Game Boy Advance, and Nintendo DS. The app offers robust controller support, save states, cheats, game backups, and cloud syncing.<br/>
<br/>
For players looking to try these new features, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/delta-game-emulator/id1048524688">Delta 1.7</a> is currently available through <a href="https://altstore.io/">AltStore PAL</a> for users in the European Union, with a global App Store release expected soon. The emulator remains free to download.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/delta-emulator-online-multiplayer-nintendo-ds/">Delta Emulator Gains Online Multiplayer for Nintendo DS Games</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/delta-emulator-gains-online-multiplayer-for-nintendo-ds-games.2454450/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Turn Off Apple Mail Categories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-off-apple-mail-categories/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-turn-off-apple-mail-categories.2454449/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 03:56:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-off-apple-mail-categories&#038;post_date=1743515772/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18.2, Apple introduced a major change to iPhone's Mail app with a new Categories feature, which has now been rolled out to iPad and Mac with iPadOS 18.4 and macOS Sequoia 15.4. Categories automatically sorts your emails into four distinct sections: Primary, Transactions, Updates, and Promotions. However, while this organizational system aims to help manage email overload, not everyone will prefer the new layout.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-mail-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957054" /><br/>
Mail Categories attempts to intelligently organize your incoming emails into different sections. Important emails are shown in a "Primary" category, with orders, newsletters, social notifications, and deals organized into three other sections.<br/>
<br/>
The "Transactions" section includes receipts, orders, and deliveries, and aims to make it easy to find orders that you've placed and shipping information for those orders. Meanwhile, the "Updates" section includes newsletters, alerts for things like doctor's appointments and correspondence, and other subscription emails. Lastly, Apple's "Promotions" category includes special offers and deal emails.<br/>
<br/>
Note that even if an email would normally fall into Transactions, Updates, or Promotions, it will also appear in your Primary inbox if it contains time-critical information. On devices that support Apple Intelligence, the system goes a step further by highlighting priority emails that require action or have deadlines.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mail Categories: Why You Might Want to Revert</h2><br/>
The new Categories view, while helpful for some, might not suit your email management style. Perhaps you prefer seeing all emails in chronological order, or have your own organization system. Or maybe you just want fast access to all your emails without switching between categories. On iPhone and iPad, you can swipe left across the categories to switch to an "All Mail" view (the same option can be found on Mac to the right of the category buttons) but what if you want to remove the categories completely?<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Return to List View in Apple Mail</h2><br/>
Categories is the default view after updating to the new software. Fortunately, Apple makes it simple to switch back to the traditional list view. Here's how it's done:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open the Mail app on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac.</li><br/>
  <li>On iPhone/iPad, tap the <strong>More</strong> button (three dots) in the upper right corner of your inbox. On Mac, you can find the More button at the top of the inbox view. <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/mac-mail-categories.jpg" alt="mail" width="814" height="336" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997292" /><br/>
  <li>On iPhone/iPad, select <strong>List View</strong> from the pop-up menu. On Mac, click <strong>Show Mail Categories</strong> to uncheck it. </li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/remove-apple-mail-categories.jpg" alt="mail" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981534" /><br/>
<br/>
Once you switch to List View, your inbox will return to showing all emails in chronological order, just as it did before. The change takes effect immediately. While categorization is not perfect, it's likely something that Apple will improve over time. You can always switch back to Categories view using the same menu if you want to try it again later. <br/>
<br/>
Note: If you're using an iPhone/iPad that supports Apple Intelligence, you'll see an additional option in the More menu for priority messages. This option won't appear on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/does-my-iphone-support-apple-intelligence/">devices without Apple Intelligence support</a>. The More menu also has an "About Categories" section where you can see how your messages have been categorized over the course of the last week, but there is no option to tell the Mail app if you believe an email has been put into the wrong category.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-off-apple-mail-categories/">How to Turn Off Apple Mail Categories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-turn-off-apple-mail-categories.2454449/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces &#039;Find My&#039; Network Availability in South Korea</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/apple-announces-find-my-network-korea/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-find-my-network-availability-in-south-korea.2454438/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 02:09:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/apple-announces-find-my-network-korea/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Find My</category>
		<category>South Korea</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/kr/newsroom/2025/03/apple-brings-additional-find-my-capabilities-to-south-korea/">announced</a> 'Find My' network availability in South Korea. The launch brings the full range of Apple's location-based ‌Find My‌ services to South Korean customers for the first time, enabling them to keep track of devices, belongings, and loved ones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Apple-Find-My-south-korea.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997289" /><br/>
With the ‌Find My‌ network enabled, users will be able to to locate their iPhones, iPads, Macs, and other Apple devices, as well as AirTag-connected personal items and third-party ‌Find My‌ compatible trackers, while maintaining strong privacy protections.<br/>
<br/>
One of the main features of the ‌Find My‌ network is its ability to pinpoint lost devices on a map, providing users with step-by-step directions to retrieve their misplaced items. The app also allows users to trigger a sound on their lost Apple devices, making it easier to locate them when in close proximity.<br/>
<br/>
‌Find My‌ also lets users stay connected with friends and family by opting to share their location with specific contacts. This can be useful when meeting up in crowded areas, particularly for owners of iPhone 15 and later models who can take advantage of the Precision Finding capability to navigate directly to their friends' exact locations.<br/>
<br/>
The original "‌Find My‌ iPhone" app was launched in 2009 alongside ‌iPhone‌ OS 3. "‌Find My‌ Mac" was added to OS X 10.7 Lion in 2011, while "‌Find My‌ Friends" was released in October 2011. With the release of iOS 13 and macOS 10.15 Catalina, the functionality of ‌Find My‌ ‌iPhone‌, ‌Find My‌ Mac, and ‌Find My‌ Friends was unified into the app we know today as ‌Find My‌.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/south-korea/">South Korea</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/apple-announces-find-my-network-korea/">Apple Announces &#039;Find My&#039; Network Availability in South Korea</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-find-my-network-availability-in-south-korea.2454438/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Expected to Run on These iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones.2454419/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:28:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> will not be available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> XR, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS, or the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS Max, according a private account on social media site X that has accurately provided information on device compatibility in the past.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-19-Mock-WWDC25-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996726" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS, and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS Max all have an A12 Bionic chip, so it looks like &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; will discontinue support for that chip. All other iPhones that run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> are expected to support &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, with a full compatibility list below.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro Max</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Plus</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 mini</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 Pro</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a></li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 Pro</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12-pro/">iPhone 12 Pro Max</a></li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 Pro</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-11-pro/">iPhone 11 Pro Max</a></li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; SE (2nd generation or later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
While these iPhones will support &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, advanced features may be limited to newer iPhones with faster processors. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, for example, only runs on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
As for iPadOS 19, it is expected to drop support for the seventh-generation low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with A10 Fusion chip. It sounds like iPads that are equipped with the A12 Bionic such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> 5 will be compatible with iPadOS 19.<br/>
<br/>
The source that shared the information also provided details on the devices that would be compatible with &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; ahead of when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; was unveiled.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning to introduce &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; and iPadOS 19 at the Worldwide Developers Conference that is set to begin on Monday, June 9.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones/">iOS 19 Expected to Run on These iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones.2454419/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Max Firmware With Lossless and Low-Latency Audio Support [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-airpods-max-firmware-7e99/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-max-firmware-with-lossless-and-low-latency-audio-support-updated.2454412/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:49:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-airpods-max-firmware-7e99/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update 4/2/25</strong>: Apple has updated an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106340">AirPods support page</a> to indicate that the AirPods Max (USB-C) firmware update version 7E99 is now "coming soon." The original article continues below.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<br/>
Apple today released a new firmware update for the USB-C version of the AirPods Max headphones. The new firmware is version 7E99, up from the prior 7A291 firmware the device was previously running.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936393" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Green-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
When paired with the iOS 18.4 update, the new AirPods Max firmware brings lossless audio and ultra-low latency audio to the USB-C version of the headphones. The USB-C AirPods Max support 24-bit 48 kHz lossless audio, which is designed to allow listeners to experience music the way the artist created it in the studio. Apple says lossless audio and Personalized Spatial Audio offer a “more sonically accurate, uncompressed, and immersive experience.”<br/>
<br/>
With lossless audio and ultra-low latency audio support, music creators are able to use the AirPods Max to create and mix in Personalized Spatial Audio with head tracking, with just a USB-C cable and a Mac with Logic Pro or other music creation software.<br/>
<br/>
Lossless audio and ultra-low latency is only available for the USB-C AirPods Max. The headphones need to be running the latest firmware and need to be paired with a device running iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, or macOS Sequoia 15.4.<br/>
<br/>
Firmware <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/27/airpods-firmware-update-instructions/">can be installed</a> by putting the AirPods Max in Bluetooth range of an iPhone, iPad, or Mac that’s connected to Wi-Fi, and then plugging them in to charge. It can take up to 30 minutes for firmware to update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your firmware version by going to Settings &gt; Bluetooth and selecting the Info button next to the AirPods Max when they are connected to an iPhone, iPad, or Mac.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-airpods-max-firmware-7e99/">Apple Releases New AirPods Max Firmware With Lossless and Low-Latency Audio Support [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-max-firmware-with-lossless-and-low-latency-audio-support-updated.2454412/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Features: Everything New in iOS 18.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-features-everything-new-in-ios-18-4.2454409/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:17:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features-2&#038;post_date=1743470263/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18.4 is the fourth major update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> operating system that first came out last September, and it adds a long list of new features. Some features are limited to Apple's newer and more powerful <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, while others are available to all &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; users.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18.4-Everything-New-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993583" /><br/>
This guide covers everything new in iOS 18.4.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="priority_notifications_-_apple_intelligence">Priority Notifications - Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 adds an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> Priority Notifications feature that shows you your most important notifications first. Priority Notifications is disabled by default, but it can be turned on by going to Settings &gt; Notifications &gt; Prioritize Notifications and tapping the toggle.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991317" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/prioritize-notifications-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Priority Notifications can also be set up on a per-app basis, with toggles available in the same sections of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992532" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-prioritize-notifications.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
With the feature enabled, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; will show notifications that may be important in a dedicated section at the top of the Lock Screen's notification center.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="visual_intelligence_for_iphone_15_pro_models">Visual Intelligence for iPhone 15 Pro Models</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/ios-18-4-visual-intelligence-iphone-15-pro/">is now available</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro Max, and it's no longer an option limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970984" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-Visual-Intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
<br/>
Since the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro and Pro Max do not have a Camera Control button, &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj; can be activated via the Control Center or with the Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="visual_intelligence_action_button">Visual Intelligence Action Button</h2><br/>
Apple added an Action Button option that activates &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj;, and it can be used as an alternative to the Camera Control button for &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj; on the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992533" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-visual-intelligence-action-button.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="control_center_apple_intelligence_section">Control Center Apple Intelligence Section</h2><br/>
In the Control Center, there's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-control-center/">an Apple Intelligence section</a>. It includes the Type to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> option that was in the now-removed &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; section, along with new options for activating &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and using &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992503" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-control-center-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="image_playground_sketch_style">Image Playground Sketch Style</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> includes a Sketch style that joins the Animation and Illustration styles. Sketch was previously available for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-wand/">Image Wand</a>, but now it is a third style that can be used in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991330" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Swap styles by tapping on the "+" button in the &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; app. Apple also replaced the previous "Winter Holidays" theme with a new "Spring" theme.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_apple_intelligence_languages">New Apple Intelligence Languages</h2><br/>
French, German, Italian, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish, Japanese, Korean, and Chinese (simplified), along with localized English for Singapore and India.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_emoji">New Emoji</h2><br/>
There are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/ios-18-4-emoji/">new emoji characters</a> in iOS 18.4, including bags under eyes, fingerprint, leafless tree, root vegetable, harp, shovel, and splatter.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992499" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18.4-Emoji-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="vision_pro_app">Vision Pro App</h2><br/>
If you have a Vision Pro headset, you'll <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/03/vision-pro-app-ios-18-4-beta-2/">see a Vision Pro app</a> on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; after installing iOS 18.4 if you have a Vision Pro headset. The Vision Pro app helps you discover and download content on the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992487" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/vision-pro-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
There are dedicated sections for Immersive Video, 3D movies, and more, with options to download apps directly to the Vision Pro without having to use the headset. Apple also added a dedicated My Vision Pro section with a user guide and tips for using the device.<br/>
<br/>
Guest setup can now be managed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> linked to a Vision Pro, making it easier for Vision Pro owners to let others test their headset. There are controls for limiting what apps a guest is able to use, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> mode for guiding the guest through Vision Pro experiences. When a guest user puts on the Vision Pro, a prompt to enable Guest Mode will appear on the headset owner's device.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_news+_food">Apple News+ Food</h2><br/>
For <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ subscribers, there's now an &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; Food section. The Food section features tens of thousands of recipes, stories about restaurants, tips for healthy eating, kitchen essentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991301" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-food-news.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Content will come from top food publishers such as Allrecipes, Bon Appétit, Food & Wine, Good Food, and Serious Eats. &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; editors will curate food-related stories, and there will be a dedicated Recipe Catalog section where new recipes are added regularly. An included cook mode provides step-by-step instructions, and users can save favorite recipes for offline access.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ambient_music">Ambient Music</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 includes an Ambient Music option that can be added to Control Center. There are four different sound categories, including Sleep, Chill, Productivity, and Wellbeing.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991311" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-ambient-music.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Each category can be added to Control Center separately, and tapping one plays a random selection of sounds or music from that particular category. If you tap on the Ambient Music button that you added while in edit mode, you can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/ios-18-4-new-music-feature/">select different options</a> within each category.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Sleep:</strong> Sleep Sounds, Bedtime Beats, Sound Bath, and Piano Sleep.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Chill:</strong> Piano Chill, Ambient Chill, Lo-Fi Jazz, and Pure Chill.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Productivity:</strong> BEATstrumentals, Binaural Frequencies, Pure Focus, and Classical Concentration.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Wellbeing:</strong> Pure Meditation, Spa, Beats & Breath, and Pure Calm.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If you play Ambient Music and then tap into the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> at the top or access the Now Playing widget, you can skip songs and see the name of what's currently playing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="privacy_indication_dots">Privacy Indication Dots</h2><br/>
The small dots that show up on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s menu bar when the camera or microphone is in use have been moved to the left and are now more apparent thanks to a black background.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991331" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/new-siri-indicator-dot-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="1134" height="182" /><br/>
<h2 id="siri_voices">Siri Voices</h2><br/>
There are two new Australian voices for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991334" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-australian-siri-voice.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="genmoji">Genmoji</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> icon for the Emoji keyboard now says "&zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj;" instead of just featuring a multi-colored smiley face. The change should make it more obvious where users go to create a &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; character.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991332" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-genmoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="photos">Photos</h2><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, there are new options to filter your library by images that were shared with you by others or by those that are not included in an album, which is useful for separating out content that you've organized into albums.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991598" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/photos-filters-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Apple also added an option to view your album list by key photo.<br/>
<br/>
The Recently Deleted section of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app now has one-tap options to delete all photos and to recover all photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992531" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-deleted-album.jpg" alt="" width="1918" height="997" /><br/>
In the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; Settings, there is a Show Recently Viewed & Shared toggle that will show or hide the Recently Viewed and Recently Shared albums from the Utilities list.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="type_to_siri">Type to Siri</h2><br/>
When you use Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; a question, the keyboard is now collapsed down when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; answers. To type another request, you need to tap on the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; bar to bring it back up. There is also a toggle to activate Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; with the side button, which would normally cause &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to listen for a voice command.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991628" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-siri-accessibility-toggle.jpg" alt="" width="1811" height="1019" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="back_tap">Back Tap</h2><br/>
If you have the Back Tap Accessibility option turned on, there is now a notification when a double tap or triple tap action is performed.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991627" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-back-tap-notification.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="app_store_review_summaries">App Store Review Summaries</h2><br/>
Apple now provides summaries of an app's customer reviews to get a quicker overview of what people think of it.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993504" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/app-store-review-summaries.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="pause_app_store_downloads">Pause App Store Downloads</h2><br/>
When you download an app from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, you can pause the download right from the update list in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rather than having to do it from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> icon for the app. Before now, you could only stop and restart an installation entirely from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, with no option for stopping it entirely.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992535" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-app-store-pause-download.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Pausing and resuming works for both new downloads and app updates.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_maps">Apple Maps</h2><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> Settings, there is a new option to set a Preferred Language.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991350" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-maps-preferred.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1267" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="passwords">Passwords</h2><br/>
In the Passwords app, verification codes for two-factor authentication have a countdown circle so you can tell when a new code is going to be generated.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991600" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-password-countdown.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="podcasts_widget">Podcasts Widget</h2><br/>
There are Library and Shows widgets that can be added to the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. The Library widget features saved content, while the Shows option displays shows that you are subscribed to.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991338" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-podcast-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
In the Podcasts app, if you tap on your profile picture, there are new options for Podcasts Settings and Notification Settings.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mac_setup">Mac Setup</h2><br/>
There is a new feature that allows a nearby &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to be used to sign into a Mac with an Apple Account for setting up a new Mac. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 is also required.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="control_center_toggles">Control Center Toggles</h2><br/>
The Cellular toggle and the Wi-Fi toggle in the Control Center now show your cellular or Wi-Fi signal strength represented in bars.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991333" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-cellular-signal-control-center.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
The Brightness and Sound toggles in Control Center have been tweaked slightly and will now change color when the sliders are lowered below the position of the icons.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991621" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-control-center-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
The Focus option in Control Center now has two small arrows that serve as a visual indicator that there are more options that can be accessed.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="shortcuts_actions">Shortcuts Actions</h2><br/>
There are multiple new actions for Apple apps in the Shortcuts app, most of which are for changing app settings.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992534" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-safari-settings.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
In Maps, for example, there are actions for things like avoid busy roads, avoid tolls, volume level, directions on radio, and more. In Safari, you can use AutoFill information, toggle on pop-up blocking, close tabs, change search engine, and change the tab bar configuration, among other options.<br/>
<br/>
There are Settings actions for Maps, Safari, Reminders, Calendar, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, Books, Notes, Voice Memos, and Weather.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also added a new Shortcuts action to open a specific conversation in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991336" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-shortcuts-open-conversation.jpg" alt="" width="1688" height="950" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="safari">Safari</h2><br/>
When you long press on an &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; link in Safari, there is an updated design for &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; link previews.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991957" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/app-store-safari-links-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
When you open up a new Safari tab and then tap the address bar, Safari shows a list of your recent searches. There is an option to disable recent searches by opening the Settings app, going to Safari, and toggling off Show Recent Searches.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991973" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-safari-search.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<h2 id="carplay">CarPlay</h2><br/>
Some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> users will have access to a third row of &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; icons on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; rather than just two rows.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991341" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/carplay-view-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><em>Image <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-beta-1-bug-fixes-changes-and-improvements.2449908/post-33753569">via the MacRumors Forums</a></em></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="default_apps">Default Apps</h2><br/>
There is an option to set a different Translation app as the default in the Default Apps section of the Settings app. In the EU, there is also an option to choose a different Navigation app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991344" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-translate-default-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="notification_center">Notification Center</h2><br/>
The animation when swiping out of the Notification Center is now smoother.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="camera_control">Camera Control</h2><br/>
Additional camera apps that can be selected for the Camera Control feature on &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are now listed in a Camera App section rather than directly in the main Camera Control menu.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991626" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/camera-control-ios-18-4-menu.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="safari_connection_security">Safari Connection Security</h2><br/>
In Safari, you can tap into the details on a website to see the certificate through a new Connection Security Details interface to ensure the site is secure.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991623" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-connection-security.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="robot_vacuum_homekit_support">Robot Vacuum HomeKit Support</h2><br/>
In iOS 18.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> supports robot vacuums. Adding a vacuum to the Home app requires a vacuum with Matter support, and that requires robot vacuum manufacturers to implement Matter. Not all Matter-enabled robot vacuums will be able to be added to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; right away.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="wallet">Wallet</h2><br/>
In the Wallet app, there is an updated menu that includes Orders, Settings, and Subscriptions and Payments. It can be accessed by tapping on the three dots in the upper right corner, which used to be just for package tracking.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992530" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ios-18-4-wallet-app.jpg" alt="" width="1835" height="1032" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="find_my">Find My</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> support has been added in South Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mail_categorization_for_ipados_18.4">Mail Categorization for iPadOS 18.4</h2><br/>
With iPadOS 18.4, an updated Mail app is available with categorization. The new Mail app organizes incoming emails into different sections. Important emails are displayed in the Primary category, with other emails organized into sections highlighting product orders, newsletters, deals, and social notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Mail categorization was previously introduced for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in iOS 18.2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features-2/">iOS 18.4 Features: Everything New in iOS 18.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-features-everything-new-in-ios-18-4.2454409/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple News+ Subscribers Can Now Access Apple News Food</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-news-food-ios-18-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-news-subscribers-can-now-access-apple-news-food.2454403/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:10:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-news-food-ios-18-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4, Apple rolled out a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ Food feature that is available for all &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-News-Food.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991773" /><br/>
&zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ Food offers tens of thousands of recipes, that users can browse through. There are built-in filter and search tools for finding specific recipes, and new content is added daily. Favorite recipes can be saved for access later, and Apple has designed a special format for recipes.<br/>
<br/>
Recipes are displayed with a list of ingredients that can be checked off while cooking, and users can tap any ingredient to see the amount needed for the current step. Timers can be set by tapping on a highlighted duration in the recipe, and there is a "cook" mode that provides step-by-step cooking instructions in a full-screen view.<br/>
<br/>
Along with an extensive recipe catalog, &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ Food includes stories about local restaurants, information on kitchen essentials, tips on healthy eating, and more. Content is sourced from major food publishers like Allrecipes, Bon Appétit, Food &amp; Wine, Good Food, and Serious Eats.<br/>
<br/>
While &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ Food is a feature that is designed for &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers, Apple does make select stories and recipes available for non-subscribers as well.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ is priced at &#36;12.99 per month, and it is also included in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> Premier plan for &#36;37.95 per month. Along with the new &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ Food feature, &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ includes access to over 400 magazines, and news from newspapers like <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em> and the <em>Los Angeles Times</em>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-news-food-ios-18-4/">Apple News+ Subscribers Can Now Access Apple News Food</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-news-subscribers-can-now-access-apple-news-food.2454403/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and macOS Sequoia 15.4 Address 50+ Vulnerabilities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-18-4-security-fixes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-ipados-18-4-and-macos-sequoia-15-4-address-50-vulnerabilities.2454390/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:10:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-18-4-security-fixes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 updates that Apple released today include a long list of fixes for security vulnerabilities, though none of the issues addressed were known to have been actively exploited.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 fix 60 vulnerabilities, including an issue that could allow sensitive keychain data to be accessible from an iOS backup, a problem where password autofill filled a password even after a failed authentication, and a bug that could allow hidden photos to be viewed without authentication.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has a full list of iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 fixes in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/122371">security support document</a>. There's a separate security support document <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/122373">for macOS Sequoia 15.4</a>, and the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4 update addresses over 120 vulnerabilities with everything from AirDrop and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> to the Dock and Kernel.<br/>
<br/>
Because iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4 fix so many vulnerabilities, it is a good idea to update as soon as possible even if there were no known instances of these security holes being used in the wild.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-18-4-security-fixes/">iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and macOS Sequoia 15.4 Address 50+ Vulnerabilities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-ipados-18-4-and-macos-sequoia-15-4-address-50-vulnerabilities.2454390/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 10 Prototype With Unique Health Sensor Revealed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-watch-series-10-prototype/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-prototype-with-unique-health-sensor-revealed.2454389/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:00:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-watch-series-10-prototype/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The account @StellaFudge today <a href="https://x.com/StellaFudge/status/1906777369546727641">shared photos</a> of an alleged Apple Watch Series 10 prototype with a unique health sensor design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Series-10-Prototype-16x9-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-997315" /><br/>
The health sensor on the prototype has a smaller array of LEDs compared to actual Apple Watch Series 10 models that launched last year. There is also an extra ring of lights around the sensor's perimeter, but it is unclear what it is for.<br/>
<br/>
The prototype was running an internal build of watchOS 11.1 that was never released to the public, according to @StellaFudge.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Prototype Apple Watch Series 10 with… A very unique health sensor arrangement.<br><br>The health sensors got shrunk down a lot and there was an extra light ring around the perimeter. The watch is also running an unreleased build of watchOS11, somewhere between 11.1b5 and 11.1rc. <a href="https://t.co/8n06JkQT39">pic.twitter.com/8n06JkQT39</a></p>&mdash; Stella - Fudge (@StellaFudge) <a href="https://twitter.com/StellaFudge/status/1906777369546727641?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 31, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The health sensor on the back of the Apple Watch is used to measure the wearer's heart rate, as well as blood oxygen on models sold outside of the United States only due to a patent dispute. It is unclear why the sensor looks different on this prototype, but the changes likely related to Apple testing future health features for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
For example, Apple has reportedly been testing a feature that could alert you to signs of high blood pressure. This feature was first rumored a few years before the Apple Watch Series 10 launched, but Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/apple-watch-blood-pressure-feature-snags/">continues to face development challenges</a>. It is unclear if the feature will be ready in time for the Apple Watch Series 11.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-watch-series-10-prototype/">Apple Watch Series 10 Prototype With Unique Health Sensor Revealed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-prototype-with-unique-health-sensor-revealed.2454389/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
