<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 03:02:31 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Ways to Use the iPhone 16 Action Button</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-action-button/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-ways-to-use-the-iphone-16-action-button.2438399/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:03:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-action-button&#038;post_date=1727481813/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, Apple brought the Action Button to all four devices, expanding it from the Pro-only limitation last year. At the same time, there's a new Camera Control button that eliminates the need to activate the camera with the Action Button, which was one of the major useful functions. At the same time, there are new Control Center options that you can set to the Action Button, expanding what's possible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-action-button-settings.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1624" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910653" /><br/>
This guide goes over what you can do with the Action Button with an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and it may be useful to help you find something new to use it for.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="base_functions">Base Functions</h2><br/>
Since the Action Button has been around since last year, Apple has several base functions that could be assigned to it.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Silent Mode</strong> - This toggles Silent Mode on and off, and it's the one-to-one replacement for the prior mute switch. This is useful if you often want to turn on sound and have the option to turn it off, but if you're a silent all the time person, it's not that functional.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Focus</strong> - You can set the Action Button to toggle on any Focus mode that you've set up. This is a good option if you've got a Do Not Disturb type of Focus that you like to turn off and on throughout the day. Of course, Focus modes can also be set to turn on and off at specific times instead, so that's able to be automated in other ways.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Camera</strong> - If you have an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; with the Camera Control button, there's no need to set the Action Button to open the Camera, unless you want it to do something like open the selfie camera while the Camera Control button opens the rear camera. It's easy to swap camera modes from the Camera Control button or the Camera app once it's open, though.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Flashlight</strong> - Flashlight is potentially one of the more useful Action Button settings if you regularly use the Flashlight function in the dark. Prior to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, the Flashlight was a mandatory Lock Screen button, but that's no longer the case. You can set other functions to the Lock Screen now, so it can make more sense to move the Flashlight to the Action Button depending on how often you use it.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Voice Memos</strong> - Setting the Action Button to Voice Memo starts a recording when you press the button the first time, and stops it with a second press. In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can get transcriptions of Voice Memos, which adds a lot more functionality. If you want to record class lectures, interviews, or meetings regularly, setting Voice Memos to the Action Button might be your best bet.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Recognize Music</strong> - This basically activates Shazam to tell you what music is playing around you. Unless you're using Shazam all the time, this is probably better to activate from Control Center.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Translate</strong> - When you press the Action Button with Translate set, it'll automatically listen to what's being said and then provide a translation. You'll need to select your languages in the Translate app, but after that, it doesn't open up a full app. It's a quick access interface where you can get a translation and even have that translation spoken aloud. There are some limitations on languages, but if you're traveling to a country where one of the available languages is spoken, this one's a super useful way to take advantage of the Action Button.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Magnifier</strong> - Magnifier opens up the Camera app and lets you set a zoom level so you can magnify small text. You can change brightness and contrast for better viewing, and put on the flash if it's dark. If you have eyesight issues and trouble with text that's too small, Magnifier has the potential to be helpful, and you'll probably need it often enough to justify assigning it to the Action Button.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Accessibility</strong> - You can set the Action Button to any Accessibility feature. There are a long list of options, but some of the more useful ones to use with a quick access toggle include Zoom, VoiceOver, Voice Control, Apple Watch Mirroring, Background Sounds, Conversation Boost, Live Speech, and Guided Access.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>No Action</strong> - Don't want to use the Action Button? Setting it to No Action means it won't do anything when it's pressed.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="shortcuts">Shortcuts</h2><br/>
You can set any Shortcut to be activated with the Action Button using the "Shortcuts" setting, and that's how some people get the most out of the feature. You can create a Shortcut that brings up several different apps and functions.<br/>
<br/>
The "<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/shortcuts/comments/188vok3/super_action_button_thanks_to_other_creators/">Super Action Button</a>" shortcut, for example, opens up a menu where you can choose from options like taking a screenshot, turning on the flashlight, creating a Reminder, starting a Voice Memo, opening <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>, creating a Calendar event, scanning a document, and more.<br/>
<br/>
You can find a bunch of these online on Reddit or <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/action-button-usages-and-shortcuts-examples-merged.2404126/">the MacRumors forums</a>, or you can create your own with the functions that you want to access quickly.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party apps that have Shortcuts created by developers will also show up in the Action Button Shortcuts section, so if you want to have the Action Button do something like open a book in Audible or create a to-do in Things, you would set that up with the Shortcuts app. Here are a few first and third-party app Shortcuts that might be useful:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>ChatGPT</strong> - Ask ChatGPT a question that you type in, or start a voice conversation.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Audible</strong> - Read a book or set a sleep timer.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Clock</strong> - Set a timer.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Files</strong> - Scan a document.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Google</strong> - Start a Google search or a voice search.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Music</strong> - Play music from your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> library or a radio station.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Phone</strong> - Call or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> someone.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Podcasts</strong> - Play a podcast.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Things</strong> - Add a to-do.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Fantastical</strong> - Create an event.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Remote</strong> - Activate the Remote Control feature for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Open an app</strong> - Set the Action Button to open any app you have installed.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
What you have available for the Shortcuts Action Button option will depend on which apps you have installed and which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> Shortcut features they've implemented. Note that this setting is distinct from the Control Center controls that you can also assign to the Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
To make things more confusing, there are different app actions in the Shortcuts app that aren't available in the Action Button settings unless you've previously set them up. You can, for example, have the Action Button launch an Amazon search, but only if you have set up a Shortcut for that function.<br/>
<br/>
So if there's something that you want to do that you're not seeing from the Shortcuts interface in the Action Button Settings, head over to the Shortcuts app, tap on the "+" button and go through the different app options there. If you find an app feature you want to use, like activating a Hue lighting scene, set that as a Shortcut and <em>then</em> you can assign it to the Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
Along with these simple app options that you already have available, you can download any Shortcut from the Shortcuts Gallery or the internet and add that to the Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="controls">Controls</h2><br/>
So in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, Apple opened up the Control Center to third-party app developers, and also added more first-party Control Center options. Some of those new Control Center features can be set to the Action Button, and you'll find them under the Controls section when you're deciding on a function for your Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Control-Center-Toggles-for-Action-Button-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955224" /><br/>
There are some Control Center controls that just aren't available. There's no option for turning on Low Power Mode with a Control Center option for the Action Button. You can set the Action Button to activate Low Power Mode, but you need to do it with Shortcuts.<br/>
<br/>
You can also do things like turn off Cellular connectivity, but not Wi-Fi, even though both of those are Control Center toggles.<br/>
<br/>
The distinction between Shortcuts and Controls is pretty confusing, especially with arbitrary restrictions like that. Some of the available Control Center toggles:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Activate <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a></li><br/>
 <li>Open the Timer interface</li><br/>
 <li>Scan a Code</li><br/>
 <li>Open an app like Instagram or Halide to the camera</li><br/>
 <li>Toggle on Airplane mode</li><br/>
 <li>Turn off cellular data</li><br/>
 <li>Open the Home app</li><br/>
 <li>Start a Quick Note</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Third-party controls are also present, and a lot of them mirror what you can do with their Shortcuts. But some apps might have Control Center controls and not Shortcuts, or there may be differences between what's available. Shortcuts generally have more options available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="lock_screen_controls">Lock Screen Controls</h2><br/>
Keep in mind that you can also set different Control Center controls to the Lock Screen now since the Camera and Flashlight options can be swapped out. It might make more sense to set a Control Center action to the Lock Screen so you can free up the Action Button for something else.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-lock-screen-controls.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958445" /><br/>
<h2 id="share_your_action_button_setup">Share Your Action Button Setup</h2><br/>
What do you use the Action Button for? Let us know in the comments below if you've come up with something clever.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-action-button/">Best Ways to Use the iPhone 16 Action Button</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-ways-to-use-the-iphone-16-action-button.2438399/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From an Apple Event in October: iPad Mini 7, Redesigned Mac Mini, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apple-event-october-2024-preview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-an-apple-event-in-october-ipad-mini-7-redesigned-mac-mini-and-more.2438385/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:47:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apple-event-october-2024-preview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will likely hold another event in October this year to announce new Macs and iPads. If so, it would be the fourth time in the last five years that Apple has held an event in October. Last year, Apple held a virtual event <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">on Monday, October 30</a> to announce new MacBook Pro and iMac models with the M3 series of chips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Black-Perspective.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961273" /><em>A concept of a smaller Mac mini</em></div><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about a potential Apple event in October, along with new products that are expected to be announced.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Event in October</h2><br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> earlier this month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-ipad-mini-rumored-for-october/">Apple will hold an October event this year</a> to announce new iPads, including an updated iPad mini, along with the first Macs with the M4 series of chips.<br/>
<br/>
"There are also new iPads in the works, including an upgraded mini version," he wrote. "They're on deck for Apple's October event alongside the M4 Macs."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to announce an October event this year, so this remains a rumor for now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Products Expected</h2><br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
Apple plans to announce updated 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max chips in the coming weeks, according to Gurman. No design changes have been rumored for the laptops this year, with improvements such as an OLED display and thinner design not expected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/macbook-pro-wont-switch-to-oled-in-2025-rumor/">until 2026 at the earliest</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last redesigned the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro in 2021, and the latest models with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips were released last October.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iMac</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-iMac-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946085" /><br/>
Apple also plans to update the iMac with the M4 chip in the coming weeks, according to Gurman. No design changes are expected for the desktop computer.<br/>
<br/>
An unanswered question: Will the Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad accessories for the iMac finally switch from Lightning to USB-C this year?<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Mac mini</h3><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Black-Ortho-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961271" /><em>A concept of a smaller Mac mini</em></div><br/>
Gurman expects the Mac mini to be updated with M4 and M4 Pro chips in the coming weeks, and he said the desktop computer will be redesigned to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">become nearly as small as an Apple TV</a>. The new Mac mini will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/01/mac-mini-to-lose-usb-a-ports-later-this-year/">apparently lack USB-A ports</a>, and instead <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/mac-mini-5-usb-c-ports-leak/">feature five USB-C ports</a>, including two on the front of the computer.<br/>
<br/>
This would be the Mac mini's first major redesign since 2010.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPad mini</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/ipad-mini-2021-youtube.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816317" /><br/>
As mentioned, Gurman expects a seventh-generation iPad mini to be unveiled at the event.<br/>
<br/>
Rumored features for the next iPad mini over the previous model include a faster chip, upgraded front and rear cameras, a fix for "jelly scrolling" screen tearing in portrait orientation, Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 support, and new color options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo previously said the next iPad mini would enter mass production <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">in the second half of 2024</a>, so there is agreement from multiple credible sources about the device being updated later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released the current iPad mini in September 2021, with new features at the time including a larger 8.3-inch display, a USB-C port, a Touch ID power button, the A15 Bionic chip, 5G support on cellular models, a 12-megapixel rear camera with Center Stage support, compatibility with the second-generation Apple Pencil, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman has said "new, lower-end iPads" plural will be unveiled in the coming weeks, so there could be an iPad 11 at Apple's event too. However, iPad 11 display shipments are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/display-shipments-macbook-air-ipad-october/">not expected to begin until October</a>, so the device could debut later.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apple-event-october-2024-preview/">What to Expect From an Apple Event in October: iPad Mini 7, Redesigned Mac Mini, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-an-apple-event-in-october-ipad-mini-7-redesigned-mac-mini-and-more.2438385/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Max: One Week Camera Review</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/iphone-16-pro-max-camera-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-max-one-week-camera-review.2438383/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:10:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/iphone-16-pro-max-camera-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been a full week since the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models launched, and we've now had enough time to give the Camera Control button and the camera setup a more in-depth look. We tested the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and Pro Max, which have triple-lens rear camera setups with 48-megapixel Fusion lens, 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, and 5x Telephoto lens.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="iPhone 16 Pro Camera Review: 1 Week Later!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CkPa2RS6PDc" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Camera Control button has turned out to be great for quickly launching the camera and snapping photos and videos, but the more in-depth adjustments that require light presses and swiping are harder to get used to.<br/>
<br/>
It's still quicker to get to these controls in the Camera app itself by tapping on the display. Maybe that's a matter of getting used to the new setup, but it's also harder to use the button in portrait orientation than landscape mode, and a lot of people take photos in portrait orientation these days. On the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max especially, the button is just too low to be comfortable to use when holding the device vertically.<br/>
<br/>
New this year is the 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, and it's a big improvement over the prior 12-megapixel Ultra Wide lens. Apple is using pixel binning to combine four pixels into one, ultimately providing a 12-megapixel finished image, but merging pixels allows for more detail and improved quality in low light.<br/>
<br/>
The 5x Telephoto lenses haven't changed, but you can get 5x optical zoom on the 16 Pro in addition to the Pro Max, which is new this year. The "Fusion" camera is also basically identical to the "Main" camera from last year, and you still have the settings to choose between 24mm, 28mm, and 35mm lenses.<br/>
<br/>
Photographic Styles are a great addition for tweaking the look of an image, and the pad for adjustments is useful to get a unique mood with minimal effort. Make sure to check out our video above to see it in action.<br/>
<br/>
For videographers, the option to shoot in 4K 120 fps is super useful, especially because you can slow it down or speed it up in post production. The Audio Mix feature for changing the audio also really makes a difference for capturing video.<br/>
<br/>
We have some &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; camera comparisons coming, where we pit the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; against some other flagship smartphones. Stay tuned to <em>MacRumors</em> to see those videos next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/iphone-16-pro-max-camera-review/">iPhone 16 Pro Max: One Week Camera Review</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-max-one-week-camera-review.2438383/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: First Discounts Hit AirPods 4 and Apple Watch Series 10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-27-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-first-discounts-hit-airpods-4-and-apple-watch-series-10.2438378/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:25:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-27-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best Apple deals include the first discounts ever on AirPods 4 and Apple Watch Series 10, plus ongoing steep markdowns on the M3 MacBook Pro. We're also still tracking a deal at Woot that has the best prices we've seen yet on iPhone 16 Silicone and Clear Cases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0013.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848004" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/02/airpods-4-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964768" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;10 off AirPods 4</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%2F">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/airpods-4-anc-first-amazon-discount/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 without ANC for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 with ANC for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week introduced the first discounts on the AirPods 4, and these deals are still available at &#36;10 off. You'll find both AirPods 4 models on sale right now, with and without Active Noise Cancellation, and only Amazon has the sale.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-watch-series-10-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968482" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;64 off Apple Watch Ultra 2 and Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYQ1VJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/25/amazon-apple-watch-10-ultra-2-low-prices/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYQ1VJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;369.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3PBKT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;64 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Black) for &#36;734.89</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Similar to the AirPods 4, this week also saw the first notable discounts on the Apple Watch Series 10 and Ultra 2 in Black. You can get &#36;30 off a few Apple Watch Series 10 models, and the Apple Watch Ultra 2 in Black has dropped to &#36;734.89.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Cases</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-cases-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968483" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on iPhone 16 cases and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases%3Fref%3Dw_gw_dd_2">Woot</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/woots-new-sale-iphone-16-cases/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Use code APPLEFIVE to see the final deal price.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases%3Fref%3Dw_gw_dd_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>iPhone 16 Cases at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot kicked off a new tech sale earlier in the week, and it includes big savings on Apple's brand new iPhone 16 case lineup. You can get Silicone and Clear Cases for the iPhone 16, 16 Pro, and 16 Pro Max at the all-time low price of &#36;29.99 when using the code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-16-case-with-magsafe-and-camera-control%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">iPhone 16 Silicone/Clear Case</a> - &#36;29.99 with code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-16-pro-case-with-magsafe-and-camera-control%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2">iPhone 16 Pro Silicone/Clear Case</a> - &#36;29.99 with code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-16-pro-max-case-with-magsafe-and-camera-control%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3">iPhone 16 Pro Max Silicone/Clear Case</a> - &#36;29.99 with code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The sale also includes a collection of electronics ranging from Beats headphones to Ring cameras and Samsung The Frame TVs. Additionally, there's a steep discount on the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2F1-or-2-pack-anker-nano-5-000mah-power-bank-with-built-in-usb-c-connector">Anker Nano 5,000 mAh Charger with Built-In USB-C</a>, available for just &#36;12.99 (1-Pack) or &#36;22.99 (2-Pack).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968484" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;500 off 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cm9BvlR0hO3">Best Buy</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/14-inch-m3-macbook-pro-record-low/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: This deal is available only to My Best Buy Plus/Total members.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cm9BvlR0hO3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;400 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro saw big discounts at Best Buy this week, and many are still available to purchase today. The headline of the sale is the 512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro for &#36;1,199.00 for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,599.00. You can find the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/14-inch-m3-macbook-pro-record-low/">full list of discounts</a> in our original post.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-27-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: First Discounts Hit AirPods 4 and Apple Watch Series 10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-first-discounts-hit-airpods-4-and-apple-watch-series-10.2438378/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 16 Pro From Lululook</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/macrumors-giveaway-lululook-iphone-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-16-pro-from-lululook.2438376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:18:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/macrumors-giveaway-lululook-iphone-16-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://www.lululook.com/">Lululook</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win one of Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models. For those unfamiliar with Lululook, it is a company that makes a wide range of Apple accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/lululook-qi2-charger-1.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="842" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968477" /><br/>
For charging an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, and AirPods, Lululook has the &#36;80 <a href="https://www.lululook.com/products/ultra-rise-qi2-15w-3-in-1-wireless-charging-station">Ultra-Rise Qi2 Charging Station</a>. It can charge a MagSafe-compatible &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at up to 15W, while also providing enough power to fast charge an Apple Watch. Both the Apple Watch and AirPods can charge at 5W.<br/>
<br/>
The Charging Station has a compact design with an upright adjustable Qi2 charging platform, which supports an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in portrait or landscape orientation so you can use StandBy. The Apple Watch charger is tucked behind the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charger, and the AirPods charge at the base of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/lululook-qi2-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968476" /><br/>
If you're looking for a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; wallet option, Lululook offers a &#36;36 <a href="https://www.lululook.com/products/leather-magnetic-wallet-stand">Leather Magnetic Wallet Stand</a> that combines a card wallet with a handy pull-out stand that you can use to watch videos, make calls, and more. It holds three cards, and it comes in black, dark brown, or brown. There's a strong magnet inside, but it's easy to detach for quick card access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/lululook-wallet.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1738" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968478" /><br/>
The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models require a 20W or higher charger for fast charging with USB-C or 30W for fast charging over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, and Lululook has the perfect 65W three-port GaN charger option. It includes two USB-C power delivery ports and a USB-A port for older accessories. The two USB-C ports split power in 30W and 30W increments, perfect for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/lululook-65w-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1542" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968479" /><br/>
Lululook ships the charger with a Universal Travel Converter so it can be used in the UK, EU, and Australia in addition to the United States, which also makes it ideal for travel. For those interested in any of Lululook's accessories, there is a <a href="https://www.lululook.com/">sitewide September sale</a> right now, just use the code 15OFF at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
We have a new 128GB &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; for one lucky winner, with the winner able to choose the color. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/UK2gT/lululook-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Lululook Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (September 27) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on October 4. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after October 4 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/macrumors-giveaway-lululook-iphone-16-pro/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 16 Pro From Lululook</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-16-pro-from-lululook.2438376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch&#039;s New Sleep Apnea Detection Feature Approved in Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apple-watch-sleep-apnea-feature-approved-in-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watchs-new-sleep-apnea-detection-feature-approved-in-canada.2438368/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:05:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apple-watch-sleep-apnea-feature-approved-in-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Health Canada this week published approval of watchOS 11's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/sleep-apnea-detection-details/">sleep apnea detection feature</a> on the Apple Watch Series 10, Apple Watch Series 9, and Apple Watch Ultra 2. The feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/apple-watch-sleep-apnea-feature-150-countries/">launched in the U.S. and over 150 other countries and regions</a> earlier this month, and Apple is now permitted to make the feature available in Canada.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/sleep-apnea-detection-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965154" /><br/>
It is unclear when Apple will expand the feature to Canada.<br/>
<br/>
Sleep apnea is a potentially serious disorder in which a person's breathing repeatedly stops and starts while they sleep. The detection feature uses the Apple Watch's accelerometer to "monitor small movements at the wrist that are associated with interruptions in normal respiratory patterns." If these disturbances occur frequently over multiple nights, they may be associated with sleep apnea, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Health-Canada-Apple-Watch-Sleep-Apnea.jpg" alt="" width="779" height="294" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968471" /><br/>
Apple says the feature was developed using "advanced machine learning" and an "extensive data set of clinical-grade sleep apnea tests," and then validated in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/health/pdf/sleep-apnea/Sleep_Apnea_Notifications_on_Apple_Watch_September_2024.pdf">clinical study</a>. The feature is intended to detect signs of moderate to severe sleep apnea in adults who have not already been diagnosed with the disorder, according to the company.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch users can view their nightly Breathing Disturbances in the Health app on the iPhone, with disturbances classified as "elevated" or "not elevated."<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apple-watch-sleep-apnea-feature-approved-in-canada/">Apple Watch&#039;s New Sleep Apnea Detection Feature Approved in Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watchs-new-sleep-apnea-detection-feature-approved-in-canada.2438368/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iPhone 16 Pro First Impressions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-pro-first-impressions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-pro-first-impressions.2438357/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:34:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-pro-first-impressions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After some hands-on time with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, Apple Watch Series 10, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a>, on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/iphone-16-pro-first-impressions/id1602394741?i=1000670954560">The MacRumors Show</a>, we talk through our first impressions of the new devices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OkOsiwbpBuc?si=9_5xSL-slicAKHQ1" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We consider some of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s most noticeable features and improvements, such as longer battery life, the 48-megapixel ultra wide camera, enhanced microphones, overhauled Photographic Styles, and the 5x telephoto camera. We also explore our mixed feelings about the all-new Camera Control button. We also discuss the revamped design of the Apple Watch Series 10, as well as the fit improvements and active noise cancellation capabilities of the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj;. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/the-macrumors-show-our-favorite-ios-18-features/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about our favorite <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> features.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-pro-first-impressions/">The MacRumors Show: iPhone 16 Pro First Impressions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-pro-first-impressions.2438357/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Back to School Promotion Ending Soon: Here&#039;s What You Can Get</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apples-2024-back-to-school-offer-ends-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-back-to-school-promotion-ending-soon-heres-what-you-can-get.2438351/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:52:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apples-2024-back-to-school-offer-ends-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Back to School Promotion</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In June, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-back-to-schoo-promotion-launches/">launched its annual Back to School promotion</a> for college students in the U.S. and select other countries. Students can get a free Apple gift card with the purchase of an eligible Mac or iPad from Apple, along with 20% off AppleCare+ plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-2024-Back-to-School-Offer.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968432" /><br/>
In the U.S. and Canada, the promotion <a href="https://www.apple.com/us/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">ends on September 30</a>, so time is running out to take advantage of the offer if you are a student. There is still more time in the U.K. and select other European countries, where the promotion ends October 21.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple is offering the following:<ul><li>A free <strong>&#36;150 Apple gift card</strong> with any new MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, or iMac</li><br/>
<li>A free <strong>&#36;100 Apple gift card</strong> with any new iPad Pro with an M4 chip, iPad Air with an M2 chip, or Mac mini</li></ul>The gift card can be used towards purchases of Apple products and accessories, App Store apps, subscriptions to services like Apple Music, iCloud+ storage, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The offer is available through Apple's online education store and at Apple Store locations for students attending or accepted to a higher-education institution, faculty and staff of higher-education institutions, parents purchasing on behalf of an eligible student, employees of a K-12 institution, and select others.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/back-to-school-promotion/">Back to School Promotion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/apples-2024-back-to-school-offer-ends-soon/">Apple&#039;s Back to School Promotion Ending Soon: Here&#039;s What You Can Get</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-back-to-school-promotion-ending-soon-heres-what-you-can-get.2438351/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>15 New Things Your iPhone Can Do in iOS 18.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/new-things-your-iphone-will-do-ios-18-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/15-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-in-ios-18-1.2438350/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:14:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/new-things-your-iphone-will-do-ios-18-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is set to release iOS 18.1 in October, bringing the first set of Apple Intelligence features to iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 16 models. This update marks a significant step forward in Apple's AI integration, offering a new Siri contextually-aware experience and a range of additional capabilities powered by on-device machine learning and large language models. There are a couple of handy new feature controls coming, too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/15-New-Things-Your-iPhone-Can-Do-in-iOS-18.1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968236" /><br/>
While not all Apple Intelligence features will be available immediately, iOS 18.1 introduces several enhancements that aim to make your iPhone smarter and more intuitive. Below, we've listed 15 new things your iPhone will be able to do when the update rolls out next month.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Reset Your Control Center</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/reset-control-center.jpg" alt="control center" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968362" /><br/>
With iOS 18, Apple made the Control Center thoroughly customizable, but there's no way to roll back your changes if things get messy. Fortunately, iOS 18.1 introduces a simple way to start fresh. In Settings  Control Center, you'll find a new option to reset your Control Center to its default layout. This feature is perfect if you've made too many customizations and want to return to a clean slate without manually rearranging everything.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Take Selfies With Camera Control</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-selfie-camera-control.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967792" /><br/>
Camera Control gets a selfie upgrade in iOS 18.1. Now, you can switch to the front-facing camera without touching your screen. Simply open the Camera app with a press of the Camera Control button, then swipe on the button to cycle through lens options. Look for the person icon at the top to activate the selfie camera, making it easier to capture that perfect self-portrait.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Proofread Your Text</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/proofread-notes.jpg" alt="notes" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968363" /><br/>
Embarrassing typos could be a thing of the past. iOS 18.1's new Writing Tools feature includes a powerful proofreading function. It not only checks for spelling and grammar errors but also suggests improvements in word choice and sentence structure. You can accept all suggestions with a single tap or review them one by one, complete with explanations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Rewrite Your Text</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/rewrite-your-text.jpg" alt="notes" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968377" /><br/>
Need to change the tone of your message? The new Rewrite tool is capable of doing just that. Whether you want your text to sound more friendly, professional, or concise, this feature can adjust your writing style without altering the core content. It's like having a personal editor at your fingertips, helping you communicate more effectively in any situation.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summarize Long Emails</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/summarize-mail.jpg" alt="mail" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968365" /><br/>
If you frequently suffer from inbox overload, this should be a welcome feature. When you receive a lengthy email, you'll now see a "Summarize" button that lets Apple Intelligence create a concise overview. Choose from options like a brief paragraph, key points, or even a bulleted list. This tool makes it easier to quickly grasp the essence of important messages without reading every word. Plus, your inbox now displays a brief AI-generated summary instead of the first few lines of each email, helping you prioritize your responses more efficiently.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Answer Apple Product Questions</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-product-knowledge.jpeg" alt="siri" width="5472" height="3078" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968368" /><br/>
Your iPhone becomes a knowledgeable Apple expert with iOS 18.1. Siri can now tap into a vast database of product information, helping you understand device features, locate settings, and even provide tutorials on how to complete tasks. It's like having Apple Support built right into your device, available whenever you need it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Offer Smart Replies to Emails and Messages</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-messages-smart-reply.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960223" /><br/>
Communication gets a boost with Smart Reply in iOS 18.1. When you receive an email or message, your iPhone will analyze the content and suggest contextually relevant responses. These quick-tap options make it easy to reply promptly and appropriately, saving you time and effort in your daily correspondence.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summarize Multiple Message Notifications</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/summarize-notifications.jpg" alt="messages" width="3018" height="1696" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968371" /><br/>
Catching up on group chats is set to get a lot easier. iOS 18.1 can summarize multiple message notifications on your Lock Screen, giving you a quick overview without the need to open the app. This feature helps you stay on top of conversations without getting overwhelmed by notification overload.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Create Memory Movies From a Short Description</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-memory-maker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960208" /><br/>
Relive your favorite moments with ease using the new Memory Movie feature. Simply provide a description like "My cat in 2024" or "Orlando in the summer," and your iPhone will automatically select relevant photos and choose appropriate music. You can further customize the mood and add specific scenes, turning your memories into beautiful short films with minimal effort.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Remove Unwanted Objects From Photos</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-Photos-Clean-Up-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962933" /><br/>
Perfect your photos with the new Clean Up tool. This feature allows you to easily remove unwanted objects from your images. Whether it's a photobomber or a distracting element in the background, you can now tap, circle, or brush over the object to make it disappear. The tool is smart enough to preserve important elements, ensuring your main subjects remain intact.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summarize Your Audio Transcripts</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/summarize-transcript.jpg" alt="notes" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968370" /><br/>
Turn long recordings into digestible content with the new transcription feature. When you record audio in apps like Notes, your iPhone can now provide a transcript along with a summary. This is particularly useful for capturing and distilling information from lectures, meetings, or interviews, making it easier to review and share key points.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Reduce Your Interruptions</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ios-18-apple-intelligence-notification-summary.jpg" alt="notifications" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968372" /><br/>
Take control of your notifications with the new Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode. This intelligent feature filters your alerts, showing you only the most important notifications that require immediate attention. It should come in handy for when you need to concentrate but don't want to miss crucial information.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Record Your Phone Calls</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-call-recording-1.jpg" alt="" width="5416" height="3047" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960199" /><br/>
iOS 18.1 introduces Phone call recording. During a call, you'll see a record button in the upper left corner of the display. Tap it, and after notifying all participants, the call will be recorded. These recordings are stored in the Notes app, where you can access transcripts and AI-generated summaries, making it easy to review important conversations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summarize Web Articles</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-safari-summarize.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960226" /><br/>
Reading long articles is about to get easier with this Safari improvement. When using Reader Mode, you can now tap a button to have Apple Intelligence summarize the article for you. This feature quickly distills the main points, allowing you to grasp the essence of the content without reading every word.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Generate Apple Intelligence Reports</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-report.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960227" /><br/>
If you're curious about how Apple Intelligence is working on your device, iOS 18.1 offers transparency through the new Apple Intelligence Report. Found in the Privacy & Security section of the Settings app, this feature allows you to export your Apple Intelligence data. It requires Face ID authentication, ensuring your privacy is protected while providing insight into how AI is enhancing your iPhone experience.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/new-things-your-iphone-will-do-ios-18-1/">15 New Things Your iPhone Can Do in iOS 18.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/15-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-in-ios-18-1.2438350/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>USB-C Apple Pencil Now Available Refurbished in Three More Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/refurbished-usb-c-apple-pencil-in-more-countries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/usb-c-apple-pencil-now-available-refurbished-in-three-more-countries.2438349/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:07:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/refurbished-usb-c-apple-pencil-in-more-countries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added the lower-cost Apple Pencil with a USB-C port to its online refurbished store for the first time in three more countries: Australia, Japan, and Singapore. Availability first began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/11/refurbished-usb-c-apple-pencil-us/">in the U.S.</a>, Canada, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/refurbished-usb-c-apple-pencil/">some European countries</a> in July.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917176" /><br/>
The refurbished model is discounted by around 15% in each country. For example, pricing is set at &#36;119 in Australia, down from &#36;139 brand new.<br/>
<br/>
Originally released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/usb-c-apple-pencil-hands-on/">in November 2023</a>, the lower-cost Apple Pencil has a similar design as the Apple Pencil 2 and Apple Pencil Pro, but with a USB-C port hidden under a sliding cap for charging and pairing with a USB-C cable. It attaches magnetically to any iPad with a USB-C port, but it does not support wireless charging or wireless pairing. It also lacks pressure sensitivity and a double-tap gesture for switching between drawing tools.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says its refurbished products undergo full functionality testing, and are subject to a thorough cleaning process and inspection. The refurbished Apple Pencils are repackaged in a plainer white box with a refurbished label.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/refurbished-usb-c-apple-pencil-in-more-countries/">USB-C Apple Pencil Now Available Refurbished in Three More Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/usb-c-apple-pencil-now-available-refurbished-in-three-more-countries.2438349/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Film &#039;Wolfs&#039; Starring Brad Pitt and George Clooney on Apple TV+</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/wolfs-george-clooney-brad-pitt-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-film-wolfs-starring-brad-pitt-and-george-clooney-on-apple-tv.2438347/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 05:32:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/wolfs-george-clooney-brad-pitt-apple-tv/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple action-comedy film "<a href="https://tv.apple.com/gb/movie/wolfs/umc.cmc.c3xhu25rw4jxxxzq4oio6snu">Wolfs</a>," featuring Hollywood stars Brad Pitt and George Clooney, premiered today exclusively on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+. The movie was originally slated for a wide theatrical release, but premiered on the streaming service today following a limited theatrical run last week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/wolfs-movie.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968383" /><br/>
Directed by Jon Watts, known for the recent Spider-Man trilogy, "Wolfs" follows two professional fixers played by Pitt and Clooney who must work together to cover up a high-profile crime. The star-studded cast also includes Amy Ryan, Austin Abrams, and Richard Kind.<br/>
<br/>
Despite positive reception from critics, Apple made the unexpected decision to pull "Wolfs" from wide theatrical release last month. The company has not publicly explained its reasoning for the change in strategy, although industry speculation suggests it may be related to the underwhelming box office performance of some recent Apple Original films.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's shift in approach for "Wolfs" reflects a broader reconsideration of its theatrical release plans. Another upcoming film, "Blitz," is also set for a limited theatrical run before streaming. Currently, Apple has only one movie, the Formula One drama "F1" (also starring Brad Pitt), scheduled for a wide theatrical release in June 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the move, Apple appears to remain committed to producing high-profile content. Matt Dentler, head of features at Apple Original Films, <a href="https://deadline.com/2024/08/apple-sets-wolfs-sequel-jon-watts-george-clooney-brad-pitt-drama-pivots-limited-theatrical-before-apple-tv-streaming-bow-1236034117/">recently described</a> "Wolfs" as a "big event movie" and announced that a sequel is already in development.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wLJUPjiRbAM?si=cV5atSdf-QR4UR--" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
"Wolfs" is produced by Clooney's Smokehouse Pictures and Pitt's Plan B Entertainment in partnership with Apple. The film is <a href="https://tv.apple.com/gb/movie/wolfs/umc.cmc.c3xhu25rw4jxxxzq4oio6snu">now streaming</a> for all &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ subscribers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/wolfs-george-clooney-brad-pitt-apple-tv/">New Film &#039;Wolfs&#039; Starring Brad Pitt and George Clooney on Apple TV+</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-film-wolfs-starring-brad-pitt-and-george-clooney-on-apple-tv.2438347/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Make Calls Faster With This New iOS 18 Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-t9-dialing-ios-phone-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-calls-faster-with-this-new-ios-18-feature.2438337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 04:12:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-t9-dialing-ios-phone-app&#038;post_date=1727446320/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has finally brought T9 dialing support to the iPhone with iOS 18, a feature long available on Android devices. This addition to the Phone app allows users to quickly find and call contacts using the number pad, which can streamline the process of making calls if you've used the feature before.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/t9-dialing-phone-keypad-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955980" /><br/>
T9 dialing, or Text on 9 keys, is a predictive text technology that emerged in the late 90s to make it easier to type text messages on devices with limited input options, such as traditional mobile phones with numeric keypads. Each number key (2-9) on a T9 keypad is mapped to a set of letters. For example, the key "2" corresponds to "ABC," "3" to "DEF," and so on.<br/>
<br/>
The best match appears first above the keypad, and tapping the person's name will call them. If there are several possible matches in your contacts, they can be revealed as a list by tapping "X more..." below the first match. Taken together, the new options should enable faster calling.<br/>
<br/>
Here's how to use T9 dialing in iOS 18:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open the Phone app and tap the keypad tab.</li><br/>
  <li>Type the contact's name using the number keys (e.g., for "Dad," press 3-2-3).</li><br/>
  <li>Above the keypad, tap the matching contact to call, or "X more..." to see additional matches.</li><br/>
</ol>This feature aims to speed up the calling process, especially for users who prefer the number pad or have difficulty navigating contact lists. It's particularly useful for one-handed operation or when quick dialing is necessary.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Add Contacts From the Keypad</h2><br/>
iOS 18 also introduces new options for adding numbers to contacts directly from the keypad. When entering a new number:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>After entering a new number, tap the new button in the top-left corner of the keypad screen.</li><br/>
  <li>Choose "Create New Contact" or "Add to Existing Contact" as needed.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/t9-phone-dialing-ios-18-keypad.jpg" alt="" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955984" /><br/>
That's all there is to it. In addition to the new features described above, Apple has also added the ability to search recent calls. Simply look for the search field at the top of your recent calls list and start typing into it to find the contact or number you're looking for.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-t9-dialing-ios-phone-app/">Make Calls Faster With This New iOS 18 Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-calls-faster-with-this-new-ios-18-feature.2438337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: 2025 Apple Vision Pro to Get M5 Chip and Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/kuo-apple-vision-pro-m5-chip-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-2025-apple-vision-pro-to-get-m5-chip-and-apple-intelligence.2438327/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 02:14:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/kuo-apple-vision-pro-m5-chip-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is developing a new version of its Vision Pro headset that is set to enter mass production in the second half of 2025, according to <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/ai-spatial-computing-to-be-the-main-selling-point-for-new-m5-powered-vision-pro-new-apple-15f409ea6c15">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944159" /><br/>
Kuo claims the most significant change in the new model will be the inclusion of Apple's M5 chip, a substantial upgrade from the M2 chip found in the current Vision Pro. The processor boost is expected to significantly improve device's computing power, with a particular emphasis on integrated Apple Intelligence features.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the upgraded internals, Kuo reports that other hardware specifications and the overall design of the Vision Pro will remain largely unchanged. This approach could help Apple manage production costs, although the price point is expected to stay close to the current &#36;3,499 starting price of the first-generation model.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo emphasized that if this new version creates compelling use cases, it could push Apple's spatial computing platform closer to mainstream adoption. He also speculates on the potential integration of advanced AI models, such as text-to-video capabilities similar to OpenAI's Sora, which could dramatically enhance the Vision Pro experience. <br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/">reports</a> that Apple plans to introduce Apple Intelligence features to the Vision Pro headset in the future. While the device is capable of running on-device AI functions such as writing tools, notification summaries, and an upgraded Siri, these features are not expected to arrive in 2024. Instead, Apple may be reserving the Apple Intelligence integration for visionOS 3, potentially launching in 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/kuo-apple-vision-pro-m5-chip-apple-intelligence/">Kuo: 2025 Apple Vision Pro to Get M5 Chip and Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-2025-apple-vision-pro-to-get-m5-chip-and-apple-intelligence.2438327/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Teardown Provides Look Inside iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/iphone-16-pro-teardown-ifixit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-teardown-provides-look-inside-iphone-16-pro-and-iphone-16-pro-max.2438298/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:45:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/iphone-16-pro-teardown-ifixit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this week, repair site iFixit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/ifixit-iphone-16-teardown/">took apart the iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> Plus to demonstrate the new battery removal process that uses electricity for adhesive removal, and today, iFixit is back with a teardown of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="iPhone 16 Pro and Pro Max Teardowns - Worth The Upgrade?" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PHQD4FcsOvs" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Apple's &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models do not have the same simplified battery removal process as the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, with Apple instead using traditional stretch release adhesive for its pricier iPhones. It's still easier to get inside, though, because you can do so through the back of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> rather than the display, which can be easily damaged.<br/>
<br/>
Apple encased the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; battery in metal like the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, but the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max does not have the metal casing around its battery, and it's not clear why. iFixit called the decision to use the metal-encased battery in just the 16 Pro and not the 16 Pro Max "perplexing."<br/>
<br/>
The LiDAR Scanner is more accessible, which makes it easier to access for repairs. In prior Pro &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, it was under the main camera assembly. The camera modules are almost identical, but not quite interchangeable due to a different cable length and a screw positioned in two separate locations inside each model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple moved the mmWave antenna to make room for the Camera Control button, and in the 16 Pro models, it's in a hollowed out space near the top of the device. iFixit says that mmWave signal could still suffer due to the titanium frame of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
USB-C port removal is "massively" simplified, but iFixit points out that Apple does not sell replacement USB-C ports. The logic board can also be pulled out with only the removal of the upper speaker assembly, which is a major improvement to the design.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, the teardown revealed that the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are using a Qualcomm SDX71M modem, which is a custom version of the SDX70M modem used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro models. Rumors had suggested the Pro models would include the Qualcomm X75 modem, which doesn't appear to be the case.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit gave the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models a repairability score of 7 out of 10 due to the design changes and the availability of repair manuals.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/iphone-16-pro-teardown-ifixit/">iFixit Teardown Provides Look Inside iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-teardown-provides-look-inside-iphone-16-pro-and-iphone-16-pro-max.2438298/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad 11: What&#039;s Next for Apple&#039;s Most Affordable Tablet</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-11/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-11-whats-next-for-apples-most-affordable-tablet.2438296/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:15:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-11&#038;post_date=1727399707/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on an update for the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, which hasn't been refreshed since 2022. As an entry-level product, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; doesn't get a lot of attention and it's not often the focus of rumors, but we've heard a little bit about what might be coming to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 11.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904791" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/ipad-green-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple overhauled the look of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in 2022, introducing a 10.9-inch all-display design and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> power button, so we're not expecting any further design changes at this point in time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Fanned-Pink.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869882" /><br/>
Apple will likely stick with the 10.9-inch display and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; Air-like design, but we could get new colors. Current colors include silver, yellow, pink, and blue. The &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; already has a USB-C port, which will stick around, and it will continue to support the USB-C <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="a-series_chip">A-Series Chip</h2><br/>
The current 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; has an A14 chip that was first used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 lineup, and it's getting outdated. The logical choice for the next &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is the A16 that was used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, but if Apple wants to make Apple Intelligence as accessible as possible, an A17 Pro chip or A18 chip isn't out of the question.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, adding Apple Intelligence support would also necessitate much more memory, and the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is currently limited to 4GB, so it might just be too expensive for Apple to give it that functionality while also keeping the price affordable.<br/>
<br/>
Either way, the A16 will be a major improvement even if it doesn't support Apple Intelligence. It'll be faster and more efficient, so battery life could potentially be improved.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_updates">Other Updates</h2><br/>
Apple has been updating most of its products with Wi-Fi 6E or better, so we can expect Wi-Fi 6E support for the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. The current model supports Wi-Fi 6, so it is not compatible with the faster 6GHz band that's available with Wi-Fi 6E routers. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="cost">Cost</h2><br/>
We haven't heard rumors of any kind of cost increase for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 11, so we're still expecting pricing to start at &#36;349 for 64GB of storage. Apple has been bumping some minimum storage options in recent years, so there's a chance we could see a boost to 128GB of storage without a cost increase, but nothing has been rumored.<br/>
<br/>
Apple only sells the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in 64GB and 256GB configurations right now.<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
Apple is rumored to be holding an event in October to unveil new M4 Macs and a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a>, so it's possible we'll see the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; then.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors about the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 11's launch date have been wishy washy, though. Analyst Ross Young recently said that display shipments for the device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/display-shipments-macbook-air-ipad-october/">wouldn't start</a> until October, which is late for an October debut and actually more appropriate for a 2025 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/01/apple-working-on-redesigned-ipad-magic-keyboard/">new Magic Keyboard</a> accessory for the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and/or the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> which is expected to come out by the middle of 2025. It may not make sense to release the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 11 until that accessory is ready, as Apple doesn't typically split up accessory and device launches.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, if it's actually an accessory solely for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, the keyboard might not have an impact on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 11 launch date at all.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="buying_advice">Buying Advice</h2><br/>
If you're planning to get a low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and you can wait, we recommend holding off for the new model. The current version is two years old at this point, and the chip inside is even older. You'll get the most out of your money if you wait for an update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-11/">iPad 11: What&#039;s Next for Apple&#039;s Most Affordable Tablet</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-11-whats-next-for-apples-most-affordable-tablet.2438296/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Upcoming Smart Home Accessory Could Feature &#039;Squarish&#039; Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-smart-home-accessory-square-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-upcoming-smart-home-accessory-could-feature-squarish-display.2438268/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 11:33:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-smart-home-accessory-square-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Smart Home Display</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is rumored to be working on a sort of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-smart-home-display/">iPad-like smart display</a> that will serve as a home hub for controlling your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> and Matter devices. We've been hearing rumors about the device for the last couple of years, and now there's some new information about its potential design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/HomePod-G4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793597" /><br/>
Called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/04/leak-confirms-apples-work-on-home-accessory/">the "HomeAccessory" internally</a>, the upcoming smart home device has a "squarish display," according to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/09/26/apples-long-awaited-homeaccessory-could-have-square-display-a18-chip-for-ai-more/">9to5Mac</a></em>. The square display would make the product distinct from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, which has a more rectangular display. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has previously described the smart home hub as "iPad-like" with features adopted from the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, but he's also described a separate &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a screen, which seems to be simpler.<br/>
<br/>
<em>9to5Mac</em> claims it is unclear whether the square design will make it into the final product, which also seems to have a built-in camera for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>. The device includes a camera that is able to identify hand gestures from afar, and it can tell one person apart from another for personalized requests. While it can run apps and play media like the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, it will also serve as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> receiver like the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> spotted signs of the HomeAccessory in Apple's backend code earlier this year. It is a product that is distinct from Apple's other home devices, the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; and the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;. It seems to run a variant of tvOS much like the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, and the test version we've seen described is equipped with an A18 chip, so there is a possibility that it might not be too far off from launching.<br/>
<br/>
With an A18 chip or later, Apple's smart home product would be able to run Apple Intelligence features, and it would support the smarter <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> that Apple plans to introduce in 2025. Prior rumors have said that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/homepod-with-ipad-like-screen-2025-rumor/">will debut in 2025</a> at the earliest, and <em>9to5Mac</em> says it could come next spring. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-smart-home-display/">Apple Smart Home Display</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-smart-home-accessory-square-display/">Apple&#039;s Upcoming Smart Home Accessory Could Feature &#039;Squarish&#039; Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-upcoming-smart-home-accessory-could-feature-squarish-display.2438268/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7a305/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware.2438264/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 11:16:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7a305/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, with the software available for both the USB-C and Lightning models. The &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 firmware has a build number of 7A305, up from the 7A302 firmware <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/18/apple-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7a302/">released earlier in September</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-825981" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/AirPods-Pro-Firmware-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2322" height="1306" /><br/>
There is no word yet on what's included in the firmware, but Apple is planning to add hearing aid and hearing test features to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 in the not too distant future.<br/>
<br/>
The firmware update could potentially lay the groundwork for those capabilities ahead of when the full feature set comes out in an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> update. Apple has already received FDA approval for the hearing aid functionality for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't have a way to manually upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air when the AirPods are in a charging case and connected to an iOS device or Mac.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7a305/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware.2438264/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes Up to &#36;1,000 Off M2 iPad Pro With Record Low Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/best-buy-m2-ipad-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-up-to-1-000-off-m2-ipad-pro-with-record-low-prices.2438257/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 10:15:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/best-buy-m2-ipad-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://howl.me/clM5ZY2SiSP">Best Buy</a> is back this week with big discounts on the M2 11-inch and 12.9-inch iPad Pro, providing up to &#36;1,000 off select models. A My Best Buy Plus/Total membership is not required to see these discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ipad-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940265" /><br/>
You'll find both Wi-Fi and cellular tablets on sale at Best Buy, with a particular focus on the larger capacity 1TB and 2TB models. All deals listed below represent record low prices on each iPad Pro model, and many of them can currently only be found at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSBs9KNeu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>M2 iPad Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With such steep savings, these previous generation iPad Pros are worth looking into purchasing for anyone who wants to prioritize saving money over owning the newest M4 iPad Pro. There are some major differences between the two generations, like the M4's support for Apple Pencil Pro and a new nano-texture display option, so be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-pro-2022-vs-2024/">read about which one works best for you</a> in our Buyer's Guide.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11-Inch iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<h3>Wi-Fi</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clM5ZY2SiSP">1TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;999.00 (&#36;500 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM50J6paxv">2TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,299.00 (&#36;600 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Cellular</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSc22N2b9">1TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,099.00 (&#36;600 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSdKc6izG">2TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,299.00 (&#36;800 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2>12.9-Inch iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<h3>Wi-Fi</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clM56AO1pl6">2TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,499.00 (&#36;700 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Cellular</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCShFBt2of">1TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,299.00 (&#36;700 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSiepS0Mp">2TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,399.00 (&#36;1,000 off)</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/best-buy-m2-ipad-pro/">Best Buy Takes Up to &#36;1,000 Off M2 iPad Pro With Record Low Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-up-to-1-000-off-m2-ipad-pro-with-record-low-prices.2438257/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing iOS 18.0.1 Update for iPhone Following Several Bugs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-preparing-ios-18-0-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-ios-18-0-1-update-for-iphone-following-several-bugs.2438253/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:34:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-preparing-ios-18-0-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple appears to be internally testing iOS 18.0.1 for the iPhone, based on evidence of the software update in our website's analytics this week. Our logs have accurately revealed many iOS versions before they were released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Generic-iOS-18.0.1-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968305" /><br/>
We expect iOS 18.0.1 to be a minor update focused on bug fixes. Issues that could be addressed with the update include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/ios-18-touchscreen-issues-reported/">touchscreen issues affecting the iPhone 16 series</a> and some older models, <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/09/18/ios-18-messages-app-crash/">an iMessage bug</a> where a shared Apple Watch face can cause the app to repeatedly crash, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-working-to-fix-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro-issue/">iPadOS 18 bricking some iPad Pro units</a> with the M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear when iOS 18.0.1 will be released, but our best guess is the update will be available towards the end of next week at the latest.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.0.1 will precede iOS 18.1, which Apple previously announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/when-will-ios-18-1-be-released/">will be released in October</a>. Already available in beta, iOS 18.1 includes the first Apple Intelligence features for the iPhone, including writing tools, notification summaries, and more. Apple Intelligence is available on the iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, and any iPhone 16 model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-preparing-ios-18-0-1/">Apple Preparing iOS 18.0.1 Update for iPhone Following Several Bugs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-ios-18-0-1-update-for-iphone-following-several-bugs.2438253/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Woot&#039;s New Sale Has iPhone 16 Cases for &#36;29.99 (&#36;19 Off), Plus More Accessory Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/woots-new-sale-iphone-16-cases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/woots-new-sale-has-iphone-16-cases-for-29-99-19-off-plus-more-accessory-deals.2438235/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 07:49:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/woots-new-sale-iphone-16-cases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot is hosting a new tech sale this week, and it includes all-time low prices on <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases%3Fref%3Dw_gw_dd_2">Apple's iPhone 16 Silicone and Clear cases</a>. You can get these accessories for just &#36;29.99 when using the code <strong>APPLEFIVE</strong> at checkout, and Woot has multiple colors in Silicone available for most models of the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-cases.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968291" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The sale also includes a <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fbest-of-tech-36%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_odet_w_crum_2_wp">collection of electronics</a> ranging from Beats headphones to Ring cameras and Samsung The Frame TVs. Additionally, there's a steep discount on the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2F1-or-2-pack-anker-nano-5-000mah-power-bank-with-built-in-usb-c-connector">Anker Nano 5,000 mAh Charger with Built-In USB-C</a>, available for just &#36;12.99 (1-Pack) or &#36;22.99 (2-Pack).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Use code APPLEFIVE to see the final deal price.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases%3Fref%3Dw_gw_dd_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>iPhone 16 Cases at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-16-case-with-magsafe-and-camera-control%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">iPhone 16 Silicone/Clear Case</a> - &#36;29.99 with code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-16-pro-case-with-magsafe-and-camera-control%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2">iPhone 16 Pro Silicone/Clear Case</a> - &#36;29.99 with code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-16-pro-max-case-with-magsafe-and-camera-control%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3">iPhone 16 Pro Max Silicone/Clear Case</a> - &#36;29.99 with code APPLEFIVE, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/woots-new-sale-iphone-16-cases/">Woot&#039;s New Sale Has iPhone 16 Cases for &#36;29.99 (&#36;19 Off), Plus More Accessory Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/woots-new-sale-has-iphone-16-cases-for-29-99-19-off-plus-more-accessory-deals.2438235/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
