<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:02:36 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>8GB RAM in M3 MacBook Pro Proves the Bottleneck in Real-World Tests</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck-in-real-world-tests.2410564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:47:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new MacBook Pro models are powered by cutting-edge M3 Apple silicon, but the base configuration 14-inch model starting at &#36;1,599 comes with just 8GB of working memory. In 2012, Apple launched the first MacBook Pro with Retina display, which also started with 8GB of RAM. Of course, Apple now uses integrated chips with unified memory architecture, which is why the company feels confident in arguing that 8GB on a Mac is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/8gb-ram-m3-macbook-pro-like-16-gb-pc/">comparable to 16GB on rival systems</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hmWPd7uEYEY?si=zIgEy80AQutgE9Xj" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
But not everyone is convinced. Apple's decision not to equip base models with at least 16GB of RAM in late 2023 has proved incongruous to many users, including Vadim Yuryev, co-host of the YouTube channel <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hmWPd7uEYEY">Max Tech</a>. Yuryev decided to perform several real-world tests on two 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro models, one with 8GB and the other upgraded to 16GB of unified memory. The embedded video above has all the results.  <br/>
<br/>
Perhaps unsurprisingly, Yuryev saw significant performance improvements across the board using the 16GB machine under both middling and heavier workloads. The 8GB model suffered double-digit losses in Cinebench benchmarks, and took several minutes longer to complete photo-merging jobs in Photoshop as well as media exports in Final Cut and Adobe Lightroom Classic.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/max-tech-8gb-16gb-mbp2.jpg" alt="" width="2491" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922139" /><br/>
These tests were conducted as single operations with nothing else running, but also repeated with browser tabs, YouTube videos, spreadsheets, emails, and the like, open in the background to simulate typical real-world multi-tasking scenarios. As expected, the performance gap between the two machines widened further as the 8GB increasingly relied on its SSD swap file, while all-round responsiveness took a hit. Yuryev even reported crashes on the 8GB model during Blender rendering and a Final Cut export.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, Blender's raytracing acceleration was available as an option on the 16GB models, but was conspicuously absent on the 8GB MacBook Pro for an identical rendering job, suggesting the reduced memory pool actually prevents the GPU cores from utilizing certain features. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/max-tech-8gb-16gb-mbp1.jpg" alt="" width="2490" height="1401" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922142" /><br/>
Tests like these present a dilemma for customers looking to purchase a new MacBook Pro (or a new 8GB iMac, for that matter). Settling for 8GB appears to hinder the M3 chip's performance, but choosing 16GB or 24GB configuration options at checkout costs an extra &#36;200 and &#36;400, respectively, and Apple's machines cannot be upgraded at a later date because of their unified memory architecture. <br/>
<br/>
After factoring in the extra &#36;200 for 16GB on a 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro, an M3 Pro model with 18GB and several other extra features is only &#36;200 more at &#36;1,999. More galling perhaps is the fact that rival laptops at similar ballpark prices (Microsoft Surface or Lenovo Thinkpad, for example) come with at least 16GB of memory as standard. Apple customers are expected to pay &#36;200 extra each jump up, which surely includes a healthy markup, however much Apple pays its RAM suppliers.<br/>
<br/>
Is Apple's 8GB starting configuration for a &#36;1,599 MacBook Pro really acceptable in 2023? And has the company's memory pricing policy affected your own purchase options? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck/">8GB RAM in M3 MacBook Pro Proves the Bottleneck in Real-World Tests</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck-in-real-world-tests.2410564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED iPad Pros, MacBook Pros, MacBook Airs to Launch in That Order</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ipad-pro-macbook-pro-macbook-air-oled-launches/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pros-macbook-pros-macbook-airs-to-launch-in-that-order.2410547/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 02:06:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ipad-pro-macbook-pro-macbook-air-oled-launches/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models with OLED displays will be followed by sequential OLED MacBook Pro and OLED <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> launches over the next three years, according to analyst Jeff Pu from Haitong International Technology Research.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/Oled-iPads-and-MackBook-Pro-Notch.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1403" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-824300" /><br/>
In a new investor memo seen by <em>MacRumors</em>, Pu said Apple intends to update the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with OLED screens sometime in 2026, which tallies with the timeframe previously predicted by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/04/macbook-pro-not-getting-oled-until-2026/">Ross Young of research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Pu also reiterated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">widely rumored</a> next-generation 11-inch and 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models launching in 2024 that will also be equipped with OLED displays, with Apple aiming to ship 10 million units in the first year. <br/>
<br/>
There are currently no Macs or iPads with OLED displays. Compared to current &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and MacBook Pro models with LCD-based mini-LED screens, benefits of OLED technology would include increased brightness, higher contrast ratio with deeper blacks, improved power efficiency for longer battery life, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Pu also said that Apple is actively developing an OLED screen for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, although the release of the OLED MacBook Pro is expected to come first. Previous reports have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/30/oled-macbook-air-now-in-development/">suggested</a> that Samsung Display is developing a 13.3-inch OLED panel for a future &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; model amid Apple's plans to switch several of its product lines to the display technology.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ipad-pro-macbook-pro-macbook-air-oled-launches/">OLED iPad Pros, MacBook Pros, MacBook Airs to Launch in That Order</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pros-macbook-pros-macbook-airs-to-launch-in-that-order.2410547/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>More UK Bank Cards Now Show Account Balance in Apple Wallet</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/more-uk-banks-show-account-balance-apple-wallet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-uk-bank-cards-now-show-account-balance-in-apple-wallet.2410543/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:45:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/more-uk-banks-show-account-balance-apple-wallet/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in iOS 17.1 began allowing ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>‌ users in the UK to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">view the account balances</a> of select bank cards and credit cards in the Wallet app, and now several more banks have added support for the feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/wallet-account-balance.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922103" /><br/>
Apple added the transaction and card balance functionality to the Wallet app in October as part of its Connected Cards feature, but initially only a handful of bank cards were compatible.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213903">updated support document</a>, account balance and full transaction history viewing now works with cards from Barclays, Barclaycard, First Direct, Halifax, HSBC, Lloyds, M&S Bank, Monzo Bank, NatWest Bank, and Royal Bank of Scotland.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">How to View UK Bank Account Balance in Apple Wallet</a></li></ul><br/>
UK banks support the Open Banking API to integrate with the Wallet app, which made the feature widely available to UK users from the off, but the Connected Cards rollout in the United States has been slower.<br/>
<br/>
Following the release of the feature, <em>MacRumors</em> discovered that code in iOS 17.1 and references on Apple's website suggested that the feature would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-wallet-connected-cards-feature-in-us/">expand to the US</a>, which turned out to be accurate. For example, users of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/">Discover cards</a> were first to see the option to view their total card balance and transaction history in Apple Wallet. <br/>
<br/>
Note that if you don't see the option to Get Started below your card in the Wallet app, your card issuer currently isn't eligible. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/more-uk-banks-show-account-balance-apple-wallet/">More UK Bank Cards Now Show Account Balance in Apple Wallet</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-uk-bank-cards-now-show-account-balance-in-apple-wallet.2410543/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Humane Debuts &#36;700 AI Pin With &#039;Laser Ink Display&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/humane-ai-pin/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/humane-debuts-700-ai-pin-with-laser-ink-display.2410525/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:17:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/humane-ai-pin/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Humane, a tech startup run by former Apple designer Imran Chaudhri, today officially unveiled its first product, <a href="https://hu.ma.ne/aipin">the Ai Pin</a>. Priced at &#36;700, the Ai Pin is a standalone device that Humane says was built from the ground up for artificial intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/humane-ai-pin-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922090" /><br/>
The Ai Pin attaches to a clothing item using a magnetic system that involves a detachable battery, which is also how the device is powered. The idea is to swap the battery out for a new battery when necessary, resulting in what Humane calls a "perpetual power system." It is not clear how long each battery lasts.<br/>
<br/>
Design wise, the Ai Pin looks something like an Apple Watch with a rounded rectangular shape, It is made from aluminum, comes in three colors, and has a Gorilla Glass touchpad. There's also an "optical sensing capsule," a 3D depth sensor, and a Qualcomm Snapdragon chip to power it.<br/>
<br/>
A laser projector inside the Ai Pin can project information onto the user's hand, and it is necessary because there is no standard display on the device itself. Humane calls the laser projector system a "Laser Ink Display." Interacting with the Laser Ink Display can be done by rolling and tilting the hand, and selecting an item is done with a finger tap similar to the tap used for Apple's own Double Tap feature on Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Touching the Ai Pin and speaking activates the "Ai Mic" that can answer questions and help users find information, including details they have previously relayed to the device, such as reminders. It plays music through a "Personic Speaker" that creates a bubble of sound around the wearer, plus there is an Interpreter feature. Humane says that the Ai Pin is "fluent in many languages" and can translate spoken words in real-time. There are no apps, with all actions and functions accessed through the AI.<br/>
<br/>
A built-in 13-megapixel ultra wide-angle camera can be used to capture photographs and videos, either using a two-finger double tap or a voice command. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> can be viewed using the "Center" website on any web browser. Center also houses notes that have been taken, music listened to, reminders, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/humane-ai-pin-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922091" /><br/>
Users can tell the Ai Pin about their activity and nutrition goals to keep tabs on their progress and better understand the energy they take in and put out. Holding up a food item to the Ai Pin will allow the device to provide nutritional information and can let a user know if it's "safe" to eat based on their health goals.<br/>
<br/>
The device has cellular connectivity and can be used to answer phone calls from trusted contacts that are designated by the wearer. Humane says the Ai Pin is able to intelligently determine what takes priority if an untrusted contact calls or sends a message, allowing interactions such as a food delivery person arriving with an order. Calls and text messages can be sent using the Ai Pin, with messages composed through voice requests.<br/>
<br/>
The Ai Pin cannot be activated without direct user interaction, so it is not listening or recording by default. When the camera, phone, or microphone are activated, there is a colored "Trust Light" that lets other people around the user know when the Ai Pin is in use.<br/>
<br/>
Orders for the Ai Pin are <a href="https://hu.ma.ne/aipin">set to begin</a> in the United States on November 16. Ai Pin is priced at &#36;700, and there is also a &#36;24 monthly subscription required to use the device on the Humane network, which is powered by T-Mobile.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/humane-ai-pin/">Humane Debuts &#36;700 AI Pin With &#039;Laser Ink Display&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/humane-debuts-700-ai-pin-with-laser-ink-display.2410525/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>App Store in iOS 17.2 Beta Features New Focus on Categories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-beta-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-in-ios-17-2-beta-features-new-focus-on-categories.2410515/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 16:38:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-beta-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is making some updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> with the iOS 17.2 software that is in beta testing, introducing a new focus on app categories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/app-store-categories.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922085" /><br/>
In the "Apps" section of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, there is a new top navigation bar that allows users to scroll through various app categories, such as Entertainment, Education, Photo &amp; Video, Music, Navigation, and more. The categories mirror the categories that can be found at the bottom of the app section in the "Browse Categories" menu.<br/>
<br/>
The "Games" section also has a similar list of categories, such as puzzle, casual, racing, indie, simulation, casino, and adventure. These also mirror the categories at the bottom of the Games tab.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping into one of the categories listed in Apps or Games shows apps that are part of that category. Apple previously had these kind of top bar navigation options for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, but they have been expanded to the other &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; sections.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">New in iOS 17.2: The AppStore now has a tab bar on top of the &quot;Apps&quot; and &quot;Games&quot; sections with different categories of apps. <br><br>Spotted by <a href="https://twitter.com/Johnthenormal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Johnthenormal</a> <a href="https://t.co/AuWqGYmCls">pic.twitter.com/AuWqGYmCls</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1722771032426070186?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 10, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple is also mirroring the "Browse Categories" design first introduced in the &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; tab. Each category is now a card, with a detailed icon. In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and earlier, categories were just text lists with a simpler icon design.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 is being beta tested right now and it is expected to see a public release sometime in December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-beta-app-store/">App Store in iOS 17.2 Beta Features New Focus on Categories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-store-in-ios-17-2-beta-features-new-focus-on-categories.2410515/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Likely to Use Modified iPhone 14 Chassis</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-modified-iphone-14-chassis.2410510/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:32:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>iPhone SE 4</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/">last in-depth report</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 4, <em>MacRumors</em> has received additional information which further confirms the claims made in our previous article. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/iphone-se-4-modified-flag-edges.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-886982" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, also known by the device identifier D59 and project codename Ghost, is a continuation of Apple’s budget-oriented line of iPhones, and is expected to replace the current third-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
With the arrival of the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;, Apple plans to finally retire the aging <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 8-style design used for the previous two generations of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;. Instead, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will feature a more modern look and increased display size, closely resembling the base model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Newly obtained specifications indicate the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will use a modified version of the existing &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; chassis, with the same flat design. The dimensions of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 in its current stage perfectly match those of the base model &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. Recent findings also confirm that the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will not include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> home button, instead featuring an all-screen design derived from the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> serving as the means of biometric identification.<br/>
<br/>
To better illustrate the size difference between the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 and the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; third-generation, we have included the dimensions for the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; dimensions and weight:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Length: 146.7 mm</li><br/>
<li>Width: 71.5 mm</li><br/>
<li>Thickness: 7.80 mm</li><br/>
<li>Weight: 172 g</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3 dimensions and weight:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Length: 138.4 mm</li><br/>
<li>Width: 67.3 mm</li><br/>
<li>Thickness: 7.3 mm</li><br/>
<li>Weight: 144 g</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is expected to be lighter than the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; by about 6 grams, weighing 165 grams. The change in weight is likely a result of the single-camera design Apple has planned for the device. Unlike the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will feature a single 48-megapixel rear camera, developed under the codename "Portland", with a custom backplate for the device to account for the design change.<br/>
<br/>
The decision to use a single-camera design lines up with all previous models of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;, with the flash located in a similar position as well. It’s worth emphasizing that there is significant evidence that backs up the single-camera design, with Apple’s internal documentation highlighting it as a key change from the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apart from the single-camera design, no other significant factors could impact the weight of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4. No changes in materials are expected, with the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; using the same 6013 T6 aluminum found in the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, along with a glass backplate. Prototypes of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 have been seen in a black color closely resembling the Midnight color variant available for the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, suggesting that black will be one of the color options Apple plans to offer with the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Although the chassis dimensions of the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 remain identical to that of the base model &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, the device will bring two significant features greatly differentiating it from previous &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models – a multi-purpose Action button and a USB-C port.<br/>
<br/>
The Action button is a user-configurable button located above the volume buttons, first introduced with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, where it replaces the mute switch. Current information suggests that Apple intends to make the Action button a standard feature across the entire <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> range, with it eventually being available on the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 as well. The current development status of the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; suggests a potential release date of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple is experimenting with an all-new capacitive Capture button for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; range, there are no indications that this feature is being tested on the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4. The Capture button is expected to remain exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
It is important to remember that the information presented here is pre-production information and may not reflect the hardware found on final mass production units, as changes are always possible during development.<br/>
<br/>
For more details on what to expect, c<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">heck out our guide for the iPhone SE 4</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">iPhone SE 4</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/">iPhone SE 4 Likely to Use Modified iPhone 14 Chassis</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-modified-iphone-14-chassis.2410510/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New &#039;Aliro&#039; Standard Aims to Simplify Unlocking Doors With Smartphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/aliro-smart-lock-standard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-aliro-standard-aims-to-simplify-unlocking-doors-with-smartphones.2410507/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 14:38:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/aliro-smart-lock-standard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Aliro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA), which includes Apple as a member, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/the-connectivity-standards-alliance-announces-aliro-a-new-effort-to-make-mobile-devices--wearables-central-to-a-digital-access-future-301982416.html">today introduced Aliro</a>, a new standard that is aimed at improving the way that smart door locks work with smartphones and wearables.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/aliro-smart-home.jpg" alt="" width="1536" height="861" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922075" /><br/>
Alliance members are working to develop a new communication protocol that will allow for interoperability between mobile devices, wearables, and access control readers. As with Matter, the idea is to have smart locks that are compatible with any smartphone or wearable device, without the need for an app.<br/>
<br/>
According to the CSA, the <a href="https://csa-iot.org/all-solutions/aliro/">goal for the Aliro protocol</a> is to "foster widespread adoption of consumer electronic devices to unlock doors and openings" by creating a consistent experience across certified hardware devices.<br/>
<blockquote>"As we've seen with the introduction of Matter, it's been proven that global collaboration around a shared mission along open standards is the best way to achieve broader adoption of new technology," explains Connectivity Standards Alliance President and CEO Tobin Richardson. "The Alliance and its members are now using that same model to unlock the potential of digital access experience, with the creation of a new standard and credential that makes adoption easier for mobile device and access control reader companies."</blockquote><br/>
Aliro would be a common communication protocol and credential that would make it much simpler to get a digital key for a smart lock and unlock a door using a wearable or smartphone. The CSA says that it will have a "lasting impact" on the way that people access homes, corporate offices, warehouses, hotel rooms, healthcare facilities, universities, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Aliro will support a wide range of transmission technologies, including NFC, Bluetooth LE, and Ultra Wideband, along with asymmetric cryptography and credential data. It is meant to work the same way across devices regardless of hardware and operating system.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is an Aliro member, and it already has some of the groundwork for the functionality as it is described by the CSA. The CSA suggests that people will be able to use smartphones and wearables to unlock their homes in place of a physical key, something that Apple supports with Home Key already. Home Key allows a digital key to be added to the Wallet app to unlock a HomeKit-compatible door over NFC without opening an app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple, Google, Qualcomm, Samsung, and other CSA members support the Aliro effort.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aliro/">Aliro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/aliro-smart-lock-standard/">New &#039;Aliro&#039; Standard Aims to Simplify Unlocking Doors With Smartphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-aliro-standard-aims-to-simplify-unlocking-doors-with-smartphones.2410507/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b32/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2410493/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:37:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b32/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced a new firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, including both the Lightning model and the new USB-C model. The new firmware is version 6B32, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/apple-releases-airpods-pro-2-firmware-update/">6A305 firmware</a> introduced in October.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not provide details on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware, so it is unclear what's new in the update, but prior software releases have been refining functionality introduced in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; added several new features for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2, such as Adaptive Audio. Adaptive Audio, which combines ANC and Transparency, is meant to deliver an ideal audio experience that blocks out loud or distracting noises.<br/>
<br/>
Adaptive Audio includes Conversation Awareness and Personalized Volume. Conversation Awareness detects when someone speaks to you, lowering the volume of what's playing and cutting down on background noise so you can hear. Personalized Volume takes into account your listening preferences and the noise in the environment to adjust sound levels.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include an option to mute and unmute the microphone by pressing on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; stem, faster automatic switching between devices, and support for activating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> without including the "Hey" wake word.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not offer instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌AirPods‌‌ or ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the firmware release, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b32/">Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2410493/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 to Expand Sensitive Content Warnings on iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-expands-sensitive-content-warnings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-to-expand-sensitive-content-warnings-on-iphone.2410492/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:36:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-expands-sensitive-content-warnings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with iOS 17.2, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/">currently in beta</a> and is expected to be released in December, Apple's opt-in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-enable-sensitive-content-warnings/">Sensitive Content Warning feature</a> will work with Contact Posters in both the Contacts and Phone apps, as well as stickers in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Sensitive-Content-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922023" /><br/>
When turned on, the Sensitive Content Warning feature uses on-device machine learning to analyze photos and videos, and blurs photos or videos with any detected nudity before users view them. Apple says it does not receive any indication that nudity was detected, and does not gain access to the photos or videos as a result.<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-enable-sensitive-content-warnings/">iOS 17: How to Enable Sensitive Content Warnings</a></li></ul>Sensitive Content Warnings are also available for messages in the Messages app, AirDrop transfers, and FaceTime video messages. The feature launched earlier this year across the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Watch. Apple has offered a similar <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-or-disable-communication-safety-ios/">Communication Safety feature for children</a> across the same devices since 2021.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-expands-sensitive-content-warnings/">iOS 17.2 to Expand Sensitive Content Warnings on iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-to-expand-sensitive-content-warnings-on-iphone.2410492/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Beta 2 Includes Feature for Recording Spatial Video on iPhone 15 Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-spatial-video-recording/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-2-includes-feature-for-recording-spatial-video-on-iphone-15-pro.2410484/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:42:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-spatial-video-recording/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The second beta of iOS 17.2 adds a new feature that allows an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max to record Spatial Video that can be viewed in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app on Apple's forthcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
Spatial Video recording can be enabled by going to the Settings app, tapping into the Camera section, selecting Formats, and toggling on "Spatial Video for &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="es" dir="ltr">iOS 17.2 Beta 2 enables Spatial Video recording <a href="https://t.co/mLMbI8aG6d">pic.twitter.com/mLMbI8aG6d</a></p>&mdash; iSoftware Updates (@iSWUpdates) <a href="https://twitter.com/iSWUpdates/status/1722684032796733923?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 9, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple says that for best results when recording Spatial Video, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> should be held stable in landscape orientation while capturing video. Video is recorded at 30 frames per second at 1080p, and one minute of video takes up 130MB of storage space.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial Videos taken with an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; can be viewed on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as well, but the video appears to be a normal video and not a Spatial Video. Spatial Videos feature a "Spatial" label to denote that they can be viewed in 3D on the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
On the Vision Pro headset, Spatial Videos are not shown full screen by default. If you expand the video, Apple warns that the video "has excess motion" and "could cause discomfort if expanded."<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-spatial-video-recording/">iOS 17.2 Beta 2 Includes Feature for Recording Spatial Video on iPhone 15 Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-2-includes-feature-for-recording-spatial-video-on-iphone-15-pro.2410484/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2-to-developers.2410481/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:17:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming two weeks after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-1/">first beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the Sonoma Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 adds an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> Favorites playlist that houses everything you've favorited, plus Apple added support for collaborative playlists. You can now share a playlist with multiple people, and each participant can add songs. <br/>
<br/>
Stickers can now be used to reply to iMessages when you long press on a chat bubble in the Messages app, and there's also now support for the extra-secure iMessage Contact Key Verification option.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2-to-developers.2410481/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2-to-developers.2410472/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:03:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming two weeks after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-ios-17-1/">first betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918852" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Cool.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The biggest new feature in iOS 17.2 is the Journal app, which can be used to record daily activities and thoughts. You can write about your day to day life, but Apple also provides topic suggestions based on the music you listen to, the places you visit, and the people you see. Journal entries support pictures, voice recordings, and location information, with the app organized by entry date.<br/>
<br/>
In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, there's a Favorites playlist that houses everything you've favorited, plus Apple added support for collaborative playlists. You can now share a playlist with multiple people, and each participant can add songs.<br/>
<br/>
Stickers can now be used to reply to iMessages when you long press on a chat bubble in the Messages app, and there's also now support for the extra-secure iMessage Contact Key Verification option. If you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, the Action Button supports Translate in iOS 17.2, and there are new Weather and Clock widgets.<br/>
<br/>
More on what's new in iOS 17.2 can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.2 beta 1 features list</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2-to-developers.2410472/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of watchOS 10.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-watchos-10-2-to-developers.2410476/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:02:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.2 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming two weeks after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-1-to-developers/">first watchOS 10.2 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.2‌ update, developers will need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, ‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌ can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.2 adds support for iMessage Contact Key Verification, a feature designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials.<br/>
<br/>
Users can ensure that there is no "man in the middle" snooping on iMessage conversations, and there is a Contact Verification Code so that iMessage users can verify that they're speaking to the correct individual during in-person meetings or on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of watchOS 10.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-watchos-10-2-to-developers.2410476/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of tvOS 17.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-2-to-developers.2410477/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:01:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.2 to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-17-2-to-developers/">release of the first tvOS 17.2 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.2 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes, but tvOS 17.2 introduces an overhauled &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app. <br/>
<br/>
The app now includes a sidebar that houses content from both Apple's services and streaming services that integrate with the tvOS Watch Now feature. There are dedicated sections for Search, Watch Now, ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>‌, MLS Season Pass, Sports, the Store, and the Library at the top of the sidebar, along with dedicated sections for streaming services like ABC, CBS, Comedy Central, Hulu, ESPN, Discovery, Peacock, Prime Video, and more.<br/>
<br/>
You can click into each streaming service to see content that's available specifically on that service, and there's also a new My TV section that replaces "My Channels."<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of tvOS 17.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-2-to-developers.2410477/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Black Friday Deal Sees Series 9 Drop to Record Low &#36;349 Price</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-watch-black-friday-deal-sees-series-9/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-black-friday-deal-sees-series-9-drop-to-record-low-349-price.2410450/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 07:30:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-watch-black-friday-deal-sees-series-9/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon has nearly every model of the Aluminum Apple Watch Series 9 on sale at new record low prices in one of the first best Black Friday deals of the season. You can get the 41mm GPS model of the brand new smartwatch for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;399.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-series-9-candy-canes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921455" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple launched the Series 9 models back in September, and since then the steepest discounts have been about &#36;10-20. This makes Amazon's sale today a notable markdown and definitely one of the overall best seen so far during Black Friday 2023. It's available in all five Aluminum models, as well as in both S/M and M/L fits.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Likewise, Amazon has the 45mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;379.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;429.00. It's also available in all five Aluminum color options, both S/M and M/L fits, and this is another record low price on the smartwatch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Cellular Apple Watch Series 9 deals are just as abundant on Amazon right now. You can get the 41mm Cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.00</strong></a> and the 45mm Cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;479.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;50 discounts and all-time low prices. You'll again find all five Aluminum options on sale at these prices, as well as multiple size options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;479.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're starting your holiday shopping this week, we've got you covered with guides for the best early Black Friday deals for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">HomePod</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">iPad</a>. We've also been keeping an eye on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">best overall Apple deals</a> in the lead-up to November 24. All of these guides will be updated as the month continues, so be sure to bookmark and revisit to stay up-to-date on the best prices for the products you have an eye on.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, we're tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories, so it's another good resource for your online holiday shopping.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-watch-black-friday-deal-sees-series-9/">Apple Watch Black Friday Deal Sees Series 9 Drop to Record Low &#36;349 Price</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-black-friday-deal-sees-series-9-drop-to-record-low-349-price.2410450/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>3D Movies Appear in Apple TV App Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/3d-movies-appear-in-apple-tv-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/3d-movies-appear-in-apple-tv-app-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2410444/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 06:57:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/3d-movies-appear-in-apple-tv-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[3D content has begun appearing in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app ahead of next year's Vision Pro headset launch (via <em><a href="https://www.flatpanelshd.com/news.php?subaction=showfull&id=1699434273">FlatPanelsHD</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/3d-movies-apple-tv-app.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1443" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-921969" /><em>Screenshot of the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; showing the new 3D content icon (via <a href="https://www.flatpanelshd.com/news.php?subaction=showfull&id=1699434273">FlatPanelsHD</a>).</em></div><br/>
tvOS 17.2's redesigned &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app shows a large selection of movies with a small 3D icon that resembles a headset alongside other icons for the likes of Dolby Atmos and 4K. Since the movies are unplayable in 3D via the TV app without a Vision Pro headset, it is currently unclear what resolution and frame rate they play in. 3D titles seen in the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app include <em>Jurassic World Dominion</em>, <em>Pacific Rim Uprising</em>, <em>Shrek</em>, <em>Trolls</em>, <em>Warcraft</em>, <em>Minions: The Rise of Gru</em>, <em>Mortal Engines</em>, <em>Everest</em>, <em>Kung Fu Panda 3</em>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">This 3D icon is live in the Apple TV app. <a href="https://t.co/EEKPRDVphx">https://t.co/EEKPRDVphx</a> <a href="https://t.co/PFvCiyj78B">https://t.co/PFvCiyj78B</a></p>&mdash; Steve Moser (@SteveMoser) <a href="https://twitter.com/SteveMoser/status/1722631501890900357?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 9, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple showcased a 3D version of <em>Avatar: The Way of Water</em> to demonstrate some of the entertainment capabilities of the Vision Pro headset when it was unveiled in June and touted the ability to play 2D, 3D, and "immersive" movies on the device, including in a virtual cinema. Apple is also expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/12/apple-tv-monsterverse-spatial-video-vision-pro/">offer Apple TV+ content</a> in a new, immersive 3D video format, including <em>Monarch: Legacy of Monsters</em>. The Vision Pro headset launches early next year. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/3d-movies-appear-in-apple-tv-app/">3D Movies Appear in Apple TV App Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/3d-movies-appear-in-apple-tv-app-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2410444/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Increases Trade-In Values for Select iPads and Apple Watches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-increases-ipad-apple-watch-trade-in-values/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-increases-trade-in-values-for-select-ipads-and-apple-watches.2410442/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 06:35:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-increases-ipad-apple-watch-trade-in-values/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Trade-In</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Wednesday increased its estimated <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">trade-in values</a> for select iPad and Apple Watch models in the U.S., according to the company's website.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPad-Pro-and-Apple-Watch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921972" /><br/>
Apple increased trade-in values for the iPad Pro, iPad Air, entry-level iPad, Apple Watch Ultra, and Apple Watch Series 7, which could incentivize customers to upgrade these devices heading into the holiday shopping season. Trade-in values for iPhones, Macs, and other iPad and Apple Watch models did not change at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's trade-in changes are outlined below:<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Device</th><br/>
 <th>Current Trade-In Value</th><br/>
 <th>Previous Trade-In Value</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">iPad Pro</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;580</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;510</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">iPad Air</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;325</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;315</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">iPad</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;260</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;170</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Ultra</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;425</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;380</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 7</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;160</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;155</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div>Apple also adjusted trade-in values for select Android smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
Trade-ins can be completed on Apple's website or at an Apple Store, and the credit can be applied to the purchase of a new Apple product or placed on an Apple gift card for later use. <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">Apple's trade-in page</a> offers a complete list of values for devices.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-trade-in/">Apple Trade-In</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-increases-ipad-apple-watch-trade-in-values/">Apple Increases Trade-In Values for Select iPads and Apple Watches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-increases-trade-in-values-for-select-ipads-and-apple-watches.2410442/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Signal Tests Sharing Public Usernames in Place of Phone Numbers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/signal-private-messenger-tests-usernames/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/signal-tests-sharing-public-usernames-in-place-of-phone-numbers.2410432/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:25:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/signal-private-messenger-tests-usernames/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>Signal</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Encrypted messaging app <a href="https://signal.org">Signal</a> has <a href="https://community.signalusers.org/t/public-username-testing-staging-environment/56866">announced</a> it is testing public account usernames so that users don't have to share their phone number to connect through the service.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/signal-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921884" /><br/>
Currently, signing up to Signal requires that you share your phone number with other users when connecting with them. While the new method still requires an account to be associated with a number during setup, it is not subsequently shared when contacting other users, making the communication even more private and secure. <br/>
<br/>
According to Signal VP of engineering Jim O'Leary, the username test is currently limited to a separate build in the platform's Staging Environment and remains "pre-beta," so it may cause crashes and other bugs to occur since it fundamentally changes the way that accounts are identified in the Signal ecosystem. <br/>
<br/>
Users who install the build will be able to share their usernames via a QR code or a link, allowing them to use it as a way for others to contact them, no phone number required. There is also an option to turn off phone number discovery in the app under Settings ➝ Privacy ➝ Phone number ➝ Who can find my number.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Signal is testing username feature. This would mean that you would not have to provide your phone number to people you want to contact. You will be able to set your phone number as private and not share it. <a href="https://t.co/OUI2S8dEtp">pic.twitter.com/OUI2S8dEtp</a></p>&mdash; Lukasz Olejnik, Ph.D, LL.M (@lukOlejnik) <a href="https://twitter.com/lukOlejnik/status/1722349114304708669?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 8, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Signal has been working on usernames since at least 2019, but it is not known when the feature will be ready for primetime. Using the pre-beta build on desktop and iOS today requires some technical knowhow involving code compiling, more information about which can be found in the <a href="https://community.signalusers.org/t/public-username-testing-staging-environment/56866">Signal forums</a>. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/signal/">Signal</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/signal-private-messenger-tests-usernames/">Signal Tests Sharing Public Usernames in Place of Phone Numbers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/signal-tests-sharing-public-usernames-in-place-of-phone-numbers.2410432/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Could Pay &#039;Total Political Crap&#039; &#36;14 Billion Tax Bill to EU After All</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-could-pay-ireland-eu-tax-dispute/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-could-pay-total-political-crap-14-billion-tax-bill-to-eu-after-all.2410427/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 04:39:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-could-pay-ireland-eu-tax-dispute/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple-Ireland Tax Case</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has suffered a setback in its €13 billion (&#36;14 billion) tax dispute with Brussels after an advisor to the EU's highest court said the company's victory in an earlier ruling should be thrown out (via <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/db2e63a1-9972-444f-9ae3-70bec32b020b">Financial Times</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
Giovanni Pitruzzella, advocate-general of the European Court of Justice (ECJ), said on Thursday that Apple's win in the EU General Court "should be set aside" because it is riddled with mistakes.<br/>
<br/>
While such opinions by advocates-general are non-binding, the top EU tribunal follows such advice in the majority of cases, and it is set to issue its binding ruling in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
In 2020, the General Court said it supported the EU's right to investigate national tax arrangements, but it ultimately overturned a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/08/30/apple-repay-14-5-billion-back-taxes-ec-rules/">ruling</a> by the European Commission stating that Apple should pay €13 billion euros in tax to the Irish government. <br/>
<br/>
Following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/09/16/luca-maestri-to-challenge-apple-irish-tax-ruling/">Apple's appeal</a>, the EU's second-highest court said the EU authority, led by antitrust chief Margrethe Vestager, had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/07/15/apple-wins-euro-tax-bill-court-appeal/">failed to show</a> that Apple had received an illegal economic advantage in Ireland over tax.<br/>
<br/>
Four years earlier, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> called the EC's original decision "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/09/01/tim-cook-tax-total-political-crap/">total political crap</a>" and said that Apple believed it would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/08/30/tim-cook-open-letter-tax-evasion/">reversed</a>. "The decision is wrong, and it's not based on law or facts, it's based on politics. And I think it's very important that we stand up and say that very loudly," said Cook at the time.<br/>
<br/>
However, Pitruzzella said on Thursday the General Court ruling had "committed a series of errors" and "failed to assess correctly the substance and consequences of certain methodological errors." Pitruzzella said the court needed "to carry out a new assessment" as a result.<br/>
<br/>
Responding to the opinion of the advocates-general, Apple said on Thursday that the lower court "was very clear that Apple received no selective advantage and no State aid, and we believe that should be upheld."<br/>
<br/>
An ECJ ruling is expected next year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ireland-tax-case/">Apple-Ireland Tax Case</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-could-pay-ireland-eu-tax-dispute/">Apple Could Pay &#039;Total Political Crap&#039; &#36;14 Billion Tax Bill to EU After All</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-could-pay-total-political-crap-14-billion-tax-bill-to-eu-after-all.2410427/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Likely to Get Exclusive AI Features in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-likely-to-get-exclusive-ai-features-in-ios-18.2410420/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:31:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Revegnus</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple at WWDC 2024 will reveal a turbo-charged version of Siri powered by large language models (LLMs) that will debut in iOS 18, but some new cutting-edge generative AI features could be exclusive to iPhone 16 models, according to a new rumor.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
Last month, <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman revealed that Apple is developing a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">large array of features that use generative AI</a>, including a "smarter version of Siri" and new LLM-based AI features that will be baked into iOS 18 and iPadOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said Apple was still debating whether to limit generative AI to on-device processing, deploy it via the cloud, or adopt a hybrid approach combining the two. It was not mentioned either way whether some AI features would require specific hardware architecture or trickle down to all models capable of running iOS 18. <br/>
<br/>
However, according to new information independently shared by the leaker <a href="https://x.com/Tech_Reve/status/1722418466647625999?s=20">@Tech_Reve</a>, iOS 18 will bring the company's new LLM to millions of existing devices by using cloud-based AI, while new on-device AI features will likely remain exclusive to the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of iOS 18 features, Gurman's sources mention a revamped interaction between ‌Siri‌ and the Messages app, enabling users to field complex questions and auto-complete sentences more effectively. We may also see auto-generated Apple Music playlists and integration with productivity apps like Pages and Keynote, such as AI-assisted writing and slide deck creation. Where this patina of AI integration crosses over into new hardware requirements is still unknown.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is designing new A-series chips for the iPhone 16 lineup, built on TSMC's latest N3E 3-nanometer node. Efficiency and performance improvements are of course expected, but there could be other benefits that feed into Apple's AI intentions. Notably, TSMC is the sole manufacturer for Nvidia's powerful H100 and A100 AI processors, the hardware that powers AI tools like ChatGPT and which also comprises the majority of AI data centers.<br/>
<br/>
All models in the iPhone 16 series are also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/iphone-16-extra-button-rumor/">rumored to have an extra button</a> that we don't know the purpose of yet. Internal versions of the iPhone 16 that Apple is working on include an extra capacitive button, known internally as the "Capture Button." <br/>
<br/>
The button is located on the same side as the Power button, and is a capacitive button that is able to detect pressure and touch, providing haptic feedback when pressed. There has been no word yet on what this button might be used for, but it could conceivably have unforeseen practical AI applications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to be on course to spend &#36;1 billion per year on AI research, with some of the company's biggest executive names overseeing development, including senior vice president of software engineering Craig Federighi, senior vice president of machine learning and AI strategy John Giannandrea, and senior vice president of services Eddy Cue.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/revegnus/">Revegnus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/">iPhone 16 Likely to Get Exclusive AI Features in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-likely-to-get-exclusive-ai-features-in-ios-18.2410420/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
