<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:02:30 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Air Models Now Arriving to Customers in New Zealand and Australia</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/m3-macbook-air-new-zealand-australia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-models-now-arriving-to-customers-in-new-zealand-and-australia.2421330/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:10:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/m3-macbook-air-new-zealand-australia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It is Friday, March 8 in New Zealand and Australia, which means customers who pre-ordered one of the new machines in those two countries are receiving their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><br/>
Introduced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">on Monday of this week</a>, the updated 13.6-inch and 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are equipped with the same M3 chip that was introduced in the MacBook Pro late last year.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer's Guide: All Differences Compared</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There are no external changes to the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, with Apple instead focusing on internal updates. The M3 chip is up to 30 percent faster than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip in terms of CPU performance, and there are notable GPU improvements with Apple adding support for Dynamic Caching, hardware-accelerated ray tracing, hardware-accelerated mesh shading, and support for AV1 decode.<br/>
<br/>
Other improvements to the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; include support for two external displays when the machine is used in clamshell mode, support for Wi-Fi 6E, enhanced voice clarity for audio and video calls, and a new anodization seal to reduce fingerprints on the Midnight finish.<br/>
<br/>
Apple retail stores in Australia are selling the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; machines, and there is plenty of stock for walk-in customers. Apple does not operate stores in New Zealand, so customers in that country need to order online.<br/>
<br/>
Following New Zealand and Australia, sales and deliveries of the new ‌&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models will launch in Asia, the Middle East, Europe, and finally, North America.<br/>
<br/>
We'll be sharing a hands-on review of the new M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; in the morning after picking up one of the new devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/m3-macbook-air-new-zealand-australia/">M3 MacBook Air Models Now Arriving to Customers in New Zealand and Australia</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-models-now-arriving-to-customers-in-new-zealand-and-australia.2421330/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New M3 MacBook Air Models to Have Day-One macOS Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/macbook-air-day-one-macos-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-m3-macbook-air-models-to-have-day-one-macos-update.2421325/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:16:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/macbook-air-day-one-macos-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models that are set to be released tomorrow will have a day-one update, according to <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937843" /><br/>
Both the 13.6-inch and 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models that are set to launch tomorrow are running a special build of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3, with a version number of 23D2057.<br/>
<br/>
Users will be prompted to update to &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 tomorrow, as the software saw a public release today. Given the timing of the software's launch and the debut of the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, Apple was not able to get the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 update installed on them.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are priced starting at &#36;1099 for the 13-inch version and &#36;1299 for the 15-inch version. Customers who pre-ordered will receive their machines on March 8, which is also when the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models will be available in Apple retail locations.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/macbook-air-day-one-macos-update/">New M3 MacBook Air Models to Have Day-One macOS Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-m3-macbook-air-models-to-have-day-one-macos-update.2421325/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Developing New Accessibility Features for iOS 18 and macOS 15</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/ios-18-macos-15-accessibility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developing-new-accessibility-features-for-ios-18-and-macos-15.2421321/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:32:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/ios-18-macos-15-accessibility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Accessibility</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With every operating system release, Apple aims to make apps more accessible and easier to navigate by providing a variety of new accessibility features and settings. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> (Codename Crystal) and macOS 15 (Codename Glow) will be no exception, and work on accessibility-related enhancements is well underway.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-18-Roundup-Article.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-924585" /><br/>
Through our industry sources, <em>MacRumors</em> has obtained information on some of the key accessibility improvements Apple has in store for its userbase. Apple is working on several new accessibility features along with improvements to existing settings, both of which should be available later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Adaptive Voice Shortcuts</h2><br/>
This feature will allow users to map a unique spoken phrase to an accessibility setting. Users will be given the option to create a custom phrase and select the accessibility setting they wish to toggle by speaking said phrase. By using Adaptive Voice Shortcuts, users will be able to toggle existing accessibility features such as VoiceOver, Voice Control, Zoom and so on.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New "Categories" Section for Live Speech</h2><br/>
The Live Speech feature, which is already present in Apple's operating systems, will receive a new section for user-created categories. Users will be able to organize phrases into categories of their choosing. When creating a category, users will be given the option to name their category and choose from a selection of around 20 different icons. Once a category has been created, users will then be able to add their desired phrases.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Apps Will Support Custom Font Sizes</h2><br/>
Apple intends to expand app support for adjustable Text Size, which is an existing feature. Located within the "Display" section of the "Accessibility" settings pane, the option allows users to choose custom font sizes for individual apps and select their preferred font size for reading.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> currently supports custom font sizes for the following five apps:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Calendar<br/>
<li>Finder<br/>
<li>Mail<br/>
<li>Messages<br/>
<li>Notes</ul><br/>
<br/>
With macOS 15, this feature will expand support to five additional apps:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Books<br/>
<li>News<br/>
<li>Stocks<br/>
<li>Tips<br/>
<li>Weather</ul><br/>
<br/>
Speaking to <em>MacRumors</em>, sources familiar with custom font sizes have said that Apple is internally testing an option to alter the font size of the menu bar within macOS, but it is unclear if the company will make this option available to end users. We were also told that Apple has additional accessibility features in the works, one of which utilizes on-device eye tracking, though further details were not available at the time of writing. More information should come to light as OS development continues in preparation for WWDC 2024.<br/>
<br/>
It is important to note that while these features are in development, it does not necessarily mean we will see them later this year. Apple has been known to cancel various projects that do not meet their standards, for one reason or another. For additional information on what to expect with this year's new OS releases, check out our dedicated rumor roundup for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/accessibility/">Accessibility</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/ios-18-macos-15-accessibility/">Apple Developing New Accessibility Features for iOS 18 and macOS 15</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developing-new-accessibility-features-for-ios-18-and-macos-15.2421321/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Let EU iPhone Users Delete Safari and More Easily Transition to Android</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-eu-safari-android-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-let-eu-iphone-users-delete-safari-and-more-easily-transition-to-android.2421315/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:42:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-eu-safari-android-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to adding support for alternative app marketplaces and alternative payment methods in the European Union, Apple is making several other changes to comply with the terms of the Digital Markets Act. Apple today outlined some of its upcoming plans in a DMA Compliance Report [<a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/dma/dma-ncs.pdf">PDF</a>].<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/transfer-to-android.jpg" alt="" width="1240" height="698" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940141" /><br/>
Apple is going to make it easier for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users to switch over to another operating system in the European Union. Apple says it is working on a solution that will help mobile operating system providers create "more user-friendly solutions" for transferring data from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to a non-Apple phone. The solution will be available by fall 2025, after which point companies like Samsung and Google will be able to offer better tools for transferring data from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
EU &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will be able to remove Safari from their devices entirely starting at the end of 2024, with an alternate browser able to take the place of Safari. As part of this plan, Apple is developing a browser switching solution for exporting and importing browser data into another browser on the same device. Apple has already began supporting alternative web browser engines, another DMA requirement.<br/>
<br/>
To improve interoperability between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and other smartphone platforms, Apple is allowing third-party payment apps to access the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s NFC chip for contactless payments that are not done through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, plus it is allowing developers to submit requests for additional interoperability.<br/>
<br/>
Interoperability requests are evaluated on a case-by-case basis to determine whether they are under the scope of the DMA, and if an effective interoperability solution can be developed.<br/>
<br/>
Developers in the EU are able to <a href="https://www.cedr.com">request additional mediation</a> that goes beyond the standard App Review Board evaluation. Developers who want to contest unsuccessful appeals to the App Review Board can request mediation, a process that Apple says is "EU-based, easily accessible, impartial, independent, and free-of-charge."<br/>
<br/>
All of these changes are limited to developers and users in the European Union as they are required by the Digital Markets Act.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-eu-safari-android-changes/">Apple to Let EU iPhone Users Delete Safari and More Easily Transition to Android</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-let-eu-iphone-users-delete-safari-and-more-easily-transition-to-android.2421315/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4.2421310/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:14:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4, the fourth major update to the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that launched last September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 comes over a month after &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3, an update that brought collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" /><br/>
The ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌‌ 14.4‌ update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings. There's also a macOS 13.6.5 release for those who are still running macOS Ventura and a macOS 12.7.4 release for those who have macOS Monterey installed.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4, Apple is introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/">new emoji characters</a> and adding support for reading Podcast Episode text in full with search support. There are new features for Business Updates in Messages, along with a toggle for showing only icons for websites in the Safari Favorites Bar. Apple's release notes for the update are below. <blockquote>macOS Sonoma 14.4 introduces new emoji as well as other features, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Emoji</strong><br/>
- New mushroom, phoenix, lime, broken chain, and shaking heads emoji are now available in emoji keyboard<br/>
- 18 people and body emoji support facing the opposite direction<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update also includes the following improvements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Podcasts Episode text can be read in full, searched for a word or phrase, clicked to play from a specific point and used with accessibility features such as Text Size, Increase Contrast, and VoiceOver<br/>
- Business Updates in Messages for Business let you get updates that you've opted into, like order status, flight notifications, fraud alerts or other transactions from trusted businesses<br/>
- Safari Favorites Bar adds an option to show only icons for websites<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>More information on the features that have been introduced in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; to date can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">found in our macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4.2421310/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 10.4 With Fix for Ghost Touch Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-4-with-fix-for-ghost-touch-bug.2421309/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:13:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.4, the fourth update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-watchos-10/">released in September</a>. watchOS 10.4 comes over a month after watchOS 10.3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-watchos-10-3/">a minor update</a> that brought a new watch face.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌‌.4 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later by opening it up and going to General &amp; Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.4 adds support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/">new emoji characters</a> that were also added to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, including lime, edible brown mushroom, phoenix, broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
There is also a Setting to disable the Double Tap feature on Apple Watch when using Vision Pro, and an option to double tap to show an expanded notification. Apple also included a fix for a bug that could cause some users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-touch-screen-issue/">experience "ghost touches" on the display</a>, a problem that was affecting the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's release notes for the update are below:<blockquote>watchOS 10.4 includes new features, improvements, and bug fixes, including:<br/>
- Tap to Show Full Notification setting now allows you to double tap to expand the notification<br/>
- Using Apple Pay with Confirm with AssistiveTouch will require a passcode for additional security and will not support double clicking the side button<br/>
- Resolves an issue that causes some users to experience false touches on the display<br/>
- Fixes an issue that prevents contacts from syncing to Apple Watch for some users<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote><br/>
More on the features that have been added in &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; to date can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">found in our dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-4/">Apple Releases watchOS 10.4 With Fix for Ghost Touch Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-4-with-fix-for-ghost-touch-bug.2421309/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases HomePod Software 17.4 With Music Preference Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4-with-music-preference-update.2421308/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:13:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new software for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, debuting &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; Software 17.4. The update comes over a month after the last &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-Midnight-Closeup-Feature-Purple-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-881769" /><br/>
With &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; Software 17.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is able to learn what a user's preferred media service is, eliminating the need to set a third-party app as the default or include an app name when asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to play content.<blockquote>This update enables Siri to learn your preferred media service, so you no longer need to include the name of the media app in your request.</blockquote>Apple has removed the Home app option that let users select a default media service as a result of the new feature addition. The change brings the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; in line with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, which already offer the option to provide a default music service selection to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; when making a song request for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party apps that work directly with the ‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌ include YouTube Music, Deezer, Pandora, TuneIn, and iHeartRadio. Streaming music services need to support ‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌ for the feature to work, and not all do, such as Spotify. You can play Spotify content on the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; by asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, but it routes the song through the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Along with ‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌ support for a preferred music service, the ‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌ 17.4 update also includes performance and stability improvements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/">Apple Releases HomePod Software 17.4 With Music Preference Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4-with-music-preference-update.2421308/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases visionOS 1.1 With Improvements to Persona, EyeSight, Virtual Keyboard and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-visionos-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-with-improvements-to-persona-eyesight-virtual-keyboard-and-more.2421306/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:08:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-visionos-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1, marking the first major update to the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; operating system that was launched <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">alongside the Vision Pro</a> in February.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; updates can be installed by going to the Settings app on the Vision Pro, selecting the General section, and choosing Software Update. The Vision Pro headset will need to be removed to install new software, with a progress bar available on the front EyeSight display.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is making several improvements to the Vision Pro with the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; update. Mobile Device Management is available for businesses, and Persona and EyeSight look better than before.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Vision Pro Persona FIXED in visionOS 1.1?" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xEixxDkYXlo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The virtual keyboard has been updated to address bugs and make cursor positioning more accurate, and there are also bug fixes for the Mac Virtual Display. Apple's release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote><strong>Mobile Device Management</strong><br/>
- Enables account-driven device and user enrollment using Managed Apple IDs<br/>
- Support for device configuration (Wi-Fi, VPN, email accounts, single sign-on, and more)<br/>
- Support for deploying apps in volume including iPhone and iPad compatible apps, visionOS apps included in a Universal purchase, and proprietary in-house visionOS apps<br/>
- Support for remote erase via MDM and device inventory data<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Messages</strong><br/>
- Adds support for iMessage Contact Key Verification<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>
- Closed captions can be anchored to the playback control while viewing Apple Immersive Video<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Persona (beta) and EyeSight</strong><br/>
- Adds an option to enroll your Persona hands-free<br/>
- Improves hair and makeup appearance<br/>
- Improves neck and mouth representation<br/>
- Improves rendering of the eyes for EyeSight<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Virtual keyboard</strong><br/>
- Cursor positioning for text input is now more accurate<br/>
- Resolves some instances where the virtual keyboard placement obscures the text input field<br/>
- Fixes an issue where in some cases, the text preview on the virtual keyboard may appear out of sync with the text field in the app<br/>
- Fixes an issue where the edit menu may appear unexpectedly<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Mac Virtual Display</strong><br/>
- Improves the reliability of discovering and connecting to a Mac using Mac Virtual Display<br/>
- Resolves an issue where Universal Control may stop working<br/>
- Addresses a connectivity issue that occurs when a previously paired Bluetooth device cannot be found<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Captive Network Support</strong><br/>
- Ability to set up your device while using a captive WiFi network such as those found at hotels, cafes and airports<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website:<br/>
https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote><br/>
The first year of the Vision Pro will see plenty of feature refinements, so expect quite a few more updates. Apple is also already working on &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 2, which will be previewed in June.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-visionos-1-1/">Apple Releases visionOS 1.1 With Improvements to Persona, EyeSight, Virtual Keyboard and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-with-improvements-to-persona-eyesight-virtual-keyboard-and-more.2421306/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases tvOS 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-tvos-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-tvos-17-4.2421307/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:06:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-tvos-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released tvOS 17.4, the fourth major update to the tvOS 17 operating system that came out last September. tvOS 17.4 comes over a month after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-tvos-17-3/">release of tvOS 17.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/apple-tv-4k-red-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850424" /><br/>
tvOS 17.4 can be downloaded using the Settings app on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>‌. Go to System &gt; Software Update to get the new software. ‌&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;‌ owners who have automatic software updates activated will be upgraded to tvOS 17.4 automatically.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to other operating system updates, tvOS 17.4 updates are often minor in scale, focusing on bug fixes and other small improvements. We did not find new features during the tvOS 17.4 beta testing process.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares release notes for tvOS <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106336">in its tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each new version of tvOS comes out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-tvos-17-4/">Apple Releases tvOS 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-tvos-17-4.2421307/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS Apps From Alternative Marketplaces Can Be Updated for 30 Days Outside of EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/alternative-apps-30-day-update-period/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-apps-from-alternative-marketplaces-can-be-updated-for-30-days-outside-of-eu.2421304/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:46:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/alternative-apps-30-day-update-period/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Europe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/118110">today clarified</a> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in the European Union can continue to update and use apps from alternative app marketplaces for a 30-day period when leaving the EU.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
With the release of iOS 17.4, Apple published a number of support documents, and one of the pages <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/alternative-ios-app-stores-eu-grace-period/">outlined what happens</a> when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user with apps installed through an alternative app marketplace leaves the EU. At the time, the document said that there would be an unspecified "grace period," but Apple has now updated it to provide exact timing.<br/>
<br/>
EU &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users who travel outside of the area can expect to be able to update apps installed through alternative app marketplaces for a 30-day period, but after that, apps will not be able to be updated.<br/>
<br/>
Installing alternative app marketplaces and the apps in those marketplaces is restricted to the European Union at all times, so travelers will not be able to install new apps through a marketplace while out of their home country or one of the 27 countries in the EU. Apps that have been downloaded can continue to be opened and used, even if they can't be updated.<blockquote>If you leave the European Union, you can continue to open and use apps that you previously installed from alternative app marketplaces. Alternative app marketplaces can continue updating those apps for up to 30 days after you leave the European Union, and you can continue using alternative app marketplaces to manage previously installed apps. However, you must be in the European Union to install alternative app marketplaces and new apps from alternative app marketplaces.</blockquote><br/>
Apple makes it clear that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users who want to install apps outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> must be physically located in a country in the European Union and their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> must also be set to a country or region in the EU. Apple uses privacy-focused on-device processing to determine whether a user is eligible to install an alternative app marketplace.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/europe/">Europe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/alternative-apps-30-day-update-period/">iOS Apps From Alternative Marketplaces Can Be Updated for 30 Days Outside of EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-apps-from-alternative-marketplaces-can-be-updated-for-30-days-outside-of-eu.2421304/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PayPal and Venmo Launch Tap to Pay on iPhone for U.S. Businesses</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-paypal-venmo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/paypal-and-venmo-launch-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-for-u-s-businesses.2421297/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:15:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-paypal-venmo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[PayPal today <a href="https://investor.pypl.com/news-and-events/news-details/2024/Tap-to-Pay-on-iPhone-Now-Available-for-Venmo-and-PayPal-Zettle-Businesses-in-the-U.S/default.aspx">announced</a> that Tap to Pay on iPhone is now widely available for businesses that use the Venmo and PayPal Zettle apps in the U.S., allowing them to accept contactless payments directly on an iPhone, with no additional hardware required.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/Apple-Tap-to-Pay-iPhone.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836277" /><br/>
More details from the announcement:<blockquote>With Tap to Pay on iPhone, Venmo business profile and PayPal Zettle users in the U.S. can get set up in minutes and begin securely accepting contactless cards and digital wallets directly on their iPhones. They can also add taxes, accept tips, send receipts, and issue refunds. In addition, funds from sales will settle quickly into a business's Venmo or PayPal Zettle account, helping to streamline operations and manage cash flow.</blockquote>PayPal had already been testing Tap to Pay on iPhone with an early access program, and the feature is now available to all merchants.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/08/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-iphone-feature/">Launched in the U.S. in 2022</a>, Tap to Pay on iPhone allows for iPhone-to-iPhone contactless payments, with no additional point-of-sale hardware from companies like Square or Clover required. The feature allows customers to tap their iPhone or Apple Watch, credit card, or other contactless payment option on the merchant's iPhone. Payment is securely completed using the same NFC technology behind Apple Pay.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has gradually expanded Tap to Pay on iPhone to additional countries, such as Australia, France, the Netherlands, Taiwan, and the U.K. Other popular payment platforms that support the feature include Square and Stripe.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-paypal-venmo/">PayPal and Venmo Launch Tap to Pay on iPhone for U.S. Businesses</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/paypal-and-venmo-launch-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-for-u-s-businesses.2421297/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Satechi Launches USB-C Multiport 8K Adapter</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/satechi-8k-multiport-adapter/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-usb-c-multiport-8k-adapter.2421296/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/satechi-8k-multiport-adapter/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Satechi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Accessory maker Satechi today <a href="https://satechi.net/products/usb-c-multiport-adapter-8k-with-ethernet-v3">announced the launch</a> of a new USB-C adapter that's designed to work with Apple's products, including the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>. The USB-C Multiport Adapter 8K with Ethernet V3 includes four USB-C ports, an 8K HDMI 2.1 port, an Ethernet port, a UHS-II SD card slot, and support for passthrough charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/satechi-multiport-adapter.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939846" /><br/>
According to Satechi, the Multiport Adapter offers display options that include 8K/30Hz, 4K/120Hz, 2K/144Hz, and 1080p/240Hz. Three of the USB-C data ports support USB 3.2 Gen 2 transfer speeds of up to 10Gb/s, while one offers 5Gb/s.<br/>
<br/>
For Macs, up to 85W passthrough charging is available, which can power either the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; or the MacBook Pro. Satechi is offering the new Multiport Adapter in space gray, silver, and midnight, matching Apple's color options, and it is made from aluminum.<br/>
<br/>
The USB-C Multiport Adapter 8K can be <a href="https://satechi.net/products/usb-c-multiport-adapter-8k-with-ethernet-v3">purchased from the Satechi website</a> for &#36;99.99.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/satechi/">Satechi</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/satechi-8k-multiport-adapter/">Satechi Launches USB-C Multiport 8K Adapter</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-usb-c-multiport-8k-adapter.2421296/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MagSafe Duo Charger Drops to New Record Low Price of &#36;74.99, Plus Steep Discounts on AirTags and iPhone 15 Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/magsafe-duo-charger-new-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/magsafe-duo-charger-drops-to-new-record-low-price-of-74-99-plus-steep-discounts-on-airtags-and-iphone-15-cases.2421291/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:19:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/magsafe-duo-charger-new-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot today has a big <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">sale on Apple accessories</a>, including low prices on the MagSafe Charger and MagSafe Duo Charger. Additionally, Amazon has steep discounts on AirTags and iPhone 15 cases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/magsafe-duo-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939069" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Both of the MagSafe Chargers in this sale are in brand new condition and come with a one year Apple manufacturer limited warranty. The MagSafe Charger comes in bulk packaging. You'll find an estimated delivery between March 19 and March 21, although those dates may change depending on your location.<br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"><strong>&#36;74.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is a new all-time low price on the accessory, beating Woot's previous discounted price by about &#36;5. The MagSafe Duo Charger can simultaneously charge an iPhone via MagSafe and an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;54 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;74.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot also has the MagSafe Charger for <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-21%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_28"><strong>&#36;26.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;39.00. This beats Woot's previous price on the accessory by &#36;3 and is one of the lowest prices that we've tracked so far in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-21%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_28"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;12 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;26.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Over at Amazon, you can find solid discounts on AirTags, including the AirTag 1 Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0933BVK6T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;24.00</strong></a> and the AirTag 4 Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;78.99</strong></a>. The deal on the AirTag 4 Pack matches the best price we've seen so far this year, and is just about &#36;4 higher when compared to the all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airtag-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940079" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;78.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has a large collection of FineWoven and Silicone Cases on sale for the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max. You can find these for as low as &#36;17.65 right now on Amazon, and no coupon codes are required to get these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;20.13, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWZ9JC9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Silicone Case</a> - &#36;23.40, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9FJTK%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;29.68, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHXDVMXJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Plus Silicone Case</a> - &#36;17.65, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2XFLN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Silicone Case</a> - &#36;31.83, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1HZST%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Max FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;51.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWVCV1Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Max Silicone Case</a> - &#36;33.98, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/magsafe-duo-charger-new-low-price/">MagSafe Duo Charger Drops to New Record Low Price of &#36;74.99, Plus Steep Discounts on AirTags and iPhone 15 Cases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/magsafe-duo-charger-drops-to-new-record-low-price-of-74-99-plus-steep-discounts-on-airtags-and-iphone-15-cases.2421291/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Announces &#039;Friday Night Baseball&#039; Returns Later This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-tv-plus-friday-night-baseball-march-29/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-announces-friday-night-baseball-returns-later-this-month.2421288/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:05:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-tv-plus-friday-night-baseball-march-29/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Major League Baseball today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/friday-night-baseball-returns-to-apple-tv-plus-on-march-29/">announced</a> that "Friday Night Baseball" is returning for the 2024 season, which begins later this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/Apple-TV-plus-MLB-Friday-Night-Baseball-hero_big.jpg.medium_2x.jpg" alt="" width="1384" height="778" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-838838" /><br/>
Friday Night Baseball is included with an Apple TV+ subscription in 60 countries and regions. The weekly doubleheader begins Friday, March 29, with the New York Yankees vs. the Houston Astros and the Los Angeles Dodgers vs. the St. Louis Cardinals:<blockquote>Fans in 60 countries and regions can enjoy two marquee matchups over 26 weeks with no local broadcast restrictions. "Friday Night Baseball" will begin on opening weekend of the 2024 season — Friday, March 29 — with some of the game's biggest stars taking center stage. Coverage begins at 7:30 p.m. ET with Juan Soto, Aaron Judge, and the new-look New York Yankees lineup taking on the Houston Astros. And beginning at 9:30 p.m. ET, Shohei Ohtani, Mookie Betts, and the Los Angeles Dodgers will host the St. Louis Cardinals.</blockquote>A schedule of Friday Night Baseball games through June 28 is included <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/friday-night-baseball-returns-to-apple-tv-plus-on-march-29/">in Apple's announcement</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple TV+ costs &#36;9.99 per month in the U.S., with various free trial options available. The subscription-based service is built into the Apple TV app, which is available on the iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple TV box, Apple Vision Pro, select Xbox and PlayStation consoles, select smart TVs and streaming devices, and online at tv.apple.com.<br/>
<br/>
Baseball fans can also keep track of MLB scores in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-announced/">new Apple Sports app</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-tv-plus-friday-night-baseball-march-29/">Apple TV+ Announces &#039;Friday Night Baseball&#039; Returns Later This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-announces-friday-night-baseball-returns-later-this-month.2421288/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Air With M3 Chip: Reviews and Unboxing Videos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-with-m3-chip-reviews-and-unboxing-videos.2421285/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 06:00:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1709830846/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">new 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models with the M3 chip</a> launch this Friday. Ahead of time, the first reviews and unboxing videos  for the laptops have been shared by some media outlets and YouTube channels.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
Key new features added to both MacBook Air models include Apple's M3 chip for faster performance, Wi-Fi 6E support, expanded external display support, an anodization seal that reduces fingerprints on the Midnight finish, and microphone improvements.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Reviews</h2><br/>
<h3>M3 Chip</h3><br/>
Both the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air are now available with the M3 chip for faster performance and improved power efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
As expected, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/first-benchmark-result-macbook-air-m3/">early benchmark result</a> revealed that the M3 chip is up to 20% faster than the M2 chip in the previous MacBook Air models in terms of CPU performance. These results are consistent with the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
Jason Snell shared benchmark results in his <a href="https://sixcolors.com/post/2024/03/m3-macbook-air-review-more-of-a-good-thing/">review on <em>Six Colors</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Six-Colors-M3-MacBook-Air.jpg" alt="" width="1382" height="1338" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940059" /><br/>
With the M3 chip, the MacBook Air has also gained hardware-accelerated ray tracing for improved graphics rendering in games, along with AV1 video decoding.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Two External Displays</h3><br/>
While previous MacBook Air models with Apple silicon officially support only one external display, the new models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-two-displays-lid-closed/">support two external displays</a>. However, a second display can only be used when the MacBook Air's lid is closed.<br/>
<br/>
When the lid is open, the new models support one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz. When the lid is closed, a second display with up to 5K resolution at 60Hz can be connected, according to Apple's tech specs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/M3-MacBook-Air-Two-External-Displays.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="676" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940064" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image Credit: CNET</em></div><a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/computing/apple-macbook-air-m3-13-inch-2024-review-the-everything-laptop/"><em>CNET</em>'s Joshua Goldman</a>:<blockquote>With the M3 MacBook Airs, you can connect two external displays directly to the Thunderbolt USB-C ports, which will also power the MacBook. <br/>
<br/>
However, doing this comes at the cost of the MacBook Air's display; the lid must be closed in order to drive both external monitors. On the surface, this doesn't seem like much of an issue, unless you typically use your laptop's keyboard and trackpad while working on an external display. For me, the bigger hiccup is the loss of Touch ID on the Air's keyboard. You can just open and close the lid to use Touch ID, but I use mine so much during the day that that would get old really fast. The better option is to get Apple's Magic Keyboard with Touch ID, and while you're at it, pick up a Magic Trackpad or Mouse to complete the package.</blockquote>Even more displays can be connected to the MacBook Air with the use of DisplayLink adapters. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Fingerprint Seal for Midnight Color</h3><br/>
Just <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">like the Space Black MacBook Pro</a>, the Midnight MacBook Air now features an "anodization seal to reduce fingerprints," according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.thestreet.com/technology/apple-13-inch-15-inch-macbook-air-m3-review"><em>TheStreet</em>'s Jacob Krol</a>:<blockquote>Thus far, it's clear that the anodization blocks most fingerprint smudges, and the M3 looks better than an M2 in the Midnight color. However, Midnight is a harder color to block all of them, as I am still seeing some, specifically on the top and bottom cases of the 15-inch. That being said, on the inside around the keyboard and on or off the trackpad, it does a really good job of stopping them.</blockquote><h3>Wi-Fi 6E</h3><br/>
The new MacBook Airs support Wi-Fi 6E for "up to twice as fast" wireless download speeds compared to the previous models with Wi-Fi 6, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 6E extends the capabilities of Wi-Fi 6 to the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference with a compatible device and router. The entire current-generation Mac lineup now supports Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Microphone Upgrades</h3><br/>
Apple says the microphones in the new MacBook Air models offer "enhanced voice clarity in audio and video calls" compared to the previous models. The microphones also gained support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/block-background-noise-facetime-mac/">"Voice Isolation" and "Wide Spectrum" modes</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Videos</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tM9oB1yYOuc?si=IYoukTXdv5VAXVnl" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HO12tGkTMDI?si=ovbiLmgtH0UQD7ju" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rNiebbGvAhU?si=SDIloJuFiy_Y5MS5" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uhXbQVViIcs?si=tJTZBFAQX9RQMsoV" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ID5CwsOGVpE?si=m8UMPQKAASA09lEk" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-air/">MacBook Air With M3 Chip: Reviews and Unboxing Videos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-with-m3-chip-reviews-and-unboxing-videos.2421285/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Probes Apple&#039;s Decision to Shut Down Epic&#039;s Developer Account</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/eu-probes-apple-termination-epic-account/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-probes-apples-decision-to-shut-down-epics-developer-account.2421267/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 01:48:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/eu-probes-apple-termination-epic-account/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The European Commission has requested "further explanations" from Apple over its decision yesterday to <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/site/en-US/news/apple-terminated-epic-s-developer-account">terminate the developer account</a> of Epic Games, the <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b0655af4-833e-4434-a6f4-5e198f914537">Financial Times</a></em> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
The EC said it was investigating under the Digital Markets Act (DMA), a new law aimed at curbing the power of the biggest online platforms. Tech companies faced a March 7 deadline to comply with the legislation. The Commission added that it was also evaluating whether Apple's actions might have breached other EU laws. <br/>
<br/>
Apple on Wednesday <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-explains-terminating-epic-games-account/">announced</a> the termination of Epic Games Sweden's developer account on a global scale, citing the game developer's recurrent untrustworthy actions. Apple said courts had previously granted Apple the authority to end the accounts of any of Epic's subsidiaries due to contractual infractions.<br/>
<br/>
The move thwarted Epic's plan to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/epic-games-store-ios-eu/">launch an Epic Games Store on iOS in the EU</a> and bring its Fortnite game back to the iPhone, which it claimed was in line with new EU regulations allowing for alternative app marketplaces on iOS. Starting with iOS 17.4, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">allows alternative app marketplaces on the iPhone in the EU</a>, as part of its compliance with the DMA. Epic argues that Apple's account termination violates the DMA and significantly limits competition on iOS devices.<br/>
<br/>
Epic condemned Apple's decision as a violation of competitive principles, interpreting it as evidence of Apple's unwillingness to allow legitimate competition on its platform. The company claimed Apple's action was an attempt to eliminate a major potential rival to the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's action was the latest in a broader legal conflict that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">started in 2020</a> when Apple removed Fortnite from the App Store for bypassing its payment system rules. In retaliation, Epic launched lawsuits in the U.S. and Australia, accusing Apple of anti-competitive behavior. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/eu-probes-apple-termination-epic-account/">EU Probes Apple&#039;s Decision to Shut Down Epic&#039;s Developer Account</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-probes-apples-decision-to-shut-down-epics-developer-account.2421267/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Planning 20-Inch MacBook With Foldable Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/20-inch-macbook-kuo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-planning-20-inch-macbook-with-foldable-screen.2421253/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 19:12:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/20-inch-macbook-kuo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Foldable MacBook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to release a 20-inch MacBook with a foldable screen in around three years, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
"Apple's only foldable product with a clear development schedule is the 20.3-inch MacBook, expected to enter mass production in 2027," said Kuo, <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1765563986089783322">in a post on X today</a>. He did not provide any additional details about the device.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo is the third source to mention the possibility of a 20-inch MacBook, alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/31/apple-foldable-notebook-2025/">display industry analyst Ross Young</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/apple-20-inch-display-future-macbook-pro/">Korean website <em>The Elec</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
The largest laptop that Apple currently sells is the 16-inch MacBook Pro. The company also once offered a 17-inch MacBook Pro, which was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2012/06/11/apple-quietly-discontinues-macbook-pro-17/">discontinued in 2012</a>. The new foldable MacBook would have a screen that measures around 20 inches diagonally when fully expanded, but Kuo did not provide any details about the device's exact design.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said the 20-inch MacBook is Apple's only foldable product with a clear development schedule, suggesting that a foldable iPhone or iPad are not coming any time soon.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-macbook/">Foldable MacBook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/20-inch-macbook-kuo/">Kuo: Apple Planning 20-Inch MacBook With Foldable Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-planning-20-inch-macbook-with-foldable-screen.2421253/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Car&#039;s Decade of Development and &#039;Failure&#039; Detailed in New Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-car-history-bloomberg-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cars-decade-of-development-and-failure-detailed-in-new-report.2421232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:15:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-car-history-bloomberg-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman and Drake Bennett today published an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2024-03-06/apple-car-s-crash-design-details-tim-cook-s-indecision-failed-tesla-deal">in-depth report</a> examining Apple's decade-long attempt at creating an electric vehicle. The project was reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">canceled last week</a> after many challenges and setbacks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/Apple-car-wheel-icon-Kevin-Lynch-feature-blue-revamp.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839900" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple vice president Kevin Lynch, who oversaw the electric vehicle project in its later years</em></div><br/>
The report described a 2020 prototype of Apple's electric vehicle:<blockquote>The prototype, a white minivan with rounded sides, an all-glass roof, sliding doors and whitewall tires, was designed to comfortably seat four people and inspired by the classic flower-power Volkswagen microbus. The design was referred to within Apple, not always affectionately, as the Bread Loaf. The plan was for the vehicle to hit the market some five years later with a giant TV screen, a powerful audio system and windows that adjusted their own tint. The cabin would have club seating like a private plane, and passengers would be able to turn some of the seats into recliners and footrests.</blockquote>Apple once considered acquiring Tesla to bolster its efforts, the report said:<blockquote>But before sketching out its own designs, Apple considered acquiring Tesla. At that point the electric-car maker's success was far from assured, and its value was less than &#36;30 billion, or a 20th of what it is today. Adrian Perica, Apple's head of corporate development, held a series of meetings with Elon Musk. But Cook, who'd succeeded Jobs three years earlier, shut the deal down while negotiations were still at an early stage.</blockquote>Apple also considered partnering with or acquiring Mercedes-Benz, BMW, Ford, Volkswagen, McLaren, and other automakers, according to the report:<blockquote>Talks with Mercedes-Benz progressed further. For a few months, Apple and the German automaker actively worked on a partnership similar to the Tesla idea, but with a twist. Mercedes would manufacture Apple's vehicle, while it would also sell its own cars with Apple's self-driving platform and user interface. Apple eventually pulled out, in part because the early work gave its executives confidence they could build a car on their own, people involved in the failed deal say.</blockquote>The project was ultimately a "failure" due to indecision, the report said:<blockquote>But Apple never got close to realizing its original vision, or any of its subsequent ones. It didn't get as far as testing a full-scale prototype on public roads. That it didn't is partly thanks to the enormous technical difficulty of its self-driving goals, as well as the punishing economics of the automaking business. The project was also a failure, at the highest levels of the company, to settle on one thing and do it.</blockquote>The report detailed how Apple's COO Jeff Williams and Apple Car chief Kevin Lynch broke the  news of the project's cancellation to employees:<blockquote>The meeting lasted about 12 minutes. Both men thanked the staffers for their work and got straight to the reorg and layoffs. Some employees would immediately get shifted to Apple's AI division, and some would move over to software engineering. A chunk of the team, though, was immediately without a job. Hardware engineers would have the opportunity to apply for roles in other groups, but there aren't spots for everyone. Other employees, such as the hundreds of car-specific engineers, test track technicians, self-driving car testers and automotive safety experts, received emails with their severance packages. As for the Arizona track, Apple is already working to sell it.</blockquote>Other notable details mentioned in the report include that Steve Jobs was apparently first to raise the idea of Apple building a vehicle, and that some Apple employees received a tour of Jay Leno's garage and his car collection early on.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2024-03-06/apple-car-s-crash-design-details-tim-cook-s-indecision-failed-tesla-deal"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s full report</a> is a worthwhile read for those interested in learning more about Apple's vehicle project, and we also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/">shared our own recap last week</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-car-history-bloomberg-report/">Apple Car&#039;s Decade of Development and &#039;Failure&#039; Detailed in New Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cars-decade-of-development-and-failure-detailed-in-new-report.2421232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 190 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2421238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 190 includes fixes and updates for CSS, History, HTML, JavaScript, Media, Networking, SVG, URLs, Web API, and Web Inspector.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Ventura and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, the latest version of macOS that Apple released in September 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 190 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2421238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing FaceTime on Apple TV With Belkin&#039;s New MagSafe iPhone Mount</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/facetime-apple-tv-belkin-magsafe-iphone-mount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-facetime-on-apple-tv-with-belkins-new-magsafe-iphone-mount.2421225/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 11:34:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/facetime-apple-tv-belkin-magsafe-iphone-mount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Belkin</category>
		<category>FaceTime</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Belkin this week released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/belkin-iphone-magsafe-mount-for-apple-tv/">new iPhone Mount with MagSafe</a>, which is designed to attach to a television for use with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Mount lets you use your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as a camera for your &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Belkin iPhone MagSafe Stand" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MdByMW-lVX0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Apple actually showed off this mount when it introduced &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; on &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, but it hasn't been available for purchase until now, and there hasn't been an official solution for mounting an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to a television set.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR1V2ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-apple-tv-4k">Priced at &#36;49.95</a>, the Belkin &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mount has a bracket that is able to attach to a TV or a display that's up to four inches thick, or it can be used with a pedestal as a standalone mount next to a TV.<br/>
<br/>
It's super simple to use the mount, and you just need to pop it on the TV and then stick your MagSafe-enabled &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the mount. You can adjust the tilt from -20 to +30 degrees for the perfect filming angle, and it works in either portrait or landscape mode.<br/>
<br/>
We tested the mount with &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;, but it is also compatible with any Continuity Camera-supported apps. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; activates automatically as the camera in &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; or another supported app, and all you need to do is be signed in with the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> on both devices.<br/>
<br/>
Note that using an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a camera for an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; requires the second-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K or later with tvOS 17, and an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; (or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>) running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later.<br/>
<br/>
Using a TV for &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; is great if you're FaceTiming with multiple people or for SharePlay sessions, and there are options to set up a split-screen layout when using &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;. The mount and the Continuity Camera feature work with Center Stage, and reactions like fireworks are supported.<br/>
<br/>
Large-screen &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; is definitely an experience that's worth trying out if you tend to do a lot of video calling. <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR1V2ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-apple-tv-4k"> Apple is selling the Belkin Mount</a> for &#36;49.95, and it's shipping out almost immediately.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/belkin/">Belkin</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/facetime-apple-tv-belkin-magsafe-iphone-mount/">Testing FaceTime on Apple TV With Belkin&#039;s New MagSafe iPhone Mount</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-facetime-on-apple-tv-with-belkins-new-magsafe-iphone-mount.2421225/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
