<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 12:03:11 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reveals Annual Japanese New Year Promotion With Special AirTag</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reveals-annual-japanese-new-year-promotion-with-special-airtag.2414723/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 11:05:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In celebration of the Japanese New Year, Apple will be <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/shop/gifts/new-year">holding a promotion</a> that offers customers in Japan a free Apple gift card worth up to ¥30,000 with the purchase of an eligible Apple product from January 2 through January 5.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Japanese-New-Year-Apple-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927987" /><br/>
Gift card values range from ¥4,000 for products like the iPhone SE and third-generation AirPods to ¥30,000 for the 15-inch MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to a gift card, the first 50,000 customers in Japan who purchase a new iPhone 14, iPhone 14 Plus, iPhone 13, or third-generation iPhone SE from Apple during the promotion will receive a limited-edition AirTag with a "Year of the Dragon" engraving.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has shared <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/shop/gifts/new-year/terms-conditions">terms and conditions</a> for the promotion with additional details. Notably, iPhone orders placed through the Apple Store app will not qualify for a limited-edition AirTag, so make sure to complete your purchase on Apple's website or at a physical Apple Store in Japan if you are interested in receiving one.<br/>
<br/>
Apple holds a Japanese New Year promotion on an annual basis, and this is the third consecutive year it has offered a special AirTag.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/">Apple Reveals Annual Japanese New Year Promotion With Special AirTag</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reveals-annual-japanese-new-year-promotion-with-special-airtag.2414723/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Lowe&#039;s Retail Stores Now Accept Apple Pay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/lowes-apple-pay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lowes-retail-stores-now-accept-apple-pay.2414712/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:52:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/lowes-apple-pay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Lowe's home improvement stores across the United States have finally started accepting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>. &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; has been available in the Lowe's app and the Lowe's website for some time, but the company has been a longtime &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; holdout for its retail store locations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Lowes/comments/18k2k1u/tap_and_pay_and_apple_pay/">On Reddit</a>, Lowe's employees said in late December that they had received a memo about the upcoming &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; and contactless payment rollout, which was set to begin on December 20.<br/>
<br/>
A Lowe's customer on the <em>MacRumors</em> forums said that he was able to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-lowes.2388023/page-2">successfully use Apple Pay</a> at two different Lowe's stores in Texas, confirming the rollout.<br/>
<br/>
The Lowe's employees on Reddit said they were glad to hear about the rollout due to the <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Lowes/comments/14uj8vt/do_you_guys_take_apple_pay/">number of customers</a> asking to use contactless payment options. There have also been many complaint threads from Lowe's customers about the lack of &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Lowes/comments/1005132/apple_pay/">on Reddit</a> and the <em>MacRumors</em> forums.<br/>
<br/>
Lowe's has more than 2,000 stores in the United States, making it the second largest home improvement store after Home Depot. Accepting &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; could lure customers to Lowe's over Home Depot, as Home Depot does not accept the payment technology at this time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/lowes-apple-pay/">Lowe&#039;s Retail Stores Now Accept Apple Pay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lowes-retail-stores-now-accept-apple-pay.2414712/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Import Ban Now Official, Apple Appeals Decision</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-import-ban-now-official-apple-appeals-decision.2414706/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:18:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ITC</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is now officially unable to sell the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> in the United States as the International Trade Commission's import ban has become final. This morning, the Biden administration announced that it would not veto the ban.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-9-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922237" /><br/>
The Office of the United States Trade Representative <a href="https://www.ustr.gov/about-us/policy-offices/press-office/press-releases/2023/december/ustr-statement-section-337-review">said that</a> after "careful consultations" it was opting not to reverse the ITC's decision.<blockquote>"On October 26, 2023, the U.S. International Trade Commission found that Apple, Inc. infringed two patents owned by Masimo Corporation and Cercacor Laboratories, Inc, both based in the United States. Since 2005, the Office of the United States Trade Representative has been delegated the President's authority under Section 337 of the Trade Act of 1930 to review the ITC's decision for a 60-day period. After careful consultations, Ambassador Tai decided not to reverse the ITC's determination and the ITC's decision became final on December 26, 2023."</blockquote>Apple in a statement to <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/biden-administration-allows-us-trade-tribunals-ban-apple-watch-imports-2023-12-26/">Reuters</a></em> said that it is "taking all measures" to get the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; back on store shelves as soon as possible.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has filed an appeal with the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit in Washington, and it has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-watch-import-ban-software-fix/">working on a software solution</a> that it hopes will allow it to resume sales.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; are not able to be sold by Apple in the United States at this time because the ITC ruled that the devices violate blood oxygen monitoring technology owned by medical device company Masimo.<br/>
<br/>
The ban is limited to Apple Watch models that have a blood oxygen sensor, so the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> is still on sale. It also only applies to Apple retail stores in the United States, so all Apple Watch models are still available in other countries. Stores like Target, Best Buy, and Walmart are able to continue Apple Watch sales as long as supplies hold out, but Apple is not able to bring more units into the United States from overseas.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will not be able to sell the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; or the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; unless the appeal is successful, it settles with Masimo, or it finds a way to change the blood oxygen sensor so it is not using Masimo's patented technology.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itc/">ITC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">Apple Watch Import Ban Now Official, Apple Appeals Decision</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-import-ban-now-official-apple-appeals-decision.2414706/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>6 Essential iPhone Camera Tips for Taking Great Photos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/6-iphone-camera-tips-great-photos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-essential-iphone-camera-tips-for-taking-great-photos.2414690/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/6-iphone-camera-tips-great-photos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhones include several headline camera features that are worth using, such as Portrait Mode and Photographic Styles. But if all you want to use is the standard photo mode, there are still several tools and settings that can improve the composition of your pictures and help you capture the perfect shot using more traditional techniques.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Blue-Three-Quarters-Perspective-Camera-Closeup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909012" /><br/>
Whether you are the owner of a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or a longtime user looking to up your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; photography game, here are six camera tools and settings in iOS that are worth checking out and experimenting with.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">1. Use the Rule of Thirds</h2><br/>
For a while now, Apple's Camera app has included a few optional settings that can help you line up your shots. Foremost in these settings is the Grid tool, which should be used when applying the rule of thirds. It divides the frame of your photo into a grid with two horizontal lines and two vertical lines, creating nine equal parts. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/grid-camera-tool.jpg" alt="" width="2716" height="1339" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927774" /><br/>
The rule of thirds helps guide the viewer's eye to the most important parts of your photo and creates a more harmonious composition. Here's how to overlay a grid on the viewfinder.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Settings app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap Camera. </li><br/>
<li>In the "Composition" section, toggle on the switch next to Grid.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/camera-grid-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927655" /><br/>
<br/>
Here are five things to keep in mind when using the grid to apple the rule of thirds.<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>Identify the Key Elements</strong>: First, identify the main subjects or elements in the scene you want to photograph. These could be a person, a building, a tree, or any focal point.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Positioning the Subjects</strong>: Place these key elements along the lines or at the points where the lines intersect. For instance, if you're taking a photo of a person, you might position them along one of the vertical lines, rather than in the center of the frame.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Horizontal Elements</strong>: For horizontal elements like the horizon in a landscape, align them with one of the horizontal lines. For a more dramatic sky, place the horizon on the lower line. For more emphasis on the land or sea, place it on the upper line.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Balancing the Image</strong>: Use the rule of thirds to balance your photo. If you place a subject on the left, consider having something of lesser importance on the right to create a sense of balance.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Experimentation</strong>: While the rule of thirds is a guideline, it's not a strict rule. Feel free to experiment with it and see how shifting elements in your frame changes the photo's impact.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">2. Straighten Top-Down Shots</h2><br/>
If you're taking a picture of something from above like a plate of food or an ornament on the ground, consider using the camera level, as it helps you capture a balanced shot without having to use a tripod arm or mount. It's also useful for taking a shot of something directly above you, like an object on the ceiling or in the sky.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/level-camera-tool-setting.jpg" alt="" width="1338" height="700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927776" /><br/>
The camera level tool used to be part of the Grid overlay, but Apple separated out the function in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, and it now has its own switch: Open the Settings app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, select Camera, then toggle on the switch next to Level. Now you are ready to use it.<br/>
<ol><br/>
<li>Open the Camera app, and set the capture mode to <strong>Photo</strong>, <strong>Portrait</strong>, <strong>Square</strong>, or <strong>Time Lapse</strong>, using the sliding menu above the shutter button.</li><br/>
<li>Point the camera straight down above your subject (or straight up if the subject/scene you want to capture is above you).</li><br/>
<li>Line up the floating crosshair with the fixed crosshair in the center of the screen by adjusting the angle of your phone's camera. The crosshairs will both glow yellow when in perfect alignment. </li><br/>
<li>Tap the shutter button to capture the shot.</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/camera-level-tool-in-action.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1058" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927779" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The aligned crosshairs turn yellow (right), indicating the lens is parallel with the ground.</em></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">3. Straighten Your Horizontal Shots</h2><br/>
By making the Level tool an individual option in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, Apple has also included an additional horizontal level for more traditional straight-on photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/ios-17-camera-level-no.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899126" /><br/>
Turning the Level option on makes a broken horizontal line appear on the screen when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; senses that you're lining up for a straight-on shot and you tilt your device slightly out of horizontal. The line appears white while your phone is out of level and then turns yellow once you achieve a level orientation to indicate success.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/ios-17-camera-level.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899127" /><br/>
With the Level setting enabled (Settings ➝ Camera ➝ Level), try it for yourself. Open the Camera app and try shooting a subject at a straight angle, and you should see the broken horizontal lines in the center of the viewfinder. Straighten your angle up to connect the lines and make a single yellow line.<br/>
<br/>
The leveling pop-up only appears briefly and only within a narrow range of angles close to horizontal (in either portrait or landscape orientation), so it won't intrusively pop up when you're intentionally trying to take a photo at an angle.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">4. Take Burst Photos</h2><br/>
Burst Mode refers to when the camera on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; captures a series of photos in rapid succession, at a rate of ten frames per second. It's a great way to shoot an action scene or an unexpected event, since you're always more likely to end up with the picture you were aiming for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/burstmode.jpg" alt="" width="940" height="460" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-386450" /><br/>
To shoot in Burst Mode, simply long press on the Volume Up button and your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will take a series of photos in quick succession. Notice that a counter increases inside the on-screen shutter button for as long as you hold down the volume button. This indicates how many shots are being captured in the current burst. Simply take your finger off the volume when you want to end the burst of shots.<br/>
<br/>
When you take a series of burst photos, they automatically appear in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app under the Album name Bursts. You'll also find them in your main Photo Library. Follow the link to learn <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/delete-redundant-burst-mode-photos-iphone-ipad/">how to view and select the best of your Burst photos</a> in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">5. Mirror Your Selfies</h2><br/>
When you take a selfie with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; using the Camera app, it automatically flips – or mirrors – the image so that it's an inverted version of the mirror image you see in the preview before you take the shot.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/stop-flipped-selfie-iphone-ipad.jpg" alt="selfie" width="2710" height="2616" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757877" /><br/>
This can look odd, since it makes a big difference to how selfies look. It can also be annoying, since most third-party social media apps automatically take mirrored selfies, which means you're more likely to be used to the mirroring functionality than the flipped selfies that your ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ takes.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, you can change this default behavior of the Camera app, meaning that you can get the mirrored selfie you're probably more accustomed to seeing. Here's how.<br/>
<ol><li>Launch the <strong>Settings</strong> app, then scroll down and select <strong>Camera</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Toggle the switch next to <strong>Mirror Front Camera</strong> to the green ON position.</li></ol><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/mirror-front-camera-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="1338" height="700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927784" /><br/>
That's all there is to it. From now on when you use the Camera app to shoot a selfie, you'll capture the same shot that you saw in the app's preview mode.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">6. View Outside the Frame</h2><br/>
On &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 and later models, there is an optional camera setting that allows you to see what is outside the bounds of your photo's frame, so you can correct the alignment of photos (and videos) without having to resort to cropping.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/capture-shot-outside-frame-iphone-11-camera-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1544" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927787" /><br/>
With the "View Outside the Frame" setting enabled, when shooting using the wide lens or the telephoto lens, the camera will simultaneously shoot using the next widest sensor. So the wide lens is active when you shoot with the telephoto lens, and the ultra-wide is active when you shoot with the wide. <br/>
<ol><li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap Camera.</li><br/>
<li>Under the "Composition" section, toggle on the switch next to View Outside the Frame.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/view-outside-frame-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="1338" height="700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927786" /><br/>
<br/>
You may have to play around with zoom levels to switch between lenses, but you'll know the feature is active when the camera interface turns semi-transparent to reveal the surroundings outside of the viewfinder.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/6-iphone-camera-tips-great-photos/">6 Essential iPhone Camera Tips for Taking Great Photos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-essential-iphone-camera-tips-for-taking-great-photos.2414690/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10 Ways to Spend an Apple Gift Card You Received for Christmas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/apple-gift-card-spending-ideas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-ways-to-spend-an-apple-gift-card-you-received-for-christmas.2414637/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/apple-gift-card-spending-ideas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you received an Apple gift card for Christmas this year, here are 10 ways to spend it, with all of the options priced under &#36;100 in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-gift-card-blue-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826644" /><br/>
The all-in-one gift card "for everything Apple" can be used towards purchases on Apple.com and at physical Apple Stores, iTunes Store music, App Store apps and games, subscriptions to services like Apple Music and Apple TV+, and more.<br/>
<br/>
To redeem an Apple gift card on an iPhone or iPad, open the App Store, tap your profile photo in the top-right corner, and tap "Redeem Gift Card or Code."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What to Buy With an Apple Gift Card</h2><br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MUYG3AM/A/magsafe-charging-case-usb%E2%80%91c-for-airpods-pro-2nd-generation">USB-C Case for AirPods Pro 2</a> (&#36;99)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-USB-C-Port-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911678" /><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/apple-selling-standalone-usb-c-airpods-pro-case/">now selling</a> a USB-C charging case for the second-generation AirPods Pro separately for &#36;99. Keep in mind that if you want your AirPods Pro earbuds to have lossless audio support with Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro headset</a>, and added IP54-rated dust resistance, you will need to purchase the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MTJV3AM/A/airpods-pro">AirPods Pro with a USB-C case</a> altogether. <br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MUWA3AM/A/apple-pencil-usb-c">Apple Pencil With USB-C Port</a> (&#36;79)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917176" /><br/>
Apple this year released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">more affordable Apple Pencil</a> with a hidden USB-C port for charging and pairing. Priced at &#36;79, it has a similar design as the second-generation Apple Pencil, but it lacks wireless charging, pressure sensitivity, a double-tap gesture for switching between drawing tools, and the option for personal engraving at the time of purchase.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-airtag/airtag">AirTag</a> (&#36;29)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/airtag-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849630" /><br/>
Keep track of your belongings with Apple's item tracker, which integrates with the Find My app on the iPhone, iPad, and Mac. A four-pack is also available for &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MNWM3AM/A/35w-dual-usb-c-port-compact-power-adapter">Apple's 35W Dual USB-C Charger</a> (&#36;59)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Apple-35W-Charger-feeature.jpg" alt="" width="2080" height="1171" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850450" /><br/>
Apple last year released 35W power adapters with dual USB-C ports, with standard and compact versions of the charger available for &#36;59 each. Both adapters feature foldable prongs and can be used to charge or power multiple lower-power Apple devices simultaneously, such as an iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, and HomePod mini.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MNC73AM/A/siri-remote">Apple TV Remote With USB-C Port</a> (&#36;59)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/siri-remote-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800838" /><br/>
Apple last year released a new version of the Siri Remote for the Apple TV with a USB-C port instead of Lightning for charging. If you already own an Apple TV model released in 2015 or later, the remote can be purchased separately for &#36;59.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MM6F3AM/A/polishing-cloth">Apple Polishing Cloth</a> (&#36;19)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/apple-polishing-cloth-green-feature.jpg" alt="" width="3036" height="1708" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-821771" /><br/>
Clean your iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch, Studio Display, and other devices with Apple's official polishing cloth, released in 2021.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-one/">Apple One</a></h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/Apple-One-Apps-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1012" height="601" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-760995" /><br/>
Redeem your Apple gift card and use the balance towards Apple One, which lets you subscribe to multiple Apple services at a discount. The base Apple One plan includes Apple Music, Apple TV+, Apple Arcade, and iCloud+ with 50GB of storage for &#36;19.95 per month, which is &#36;9 less per month compared to subscribing to these services separately.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HNNT2ZM/A/twelve-south-airfly-pro-bluetooth-transmitter">Twelve South's AirFly Pro</a> (&#36;54.95)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirFly-Pro-Twelve-South-feature.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878316" /><br/>
Twelve South's popular AirFly Pro accessory lets you use AirPods or Beats wireless headphones with an airplane's in-flight entertainment system. Simply plug AirFly Pro into the headphone jack on a plane to watch or listen with your AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQGM2ZM/A/Nanoleaf%20Essentials%20Matter%20A19%20Smart%20Bulb%20-%20Thread%20&%20Matter-Enabled%20Smart%20LED%20Light%20Bulb%20-%20White%20and%20Color">Nanoleaf's Essentials A19 Light Bulb</a> (&#36;19.95)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Nanoleaf-A19.jpeg" alt="" width="800" height="480" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878315" /><br/>
Nanoleaf's smart color-changing LED bulb is compatible with HomeKit, allowing it to be controlled in the Home app and with Siri. A three-pack is also available for &#36;49.95.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ642ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-mac-notebooks">Belkin's iPhone Mount for Continuity Camera</a> (&#36;29.95)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/continuity-camera.jpg" alt="" width="1930" height="1276" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848371" /><br/>
Belkin sells an iPhone mount for use with Continuity Camera, a feature that allows an iPhone to be used as a Mac's webcam. Priced at &#36;29.95, the mount attaches to the iPhone with MagSafe and can then be affixed to the top lid of a MacBook Air or MacBook Pro for use with Continuity Camera. Belkin also offers a desktop version of the mount <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ652ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-mac-desktops-and-displays">compatible with the 24-inch iMac and the Studio Display</a> for &#36;39.95.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/apple-gift-card-spending-ideas/">10 Ways to Spend an Apple Gift Card You Received for Christmas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-ways-to-spend-an-apple-gift-card-you-received-for-christmas.2414637/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Vision Pro Mass Shipments Begin Next Week, Launch by February</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-vision-pro-mass-shipments-begin-next-week-launch-by-february.2414633/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:18:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mass shipments of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro</a> to Apple will begin in the first week of January, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/2024%E5%B9%B4%E6%B6%88%E8%B2%BB%E9%9B%BB%E5%AD%90%E7%94%A2%E6%A5%AD%E4%B8%89%E5%A4%A7%E9%97%9C%E9%8D%B5%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%B6%A8%E5%8B%A2-android%E5%BA%AB%E5%AD%98%E5%9B%9E%E8%A3%9C-vision-pro%E8%88%87ai-pc-%E6%89%8B%E6%A9%9F-three-key-consumer-electronics-investment-42e680eb253b">Christmas Eve note</a>, Kuo said the Vision Pro will most likely hit shelves in late January or early February based on this schedule.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo estimates that Vision Pro shipments in 2024 will reach approximately 500,000 units.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced the Vision Pro at WWDC in June, and said it would launch in the U.S. in early 2024, followed by more countries later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
Happy Holidays!<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/">Kuo: Vision Pro Mass Shipments Begin Next Week, Launch by February</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-vision-pro-mass-shipments-begin-next-week-launch-by-february.2414633/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares iPhone 15 Plus Ad Highlighting Device&#039;s Long Battery Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/iphone-15-plus-battery-life-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-iphone-15-plus-ad-highlighting-devices-long-battery-life.2414578/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 10:10:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/iphone-15-plus-battery-life-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a short <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=07cKD8GK__c">iPhone 15 Plus ad</a> on its YouTube channel that highlights the device's long-lasting battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/07cKD8GK__c?si=04fBHbahr4x4VHTL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the video, an electrical outlet becomes sentient and sings the song "Way Too Long" by rapper Doe Boy. The outlet is sad that the iPhone 15 Plus lasts so long between charges, resulting in the device being plugged in less often.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's tech specs say the iPhone 15 Plus can provide up to 26 hours of offline video playback, and up to 100 hours of audio playback. Like the iPhone 14 Plus, the iPhone 15 Plus offers the longest advertised battery life of any iPhone ever.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's video description:<blockquote>Big screen. Big battery life. iPhone 15 Plus is here. Dynamic Island. New 48MP Main camera. 2x Telephoto. Next-generation portraits. Water resistant (IP68). USB-C. Durable color-infused glass. Aluminum design. You don't want to miss it.</blockquote>The ad was also shared as a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/OFP0c6zBVHs">YouTube Short</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/iphone-15-plus-battery-life-ad/">Apple Shares iPhone 15 Plus Ad Highlighting Device&#039;s Long Battery Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-iphone-15-plus-ad-highlighting-devices-long-battery-life.2414578/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>5 iPhone Camera Features to Try Out This Holiday Season</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out-this-holiday-season.2414545/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the holiday season, capturing photos and videos of the festivities with family and friends is an important activity for many. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> has a suite of camera features that can significantly elevate the quality and creativity of your holiday photos and videos. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Five-iPhone-Camera-Features-to-Try-This-Holiday-Season-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-927844" /><br/>
It's easy to forget about many of the individual camera features the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has to offer, and many capabilities go unused by most users, so the holidays is the perfect time to revisit them and try something new. For users of Apple's latest models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> takes things even further with several exclusive camera features. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Spatial Video</h3><br/>
For <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> users, the holiday season presents an ideal opportunity to experiment with Spatial Video capture feature. Available on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max running iOS 17.2 or later, the feature allows users to record videos in a three-dimensional format, bringing a new level of depth and realism to holiday memories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
While Apple's Vision Pro or a device like the Meta Quest 3 is required for the best experience when playing back Spatial Video, this should not deter users from exploring the feature. Spatial Video capture is available now to help users begin creating a library of immersive videos right away. Spatial Videos can also be played back as normal 2D content on other devices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/record-spatial-video-iphone/">iOS 17.2: How to Record Spatial Video on iPhone 15 Pro</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The technology behind Spatial Video Capture involves using the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s Main and Ultra Wide cameras. When recording, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; seamlessly combines inputs from these cameras to create a single video file that encapsulates a three-dimensional perspective. This is achieved through sophisticated computational videography techniques, which intelligently scale the field of view from the Ultra Wide camera to match that of the Main camera.<br/>
<br/>
The result is a video that, while technically 2D in format, contains depth information that can be utilized by compatible devices to produce a 3D viewing experience. The spatial dimension added to these videos creates a sense of immersion and presence that far surpasses traditional video, supposedly making the viewer feel as if they are actually part of the captured moment.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Cinematic Mode</h3><br/>
The holiday season is a good time for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> and newer model users to try out Cinematic mode, a feature that adds a depth-of-field effect to videos. Cinematic mode uses advanced computational algorithms to automatically focus on subjects and creatively blur the background, akin to what you would see in high-end cinematography. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Cinematic-Mode-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-900525" /><br/>
Cinematic mode allows users to focus on details in a creative way, by shifting focus smoothly from one subject to another. Cinematic mode also simplifies capturing these moments by automatically adjusting focus when people enter or leave the frame, or when the subject of the video looks in a different direction. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/shoot-video-in-cinematic-mode-iphone-13-iphone-14/">How to Shoot Video in Cinematic Mode</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Ultra Wide-Angle Lens for Group Shots</h3><br/>
The holiday season presents the perfect opportunity to utilize the often under-utilized Ultra Wide camera lens. This lens, available on most &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models starting from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, offers unique advantages that are particularly useful during the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/12/iphone-11-pro-ultra-wide.jpg" alt="" width="2264" height="1186" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-722975" /><br/>
The Ultra Wide lens is particularly adept at photographing in confined spaces that would be difficult to capture fully with a standard Wide lens. One of the most significant advantages of the Ultra Wide lens is its ability to fit more into the frame without needing to move back. This is especially helpful during family gatherings where you might want to capture a large group of people in one photo.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Portrait Mode</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup introduced some substantial improvements to Portrait mode. Now, users can adjust the focus of an image or add background blur after its capture, even if Portrait mode isn't initially selected. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-portrait-photo.jpg" alt="" width="2503" height="1401" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-912809" /><br/>
Post-shot editing capability allows you to experiment with different focal points, ensuring that each portrait captures the subject in the most flattering and interesting way. This improvement is especially useful for snapping quick, candid shots of family members and pets over the holiday period. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s Portrait mode has also been refined to perform better in low-light conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-how-to-take-portrait-mode-photos/">iPhone 15: How to Take Portrait Mode Photos</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Photographic Styles</h3><br/>
Photographic Styles, a feature introduced in the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; series, offers a personalized photography experience that can help enhance holiday photos. The feature allows users to choose and customize a photographic style that automatically applies to their photos, ensuring that every shot reflects their preferred aesthetic. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/photographic-styles-iphone-13.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-817882" /><br/>
Photographic Styles are not one-size-fits-all filters. Instead, they are smart adjustments that apply selectively to different parts of the photo, such as skin tones and sky. Photographic Styles intelligently adapt to the lighting conditions in each shot, adjusting to preserve natural-looking skin tones and textures.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-photographic-styles-iphone-13-pro/">How to Use Photographic Styles in the Camera App</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Users can choose from preset styles like Rich Contrast, Vibrant, Warm, and Cool, each offering a unique look. During the holidays, this means you can select a style that best suits the festive mood and give your images a distinctive look.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out/">5 iPhone Camera Features to Try Out This Holiday Season</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out-this-holiday-season.2414545/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Track Santa&#039;s Journey From the North Pole Using Google&#039;s Santa Tracker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-north-pole-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole-using-googles-santa-tracker.2414541/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-north-pole-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Have you been good this year? Then you may be interested to learn that Google today launched its annual <a href="https://santatracker.google.com/">Santa tracking feature</a>, allowing Santa to be tracked in real time on his journey to the North Pole as he prepares to deliver presents to kids around the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/santa-tracker-1.jpg" alt="" width="2096" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-830800" /><br/>
Google's Santa Tracker continues a two-decade tradition for the company, allowing excited children (and grown-ups!) to keep up with the jolly gift-giver's travels throughout December 24. On this day, Santa's Village transforms into a tracking experience where children can follow Santa and his reindeer as they merrily go about their important work.<br/>
<br/>
Santa can be tracked using a web browser on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac by visiting Google's <a href="https://santatracker.google.com/">official Santa Tracking website</a>. The site features a live map of Santa's current location, his next stop, a live video feed of his journey, and the estimated time that he will arrive in each specific location.<br/>
<br/>
The Santa site provides pictures of locations that Santa has already visited, a live count of gifts that have been delivered, and Santa's current distance from your location. There are also a selection of games to play, creative things to do, and videos to watch.<br/>
<br/>
Other Santa tracking services are also available, such as the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/norad-tracks-santa-claus/id1181633163">NORAD Tracks Santa Claus app</a> and website, but Google's site is often the most interactive and detailed. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-north-pole-2/">Track Santa&#039;s Journey From the North Pole Using Google&#039;s Santa Tracker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole-using-googles-santa-tracker.2414541/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Watch Sales Ban, Next-Generation CarPlay Preview, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/23/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-ban/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-ban-next-generation-carplay-preview-and-more.2414486/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/23/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-ban/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2023 is rapidly drawing to a close with the holiday season, but that certainly doesn't mean there hasn't been any major Apple news over the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/top-stories-23dec2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927870" /><br/>
The week's biggest news was Apple's move to halt sales of its flagship Apple Watch models over a patent dispute, while Apple also squeaked in under the wire to tease the first implementation of next-generation CarPlay from a couple of car manufacturers before the end of the year. Other news and rumors this week involved an iOS 17.2.1 bug fix update, rumors about the iPhone 16 and "Apple Watch X," and more, so read on below for all the details! <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pauses Sales of Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 in U.S. Due to Patent Dispute</h2><br/>
Following an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-pausing-series-9-ultra-2-sales-in-us/">announcement earlier this week</a>, Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">"paused" online sales of the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> in the U.S. due to an ongoing patent dispute with medical tech company Masimo, which has accused Apple of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/01/09/apple-masimo-apple-watch-lawsuit/">copying its blood oxygen sensing functionality</a>. Sales in Apple's U.S. retail stores will cease after December 24, and Apple will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-import-ban-repair-issue/">unable to perform out-of-warranty hardware repairs</a> on many recent Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/apple-watch-sales-banned.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927868" /><br/>
In October, the International Trade Commission (ITC) <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered a ban on some Apple Watch imports into the U.S.</a> after finding that Apple violated Masimo's patents related to non-invasive blood oxygen sensing. U.S. President Joe Biden has until December 25 to review the order, but presidential vetoes of ITC import bans have historically been rare.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-watch-import-ban-software-fix/">working on software changes</a> to address the alleged patent infringement, but Masimo believes that the Apple Watch's hardware design will have to change to become compliant.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases iOS 17.2.1 Update for iPhone</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/19/apple-releases-ios-17-2-1/">released a minor iOS 17.2.1 update for the iPhone</a> with "important bug fixes."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.2.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927308" /><br/>
Unlike in the U.S., the release notes for iOS 17.2.1 in China and Japan indicate that the update also "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/ios-17-2-1-release-notes-battery-drain-fix/">addresses an issue that can cause the battery to drain faster</a> under certain conditions."<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3 remains in beta, and has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/ios-17-3-beta-features-so-far/">two significant new features so far</a>, including Stolen Device Protection and collaborative Apple Music playlists.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>First Vehicles With Next-Generation Apple CarPlay Previewed</h2><br/>
Aston Martin and Porsche this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed the first vehicle dashboards with support for Apple's next-generation CarPlay experience</a>, which is expected to be available at some point in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Gen-Carplay-Thumb-3.5.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927723" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">Next-generation CarPlay</a> features integration with the instrument cluster and climate controls, support for multiple displays across the dashboard, a dedicated FM radio app, widgets for apps, and more. The interface can be tailored to each specific vehicle model and automaker's brand identity.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Gurman: iPhone 16's Capture Button Will Be for Taking Video</h2><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman this week confirmed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/iphone-16-capture-button-video/">iPhone 16 models will be equipped with a new dedicated button for recording video</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPhone-16-Side-New-Action-Button-Emphasis-Bump.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917543" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> was first to report that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">iPhone 16 models would feature a so-called "Capture Button,"</a> which is expected to be positioned below the power button on the right side of the iPhones. This will require the mmWave 5G antenna window to be relocated on U.S. models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beeper Mini Says Jailbroken iPhone Solution is Final Effort</h2><br/>
Beeper promises that its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/beeper-mini-jailbreak-iphone-last-effort/">cat-and-mouse game with Apple over iMessage is ending</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Beeper-Mini-Broken-By-Apple-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927710" /><br/>
Beeper announced that its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/beeper-mini-jailbroken-iphones-rescue-imessage/">plan to let Android users use a jailbroken iPhone</a> to register a phone number with iMessage will be its final attempt at maintaining its Beeper Mini service, which is designed to let Android users use iMessage without using an iPhone as their primary smartphone. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/beeper-mini-continued-outages/">Apple has made efforts</a> to prevent the service from working.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Your Apple Watch Bands May Not Work With Next Year's Model</h2><br/>
Next-generation Apple Watch models will feature a completely redesigned band connector, rendering them <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/your-apple-watch-bands-may-not-work-with-new-model/">incompatible with all current bands</a>, according to an Apple leaker known as "Kosutami."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2014/09/apple-watch-series-8-digital-crown.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="957" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864978" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has previously reported that the upcoming "Apple Watch X" could feature a different way to attach bands to the device. Apple has allegedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">considered a magnetic band attachment system</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/dec-21-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/23/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-ban/">Top Stories: Apple Watch Sales Ban, Next-Generation CarPlay Preview, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-watch-sales-ban-next-generation-carplay-preview-and-more.2414486/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Apple Products to Look Forward to in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/top-5-apple-products-to-look-forward-to-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-5-apple-products-to-look-forward-to-in-2024.2414441/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:06:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/top-5-apple-products-to-look-forward-to-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2024 is shaping up to be a landmark year for Apple, with the company set to enter a new product category for the first time since 2015. We're counting on the Vision Pro headset, new iPads, an impressive new Apple Watch, and so much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Top-5-Apple-Products-to-Look-Forward-to-in-2024-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927759" /><br/>
Below, we've highlighted the top five most interesting Apple product updates that are set to come out in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4</h2><br/>
New AirPods coming in 2024 will have an updated design with shorter stems, so they'll look something like a cross between the current AirPods and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>. Fit and sound quality will be improved, and there is one more major change -- two models.<br/>
<br/>
There will be two versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a> at different price points, and the more expensive model will have Active Noise Cancellation, a feature that has been limited to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;. The &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; will also get an updated case that has a speaker for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> alerts and a USB-C charging port instead of a Lightning port.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a> were similar in function to the AirPods 2 and had a limited number of new features to lure customers, so a fresh look and ANC at a lower cost than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; should make the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; much more appealing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>OLED iPad Pro</h2><br/>
Apple is bringing OLED technology to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> in 2024, and it'll be the first time that Apple has released such a large OLED display. Compared to mini-LED or LED, OLED offers deeper blacks, better contrast, improved HDR, and better power efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are going to get a redesign and will come in updated 13-inch and 11.1-inch sizes. OLED displays are thinner, so Apple may be able to slim down the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, plus we can count on a faster M3 chip that's an upgrade over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> in the current model.<br/>
<br/>
We haven't had an &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; design update for years, and a new look with updated display technology is a welcome change.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch X</h2><br/>
We're due for the Apple Watch Series 10 or "X" next year, which lines up with the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch if you're counting from the 2014 introduction date rather than the 2015 launch date.<br/>
<br/>
The 2024 Apple Watch is going to get a refreshed design that may include a slimmed down body and a new magnetic band attachment system. A magnetic band attachment method would allow Apple to save valuable internal space inside the Apple Watch for a larger battery or other components, but it might mean that existing bands are not compatible with the new model.<br/>
<br/>
Along with a new look, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a> is rumored to feature blood pressure monitoring and sleep apnea detection. Blood pressure monitoring on the wrist is a notable feat, and the Apple Watch will be able to tell the user if their blood pressure is trending upwards and heading toward hypertension. Specific systolic and diastolic readings won't be available, but blood pressure monitoring will still provide valuable information.<br/>
<br/>
As for sleep apnea, the &zwnj;Apple Watch X&zwnj; will use sleep tracking and monitoring of breathing patterns to determine whether a person is possibly experiencing breathing interruptions during sleep. The information will be able to be relayed to a doctor for further testing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16</h2><br/>
The standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models will get several of the features that were limited to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, including the Action Button and a faster 3-nanometer A-series chip. The Action Button could be capacitive this year rather than mechanical, so Apple might be able to slim it down.<br/>
<br/>
A new vertical camera lens arrangement will likely allow for capturing spatial video, a feature limited to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models right now. Apple is also adding a new capacitive Capture Button to all four &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, with the button located on the right side of the device below Power button. The button will sense pressure and will support haptic feedback, and rumors suggest it will be used for capturing video.<br/>
<br/>
While the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have same design as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models will feature larger displays. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will measure in at 6.3 inches, up from 6.1 inches, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will be 6.9 inches, up from 6.7 inches.<br/>
<br/>
Other &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro-exclusive rumors include a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, Wi-Fi 7, and a faster 5G chip from Qualcomm.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro</a></h2><br/>
It's been half a year since Apple unveiled the Vision Pro headset, and in early 2024, customers are finally going to get to try it out.<br/>
<br/>
Apple sees the Vision Pro as the future of computing, referring to the device as the first spatial computer. It is a mixed reality headset, so you'll be able to swap between AR and VR using a Digital Crown on the side of the device. It won't be quite like any other headset on the market because Apple is using super high-resolution micro-LED displays with hand and eye tracking for controls.<br/>
<br/>
Immersive apps, games, and experiences are planned for the Vision Pro, and users will be able to record spatial video to play back on the device.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro isn't at the top of our list because it's not going to be for everyone. It's prohibitively expensive at &#36;3,500, and Apple is manufacturing a limited number of the headsets due to their complexity. At launch, the Vision Pro will only be sold in the United States, further limiting its availability.<br/>
<br/>
People who have been able to try out the Vision Pro have said the initial iteration can be heavy and uncomfortable to wear, which will deter some users, but even with all of these caveats, the Vision Pro is going to shape Apple's future for some time to come.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Add Yours</h2><br/>
What are you looking forward to seeing from Apple in 2024? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/top-5-apple-products-to-look-forward-to-in-2024/">Top 5 Apple Products to Look Forward to in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-5-apple-products-to-look-forward-to-in-2024.2414441/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wants to Partner With Major Publishers to Train AI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/apple-ai-major-publisher-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wants-to-partner-with-major-publishers-to-train-ai.2414433/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 13:07:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/apple-ai-major-publisher-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has approached several major publishers to establish deals that would allow the Cupertino company to train generative artificial intelligence systems on news content, reports <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/12/22/technology/apple-ai-news-publishers.html">The New York Times</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Apple is aiming for multiyear deals and has approached Condé Nast, NBC News, and IAC. <a href="https://www.condenast.com">Condé Nast publications</a> include Vogue, Wired, Vanity Fair, Ars Technica, Glamour, The New Yorker, GQ, and more, while IAC owns publications like People, The Spruce, Serious Eats, Martha Stewart Living, Real Simple, Entertainment Weekly, and Better Homes &amp; Gardens.<br/>
<br/>
Proposed deals have been worth at least &#36;50 million, and would allow Apple to license archives of news articles. According to <em>The New York Times</em>, some of the publishers were "lukewarm" on Apple's offer. Apple's terms are said to be "too expansive," and Apple has been vague about how it will apply generative AI to news.<br/>
<br/>
Other publishers were "optimistic" about a potential partnership, and were pleased that Apple asked to use their content rather than just training generative models on published news without permission as other AI companies have done.<br/>
<br/>
Multiple rumors have suggested that Apple is working overtime to catch up to its rivals on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">generative AI offerings</a>, with Apple testing an "AppleGPT" chatbot internally and planning for new AI features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft, Google, and Meta have all incorporated generative AI into their products over the course of the last year, which means Apple is lagging behind when it comes to AI technology. ChatGPT, the most popular chatbot from OpenAI, was trained on a huge amount of data that includes books, articles, and web pages.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the copyright issues that come with the broad scraping of internet content, ChatGPT has sometimes been criticized for the accuracy of the information that it sometimes surfaces. By training an AI model on a more tailored set of information, Apple could end up with a more reliable product. Apple is also said to be planning to incorporate generative AI features across its app offerings, so a model that has been fed content from news sources could perhaps be added into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The New York Times</em> says that Apple executives have been "debating" how to get the data needed for generative AI products. Apple has not wanted to source information from the internet because of its focus on privacy, so deals with news publishers provide an alternative.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/apple-ai-major-publisher-deals/">Apple Wants to Partner With Major Publishers to Train AI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wants-to-partner-with-major-publishers-to-train-ai.2414433/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17: 10 Features You Might Not Know About</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/ios-17-ten-hidden-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-10-features-you-might-not-know-about.2414424/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 11:18:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/ios-17-ten-hidden-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> has been available for a few months now, but there are so many new features in the update that some have gone under the radar. There are also hidden settings and little tweaks and changes that you might not know about, so we thought we'd round up some of the lesser-known &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; features.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zPFksPy78fU" title="New iOS 17 Tips &amp; Hidden Features!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Messages</strong> - If you hold down the "+" button in the Messages app, you can get right to the photo picker to send an image. It's quicker than tapping "+" and then tapping on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> to get to your images.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Links in Mail</strong> - To add a link to text in the Mail app, copy a link, select the text, and then paste it to turn the text into a hyperlink.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Add Text to Shapes</strong> - In the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, if you've added a shape to an image using Markup, double tap it to be able to insert text.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Laundry Symbols</strong> - You can use the Visual Look Up feature on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to figure out what a laundry symbol means. Just take a picture and tap on the Visual Look Up symbol in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app to get symbol information.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Apple Watch Ping</strong> - In the Control Center, there's a new option to ping your Apple Watch from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in case you misplace your Apple Watch.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Focus Mode Silence Notifications</strong> - When setting up a Focus Mode, you can now choose to silence notifications always or only when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Journal App Lock</strong> - If you want to keep your journal entries secure, you can turn on the "Lock Journal" option in the Settings app to require <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> to open up the Journal app.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Journaling Schedule</strong> - Having trouble remembering to use the Journal app? Enable Journaling Schedule in the Journal section of the Settings app to get a reminder to add a journal entry at a specific day and time.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Adjust Haptic Touch Speed</strong> - Under Accessibility &gt; Touch &gt; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/haptic-touch-vs-3d-touch-whats-the-difference/">Haptic Touch</a> you can adjust the time that it takes to activate content with a long press. Options include fast, default, and slow, and the fast setting makes haptic touch feel closer to the now-removed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3d-touch/">3D Touch</a> feature.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Shake to Undo</strong> - If you've move a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> app or a widget and then change your mind on the position, you can use a shake to undo gesture to put the apps and widgets back where they were before you made the adjustment. </li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Know of a hidden &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; feature that we didn't mention here? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/ios-17-ten-hidden-features/">iOS 17: 10 Features You Might Not Know About</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-10-features-you-might-not-know-about.2414424/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: 2024 Apple Rumor Q&amp;A</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-qa/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-q-a.2414415/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:02:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-qa/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As 2023 begins to draw to a close, on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/apple-watch-is-officially-banned-2024-rumor-q-a/id1602394741?i=1000639463892">The MacRumors Show</a> we take your questions about Apple rumors and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/avzNQtZdwR4?si=-LdIvZFgw0OOQIwP" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We answer your queries about the chances of another Apple event for Vision Pro, whether the device really has the potential to replace the Mac, and the potential "failure" of the headset. We also talk <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> accessories, when new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> models could launch, the potential of more <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> models adopting a landscape front-facing camera, and the usefulness of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> charging on next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models, as well as when we could see an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> update that adds app sideloading capabilities in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so head over and subscribe to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/the-macrumors-show-imessage-on-android/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the recent controversy surrounding Android apps that seek to enable iMessage functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-qa/">The MacRumors Show: 2024 Apple Rumor Q&amp;A</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-2024-apple-rumor-q-a.2414415/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Department of Justice and FTC Looking Into Beeper iMessage Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/doj-and-ftc-looking-into-beeper-controversy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/department-of-justice-and-ftc-looking-into-beeper-imessage-controversy.2414405/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 06:35:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/doj-and-ftc-looking-into-beeper-controversy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>New York Times</category>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Department of Justice (DOJ) and Federal Trade Commission (FTC) are intensifying their investigations into Apple's alleged anti-competitive practices following the recent blocking of the iMessage for Android app Beeper Mini, the <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/12/22/technology/apple-iphone-beeper-mini.html">New York Times</a></em> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Beeper-Mini-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-926724" /><br/>
Following calls from a bipartisan group of senators for a DOJ investigation into the matter, Beeper founder Eric Migicovsky reportedly met with DOJ antitrust lawyers on Tuesday, December 12. The DOJ is currently embroiled in a four-year-long investigation into Apple's alleged anticompetitive conduct.<br/>
<br/>
The <em>New York Times</em> also suggested that the FTC is involved, pointing to a <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/policy/advocacy-research/tech-at-ftc/2023/12/interoperability-privacy-security">blog post</a> published yesterday by the commission warning that it will evaluate "privacy and security" justifications for refusing to interoperate with other companies' technology:<blockquote>In the face of concerns about anticompetitive conduct, companies may claim privacy and security reasons as justifications for refusing to have their products and services interoperate with other companies' products and services. As an agency that enforces both competition and consumer protection laws, the Commission is uniquely situated to evaluate claims of privacy and data security that implicate competition.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Beeper <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/beeper-mini-brings-imessage-to-android/">launched Beeper Mini</a> earlier this month, aiming to bridge the gap between Android and iMessage. Apple quickly moved to shut down the app, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/apple-confirms-it-shut-down-beeper-mini/">citing security concerns</a> and unauthorized access to its iMessage servers.<br/>
<br/>
Despite multiple attempts by Beeper to circumvent Apple's restrictions, the company has now effectively <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/beeper-mini-jailbreak-iphone-last-effort/">admitted defeat</a>, touting jailbroken iPhones as the final solution to keep the service up and running amid an acknowledgement of the unsustainable nature of its efforts. While Apple has consistently defended its actions as necessary for maintaining user security and the integrity of its services, increased attention from two major regulatory bodies indicates the seriousness of ongoing antitrust allegations against the company.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nytimes-com/">New York Times</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/doj-and-ftc-looking-into-beeper-controversy/">Department of Justice and FTC Looking Into Beeper iMessage Controversy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/department-of-justice-and-ftc-looking-into-beeper-imessage-controversy.2414405/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Infinite Loop Store Permanently Closing Next Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apples-infinite-loop-store-closing-next-month/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-infinite-loop-store-permanently-closing-next-month.2414366/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 13:03:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apples-infinite-loop-store-closing-next-month/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today confirmed that it will be permanently closing its <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/infiniteloop/">Infinite Loop retail store</a> in Cupertino, California on January 20. Infinite Loop served as Apple's headquarters between the mid-1990s and 2017, when its current Apple Park headquarters opened a few miles away.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-Infinite-Loop-Store.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1612" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927735" /><br/>
Apple will be offering all employees at the store the opportunity to continue working with the company. A source informed us that at least some employees will be able to relocate to nearby stores, including the <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/appleparkvisitorcenter/">Apple Park Visitor Center</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/valleyfair/">Apple Valley Fair</a>.<br/>
<br/>
"After many years of serving customers at our stores in the Bay Area, we plan to close our store at Infinite Loop," an Apple spokesperson said, in a statement shared with <em>MacRumors</em>. "All of our valued team members will have the opportunity to continue their roles with Apple. We look forward to welcoming our customers at our nearby Apple Park Visitor Center and other locations, on Apple.com, and the Apple Store app."<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also <a href="https://www.kitv.com/news/business/apple-store-in-royal-hawaiian-center-closing-in-january-2024/article_f4bb8ae6-87d9-11ee-a6f9-673f5ba817a9.html">permanently closing its Royal Hawaiian store</a> in Honolulu on January 20. Apple said it remains committed to "providing an excellent experience for our customers," and noted it has opened new stores this year in the U.S., China, India, South Korea, and the U.K., plus expanded its online store to Chile and Vietnam.<br/>
<br/>
The offices at the Infinite Loop campus will continue to be used by Apple's corporate employees, with only the store closing. The main building's atrium is under construction until early 2024, according to a sign posted outside the entrance.<br/>
<br/>
The store first opened in 1993 as The Company Store, and it focused primarily on selling Apple-branded merchandise. Following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/19/apple-store-infinite-loop/">renovations in 2015</a>, it reopened as a more traditional Apple retail store, with products like the iPhone, Mac, and Apple Watch displayed on beige tables, but it continued to sell a limited selection of merchandise, like t-shirts, reusable bottles, mugs, and notebooks. The store is one of Apple's smaller locations, and it does not offer Genius Bar appointments or "Today at Apple" creative sessions.<br/>
<br/>
Infinite Loop is a popular attraction for Apple enthusiasts, who often make the pilgrimage to the campus and the store. However, it has been overshadowed by the Apple Park Visitor Center since that location opened in 2017.<br/>
<br/>
A different collection of Apple-branded merchandise is available for purchase at the Apple Park Visitor Center, and the location also serves as a traditional Apple retail store. Other features at the Visitor Center include a Caffè Macs coffee bar, a rooftop patio with a seating area, and a large AR model of the Apple Park campus.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apples-infinite-loop-store-closing-next-month/">Apple&#039;s Infinite Loop Store Permanently Closing Next Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-infinite-loop-store-permanently-closing-next-month.2414366/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 No Longer Available From U.S. Online Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-apple-watch-ultra-2-no-longer-available-from-u-s-online-store.2414360/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As promised, Apple today stopped selling the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> in its online store in the United States, with the devices pulled from sale just days ahead of when an Apple Watch import ban goes into effect. When attempting to purchase an &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; or &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; to the online store, the devices say "currently unavailable." Apple has also removed refurbished Apple Watch Series 7 and Series 8 models from its website. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/apple-watch-ultra-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875262" /><br/>
Apple on Monday said that it would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-pausing-series-9-ultra-2-sales-in-us/">need to pause sales</a> of the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; in order to comply with an International Trade Commission order preventing components related to the Apple Watch blood oxygen monitoring technology from being imported into the United States. The ITC made the ruling after deciding that the Apple Watch blood oxygen sensor violates patents owned by medical device company Masimo.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch is still available for purchase from Apple's retail stores, but Apple will stop store sales after December 24. Sales will be paused only in the United States and only at Apple's own retail locations. Third-party stores like Target, Walmart, and Best Buy can continue to sell the Apple Watch until supplies run out. Apple will be able to sell the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, as it does not have a blood oxygen sensor.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could reinstate sales if the White House vetoes the import ban, and it has until December 25 to review the order and decide whether to intervene. If the White House does not veto the import ban, Apple will not be able to sell the Apple Watch until it removes the infringing technology.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning to appeal as soon as it can on December 26, and the company said it is "pursuing a range of legal and technical options" to get the Apple Watch models back on store shelves as soon as possible.<br/>
<br/>
Apple believes that a software fix might be enough to mitigate the problem, and Apple engineers are adjusting how oxygen saturation is determined and how the data is provided to customers. Apple said that it is working to submit a workaround to US Customs to get the ban lifted, but it is unclear if a software fix will be sufficient because the patents in question pertain to the hardware.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 No Longer Available From U.S. Online Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-apple-watch-ultra-2-no-longer-available-from-u-s-online-store.2414360/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Won&#039;t Be Able to Repair Out-of-Warranty Apple Watches Due to Import Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-import-ban-repair-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wont-be-able-to-repair-out-of-warranty-apple-watches-due-to-import-ban.2414359/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:51:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-import-ban-repair-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ITC</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When the Apple Watch import ban goes into effect after December 25, 2023, Apple will not be able to repair out-of-warranty Apple Watch models in the United States. Apple Watch repairs typically involve replacing a broken unit with a new model rather than fixing an individual component, and replacement devices will not be available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/apple-watch-ultra-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-879886" /><br/>
Apple shared the news with retail employees in a memo that was sent out this week. Portions of the memo were seen by <em>MacRumors</em>, and it was also shared by <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-21/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-ban-means-no-repairs-on-out-of-warranty-models">Bloomberg</a></em>. Apple is set to stop all U.S. online sales of the Apple Watch in just a few hours, with in-store sales to cease after December 24.<br/>
<br/>
"Product replacement (CRU) programs aren't available in the United States for the watches below: Apple Watch Series 6 or later, Apple Watch Ultra or later," reads the memo.<br/>
<br/>
Apple cannot provide replacements for any out-of-warranty Apple Watch with a blood oxygen sensor, which includes the Apple Watch Series 6 and later and the original Apple Watch Ultra. Customers who damage their Apple Watch will need to wait on repairs until hardware replacements are available again. Software-based repairs will remain available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch models that are under warranty are allowed to be replaced. This includes both the standard one-year warranty for new devices and devices protected through an extended <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> warranty.<br/>
<br/>
Customers will not be able to exchange an Apple Watch after the ban comes into effect, but accessories like bands can be replaced and returns will be accepted.<br/>
<br/>
The United States International Trade Commission is putting a stop to imports of Apple Watches with blood oxygen sensing technology, which means Apple cannot bring them to the United States from overseas where they are manufactured. The ITC in October said that Apple infringed on blood oxygen patents owned by medical device company Masimo, and set the ban for December 25.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could avoid a pause in sales if the White House steps in and vetoes the ban, but that has not happened as of yet. The White House has until December 25 to make a decision.<br/>
<br/>
Other options include settling the dispute with Masimo, which would involve Apple having to pay Masimo to license the patent technology, or removing the infringing technology. Apple is working on a software fix for the Apple Watch blood oxygen sensing algorithm that it believes will be sufficient to get the Apple Watch back on store shelves.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple has to stop selling the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> will remain available. Third-party retailers like Best Buy, Target, and Walmart will also be able to continue sales of all Apple Watch models while supplies last.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itc/">ITC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-import-ban-repair-issue/">Apple Won&#039;t Be Able to Repair Out-of-Warranty Apple Watches Due to Import Ban</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wont-be-able-to-repair-out-of-warranty-apple-watches-due-to-import-ban.2414359/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Offering Free Two-Hour Delivery for Last-Minute Gifts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-free-two-hour-delivery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offering-free-two-hour-delivery-for-last-minute-gifts.2414356/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:31:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-free-two-hour-delivery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began sending out emails to customers letting them know about a free two-hour delivery option on a selection of products available from its online store. Apple says that customers can get free delivery when ordering online before 12:00 p.m. on Sunday, December 24. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/apple-free-two-hour-delivery.jpg" alt="" width="1993" height="1121" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927715" /><br/>
Courier delivery will be used for these orders, and the option usually costs &#36;9 in the United States. Courier deliveries are provided by companies like Uber and Postmates, and the shipping option is available on Apple products in metro areas in the United States and Canada. In Australia, free three-hour delivery is available.  <br/>
<br/>
Devices eligible for free two-hour shipping include the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, AirPods, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, with other non-Apple products and accessories not included in the offer. Note that the Apple Watch may only be available for a limited time as online sales in the U.S. are set to stop today.<br/>
<br/>
Many other products are still available for free express shipping from Apple at this time, but free two-hour delivery will be an option up until Christmas Eve. <br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-free-two-hour-delivery/">Apple Offering Free Two-Hour Delivery for Last-Minute Gifts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offering-free-two-hour-delivery-for-last-minute-gifts.2414356/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Record Low MacBook Deals Include Massive &#36;300 Discount on 15-Inch MacBook Air, Starting at &#36;999</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/new-record-low-macbook-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-record-low-macbook-deals-include-massive-300-discount-on-15-inch-macbook-air-starting-at-999.2414354/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 10:17:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/new-record-low-macbook-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're highlighting a few record low prices on the MacBook Air and MacBook Pro, all of which are available at Best Buy. The highlight of the sale is the <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN">256GB 15-inch MacBook Air</a> for &#36;999.00, a &#36;300 discount and all-time low price on the notebook.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923153" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The deal on the MacBook Air does not require a <a href="https://howl.me/clfvrWQFexb">My Best Buy Plus or Total membership</a>, but the MacBook Pro sales do require a membership. These start at &#36;49.99 per year and grant exclusive access to certain deals, extended return windows, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Best Buy still has a few options that ensure delivery before Christmas, including same and next-day shipping, as well as in-store pickup if your local Best Buy has stock. We are quickly approaching deadlines even for these options, so if you're still shopping be sure to place orders today or tomorrow to ensure delivery before the 25th.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>15-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/15in-macbook-air-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923161" /><br/>
<br/>
Previously, this &#36;300 markdown on the 15-inch MacBook Air was exclusive to My Best Buy Plus/Total members, but this massive deal is now available to everyone.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15.3-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There's also the 512GB 15.3-inch M2 MacBook Air at &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,499.00, which is another steep &#36;300 markdown on the 2023 MacBook Air. You'll find every color on sale for both of these computers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxm6NM1wV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15.3-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><h2>14-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/16in-macbook-pro-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923158" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 512GB 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro is available for a record low &#36;1,349.00 for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,599.00. Non-members can still purchase the notebook at a solid second-best price of &#36;1,399.00.<br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has the 1TB 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro for &#36;1,549.00, down from &#36;1,799.00. This one is a also a new all-time low price at &#36;250 off, and it's again only available for My Best Buy Plus and My Best Buy Total members. The non-member price of &#36;1,599.00 is still an excellent discount, however.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck8G8OHT1KE"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 512GB) for &#36;1,349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck8Hb3SFzUT"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 1TB) for &#36;1,549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are a few higher-end M3 Pro and M3 Max models on sale as well, and solid low prices across the board. These also require My Best Buy Plus or Total memberships.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clfT9OqCUyV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (11-Core M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clfUbnWr9yl"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M3 Pro, 1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clfUctFG8WS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (14-Core M3 Max, 1TB) for &#36;2,949.00</div></a></div><h2>16-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/14in-macbook-pro-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923159" /><br/>
<br/>
You'll find similar discounts on the 16-inch models of the new MacBook Pro, with up to &#36;300 off select models for My Best Buy Plus/Total members and second-best prices for everyone else.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clfUfJ9rzYM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB) for &#36;2,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clfUgS6eVHF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB) for &#36;2,599.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clfUeeUi1gZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (16-Core M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB) for &#36;3,749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/new-record-low-macbook-deals/">New Record Low MacBook Deals Include Massive &#36;300 Discount on 15-Inch MacBook Air, Starting at &#36;999</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-record-low-macbook-deals-include-massive-300-discount-on-15-inch-macbook-air-starting-at-999.2414354/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
