<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 03:00:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>These 5 Features Will Make the iPhone 17 the Biggest Update in Years</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-5-major-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-5-features-will-make-the-iphone-17-the-biggest-update-in-years.2431980/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 16:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-5-major-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">upcoming iPhone 16 models</a> that we're expecting to see in September are going to be quite similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, but rumors suggest that Apple is making big changes in 2025. We've been hearing hints of an all-new device in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup, and it may be the most expensive &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Apple has offered to date.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iPhone-17-Plus-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959520" /><br/>
<h2>New 'Slim' Design</h2><br/>
Rumors have taken to referring to the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> that Apple has planned as the "&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim," but Apple almost certainly won't use that naming. The "slim" descriptor references the sleeker, thinner design of the device.<br/>
<br/>
With the 12.9-inch M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> model, Apple shaved over a millimeter off of the thickness, resulting in the thinnest device Apple has made to date. That same focus on a svelte design is expected in 2025, and the upcoming &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is said to be "significantly thinner" than current iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
We don't know specifics on just how thin Apple is going to make this &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is just 5.1mm thick and could serve as a blueprint on what to expect.<br/>
<br/>
As for size, the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim is expected to fall somewhere between the 6.1-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and the 6.7-inch &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. Separate rumors have targeted <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">6.55 inches</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-rumor/">6.6 inches</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/">6.65 inches</a> as the display size that Apple has settled on, which would make it smaller than the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max (and the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max).<br/>
<br/>
Though Apple has used titanium for the higher-end &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models since last year, the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim is rumored to have an aluminum chassis. The first rumors that surfaced about the device actually indicated that it would replace the "Plus" &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in Apple's lineup, but later information points toward a new high-end &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that's even more expensive than the Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
Based on the rumors we've heard so far, it sounds like the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim will be akin to the 2017 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X marked a major jump forward in technology, and it was sold alongside the standard &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8 models.<br/>
<br/>
It's sounding like we're going to get an &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, an &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro, an &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro Max, and this new high-end &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim, with Apple eliminating the Plus model entirely. The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim could be more expensive than the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, which Apple currently starts at &#36;1,199.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Relocated Cameras</h2><br/>
Along with a thinner and lighter design, the high-end &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; could feature the first major rear camera overhaul. Rumors suggest that the cameras could be relocated from the top-left corner of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the top center, which could result in a design similar to the Google Pixel.<br/>
<br/>
The Pixel 8 Pro has a raised band across the back of the device that houses a trio of cameras, a laser detect auto focus sensor, and a flash.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is still testing designs for the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, but the relocated camera bump is a possibility.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Display Improvements</h2><br/>
ProMotion display technology that allows for variable refresh rates from 1Hz to 120Hz is expected for all &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models in 2025, including the high-end model, but the bigger news is that Apple is rumored to be using a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/">new display coating</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The new coating is said to have improved anti-reflective properties and better scratch resistance than the current Ceramic Shield coating. It's been described as a "super-hard anti-reflective layer" in leaks.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has used Ceramic Shield since 2020. It's a ceramic-glass hybrid material developed in partnership with Corning. Corning has since made improvements in its protective glass products, and the company's <a href="https://www.corning.com/gorillaglass/worldwide/en/corning-gorilla-armor.html">Gorilla Armor material</a> reduces reflectance by up to 75 percent while also boosting drop protection and scratch resistance. Corning has had a longtime relationship with Apple, and while Gorilla Armor was developed for Samsung, Corning could make a similar product for Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Better Selfie Cam and Dynamic Island Changes</h2><br/>
A slimmed down <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> that takes up less screen space is expected for the new &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;. There have been rumors for years about under-display <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> technology, and we could see the first hints of it in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
There will be a smaller hole and pill-shaped cutout for the front-facing camera, but it doesn't sound like Apple is going to reach its all-display design goals just yet.<br/>
<br/>
As part of the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj; redesign, Apple is rumored to be adopting a 24-megapixel front-facing camera, which would be an upgrade over the current 12-megapixel selfie camera. It will feature a six-element lens for improved image quality, and the boost in resolution will capture more detail and allow for more cropping in without sacrificing quality.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Faster Chips</h2><br/>
It sounds like &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; series won't get TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/iphone-17-unlikely-to-get-2nm-chip/">next-generation 2-nanometer chips</a>, but we are expecting A19 chip technology that's likely built on an upgraded 3-nanometer process. Apple typically upgrades iPhones with faster and more efficient chip technology each year, and we're expecting the best chip available in 2025 to be included in the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC is working on 2nm chips, but mass production isn't expected until the end of 2025, which would be too late for the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models. If work speeds up, that could change. Compared to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> chip technology, 2nm fabrication process could bring a 10 to 15 percent speed improvement at the same power or a 25 to 30 percent power reduction at the same speed.<br/>
<br/>
Chips built on an upgraded 3-nanometer process won't have the same gains as chips built on the 2-nanometer process, but we can still count on modest boosts to CPU and GPU speeds. With Apple's heavy focus on AI, the dedicated Neural Engine for machine learning tasks is also likely to see improvement.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC is working on its N3P process, with mass production set to begin in late 2024. <a href="https://www.anandtech.com/show/21394/tsmc-performanceoptimized-3nm-process-technology-on-track-for-mass-production-this-year">Compared to earlier versions</a> of &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; chips, the N3P chips offer increased performance efficiency and increased transistor density.<br/>
<br/>
Up to 12GB RAM has been rumored for the high-end &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models, and that jump would make sense in the more expensive &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Slim. Currently, RAM maxes out at 8GB.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Read More</h2><br/>
For more on what to expect from the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; lineup in 2025, make sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/"><strong>check out our iPhone 17 roundup</strong></a>. Our roundups receive regular updates with all of the latest rumors, making them a great resource for tracking rumor development over time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-5-major-features/">These 5 Features Will Make the iPhone 17 the Biggest Update in Years</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-5-features-will-make-the-iphone-17-the-biggest-update-in-years.2431980/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google No Longer Plans to Eliminate Third-Party Cookies in Chrome</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/google-keeping-third-party-cookies-chrome/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-no-longer-plans-to-eliminate-third-party-cookies-in-chrome.2431972/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:57:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/google-keeping-third-party-cookies-chrome/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google no longer plans to deprecate third-party cookies in the Chrome browser, marking a notable change to a prior decision to phase out third-party cookies by 2025. Google announced its cookie updates <a href="https://privacysandbox.com/intl/en_us/news/privacy-sandbox-update/">in a blog post</a> shared today, where the company said that it instead plans to focus on user choice.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
Rather than eliminating third-party cookies entirely, Google will introduce "a new experience in Chrome" that is designed to allow people to "make an informed choice" applicable across their web browsing.<br/>
<br/>
Back in 2020, Google claimed that it would phase out support for third-party cookies in Chrome by 2022, a timeline that was pushed back multiple times due to complaints from advertisers and regulatory issues. Google has been working on a Privacy Sandbox to find ways to improve privacy while still delivering info to advertisers, but third-party cookies will now be sticking around so as not to impact publishers and advertisers.<br/>
<br/>
The UK's Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) had opposed Google's plan to stop relying on third-party cookies because a shift to Privacy Sandbox could limit competition in digital advertising, and now the CMA says that it is <a href="https://x.com/CMAgovUK/status/1815465046689882274">reviewing Google's new plan</a> for a user-choice prompt.<br/>
<br/>
Google does not plan to stop working on its Privacy Sandbox APIs, and the company says they will improve over time so that developers will have a privacy preserving alternative to cookies. Additional privacy controls, such as IP Protection, will be added to Chrome's Incognito mode.<br/>
<br/>
As of now, the new customer choices that Google is planning for are being discussed with regulators, with more information to come at a later date.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/google-keeping-third-party-cookies-chrome/">Google No Longer Plans to Eliminate Third-Party Cookies in Chrome</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-no-longer-plans-to-eliminate-third-party-cookies-in-chrome.2431972/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Blames European Commission for Major Worldwide Outage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/microsoft-blames-european-commission-for-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-blames-european-commission-for-major-worldwide-outage.2431960/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 11:55:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/microsoft-blames-european-commission-for-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last Friday, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/">a major CrowdStrike outage</a> impacted PCs running Microsoft Windows, causing worldwide issues affecting airlines, retailers, banks, hospitals, rail networks, and more. Computers were stuck in continuous recovery loops, rendering them unusable.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959336" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bsod.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The failure was caused by an update to the CrowdStrike Falcon antivirus software that auto-installed on Windows 10 PCs, but Mac and Linux machines were not affected even though they received the same software. A report from <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/cybersecurity/microsoft-tech-outage-role-crowdstrike-50917b90">The Wall Street Journal</a></em> delves into what happened and includes some critical information from Microsoft on why Macs did not get taken out by the update.<br/>
<br/>
On Windows machines, CrowdStrike's Falcon security software is a kernel module, which gives the software full access to a PC. The kernel manages memory, processes, files, and devices, and it's basically the heart of the operating system. Much of the software on a PC is typically limited to user mode, where bad code can't cause harm, but software with kernel mode access can cause catastrophic total machine failures, like what was encountered last week.<br/>
<br/>
The Falcon software was not able to wreak similar havoc on Macs because Apple does not give software makers kernel access. In macOS Catalina, which came out in 2019, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/18/apple-updates-platform-security-guide/">deprecated kernel extensions</a> and transitioned to system extensions that run in a user space instead of at a kernel level. The change made Macs more stable and more secure, adding protection against unstable software updates like the one CrowdStrike pushed out. It is not possible for Macs to have a similar failure because of the change that Apple made.<br/>
<br/>
In a statement to <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em>, Microsoft blamed the European Commission for an inability to offer the same protections that Macs have. Microsoft said that it is unable to wall off its operating system because of an "understanding" with the European Commission. <a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2009/12/16/microsoft-statement-on-european-commission-decision/">Back in 2009</a>, Microsoft agreed to interoperability rules that provide third-party security apps with the same level of access to Windows that Microsoft gets. Microsoft agreed to provide kernel access in order to resolve multiple longstanding competition law issues in Europe.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not been forced to make changes to how Macs work, but the European Commission has been targeting the closed nature of iOS, and Apple has warned that the updates <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/dma-and-apps-in-the-eu/">that have already been implemented</a> could lead to security risks in the future. The European Union's Digital Markets Act has pushed Apple to allow developers to offer apps through third-party marketplaces and websites. Apple says explicitly that the DMA compromises its ability to "detect, prevent, and take action against malicious apps."<br/>
<br/>
The major CrowdStrike failure that affected Windows PCs highlights some of the unintended consequences and the tradeoffs inherent in legislation that weakens security in the name of open access. CrowdStrike's simple software update impacted global infrastructure, bringing travel, commerce, and healthcare to a standstill.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft does not seem to have a way to stop a recurrence because it can't cut off kernel access. The company says that significant incidents "are infrequent" and that less than one percent of all Windows machines were impacted. CrowdStrike says that it is "deeply sorry for the inconvenience and disruption," and that in the future, it will share the steps that it is taking to prevent a similar situation.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/microsoft-blames-european-commission-for-outage/">Microsoft Blames European Commission for Major Worldwide Outage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-blames-european-commission-for-major-worldwide-outage.2431960/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Classical Gains New Top 100 Chart</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-music-classical-top-100-chart/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-classical-gains-new-top-100-chart.2431946/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:23:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-music-classical-top-100-chart/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music Classical</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added a Classical Top 100 chart to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> Classical, the classical music streaming service that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/28/apple-music-classical-now-available/">introduced in early 2023</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Apple-Music-Classical-hero.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890191" /><br/>
The list features the most popular classical music albums that are streamed globally, combining five data sources from more than 165 countries. Top 100 comes from &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical streams, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; streams, iTunes downloads, iTunes song sales, and Shazam tags.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the Classical Top 100 list is the most comprehensive classical music chart available. The first number one album is Bach: Keyboard Concertos with Chinese pianist Tianqi Du and the Academy of St Martins in the Fields conducted by Jonathan Bloxham. The top five albums feature artists from Canada, China, Brazil, Latvia, Norway, and the UK, and encompass everything from full orchestral symphonies to solo guitar.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to update the Apple Classical Top 100 list each Monday, and it can be found on the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical Home tab. Each chart includes activity from the prior week.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical is a standalone music app designed for classical music lovers and musicians. It has the world's largest classical music catalogue, and it can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for free. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-music-classical/id1598433714">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-classical/">Apple Music Classical</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-music-classical-top-100-chart/">Apple Music Classical Gains New Top 100 Chart</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-classical-gains-new-top-100-chart.2431946/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sports App for iPhone Updated With MLS and MLB Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-sports-updated-for-mls-mlb/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-for-iphone-updated-with-mls-and-mlb-improvements.2431943/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:21:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-sports-updated-for-mls-mlb/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated its <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-sports/id6446788829">Sports app for iPhone</a> with some changes related to Major League Soccer and Major League Baseball.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Sports-App-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1961" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937385" /><br/>
The release notes for version 1.5 of Apple Sports indicate that the app now supports Leagues Cup matches between MLS and Liga MX clubs, and the latest version also features an indicator in MLB box scores for pitcher statistics.<br/>
<br/>
The release notes:<blockquote>• Follow live as every MLS and Liga MX club competes for the Leagues Cup.<br/>
• Added an indicator to MLB box scores for pitcher wins, losses, and saves.</blockquote>Released in February, the Apple Sports app shows scores, schedules, stats, and more for a variety of leagues, such as the NBA, NHL, MLB, MLS, and Premier League. The app also displays real-time play-by-play information for ongoing games.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports is available for free <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-sports/id6446788829">on the App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-sports-updated-for-mls-mlb/">Apple Sports App for iPhone Updated With MLS and MLB Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-for-iphone-updated-with-mls-and-mlb-improvements.2431943/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung&#039;s &#039;Black Friday In July&#039; Sale Features Lowest-Ever Prices on Popular Monitors and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/samsung-black-friday-in-july/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-black-friday-in-july-sale-features-lowest-ever-prices-on-popular-monitors-and-more.2431939/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:56:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/samsung-black-friday-in-july/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung is hosting a new <a href="https://howl.me/cmH18MxkNu2">"Black Friday in July" sale</a>, which includes big discounts on multiple product lines sitewide. The popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and new Smart Monitor M80D are both discounted during this sale, but you'll also find sales on storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-smart-monitor-m80d-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958530" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The Smart Monitor M80D was announced at CES in January and launched in early June. The display retains key features of the previous model, like USB-C charging connectivity, AirPlay 2 support, an integrated webcam, and several smart TV features that enable it to be used when not connected to a PC. It's on sale today for <a href="https://howl.me/cmEbIKKFC8A"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a>, which is a new all-time low price and beats the previous deal from earlier in the month by about &#36;50.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbIKKFC8A"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>32-inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In terms of new features, the M80D includes a Multi Control feature that allows images and text to be moved between the display and a Galaxy Book, Tablet, or Phone. You can also pair Galaxy Buds to the monitor for a spatial audio experience with head tracking, as well as guided workouts when paired with a Galaxy Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/viewfinity-s9-samsung-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958532" /><br/>
You can also get the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for <a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. At &#36;700 off this is an all-time low price on the 2023 display, which has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up a few more discounts below on TVs, monitors, and Galaxy products, but remember that this sale is sitewide and you can save on many more devices, including <a href="https://howl.me/cmh4mcpiYhQ">household appliances and more</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXYAoJPWk">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXY1mXjV0">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmh387N2uIj">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZtLQWw9">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmh365mLB6T">The Frame TV</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZZbVCrL">70-inch QLED 4K QE1C TV</a> - &#36;1,229.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX0OsAHAg">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1gp9dhd">55-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX2c09le2">85-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;2,599.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Galaxy Products</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbV7Ybcky">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,500 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbXJFsJWi">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbYxetDfM">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;480</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbZknUAIi">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;180</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/samsung-black-friday-in-july/">Samsung&#039;s &#039;Black Friday In July&#039; Sale Features Lowest-Ever Prices on Popular Monitors and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-black-friday-in-july-sale-features-lowest-ever-prices-on-popular-monitors-and-more.2431939/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Rumored to Launch Early Next Year With OLED Display, 48MP Camera, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-launch-early-next-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-launch-early-next-year-with-oled-display-48mp-camera-and-more.2431934/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:22:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-launch-early-next-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Ice Universe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The fourth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> will offer a series of major upgrades over the current model, the leaker known as "Ice Universe" claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
The information was listed in a <a href="https://weibo.com/5673255066/OoxQuAnxl?pagetype=profilefeed">post on Weibo</a>, which also detailed the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/">specifications of the iPhone 17 lineup</a>. As previously rumored, the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is expected to feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> and USB-C, marking a major upgrade from current and previous models that have all featured a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> Home button and a Lightning port.<br/>
<br/>
The device's display will apparently grow in size from 4.7 inches to 6.06 inches and feature an OLED panel for the first time. The new &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is also expected to tout an A18 chip like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, 6GB to 8GB of LPDDR5 memory, an aluminum chassis, and a single rear 48-megapixel camera. The fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will apparently launch between March and May of 2025 with a price point of &#36;499 to &#36;549. The current model launched in March 2022 for &#36;429.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ice-universe/">Ice Universe</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-launch-early-next-year/">iPhone SE 4 Rumored to Launch Early Next Year With OLED Display, 48MP Camera, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-launch-early-next-year-with-oled-display-48mp-camera-and-more.2431934/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Max Drop to New All-Time Low Price of &#36;382.70 on Amazon [Update: Expired]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/airpods-max-new-all-time-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-drop-to-new-all-time-low-price-of-382-70-on-amazon-update-expired.2431928/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:37:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/airpods-max-new-all-time-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's high-end AirPods Max headphones have dropped to a new record low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJ8FZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;382.70</strong></a> in Pink, down from &#36;549.00. This deal is only available in the Pink colorway right now, and it beats the Prime Day price by about &#36;12.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/AirPods-Max-Deal-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-805804" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Prime members can get the AirPods Max delivered as soon as July 24, while most other customers can expect a delivery by this Sunday, July 28. AirPods deals were very popular last week during Prime Day, but now the AirPods Max is the only model with a deal that beats those prices, although you can find some solid second-best prices on AirPods 2 and AirPods Pro 2 on Amazon this week.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJ8FZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;166 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;382.70</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This deal has expired.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/airpods-max-new-all-time-low/">AirPods Max Drop to New All-Time Low Price of &#36;382.70 on Amazon [Update: Expired]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-drop-to-new-all-time-low-price-of-382-70-on-amazon-update-expired.2431928/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Curbs Costs After Expensive Projects Fail to Capture Viewers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-tv-plus-curbs-costs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-curbs-costs-after-expensive-projects-fail-to-capture-viewers.2431925/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:11:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-tv-plus-curbs-costs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is scaling back its Hollywood spending after investing over &#36;20 billion in original programming with limited success, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-07-21/apple-tries-to-rein-in-hollywood-spending-after-years-of-losses"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-TV-Plus-Feature-2-Magenta-and-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959290" /><br/>
This shift comes after the streaming service, which launched in 2019, struggled to capture a significant share of the market, accounting for only 0.2% of TV viewership in the U.S., compared to Netflix's 8%. Despite heavy investment, critical acclaim, and numerous award nominations, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> purportedly generates less viewing in one month than Netflix does in a single day.<br/>
<br/>
Over the last five years, the &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; has had only four series make Nielsen's weekly list of the ten most popular original streaming shows. While <em>Ted Lasso</em> was the most-watched streaming show of 2023, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; still accounts for a smaller share of top ten hits than any streaming service except Paramount+.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's initial foray into streaming was marked by lavish spending on high-profile projects and talent, including deals with big names like Oprah Winfrey, Steven Spielberg, and Jennifer Aniston. The company's Hollywood operation, led by studio chiefs Zack Van Amburg and Jamie Erlicht, positioned itself as a talent-friendly destination, reminiscent of HBO, offering creators seemingly unlimited financial resources.<br/>
<br/>
Apple spent more than &#36;500 million combined on movies from directors Martin Scorsese, Ridley Scott, and Matthew Vaughn, and upwards of &#36;250 million on the World War II miniseries <em>Masters of the Air</em>. Despite the strong reviews and awards nominations, these projects have not yielded the viewership that Apple apparently hoped for.<br/>
<br/>
The company's new strategy is said to involve tighter budget controls and a more cautious approach to spending. This includes paying less upfront for shows, being quicker to cancel underperforming series, and delaying productions to manage costs better. For instance, the production of the sci-fi series <em>Foundation</em> was postponed to prevent budget overruns caused by delays related to the 2023 actors and writers strikes.<br/>
<br/>
The cost of the second season of <em>Severance</em> surged to over &#36;20 million per episode due to pandemic-related delays, internal conflicts, and additional expenses such as hiring <em>House of Cards</em> creator Beau Willimon for script contributions. Management has asked the producers of <em>Severance</em> to reduce the budget for future seasons, emphasizing the need for financial sustainability.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also become more selective in acquiring new projects, declining to buy some shows that sellers believe the company would have accepted just a few years ago. The company allegedly wants to shed the image of being Hollywood's biggest spender and bring more discipline and strategy to its content investments.<br/>
<br/>
While still willing to invest heavily in certain high-profile projects, such as <em>The Morning Show</em>, where cast salaries alone exceed &#36;50 million for the upcoming season, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; is becoming more fiscally conservative. <em>The Morning Show</em> stars Jennifer Aniston and Reese Witherspoon will each earn more than &#36;2 million per episode. This recalibration comes at a time when other major studios like Disney, Warner Bros., and Paramount are similarly cutting back on streaming budgets due to mounting losses. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/apple-tv-plus-curbs-costs/">Apple TV+ Curbs Costs After Expensive Projects Fail to Capture Viewers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-curbs-costs-after-expensive-projects-fail-to-capture-viewers.2431925/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Lineup Specs Detail Display Upgrade and New High-End Model</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-display-upgrade-and-new-high-end-model.2431922/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:33:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ice Universe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Key details about the overall specifications of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup have been shared by the leaker known as "Ice Universe," clarifying several important aspects of next year's devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-17-Plus-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-952009" /><br/>
Reports in recent months have converged in agreement that Apple will discontinue the "Plus" <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> model in 2025 while introducing an all-new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/iphone-17-slim-everything-we-know/">iPhone 17 "Slim" model</a> as an even more high-end option sitting above the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro Max in the lineup. The latest information from Ice Universe, shared yesterday <a href="https://weibo.com/5673255066/OoxQuAnxl?pagetype=profilefeed">on Weibo</a>, corroborates this and claims that the alleged display sizes and price points will be as follows:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li><strong>iPhone 17</strong>: 6.27-inch LTPO display (&#36;799)</li><br/>
  <li><strong>iPhone 17 Pro</strong>: 6.27-inch LTPO display (&#36;1,099)</li><br/>
  <li><strong>iPhone 17 Pro Max</strong>: 6.86-inch LTPO display (&#36;1,199)</li><br/>
  <li><strong>iPhone 17 "Slim"</strong>: 6.65-inch LTPO display (&#36;1,299)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Notably, all four &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models will apparently feature LTPO displays for the first time, enabling ProMotion for a variable refresh rate up to 120Hz. To date, ProMotion displays have been exclusive to Apple's "Pro" devices, so the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; may be the first time that the technology expands to a lower-cost device.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; "Slim" is said to become the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; flagship with a price tag of approximately &#36;1,299, making it the most expensive &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; model to date. It will allegedly feature a 6.65-inch display, placing it between the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro Max in size.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro models will purportedly feature 12GB of memory, a triple 48-megapixel rear camera system, and an A19 Pro chip fabricated with TSMC's N3P process, whereas the standard model will feature a separate A19 chip. This contrasts with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, which is expected to feature the same A18 chip across the board.<br/>
<br/>
The post also suggests that the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; "Slim" will feature an A19 chip, a dual dear camera system, an aluminum chassis, and 8GB of memory, but it is not clear if this is accurate. It is possible that this information has simply been assumed based on its replacement of the "Plus" model and it seems potentially strange for the new high-end model to have inferior specifications to the Pro models. The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; lineup is expected to be introduced in September 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ice-universe/">Ice Universe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/">iPhone 17 Lineup Specs Detail Display Upgrade and New High-End Model</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-display-upgrade-and-new-high-end-model.2431922/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get OWC&#039;s 14-Port Mac Thunderbolt Dock for Best-Ever &#36;99.99 Price (&#36;180 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/owcs-14-port-mac-thunderbolt-dock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-owcs-14-port-mac-thunderbolt-dock-for-best-ever-99-99-price-180-off.2431817/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 09:02:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/owcs-14-port-mac-thunderbolt-dock/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OWC this week knocked the price of the popular <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock</a> down to &#36;99.99, from its original price of &#36;279.99, and this deal is still around this weekend. This is a match of the all-time low price on the accessory, which we last tracked way back in April. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/owc-docks-white-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944277" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with OWC. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Besides this dock, you'll find a <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">large collection of accessories on sale</a> at this time on OWC, including USB-C hubs, external drives and enclosures, and internal memory upgrade kits for Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;180 OFF</div>OWC 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock, this accessory features two Thunderbolt 3 ports, five USB Type-A ports, one USB Type-C port, one Mini DisplayPort port, one gigabit Ethernet port, one S/PDIF digital audio output port, and one 3.5mm stereo audio input/output port. There are also two memory card slots for microSD and SD cards.<br/>
<br/>
All of the devices listed below are in new condition at OWC, although the retailer does provide various item condition options for anyone who might want to save money by purchasing open box items. Be sure to visit <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">OWC's sale landing page</a> to browse the full sale, which also features deals on cables, Mac accessories, keyboards, and headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Docks and Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTCDSDRDR%2F">Atlas Dual SD Card Reader</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3MDK5P%2F">Thunderbolt Mini Dock</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4HUB5P%2F">Thunderbolt Hub</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4DKG11P%2F">Thunderbolt Go Dock</a> - &#36;299.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>External Drives and Enclosures</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T04C%2F">4TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;124.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T08C%2F">8TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;217.76, down from &#36;394.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S32P%2F">32GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;74.74, down from &#36;89.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S64S%2F">64GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;147.74, down from &#36;179.96</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCBLUSCC2M1%2F">2M USB-C to USB-C Charging Cable</a> - &#36;2.99, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FMatias%2FFK416BT%2F">Matias Wireless Multi-Pairing Keyboard</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;69.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/owcs-14-port-mac-thunderbolt-dock/">Get OWC&#039;s 14-Port Mac Thunderbolt Dock for Best-Ever &#36;99.99 Price (&#36;180 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-owcs-14-port-mac-thunderbolt-dock-for-best-ever-99-99-price-180-off.2431817/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 18 Public Beta, HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta-homepod-mini-in-new-midnight-color-and-more.2431808/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The public betas of iOS 18 and other upcoming major operating system updates are finally here! Apple has spent the past month refining the betas through developer testing, and it's now time to open them up for broader access ahead of a full public launch several months from now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/top-stories-20jul2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959414" /><br/>
We also got a surprise hardware update this week, but it was one of the most minor updates imaginable – swapping out the Space Gray color of the HomePod mini for a new version in an extremely similar Midnight color. This week also saw us taking a look ahead at the upcoming iPhone 16 and Apple Watch lineups that should now be less than two months way, while we went hands-on with Samsung's new earbuds that have some striking similarities to Apple's AirPods Pro, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases First iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 Public Betas</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/">first public beta of iOS 18 is now available for the iPhone</a>, allowing anyone to test the update for free. We recommend installing the beta on a secondary iPhone, rather than the one that you use daily, as there are often bugs and other issues with pre-release software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Public-Beta-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957836" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">How to Install the iOS 18 Public Beta</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 features more Home Screen and Control Center customization options, a completely redesigned Photos app, the ability to use any emoji as a Tapback in the Messages app, an option to lock apps behind Face ID or Touch ID, and much more. The tentpole feature of iOS 18 is Apple Intelligence, which is Apple's new suite of generative AI features coming to iPhone 15 Pro models and newer later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color</h2><br/>
Apple this week announced that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/">HomePod mini is now available in a new Midnight color</a>, which replaces the Space Gray color previously offered.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/HomePod-Mini-Midnight-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958753" /><br/>
There does not appear to be any other changes to the HomePod mini, which continues to start at &#36;99 in the United States. In fact, Midnight looks nearly identical to Space Gray, so there is little reason for any existing HomePod mini owners to purchase the new color option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Series Is Just Two Months Away: Everything We Know</h2><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">next-generation iPhone 16 series</a> is just two months away from being unveiled, and there are already many rumors for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
Earlier this week, we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">listed everything that we know about the iPhone 16 series</a> based on leaked information, with one key change expected to be larger displays on the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max. Plenty of other new features are expected, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">check out the full list</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2024 Apple Watch Lineup: Key Changes We're Expecting</h2><br/>
Alongside the iPhone 16 series later this year, we can expect the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/">next-generation Apple Watch lineup</a>, including so-called Apple Watch Series 10, Apple Watch Ultra 3, and Apple Watch SE 3 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
Earlier this week, we rounded up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/">key changes to expect from the next Apple Watch lineup</a>, including larger display sizes for some models. As is often the case, new health features like sleep apnea detection have also been rumored.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 Passwords App: All the Features</h2><br/>
iOS 18 features a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/">standalone Passwords app</a> from Apple that surfaces some of the iCloud Keychain functionality built into the Settings app on previous versions of iOS for more convenient access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Passwords-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959050" /><br/>
We recently shared a guide that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/">highlights all of the features built into the Passwords app</a>, which features a simpler layout compared to the previous iCloud Keychain section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple's AirPods Pro 2 vs. Samsung's Galaxy Buds3 Pro</h2><br/>
Samsung last week introduced its latest earbuds, the Galaxy Buds3 Pro, which look quite a bit like Apple's AirPods Pro 2. Given the similarities, we thought we'd <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">compare Samsung's new earbuds to the ‌AirPods Pro‌</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/AirPods-Pro-vs-Galaxy-Buds3-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2298" height="1292" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958664" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">Check out our hands-on video</a> that goes through the design similarities and differences, performance comparisons, and other features to get an idea of how they match head-to-head. Apple users will almost certainly want to stick with AirPods Pro while Android users would want to opt for the Galaxy Buds, but it's always good to see what the competition is up to.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jul-18-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta/">Top Stories: iOS 18 Public Beta, HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta-homepod-mini-in-new-midnight-color-and-more.2431808/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Mirroring in macOS Sequoia and iOS 18: Everything You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-mirroring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-mirroring-in-macos-sequoia-and-ios-18-everything-you-need-to-know.2431770/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:27:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-mirroring&#038;post_date=1721424459/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expanding how its cross-platform Continuity features work in 2024, introducing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring option in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. As the name suggests, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring lets you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with your Mac by mirroring your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s display to your Mac's display. You can manage your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, using your mouse, keyboard, and trackpad with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, notifications, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fBxHMuDhvd4" title="This is Apple&#39;s BEST New Feature &#x1f92f;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
This guide walks through all of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring features and explains how it works.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_basics">iPhone Mirroring Basics</h2><br/>
After upgrading to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, there's a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app in the Dock, and that's how you start an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-interface.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959426" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>From your Mac's Dock, click on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app.</li><br/>
 <li>Click on Continue at the pop-up informational screen.</li><br/>
 <li>Select the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that you want to use if you have more than one &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>Unlock your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a passcode to allow the connection.</li><br/>
 <li>Click on Get Started.</li><br/>
 <li>Use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> on the Mac to authenticate (alternatively, enter your password).</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
When you start up &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring for the first time, you can opt to have it require authentication with every connection or to allow a connection automatically. If you choose automatic authentication, you will not need to authenticate with &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; or a password to use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring when your Mac is unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-settings.jpg" alt="" width="1221" height="555" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959433" /><br/>
Otherwise, you will need to authenticate on your Mac each time you want to use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring. Note that an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; needs to be locked while an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session is in progress, so you can't use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; while it's being mirrored to your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
If your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is not locked and you attempt to initiate &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring from your Mac, you will get a warning that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in use.<br/>
<br/>
There is no option for launching an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; -- it needs to be done from a Mac. While the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app icon should be in the Dock, if it's not there, you can get to it from the Launchpad or the Applications folder, because it is treated as a standard app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_interface">iPhone Mirroring Interface</h2><br/>
Your full &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; interface is shown as a dedicated app on the Mac, with your wallpaper and app icons all visible and accessible. You can click in to any of your apps and use it on the Mac just like you would on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-mac-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959427" /><br/>
You can get to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> by clicking on the bottom bar, and swap between pages with the trackpad or with a click and drag gesture using a mouse. There are menu options for getting to the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; and for bringing up the app switching interface, but most control is done within the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring window.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-menu-options.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="638" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959432" /><br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_requirements">iPhone Mirroring Requirements</h2><br/>
To use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, you need a Mac that runs &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; and that has an Apple silicon chip (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or later) or a T2 security chip. Macs with T2 security chips are Intel-based and include the following machines:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>2018 and later MacBook Pro</li><br/>
 <li>2018 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></li><br/>
 <li>2020 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro</li><br/>
 <li>2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></li><br/>
 <li>2019 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
These Macs have Apple silicon chips:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>2020 and later &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>2020 and later &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>2021 and later &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>2021 and later MacBook Pro (14 and 16 inch)</li><br/>
 <li>2020 13-inch MacBook Pro</li><br/>
 <li>2022 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a></li><br/>
 <li>2023 &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj;</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Any &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that runs &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; works with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models</li><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models</li><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> models</li><br/>
 <li>All &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models</li><br/>
 <li>All &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 models</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS and XS Max</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> (2nd and 3rd gen)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac need to be signed into the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, and two-factor authentication must be enabled for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring feature to work. You will also need to turn on Bluetooth and Wi-Fi, and the two devices will need to be near each other.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-app-switcher.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1352" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959434" /><br/>
During an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session, your Mac and your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; need to be close to one another, essentially in the same room.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="privacy_and_security">Privacy and Security</h2><br/>
You need to be signed into the same &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and your Mac for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring to work. While &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring is active, your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; does not need to be unlocked. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-in-use-notification.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="1323" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959428" /><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can remain tucked away in a pocket or a bag while you control it from your Mac, so no one can access it or see what you're doing with it. You do need to have your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; close enough to your Mac for there to be a Bluetooth connection, likely for security purposes. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="using_a_mouse_and_keyboard_with_iphone">Using a Mouse and Keyboard with iPhone</h2><br/>
Your Mac's keyboard, trackpad, and mouse can be used with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which is useful if you need to type something lengthy in an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-ring-app.jpg" alt="" width="2415" height="1454" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959429" /><br/>
<h2 id="audio_camera_and_microphone">Audio, Camera, and Microphone</h2><br/>
If you play a video on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; while &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring is enabled, the audio comes through your Mac. You can't turn on the Camera app or use the microphone, though.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_notifications_on_mac">iPhone Notifications on Mac</h2><br/>
With &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring turned on, incoming &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications show up right alongside your Mac notifications in the Notification Center at the upper right hand corner of the Mac's display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-notifications.jpg" alt="" width="759" height="871" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959431" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications are denoted with a small &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; icon, but they otherwise look like native Mac notifications.<br/>
<br/>
You can click on a notification and open up the app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, interacting with it directly from the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="standby">StandBy</h2><br/>
While your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is being mirrored to your Mac, it can be on a charger and in StandBy mode, displaying the time and other information.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="drag_and_drop">Drag and Drop</h2><br/>
Later this year, Apple plans to add &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring's best feature, file transfers. You will be able to transfer files, photos, and videos from your Mac to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and vice versa using drag and drop gestures.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that it will work just like dragging files from one Mac app to another.<br/>
<br/>
While drag and drop has yet to be implemented, you can sort of work around this by using AirDrop to move photos and files from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to your Mac, initiating AirDrop from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; without having to unlock it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_limitations">iPhone Mirroring Limitations</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring will not work if the Mac is using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> to stream music or video content to another device, or if <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sidecar/">Sidecar</a> is enabled with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. Continuity Camera cannot be enabled either, so if you're using your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a webcam for your Mac, you can't use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring at the same time.<br/>
<br/>
Attempting to watch movies and TV shows from some apps like Hulu and Netflix does not work, with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app showing just a blank black screen, likely due to DRM restrictions.<br/>
<br/>
There is no option to resize the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring window, and you can't manually move it into landscape orientation. If an app or a game is displayed in landscape orientation, the window will shift into landscape.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-landscape-mode.jpg" alt="" width="1926" height="1083" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959435" /><br/>
You can delete apps when using &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring by going to the Settings app, but apps cannot be deleted from the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;. You also can't rearrange apps because there's no option to get into the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; (or Lock Screen) editing interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-safari.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959436" /><br/>
Control Center and Notification Center are also inaccessible.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For more on the new features that Apple is adding in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">we have a dedicated iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-mirroring/">iPhone Mirroring in macOS Sequoia and iOS 18: Everything You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-mirroring-in-macos-sequoia-and-ios-18-everything-you-need-to-know.2431770/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Prepares for 2024 Summer Olympics With Updates to Maps, TV Coverage, Featured Apps and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/summer-olympics-apple-maps-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-prepares-for-2024-summer-olympics-with-updates-to-maps-tv-coverage-featured-apps-and-more.2431769/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:56:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/summer-olympics-apple-maps-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week updated the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> app in Paris in preparation for the 2024 Summer Olympics, which are set to begin on Friday, July 26. All permanent venues, such as the Parc de Princes and Centre Aquatique Olympique, are displayed as custom, hand-built 3D landmarks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/2024-summer-olympics-maps-update.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959419" /><br/>
Iconic sites like Gare de l'Est, Pont d'Iéna, and Place de la Madeleine are also rendered with more detail, and for the first time, the Maps app is displaying pop up locations that include temporary venues, souvenir shops, and public gathering sites. support for pop up locations will help attendees find important places for the summer games.<br/>
<br/>
All game locations and ceremony sites have special icons to help visitors find where they need to be, and Apple says that Maps displays all of the latest updates on road closures and advisories due to the games to help users navigate the city. There are curated Maps Guides for restaurants, hotels, and shopping, with dozens of new Guides from Le Bonbon, Le Fooding, Radio France, Madame Figaro, and My Little Paris.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the Maps updates, Apple plans to feature stories spotlighting popular events like gymnastics and swimming in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and it recommends that people download the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/paris-2024-olympics/id808794344">official Paris 2024 Olympics app</a> to follow along. Sports-themed mobile games and health and fitness apps will be highlighted as well.<br/>
<br/>
Full coverage of Olympic events will be available through the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/peacock-tv-stream-tv-movies/id1508186374">Peacock</a> and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nbc-sports/id542511686">NBC Sports apps</a>, which can be downloaded from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. A daily Olympic recap will be available on Peacock for fans in the U.S., offering customized playlists of highlights from relevant events from the prior day.<br/>
<br/>
There is a dedicated NBC Olympics Hub in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app for quick access to NBC coverage.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> will feature shows and episodes celebrating sports and the power of gathering together in Paris, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a> <a href="https://apple.news/TKLrmq8dkSgOQOchItCi2FA">will have curated coverage</a> of the events and the stars of the games along with a <a href="https://apple.news/2024_olympics_event_schedule">schedule of events</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> also plans to publish a Guide to French Music, which is an in-depth editorial feature of all the musical genres in France. It will go live later this week.<br/>
<br/>
The Summer Olympics will begin next Friday with an Opening Ceremony that begins at 1:30 p.m. Eastern Time or 7:30 p.m. Paris time. Soccer games will begin on July 24, with badminton, handball, rowing, volleyball, fencing, field hockey, shooting, diving, and gymnastics set to begin on July 27. Events will continue until August 11.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/summer-olympics-apple-maps-update/">Apple Prepares for 2024 Summer Olympics With Updates to Maps, TV Coverage, Featured Apps and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-prepares-for-2024-summer-olympics-with-updates-to-maps-tv-coverage-featured-apps-and-more.2431769/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Talking Vision Pro and iOS 18 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro-and-ios-18-beta.2431763/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:59:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/revisiting-apple-vision-pro-ios-18-public-beta-impressions/id1602394741?i=1000662756752">The MacRumors Show</a>, we revisit the experience of using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> and talk through our first impressions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> public beta. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fMftJc2guqw?si=hdalsHnMQdTxrKZe" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple's Vision Pro headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/12/apple-vision-pro-launched-uk-canada-france-germany/">now available</a> in the UK, Canada, France, Germany, Australia, China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore, prompting renewed interest in the spatial computing device. We discuss our thoughts on the best aspects of the Vision Pro, such as immersive video, spatial photos and video, gestures, and UI design, as well as its shortcomings, such as weight and comfort, video passthrough in dark environments, limited content, and general usefulness.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/">first public beta of iOS 18</a>, bringing the new software to the general public for the first time since the Worldwide Developers Conference in June. Apple has seeded three developer betas so far, and the first public beta includes the same content that's in the third developer beta. We talk over our thoughts on &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;'s new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> and Control Center customization features, the redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Let us know what you think about the experience of using the Vision Pro headset and the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta in the comments. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/12/the-macrumors-show-samsung-challenge-to-apple/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about all of the major new device announcements from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6/">Samsung's 2024 Galaxy Unpacked event</a> and how they compare to Apple's offerings.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro/">The MacRumors Show: Talking Vision Pro and iOS 18 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro-and-ios-18-beta.2431763/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods Pro and Max Get New Low Prices, Plus Big Discounts on iPads and MacBooks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-7-19-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-pro-and-max-get-new-low-prices-plus-big-discounts-on-ipads-and-macbooks.2431760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:37:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-7-19-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day took place earlier this week, and it introduced huge discounts on a wide variety of Apple products, including AirPods Max, MacBook Pro, and iPad Pro. Even though Prime Day has ended, we're still tracking quite a few of these record low prices as we head into the weekend, so if you missed out be sure to check out the deals below before they're gone for good.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-hero-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959384" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/airpods-max-pro-2-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959389" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;154 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;154 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
As is usual during big discount events, some of the best deals this week could be found on Apple's AirPods, and most of them are still available right now on Amazon. You'll find the AirPods Pro 2 and AirPods Max at all-time low prices today on Amazon, and the AirPods 2 at a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/pencil-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959387" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;19 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;109.99, down from the regular price of &#36;129.00. This is a new record low price for the accessory, beating the previous sale price by &#36;10. The Apple Pencil 2 is also at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/macbook-pro-m3-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959391" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;700 off MacBook Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>16-inch M3 Max MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;2,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's and Amazon's deals include all-time low prices on the 14-inch and 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro, and the best discounts will be found on the larger screen computers. The 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro is currently discounted by &#36;500 for all customers on Best Buy, but if you have a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, you can add up to an extra &#36;200 off select models.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,399.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">only at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,899.00 (&#36;600 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,299.00 (&#36;600 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,799.00 (&#36;700 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;3,299.00 (&#36;700 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m2-macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959392" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;200 off MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmHz6LU8QC4">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmHz6LU8QC4"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmHz8wfGa0G"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon and Best Buy are taking &#36;200 off the previous generation M2 MacBook Air this week, starting at &#36;799.00 for 256GB and rising to &#36;999.00 for 512GB. Both of these are all-time low prices for the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ipad-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959393" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;385 off the new M4 iPad Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>11-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;919.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week had all-time low prices on a few models of the 11-inch and 13-inch M4 iPad Pro, and most are still available. Prices start at &#36;919.00 for the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and also include multiple cellular tablets. Our original post has the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">full list of tablets on sale</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ipad-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959394" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking &#36;50 off the Wi-Fi models of the 2022 iPad, starting at &#36;299.00 for 64GB Wi-Fi. You'll also find both cellular devices on sale this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-7-19-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods Pro and Max Get New Low Prices, Plus Big Discounts on iPads and MacBooks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-pro-and-max-get-new-low-prices-plus-big-discounts-on-ipads-and-macbooks.2431760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Rumored to Use Same Rear Chassis as iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-use-same-rear-chassis-as-iphone-16.2431751/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:16:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will adopt the same rear chassis manufacturing process for the iPhone SE 4 that it is using for the upcoming standard iPhone 16, claims a new rumor coming out of China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iPhone-SE-4-Vertical-Camera-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959379" /><br/>
According to the Weibo-based leaker "<a href="https://weibo.com/5821279480/Oof995QJj">Fixed Focus Digital</a>," the backplate manufacturing process for the iPhone SE 4 is "exactly the same" as the standard model in Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 lineup, which is expected to be released in September. The iPhone SE 4, meanwhile, is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/when-to-expect-the-next-iphone-se/">expected</a> to arrive in the spring.<br/>
<br/>
The latest claim casts doubt on a previous rumor suggesting Apple would use a modified iPhone 14 chassis as the basis for a fourth-generation iPhone SE. In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/">November 2023</a>, <em>MacRumors</em> learned from a source close to Apple's manufacturing process that the dimensions of the ‌iPhone SE‌ 4 "perfectly matched" those of the base model ‌iPhone 14 <em>in its current stage</em>‌. <br/>
<br/>
While it's still unclear what may have led to the change, it's possible that Apple chose to adopt its newer rear chassis process for the more affordable SE model to achieve economy of scale at the point of production as the manufacture of iPhone 14 models winds down towards retirement. <br/>
<br/>
However, it could also indicate a change to the camera system on the fourth-generation iPhone SE. Unlike the ‌iPhone 14‌, the ‌iPhone SE‌ 4 was previously rumored to include a single 48-megapixel rear camera with a custom backplate for the device to account for the design change. <br/>
<br/>
In contrast, for the iPhone 16 models, Apple is planning a new vertical camera lens arrangement that is a departure from the diagonal lens setup found on iPhone 15 models. The new orientation will presumably allow the standard iPhone 16 models to capture Spatial Video for the Vision Pro headset. Adopting the same backplate for the iPhone SE 4 would seem to suggest it will feature the same dual camera setup, although we haven't heard any rumors specifically claiming that this is in Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to be targeting a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/iphone-se-4-face-id-price-rumor/">sub-&#36;500 starting price</a> for its fourth-generation iPhone SE model, despite a raft of rumored upgrades coming to the more affordable device. Touch ID and the Home button will be replaced by Face ID and a display notch, while the display size will increase from 4.7 inches to 6.1 inches. Other features expected for the next iPhone SE include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/">USB-C port and an Action button</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The third-generation iPhone SE was released in March 2022, so there is likely pent-up demand for a new model that includes some of the latest features of Apple's flagship iPhone models. For everything else we know about the iPhone SE 4, be sure to check our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/">iPhone SE 4 Rumored to Use Same Rear Chassis as iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-use-same-rear-chassis-as-iphone-16.2431751/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Crowdstrike Says Global IT Outage Impacting Windows PCs, But Mac and Linux Hosts Not Affected</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/crowdstrike-says-global-it-outage-impacting-windows-pcs-but-mac-and-linux-hosts-not-affected.2431738/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 03:12:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Windows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A widespread system failure is currently affecting numerous Windows devices globally, causing critical boot failures across various industries, including banks, rail networks, airlines, retailers, broadcasters, healthcare, and many more sectors. The issue, manifesting as a Blue Screen of Death (BSOD), is preventing computers from starting up properly and forcing them into continuous recovery cycles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bsod.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959336" /><br/>
The cause of the failure has been identified as an update to Crowdstrike Falcon antivirus software installed on Windows 10 PCs, but Mac and Linux machines running the same cybersecurity software have been spared. <a href="https://www.crowdstrike.com">Crowdstrike</a>, which specializes in endpoint security protection for corporate networks, has just <a href="https://x.com/George_Kurtz/status/1814235001745027317">released the following statement</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>"Crowdstrike is actively working with customers impacted by a defect found in a single content update for Windows hosts.<br/>
<br/>
"Mac and Linux hosts are not impacted. This is not a security incident or cyberattack.<br/>
<br/>
"The issue has been identified, isolated and a fix has been deployed.<br/>
<br/>
"We refer customers to the support portal for the latest updates and will continue to provide complete and continuous updates on our website.<br/>
<br/>
"We further recommend organisations ensure they're communicating with Crowdstrike representatives through official channels.<br/>
<br/>
"Our team is fully mobilized to ensure the security and stability of Crowdstrike customers."</blockquote>Unfortunately, the nature of the problem means that fixing it isn't as simple as installing a patch. The workaround to break the infinite boot cycle on affected Windows machines involves manually booting into safe mode, navigating to the CrowdStrike directory, and deleting the system file that caused the problem. As such, it could be a while before all services impacted by the content update are back up and running. <br/>
<br/>
For those who have a Windows machine that has succumbed to the botched update (now rolled back), Crowdstrike has outlined the following steps system admins need to take to get back up and running: <br/>
<ol><li>Boot Windows into Safe Mode or the Windows Recovery Environment.</li><br/>
<li>Navigate to the C:\Windows\System32\drivers\CrowdStrike directory.</li><br/>
<li>Locate the file matching 'C-00000291*.sys', and delete it.</li><br/>
<li>Boot the host normally.</li></ol><br/>
As expected, Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">system status webpage</a> shows no issues with its services, however there have been scattered reports of problems with contactless payments across some businesses, which could prevent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> transactions from being processed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/windows/">Windows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/">Crowdstrike Says Global IT Outage Impacting Windows PCs, But Mac and Linux Hosts Not Affected</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/crowdstrike-says-global-it-outage-impacting-windows-pcs-but-mac-and-linux-hosts-not-affected.2431738/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Eve Launches Matter-Enabled Eve Weather Smart Station</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/eve-weather-matter-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eve-launches-matter-enabled-eve-weather-smart-station.2431717/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:47:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/eve-weather-matter-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		<category>Matter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Smart home company Eve Systems today announced the launch of a new version of the Eve Weather that offers Matter support. With Matter, the new Eve Weather can be added to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> or smart home setups from other companies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/eve-weather.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959321" /><br/>
Eve Weather is a small cube-shaped accessory that is designed to provide outdoor weather temperature, humidity, and the local 12-hour weather trend. A display at the front allows you to see temperature and humidity at a glance, but the data also syncs to the Eve app.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; integration, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> can be used to provide details on the outdoor weather conditions, and the data can be used to trigger &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; automations. Eve Weather offers IPX4 water resistance so it can be kept outdoors year-round and displayed anywhere.<br/>
<br/>
Eve Weather can be purchased <a href="https://www.evehome.com/en-us">from the Eve website</a> or <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FEve-Weather-Matter-temperature-resistance%2Fdp%2FB0D81BVH6P">from Amazon.com</a> for &#36;80. Eve is continuing to sell the &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; version of the device as well for those who do not have a Matter-enabled hub, which includes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/matter/">Matter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/eve-weather-matter-support/">Eve Launches Matter-Enabled Eve Weather Smart Station</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eve-launches-matter-enabled-eve-weather-smart-station.2431717/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Gains 8 Million Global Subscribers Amid Price Hikes and Push to Ad-Supported Streaming</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/netflix-global-subscriber-increase-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-gains-8-million-global-subscribers-amid-price-hikes-and-push-to-ad-supported-streaming.2431710/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:59:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/netflix-global-subscriber-increase-ads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix has gained more than 8 million global paid subscribers since April, according to new subscriber information included in the company's second quarter earnings results [<a href="https://s22.q4cdn.com/959853165/files/doc_financials/2024/q2/FINAL-Q2-24-Shareholder-Letter.pdf">PDF</a>]. With the jump in paid subscriptions, Netflix now has a total of 277.65 million paid subscribers around the world, marking 16.5 percent year-over-year growth.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884791" /><br/>
Ad tier memberships increased 34 percent quarter-over-quarter, thanks to Netflix pushing its ad-supported tier. Netflix eliminated its cheapest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/netflix-removes-basic-plan/">ad-free "Basic" subscription tier</a> last year, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/03/netflix-phasing-out-basic-ads-free-plan/">earlier in July</a>, the company began warning customers in the UK and Canada that they would need to move to a new plan.<br/>
<br/>
In the United States, the Basic plan was priced at &#36;9.99 per month, but the cheapest ad-free Netflix plan is now priced at &#36;15.49 a month. Netflix had been allowing customers that were already on the Basic plan to continue using it, but that is being phased out. Ad tier memberships grew 34 percent from the first quarter to the second quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix with ads is priced at &#36;6.99 per month, and it includes between four and five minutes of ads per hour. Ads vary in length from 15 to 30 seconds and play before and during TV shows and movies. The company says that it will soon test an in-house ad tech platform in Canada, with plans to launch it broadly in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix saw 17 percent growth in revenue year-over-year, and it is expecting overall 2024 growth to be at 14 to 15 percent. Netflix is expecting ad memberships to increase in 2025 and beyond, with ad revenue becoming a more meaningful contributor to its business.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/netflix-global-subscriber-increase-ads/">Netflix Gains 8 Million Global Subscribers Amid Price Hikes and Push to Ad-Supported Streaming</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-gains-8-million-global-subscribers-amid-price-hikes-and-push-to-ad-supported-streaming.2431710/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
