<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:03:55 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Beta: All the New Features So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-all-the-new-features-so-far.2410880/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 14:32:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features&#038;post_date=1699925571/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is beta testing iOS 17.2, the second major update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system that came out in September. We are expecting to see a public launch in December, so there are still several betas to go before the software debuts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918853" /><br/>
This guide includes everything new in the iOS 17.2 beta, and we'll be updating it throughout the beta testing period. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="journal_app">Journal App</h2><br/>
iOS 17.2 includes the Journal app that Apple announced as part of &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;. With the Journal app, users can record their daily activities and thoughts, with Apple providing optional prompts that can be used as inspiration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Journal-App-iOS-17-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1469" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918878" /><br/>
A Journal entry can be added by tapping on the "+" button in the Journal app, and from there, users can choose a suggestion as the basis for their writing or just opt for "New Entry" to write anything at all.<br/>
<br/>
Entries are automatically tagged with a date for organizational purposes, but there are options for bookmarking, too. Journal entries can include images, voice recordings, and location tags.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_app_sticker_reactions">Messages App Sticker Reactions</h2><br/>
You can now long press on any chat bubble in the Messages app to add a sticker response that serves as an alternative to a tapback reaction. Tapping on "Add Sticker" lets you choose either a sticker or an emoji to apply to the corner of an iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tapback-reply-sticker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918892" /><br/>
There was already an option to drag a sticker or an emoji onto any message bubble, but this is a much quicker method of quickly responding to an incoming message with a quick graphic that is more expressive than a tapback reaction.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="spatial_video_recording">Spatial Video Recording</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.2, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max can be used to record spatial video that will be viewable in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app on the Vision Pro headset. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
Spatial video recording can be enabled by going to the Settings app, tapping into the Camera section, selecting Formats, and toggling on "Spatial Video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>." Apple says that for best results when recording spatial video, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> should be held stable in landscape orientation while capturing video. Video is recorded at 30 frames per second at 1080p, and one minute of video takes up 130MB of storage space.<br/>
<br/>
When spatial videos captured with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; are viewed on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, they appear as normal videos. Viewing the video in 3D requires the Vision Pro headset. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="collaborative_apple_music_playlists">Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</h2><br/>
There is now an option to create a playlist in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> that multiple people can add to. In a playlist you have made, tap on the three-dot icon in top right of the app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-collaborative-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="5484" height="3085" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918890" /><br/>
From there, select the Collaborate option and choose "Start Collaboration." You'll be able to create a link to the playlist, and anyone who has access to that link can add to it. You can also invite people to join via QR code, and if you want, you can approve each person that asks to join.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="favorites_apple_music_playlist">Favorites Apple Music Playlist</h2><br/>
Songs that you have favorited in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app are now aggregated into a Favorites playlist.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-favorite-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918891" /><br/>
<h2 id="apple_music_listening_history_focus_filter">Apple Music Listening History Focus Filter</h2><br/>
There is a Focus Filter for the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Listening History feature, so if you want to let someone else use your device to listen to music, you can activate this to turn off the Listening History so their song choices won't affect your recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-focus-filters.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918906" /><br/>
<h2 id="action_button_translate">Action Button Translate</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max users can now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-translate-action-button/">choose a new Translate option</a> for the Action button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-translate.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918874" /><br/>
When the Action button is set as Translate, pressing to hold causes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to pop up a Translate window that listens for spoken text. It is able to translate from one set language to another, using the languages that you have previously set up in the Translate app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="imessage_contact_key_verification">iMessage Contact Key Verification</h2><br/>
First previewed in December 2022, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-imessage-contact-key-verification/">iMessage Contact Key Verification</a> is a feature designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-iMessage-Contact-Key-Verification_screen-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876653" /><br/>
Users can ensure that there is no "man in the middle" snooping on iMessage conversations, and there is an option to display a Contact Verification Code so that iMessage users can verify that they're speaking to the correct individual during in-person meetings or on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_in_icloud_syncing">Messages in iCloud Syncing</h2><br/>
The "Messages" section in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> in the Settings app has been renamed to "Messages in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;." It shows the total amount of storage that messages are taking up, the number of messages synced to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;, and the time of the last sync. There's also a "Sync Now" option to force an update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-messages-in-icloud.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918896" /><br/>
Apple previously said that additional settings would be synced through Messages in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, like Text Message Forwarding, Send & Receive accounts, and SMS filters across devices, so this may see those additional settings syncing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_tv_app">Apple TV App</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/">removed the separate tabs</a> for Movies and TV shows in the Store section of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said that Apple also plans to remove the option to purchase TV shows and movies from the iTunes app as part of a TV app redesign, but that has not yet happened.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tv-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918905" /><br/>
<h2 id="emergency_alerts_local_awareness">Emergency Alerts Local Awareness</h2><br/>
Under Notifications & Emergency Alerts in the Settings app, there is a new "Local Awareness" option that can be turned on. Apple says that Local Awareness uses your approximate location to improve the timeliness, accuracy, and reliability of emergency alerts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-emergency-local-awareness.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918902" /><br/>
<h2 id="weather_widgets">Weather Widgets</h2><br/>
There are new Details, Daily Forecast, and Sunrise/Sunset widgets for the Weather app. Details shows information like precipitation chance, UV index, wind speed, and air quality, while Daily Forecast offers the weather for the next few days in a small widget size. Sunrise/Sunset shows the sunrise and sunset times for each day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/weather-app-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918889" /><br/>
<h2 id="digital_clock_widget">Digital Clock Widget</h2><br/>
There is a new Digital Clock widget that can be added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-clock-widget.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918894" /><br/>
<h2 id="contact_posters">Contact Posters</h2><br/>
You can now select rainbow-colored text for your name when setting up a Contact Poster in the Contacts app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-contact-poster-rainbow.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918893" /><br/>
<h2 id="books_page-turning_animation">Books Page-Turning Animation</h2><br/>
There's a new "Fast Fade" option for the page-turning animation in the Books app. Apple has also removed the icon that you could turn on to scroll through content quickly.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-page-turn-animation.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918897" /><br/>
<h2 id="airplay">AirPlay</h2><br/>
There's a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> Receiver" setting that will allow the upcoming &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; headset to stream or share content to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-airplay-handoff.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918898" /><br/>
It also looks like the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; feature for hotels that Apple announced earlier this year is live or will be live soon. It is designed to let you &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; content from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to an AirPlay-equipped smart TV.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="memoji">Memoji</h2><br/>
Apple added a "Body" section for Memoji where users can customize waist, bust, shoulders, and arms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-memoji-body.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918895" /><br/>
<h2 id="news_app">News App</h2><br/>
The News app now supports Live Activities for following news-related events such as elections.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-apple-news-live-activities.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918899" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="expanded_sensitive_content_warnings">Expanded Sensitive Content Warnings</h2><br/>
Apple's opt-in Sensitive Content Warning feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-expands-sensitive-content-warnings/">is expanding</a> to Contact Posters in the Contacts and Phone apps, as well as in stickers in the Messages app. Sensitive Content Warnings use on-device machine learning to blur out photos or videos with any nudity detected before users view them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Sensitive-Content-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922023" /><br/>
<h2 id="app_store_categories">App Store Categories</h2><br/>
The "Apps" and "Games" sections of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-beta-app-store/">new top bar navigation</a> that allows users to scroll through various app categories, exploring apps in that category with a tap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/app-store-categories.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922085" /><br/>
The categories mirror the categories that can be found at the bottom of each &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; section, and it is a layout that Apple has previously used for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="applecare+_coverage_menu">AppleCare+ Coverage Menu</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ "Coverage" menu is now in Settings > General rather than Settings > General > About, making it more visible than before. The Coverage interface lists &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ on your device and any paired AirPods. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="siri">Siri</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> in iOS 17.2 can provide details on an estimated time of arrival when there are active turn-by-turn directions in the Maps app, and the personal assistant can provide altitude data. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="more_ios_17.2_beta_features">More iOS 17.2 Beta Features</h2><br/>
Know of a feature that we've missed on this list? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">iOS 17.2 Beta: All the New Features So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-all-the-new-features-so-far.2410880/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Performance Comparison: M3 Max MacBook Pro vs. M1 Max MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/m3-max-macbook-pro-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/performance-comparison-m3-max-macbook-pro-vs-m1-max-macbook-pro.2410875/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 13:41:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/m3-max-macbook-pro-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last week launched its new MacBook Pro models with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips. We already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-macbook-pro-hands-on/">took a look at the M3 Pro MacBook Pro</a>, but we also wanted to test out the top-of-the-line M3 Max chip to see how it measures up.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/up1ZUwgJCBc" title="MacBook Pro Face-off: M3 Max vs M1 Max Benchmarks Breakdown!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
While the M3 Pro's performance was disappointing overall compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro and even the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-pro/">M1 Pro</a>, the same can't be said of the M3 Max. <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/v6/cpu/3529039">Using Geekbench</a>, the M3 Max is about as fast as the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra, earning a single-core score of 3217 and a multi-core score of 21597. The &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max has a single-core score of 2737 and a multi-core score of 14503, and the difference is even more pronounced compared to the 2021 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-max/">M1 Max</a>, the first 16-inch MacBook Pro to get an Apple silicon chip. The &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj; has a single-core score of 2379 and a multi-core score of 12206.<br/>
<br/>
Other benchmarking tests show similar major improvements between the 2023 M3 Max and the 2021 &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj;. In Cinebench, the M3 Max earned a multi-core CPU score of 1601, compared to a 788 score from the &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj;. A classroom render in Blender took three and a half minutes with the M3 Max machine, and eight and a half minutes with the &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj; machine.<br/>
<br/>
Exporting a 16 minute 4K video with multiple effects took five and a half minutes on the M3 Max, and seven and a half minutes on the &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
As for SSD speeds, those were about the same. The &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj; saw read/write scores of 5727/5980, respectively, while the M3 Max had read/write scores of 5032/6197, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
You'll want to watch our full video for a more detailed comparison between the two machines, which gives a useful look into just how far Apple silicon has come in two years. The &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj; is still a super fast chip and you're probably not going to want to upgrade to the M3 Max if you've already got an &zwnj;M1 Max&zwnj; machine, but in some tests, the new chip is up to twice as fast.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/m3-max-macbook-pro-hands-on/">Performance Comparison: M3 Max MacBook Pro vs. M1 Max MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/performance-comparison-m3-max-macbook-pro-vs-m1-max-macbook-pro.2410875/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Gets 36% of Google&#039;s Safari Search Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-google-safari-search-revenue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gets-36-of-googles-safari-search-revenue.2410862/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 10:39:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-google-safari-search-revenue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As Google battles an antitrust lawsuit from the U.S. Department of Justice, secrets about its search deals with Apple have been leaking out. We previously learned that Google is paying Apple billions of dollars to be the primary search engine on Apple devices, and now, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-13/apple-gets-36-of-google-revenue-from-search-deal-witness-says"><em>Bloomberg</em> has shared</a> the total percentage of Google's revenue that Apple earns.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/safari-google-search.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916340" /><br/>
Google pays Apple 36 percent of the total revenue that it earns from searches conducted on the Safari browser on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac, with the number shared by an economics expert testifying on Apple's behalf. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, Google's main lawyer "visibly cringed" when the revenue data was shared, as it was meant to remain confidential.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, wealth management company Bernstein suggested that Apple is getting anywhere <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/">from &#36;18 billion to &#36;20 billion</a> per year, representing somewhere around 15 percent of Apple's total annual operating profits.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Google have both worked to keep details in the antitrust lawsuit private, claiming that publicly sharing the information would "undermine Google's competitive standing."<br/>
<br/>
Google has been the default search engine on Apple devices since 2002, though the agreement between the two tech companies has been revised multiple times. Apple earns a ton of money from the deal, while Google gets to be the default search option on the world's most popular smartphone.<br/>
<br/>
The United States Department of Justice is investigating Google because it believes that Google has a search monopoly. Google's lucrative search engine deal with Apple has been a main focus of the legal battle, which is expected to last until the end of November.<br/>
<br/>
In October, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella said that the agreement between Apple and Google has made it impossible for other search engines like Bing to compete. "You get up in the morning, you brush your teeth, and you search on Google," said Nadella. "With that level of habit forming, the only way to change is by changing defaults."<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft at one point approached Apple about buying Bing, which would have allowed Apple to create its own search engine, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/microsoft-bing-acquisition-talks/">Apple was not interested</a>. The company was concerned that Bing would not be able to compete with Google in "quality and capabilities," and also, Apple had no motivation to lose out on the money that it earns from Google.<br/>
<br/>
Apple services chief <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-on-why-google-is-default-on-iphone/">testified in the trial in October</a>, and he said that Google is the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s default search engine because it is the best option. "We make Google be the default search engine because we've always thought it was the best," Cue said. Apple has not been able to make changes to the arrangement because there is no "valid alternative."<br/>
<br/>
While Google is the default search engine on Apple devices, users can opt to swap to Yahoo, Bing, DuckDuckGo, or Ecosia as an alternative, but doing so requires going into the Safari browser's settings.<br/>
<br/>
If Google loses the antitrust lawsuit, and there is a chance that could happen, the deal between Apple and Google could be dissolved. Apple could be pushed into allowing customers to choose a search engine option when setting up an Apple device rather than having Google set as the default.<br/>
<br/>
Losing out on billions of dollars from Google could potentially be the catalyst Apple needs to develop its own search engine, and Apple has indeed considered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/19/apple-to-launch-search-engine-to-rival-google/">building a search solution</a>. Apple's AI chief John Giannandrea runs a search team within Apple, and that team has developed a next-generation search engine for Apple apps that could potentially serve as the basis for a full Google Search alternative.<br/>
<br/>
Should the Google/Apple deal come to an end, it could be several years before changes are required. A decision in the lawsuit won't come for some time, and once its does, we can expect a lengthy appeals process if it does not go Google's way.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-google-safari-search-revenue/">Apple Gets 36% of Google&#039;s Safari Search Revenue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gets-36-of-googles-safari-search-revenue.2410862/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All the Hardware Apple Still Sells With a Lightning Port</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/hardware-apple-still-sells-lightning-port/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-the-hardware-apple-still-sells-with-a-lightning-port.2410854/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 09:16:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/hardware-apple-still-sells-lightning-port/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Lightning</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple introduced the Lightning port in September 2012 with the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 5. The connector was a significant change from the previous 30-pin connector used in Apple devices, offering a smaller, more efficient connection that could be inserted either way up, enhancing ease of use. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/lightning-connector-feature-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891737" /><br/>
In September 2023, over a decade later, Apple caught up with the rest of the industry and removed the Lightning port from its flagship <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> series, replacing it with USB-C, the widely adopted standard used in electronics for connectivity and charging. <br/>
<br/>
And yet the Lightning port lives on in a variety of hardware still sold by Apple. We've compiled this list of Lightning products in one place so you won't be surprised when your USB-C to USB-C cables don't fit your new purchase. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone SE (2022)</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/iPhone-SE-3.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-838856" /><br/>
Apple introduced the third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> in March 2022. The &#36;429 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; comes with an A15 Bionic chip, 5G connectivity, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> for those who prefer a Home button. And a Lightning port.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 13</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/Apple-iPhone-13-colors-lineup-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839128" /><br/>
In 2021, Apple unveiled the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>‌ as the successor to the popular ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 12, with improved rear cameras, longer battery life, the A15 Bionic chip, and more. It starts at &#36;599, Lightning port included.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/iphone-14-purple-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867914" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> now sits in the middle of Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup below the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, but above the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj;. The &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; starts at &#36;599, and is still highly capable for everyday use, if you love Lightning ports. The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ and ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ Plus are priced at &#36;699 and &#36;799, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad (9th generation)</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916839" /><br/>
A lower-priced alternative to the latest 10th-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, the ninth-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; has remained on sale since September 2021 and goes for &#36;329 - &#36;120 less than its successor. This device sports the A13 Bionic chip and an older design with a smaller display, but the Lightning port is the same size.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/airpods-max-flat.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-775235" /><br/>
Introduced in December 2020, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> have now been in Apple's product lineup for three years. Apple is expected to replace the Lightning port for USB-C to comply with European regulations and for consistency across its AirPods lineup, but not until late 2024. Staying retro until then, but in a high-tech way.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil (1st generation)</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2014/11/ipadproapplepencil.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="581" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-570919" /><br/>
There are three versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> that Apple still sells. This first version was released in 2015, the second version was released in 2018, and the third version was released in 2023. The first-generation has a Lightning adapter and charges by plugging into a lightning port on either an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or a charging adapter, the second-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; charges wirelessly, but the latest &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; has a futuristic USB-C port.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Magic Keyboard</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/mac-magic-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836750" /><br/>
The Magic Keyboard is sold in several variations by Apple, and all with a Lightning port for charging and connectivity. Even the newly announced M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> is still accompanied by a Magic Keyboard with a Lightning port for pairing and charging, rather than USB-C as rumored.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Magic Mouse</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/magic-mouse-2-lightning.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-835832" /><br/>
The only mouse that insists on doing a backflip to recharge. It's almost a joke, but the &#36;99 Magic Mouse still retains the clownish Lightning port on the underside. It's pretty amazing Apple still has this thing around, and is even prepared to ship new iMacs with one.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Magic Trackpad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/magic-trackpad-colors.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1348" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-795351" /><br/>
Surprisingly, a Magic Trackpad with USB-C is still a fantasy. Technically, you could always buy a MacBook, but that works out pricier.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Cables and Adapters</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Apple-Lightning-to-USB-3-Camera-Adapter.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896492" /><br/>
Apple also sells a variety of cables and adapters that feature Lightning connections and ports, so keep an eye out if you're shopping Apple's accessories for your legacy devices.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lightning/">Lightning</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/hardware-apple-still-sells-lightning-port/">All the Hardware Apple Still Sells With a Lightning Port</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-the-hardware-apple-still-sells-with-a-lightning-port.2410854/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Pro OLED Panels Rumored to Start Production in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/ipad-pro-oled-panel-production-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-pro-oled-panels-rumored-to-start-production-in-2024.2410845/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:05:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/ipad-pro-oled-panel-production-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Korea Herald</category>
		<category>LG Display</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Production of OLED displays designed for the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> will begin in February 2024, the <a href="https://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20231112000126"><em>Korea Herald</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/OLED-iPad-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2363" height="1329" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-788296" /><br/>
Sources familiar with the matter speaking to the <em>Korea Herald</em> claim that LG Display is set to initiate OLED production for the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; as early as February next year at their facility in Paju, Gyeonggi Province – a time frame around three months sooner than previously expected. The displays are expected to be three times the price of those used in iPhones, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/09/2024-oled-ipad-pro-starting-prices/">could translate to higher prices</a> for customers. The information largely corroborates a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/ipad-pro-oled-display-production-february-report/">report from last week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The current 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is equipped with an LCD panel, while the 12.9-inch model features mini-LED backlighting for increased brightness and a higher contrast ratio. OLED technology would eliminate the need for backlighting, with benefits including even higher contrast ratio with deeper blacks, lower power consumption, and more. Apple is expected to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/ipad-pro-2024-oled-hybrid-tech/">very thin hybrid OLED displays</a> with a combination of flexible and rigid materials, which could allow the next &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models to be slightly thinner.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is reportedly seeking around 10 million OLED panels for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in 2024. LG is expected to supply around 60% of the OLED panels, with the remaining portion supplied by Samsung, which is expected to focus on the 11-inch model only. Production of the panels for the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is expected to help LG Displays' financial recovery next year. LG and Samsung are said to be currently finalizing price negotiations with Apple.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to OLED display technology, the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature slightly larger screens, the M3 chip, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">redesigned Magic Keyboard accessory</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/2024-ipad-pro-what-to-expect/">2024 iPad Pro: 12 Rumors About What to Expect</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> expects the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">launch in the second quarter of 2024</a>, which runs from April to June. This timeline broadly aligns with the latest rumor from the <em>Korea Herald</em>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/koreaherald-com/">Korea Herald</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg-display/">LG Display</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/ipad-pro-oled-panel-production-in-2024/">iPad Pro OLED Panels Rumored to Start Production in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-pro-oled-panels-rumored-to-start-production-in-2024.2410845/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Black Friday MacBook Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-macbook-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-macbook-deals.2410838/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 07:00:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-macbook-deals&#038;post_date=1699898434/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We've been highlighting all of the best Apple product deals you can already get in the lead-up to Black Friday on November 24, but have yet to focus on MacBooks. In this article we're doing just that, with the best early Black Friday MacBook Air and MacBook Pro deals you can get right now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-presents.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922400" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there is a chance that we could see better deals on these MacBook models arrive as Black Friday gets closer. This is a risk anyone has to take while shopping during the holidays, so with that in mind, many of the deals shared below are currently their best prices ever seen. More information on these sales can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_macbook_deals">Best MacBook Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>15-inch M2 MacBook Air</strong></a> for &#36;1,049.99 at Amazon (&#36;249 off)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_black_friday_deals">Best Black Friday Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday AirPods Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday iPhone Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday iPad Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday HomePod Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-apple-watch-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday Apple Watch Deals</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for the all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;1,049.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model is also available for the record low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76B7QHC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,249.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Both have all colors on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76B7QHC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple's latest MacBook Air model is a great option with numerous pro-level features without the price tag. For a deep dive into all the similarities and differences between each line, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro-buyers-guide/">read our buyer's guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
We aren't tracking any notable deals on the MacBook Pro line right now, but if that changes we'll be sure to update this guide.<br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-macbook-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday MacBook Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-macbook-deals.2410838/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AI-Infused iOS 18 Lauded as &#039;Ambitious and Compelling&#039; by Apple Execs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ai-infused-ios-18-lauded-as-ambitious-and-compelling-by-apple-execs.2410835/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 06:06:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple internally believes its iOS 18, macOS 15, watchOS 11, and tvOS 18 updates next year will be "ambitious and compelling," thanks to major new software features and designs in the works for iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, Apple TV, and Mac. That's according to the latest information relayed by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-11-12/apple-aapl-plans-ambitious-ios-18-and-macos-15-updates-seeks-to-squash-bugs-lovjlsf6"><em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
While little is known about the specifics, many of the changes are believed to involve <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/"> generative AI</a>, including a smarter version of Siri that takes the virtual assistant's integration with the operating systems to a new level. According to the leaker <a href="https://x.com/Tech_Reve/status/1722418466647625999?s=20">@Tech_Reve</a>, Apple is relying on large-language models (LLMs) to completely revamp Siri and make it the "ultimate virtual assistant" and "Apple's most powerful killer AI app."<br/>
<br/>
Apple is reportedly working on revamped interaction between ‌Siri‌ and the Messages app, enabling users to field complex questions and auto-complete sentences more effectively, according to Gurman. We may also see auto-generated Apple Music playlists and integration with productivity apps like Pages and Keynote, such as AI-assisted writing and slide deck creation. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to be on course to spend &#36;1 billion per year on AI research, with some of the company's biggest executive names overseeing development. Indeed, Gurman says the company is "racing to catch up with Google and OpenAI" in the generative AI space, and with few major iPhone 16 hardware advances on the cards next year, the stakes are even higher. As a result, Gurman believes iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 could be "groundbreaking" relative to updates in the last few years.<br/>
<br/>
With so much riding on the outcome, however, Apple is said to be taking a particularly cautious approach to its software development. Recently we learned that all development on future features was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-engineers-ios-18-bug-fix-focus/">paused within Apple</a> to allow its engineers to work solely on improving the existing software. <br/>
<br/>
According to Gurman, Apple last month finished the first "M1" versions of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS 15, but the software engineering management team found too many bugs that were missed in internal testing, so a week was set aside to address the issues. Development has since resumed, but Apple is still said to be debating whether to deploy its new generative AI technology via the cloud, as an on-device experience, or a mixture of both.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to reveal its LLM-powered version of Siri at WWDC 2024 during its iOS 18 developer preview, although other generative AI features it is working on could be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/">exclusive to iPhone 16 models</a> and therefore may not be revealed until Apple launches its next-generation flagship smartphones in September 2024.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/">AI-Infused iOS 18 Lauded as &#039;Ambitious and Compelling&#039; by Apple Execs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ai-infused-ios-18-lauded-as-ambitious-and-compelling-by-apple-execs.2410835/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wi-Fi 6E Support: What iPhone, iPad, and Mac Users Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-wi-fi-6e-iphone-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wi-fi-6e-support-what-iphone-ipad-and-mac-users-need-to-know.2410829/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 03:28:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-wi-fi-6e-iphone-mac&#038;post_date=1699885698/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Wi-Fi 6E</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Wi-Fi 6E, the latest advancement in Wi-Fi technology, offers several benefits when enabled on your iPhone or Mac, but it can also cause problems. This article explains what Wi-Fi 6E is, which Apple devices support it, and how to turn it off if you encounter issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Mac-Pro-Fifteen-Inch-Air-Yellow-iphone-14-Triptych-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2482" height="1396" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-887564" /><br/>
<h2>What is Wi-Fi 6E?</h2><br/>
Wi-Fi 6 operates on the 2.4GHz and 5GHz bands, while Wi-Fi 6E also works over the 6GHz band for increased bandwidth. Wi-Fi 6E offers faster wireless speeds, lower latency, and less signal interference, so long as a supported device is connected to a Wi-Fi 6E router, which are available from brands like TP-Link, Asus, and Netgear. <br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 6E can handle more simultaneous connections without a decrease in performance, making it ideal for environments with many connected devices, such as smart homes and modern offices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Does My Apple Device Support Wi-Fi 6E?</h2><br/>
As Wi-Fi 6E is relatively new, not all devices support it yet. This means you might not be able to take full advantage of its features if other devices in your network are not Wi-Fi 6E compatible. Apple devices that support the standard are as follows:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>iMac (24-inch, Nov 2023)</li><br/>
  <li>MacBook Pro (14-inch, Nov 2023)</li><br/>
  <li>MacBook Pro (16-inch, Nov 2023)</li><br/>
  <li>MacBook Pro (14-inch, 2023) or MacBook Pro (16-inch, 2023)</li><br/>
  <li>Mac mini (2023)</li><br/>
  <li>Mac Studio (2023)</li><br/>
  <li>Mac Pro (2023)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPad Pro 11-inch (4th generation) or iPad Pro 12.9 inch (6th generation)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Using Wi-Fi 6E Networks</h2><br/>
To use a Wi-Fi 6E network with an Apple device, you need a Wi-Fi 6E router that also has its 2.4GHz or 5GHz bands enabled. For the best Wi-Fi performance, Apple recommends using a single network name across the router's 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands. Otherwise, your Apple device will identify the network as having "limited compatibility," and the overall experience with some activities over the network might not be as expected.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macos-ventura-also-join-5g-separate-network-name-for-6ghz-wi-fi.jpg" alt="" width="900" height="376" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922360" /><br/>
<h2>Disabling Wi-Fi 6E Networks</h2><br/>
The 6 GHz frequency band can have a shorter range and less ability to penetrate walls and other obstacles compared to the lower 2.4 GHz band. This might require more strategic placement of routers or the use of range extenders in larger spaces. Additionally, if your Mac is experiencing the "limited connectivity" issues described above, it may potentially lead to increased power consumption on your Mac, which could impact battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, if you experience any issues with a Wi-Fi 6E network, you can turn off Wi-Fi 6E mode for that network, and your Apple device will no longer use that network's 6GHz band. <br/>
<h3>On Mac</h3><br/>
<ol><li>Click the Apple logo () in the menu bar and select <strong>System Settings</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Click <strong>Wi-Fi</strong> in the side column.</li><br/>
<li>Click <strong>Details</strong> next to the name of the Wi-Fi 6E network you're connected to.</li><br/>
<li>From the pop-up menu next to "Wi-Fi 6E Mode," choose <strong>Off</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/wi-fi-settings-macos.jpg" alt="settings" width="2054" height="722" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922366" /><br/>
<h3>On iPhone and iPad</h3><br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app and tap <strong>Wi-Fi</strong>.<br/>
<li>Tap the name of the Wi-Fi 6E network you're connected to.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Wi-Fi 6E Mode</strong>, then tap <strong>Off</strong>. </li></ol>Note that Wi-Fi 6E is not available in China mainland, while in Japan, Wi-Fi 6E requires iOS 16.2 or later or macOS 13.2 or later.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wi-fi-6e/">Wi-Fi 6E</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-wi-fi-6e-iphone-mac/">Apple Wi-Fi 6E Support: What iPhone, iPad, and Mac Users Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wi-fi-6e-support-what-iphone-ipad-and-mac-users-need-to-know.2410829/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone App Sideloading Coming to Users in the EU in First Half of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-app-sideloading-coming-to-users-in-the-eu-in-first-half-of-2024.2410823/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 02:00:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone users in the EU next year will be able to download apps hosted outside of Apple's official App Store to comply with European regulations, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/General-iOS-17-Feature-Blue-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898581" /><br/>
Otherwise known as sideloading, the change coming sometime in the first half of 2024 will allow customers to download apps without needing to use the App Store, which will mean developers won't need to pay Apple's 15 to 30 percent fees.<br/>
<br/>
Writing in the latest subscriber edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-11-12/apple-aapl-plans-ambitious-ios-18-and-macos-15-updates-seeks-to-squash-bugs-lovjlsf6">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman said Apple will introduce a "highly controlled system" that lets EU users install apps hosted elsewhere. Apple also will reportedly alter Messages and payment apps as part of the changes, likely via a localized iOS 17 update. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman's update contradicts a recent <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/10/ios-17-2-sideload-apps/">report</a> that suggested sideloading could arrive with Apple's iOS 17.2 software update, which is expected to be released next month. The report mistook as sideloading-related some new code that has to do with an <a href="https://x.com/aaronp613/status/1723177277351923886?s=46">upcoming framework</a> for organizations to distribute apps to employees.<br/>
<br/>
The European Union's Digital Markets Act (DMA), which went into effect on November 1, 2022, requires "gatekeeper" companies to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/01/dma-eu-law-could-force-major-changes-apple/">open up their services and platforms</a> to other companies and developers.<br/>
<br/>
The DMA will have a big impact on Apple's platforms, and it could result in Apple making major changes to the ‌App Store‌, Messages, FaceTime, Siri, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has claimed that sideloading will "undermine the privacy and security protections" that iPhone users rely on, leaving people vulnerable to malware, scams, data tracking, and other issues. Regardless of its stance, Apple must comply with the DMA or it risks fines of as much as 20 percent of its global revenue if the EU laws are violated.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-13/will-apple-allow-users-to-install-third-party-app-stores-sideload-in-europe">December 2022 report</a>, Gurman said Apple was considering implementing security requirements such as verification, a process that it could charge a fee for in lieu of collecting money from app sales. Apple has a verification system on Mac that allows users to be safe while giving them access to apps outside of the Mac App Store.<br/>
<br/>
If other countries introduce similar legislation, alternate app stores could conceivably expand beyond the European Union. The United States, for example, is considering legislation that would require Apple to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/26/apple-statement-revised-sideloading-bill/">allow sideloading</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/">iPhone App Sideloading Coming to Users in the EU in First Half of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-app-sideloading-coming-to-users-in-the-eu-in-first-half-of-2024.2410823/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Larger 12.9-inch iPad Air Coming Early 2024 Amid Lineup Refresh</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-larger-12-9-inch-ipad-air-coming-early-2024-amid-lineup-refresh.2410742/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 02:50:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will add a new larger 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> to an entirely refreshed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup coming next year, with two &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models taking priority in Apple's launch roadmap, according to Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
In his <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/2024年新款ipad機型與量產時程預測-predictions-for-new-ipad-models-and-production-timeline-in-2024-650a5fc9bbee">latest outlook</a>, Kuo predicts that Apple will compensate for this year's lack of movement in its &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lineup by updating all existing models, starting with a refreshed 10.9-inch and new 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with new chips scheduled for mass production in the first quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo says the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-working-on-larger-ipad-air/">previously rumored</a> all-new 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will have an LCD screen that lacks the mini-LED technology of Apple's current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models, but will benefit from the same oxide backplane. This will offer better display performance than the current 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; that uses an a-Si backplane.<br/>
<br/>
Next in line for release are the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a> models that have been rumored for some time. Apple will launch a new 11-inch and 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with a redesigned chassis and new M3 chip in the second quarter.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes that last on Apple's 2024 production roadmap are a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, and an 11th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; – a new version of Apple's most affordable tablet. This will see the discontinuation of Apple's 9th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; currently still offered alongside the 10th-generation model in Apple's lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes these changes will see only modest gains in &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; shipments compared to this year, and predicts around 52-54 million units in 2024 compared to 2023. Such an increase remains way off Apple's peak of 63 million iPads shipped in 2022 during the pandemic.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> recently also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/all-ipads-expected-to-be-updated-in-2024/">suggested</a> Apple will update its entire &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lineup throughout 2024, but his timeline prediction is slightly different to Kuo and does not mention a new larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-march-2024-launch/">previously reported</a> that the low-end to mid-range iPads could be updated as early as March 2024, while he expects new 11-inch and 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models with the M3 chip and OLED displays to launch in the first half of 2024. The next &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; are likely to be equipped with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> and A16 Bionic chips, respectively.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">Kuo: Larger 12.9-inch iPad Air Coming Early 2024 Amid Lineup Refresh</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-larger-12-9-inch-ipad-air-coming-early-2024-amid-lineup-refresh.2410742/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: M3 Macs Launch, iOS 17.1.1 Released, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/11/top-stories-m3-mac-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-m3-macs-launch-ios-17-1-1-released-and-more.2410665/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/11/top-stories-m3-mac-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following Apple's "Scary Fast" event on October 30, the new M3-based MacBook Pro and iMac models have officially launched, so media and everyday users alike have been sharing their thoughts on what's almost certainly the last of Apple's new hardware for 2023.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/top-stories-11nov2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922221" /><br/>
While hardware may be wrapping up for the year, Apple's still hard at work on software updates with a number of bug-fix releases this week plus a new round of betas for more significant updates we're expecting to see released before the end of the year. Black Friday deals are also starting to get underway several weeks ahead of the big day, so be sure to read on below for all of this week's top stories!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New MacBook Pro Reviews: Scary Fast, But M3 Pro Chip Has a Catch</h2><br/>
The new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips began arriving to customers and launched in stores this week, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-pro/">first reviews of the laptops have been shared</a>. We also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-macbook-pro-hands-on/">shared our own hands-on video of the new MacBook Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-MacBook-Pro-Unboxing-Thumb-3.1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921534" /><br/>
The new iMac with the M3 chip is also now available, and we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-imac/">rounded up reviews</a> of the all-in-one desktop computer.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Says There Won't Be a 27-Inch iMac With Apple Silicon</h2><br/>
Apple discontinued both the Intel-based 27-inch iMac and iMac Pro over the past two years, and it has yet to launch a larger-screen iMac with an Apple silicon chip as a replacement, leaving the 24-inch iMac as its only all-in-one desktop computer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iMac-Pro-2022-27-and-24-iMac.jpg" alt="" width="1626" height="914" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833952" /><br/>
Apple this week confirmed that it has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/no-27-inch-with-apple-silicon/">no plans to release a new version of the 27-inch iMac with Apple silicon</a>, but that does not explicitly rule out the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/new-32-inch-imac-pro-expected-2024-or-2025/">rumored 32-inch iMac Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases iOS 17.1.1 With Bug Fixes for BMW Wireless Charging and Weather Widget</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/">released a minor iOS 17.1.1 update for the iPhone with a pair of bug fixes</a>. Specifically, the update resolves a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-to-fix-iphone-15-bmw-charging-issue/">BMW wireless charging issue</a> affecting the iPhone 15 lineup, and it addresses a bug related to the Weather widget displaying snow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-17.1.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920500" /><br/>
The update is available for the iPhone XS and newer, and it can be installed in the Settings app by tapping on General → Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases watchOS 10.1.1 With Fix for Apple Watch Battery Drain Bug</h2><br/>
Alongside iOS 17.1.1, Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-1/">released a minor watchOS 10.1.1 update for the Apple Watch</a>. The update resolves an issue causing excessive battery drain on a variety of Apple Watch models that had been updated to watchOS 10.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" /><br/>
Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/watchos-update-to-fix-battery-drain-issue/">acknowledged the battery drain issue in an internal memo</a> obtained by <em>MacRumors</em>, and it has now delivered on its promise to make a fix available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17.2 Will Add These 10 New Features to Your iPhone</h2><br/>
iOS 17.2 remains in beta testing, and while we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/ios-17-2-features-list/">published an overview of ten features coming in the update</a> based on the first beta, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/">second beta released late this week</a> added even more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/10-New-Features-With-iOS-17.2-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919096" /><br/>
New features in the second iOS 17.2 beta include the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-spatial-video-recording/">record spatial video on iPhone 15 Pro models</a> for viewing on Vision Pro and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-expands-sensitive-content-warnings/">expansion of the optional Sensitive Content Warning feature</a> to include Contact Posters, stickers in the Messages app, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Silicon Buyer's Guide: Which Chip Should You Choose?</h2><br/>
Choosing a new Mac often involves consideration of the many Apple silicon chips now on offer, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon-buyers-guide/">our comprehensive guide covers their generations, variations, and performance benchmarks</a> to help you decide which is best for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Mac-Chip-Comparison-Buyers-Guide-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902570" /><br/>
Our guide includes Apple's latest M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips announced for the 14-inch MacBook Pro, 16-inch MacBook Pro, and 24-inch iMac last month.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday</a> is still two weeks away, but the holiday shopping season is already ramping up with tons of solid deals on Apple products and more. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-early-black-friday-deals.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920468" /><br/>
We're <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">keeping track of the best deals</a>, regularly updating our coverage to reflect the rapidly changing deal situation, and we've got dedicated deal guides for Apple's major product categories linked in there for closer looks.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/nov-9-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/11/top-stories-m3-mac-launch/">Top Stories: M3 Macs Launch, iOS 17.1.1 Released, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-m3-macs-launch-ios-17-1-1-released-and-more.2410665/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Shares M3 MacBook Pro Teardown, Explains How Apple Created Space Black Finish</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ifixit-m3-macbook-pro-teardown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-shares-m3-macbook-pro-teardown-explains-how-apple-created-space-black-finish.2410617/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ifixit-m3-macbook-pro-teardown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Repair website iFixit today shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3yXCKMNEJUo">video teardown</a> of the new 14-inch MacBook Pro with both the M3 and M3 Pro chips, providing a closer look inside the laptops. The internal design is virtually unchanged compared to the previous MacBook Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
iFixit also <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/86128/how-apple-made-the-space-black-macbook-pro-darker-than-ever">shared a blog post</a> in which it explains how it believes Apple achieved its new, darker Space Black finish for the MacBook Pro. In short, it said that Apple managed to make the Space Black finish's anodized surface "more uneven" at a microscopic level, resulting in more light reflecting off it for a darker appearance.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple found they could etch the already rough anodized surface, making it more uneven," wrote iFixit's Kevin O'Reilly. "The resulting nooks and crannies further diffuse incoming light rays, sending them off in even more directions. Less white light makes its way to our eyeballs—resulting in that slick matte finish."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3yXCKMNEJUo?si=MOVMnmMtbh2R4I2e" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
iFixit provides an in-depth, scientific overview of the Space Black finish, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">new anodization seal that reduces fingerprints</a>, in its <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/86128/how-apple-made-the-space-black-macbook-pro-darker-than-ever">blog post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The new MacBook Pro models launched earlier this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ifixit-m3-macbook-pro-teardown/">iFixit Shares M3 MacBook Pro Teardown, Explains How Apple Created Space Black Finish</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-shares-m3-macbook-pro-teardown-explains-how-apple-created-space-black-finish.2410617/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Project Alaska: Apple&#039;s Second-Generation Vision Pro Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/project-alaska-second-generation-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/project-alaska-apples-second-generation-vision-pro-headset.2410615/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 14:00:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/project-alaska-second-generation-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the last several months, we've heard reports that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/vision-pro-2-focusing-on-size-weight-lenses/">working on a second-generation AR/VR headset</a>, although there have been few details shared about the device. <em>MacRumors</em> has now received new information about the project, giving us some insight into the design and hardware of the successor to the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898552" /><br/>
The second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset, known internally under the codename Project Alaska and device identifier N109, bears striking resemblance to the first-generation Vision Pro announced at WWDC 2023. While the device maintains the curved aesthetic and button placement of the first Vision Pro, the speaker placement is expected to be different. <br/>
<br/>
Early designs of the second-generation Apple headset do not include the rounded areas that house the speakers on the first-generation model. Instead, the headset features temples that are flat and uniform throughout their entire length. Documentation related to the Alaska project contains references to a non-descript audio accessory, possibly an external speaker. At one point in development, there were two different design configurations for the top vents – one being the same as the vents on the first-generation &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;, and the latter featuring two clusters of tiny speaker-type holes.<br/>
<br/>
Another key difference has to do with the rear straps. The second-generation headset features straps that are simpler in design and appearance, being somewhat reminiscent of the flat straps commonly found on laptop bags or backpacks. Prior rumors have suggested that the next Apple headset could be cheaper than the Vision Pro, and the design of the rear straps on the second-generation headset lends some credence to this theory. More streamlined straps would presumably be easier to mass produce, perhaps resulting in a lower overall price for end consumers. <br/>
<br/>
Along with the possibility of an audio accessory, information from our sources suggests that Apple has plans for an external battery pack, similar to the battery pack used for the first-generation &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of hardware, the second-generation Vision Pro will continue to include an array of cameras and sensors similar to those in the first headset. To be more specific, the device will feature a compass, ambient light sensor, magnetometer, and gyroscope, all of which are already present in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. For connectivity, the second generation Apple headset will support Wi-Fi, Bluetooth 5, and ultra-low latency audio (ULLA).<br/>
<br/>
Key hardware components of the second-generation Apple headset:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>2 micro-OLED displays</li><br/>
<li>1 TrueDepth camera</li><br/>
<li>4 computer vision (CV) cameras</li><br/>
<li>2 RGB cameras</li><br/>
<li>2 low light infrared illuminators</li><br/>
<li>Semi-automatic interpupillary distance (IPD) adjustment</li><br/>
<li>Compass, ambient light sensor, magnetometer, accelerometer, gyrocope</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Current information indicates that the second-generation Apple headset is scheduled for the product validation testing (PVT) stage of development in 2025, suggesting a release date of late 2025 or early 2026. The information we've shared comes from a reliable source that has provided us with details about Apple's plans in the past, but it is worth noting that this is pre-production information and Apple's plans could change before final mass production begins on the second-generation headset. <br/>
<br/>
For more information on the current &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">dedicated Vision Pro roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/project-alaska-second-generation-vision-pro/">Project Alaska: Apple&#039;s Second-Generation Vision Pro Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/project-alaska-apples-second-generation-vision-pro-headset.2410615/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Black Friday Sales Introduce Big Discounts on AirPods, Apple Watch, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-11-10-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-black-friday-sales-introduce-big-discounts-on-airpods-apple-watch-and-more.2410599/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:29:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-11-10-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're just two weeks away from Black Friday, and Apple deals are in full swing right now. We're tracking the year's best prices on Apple Watch Series 9, AirPods 2, HomePod, HomePod mini, and more in our recap of the week's best deals. For a more in-depth look at the current best Black Friday deals, check out our post on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">early Black Friday Apple deals</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0008.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847998" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/anker-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922238" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take 25% off Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu">Anker</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/anker-black-friday-early-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">25% OFF</div>Anker Black Friday Early Access</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker is always a reliable source for deals throughout the year, and Black Friday season is definitely no different. The company is currently offering 25 percent off your entire order when you buy two or more accessories at once, as well as quite a few straight cash discounts without needing a bundle.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-9-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922237" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off Apple Watch Series 9</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-watch-black-friday-deal-sees-series-9/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One great early Black Friday deal can be found on the new Apple Watch Series 9, which Amazon has for &#36;50 off right now. This includes both GPS and cellular models, with prices now starting at &#36;349.00 for 41mm GPS, a new record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-red-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922236" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;60 off AirPods 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/153062/565706/9383?veh=aff&sourceid=imp_000011112222333344&u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-AirPods-with-Charging-Case-2nd-Generation%2F604342441">Walmart</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/airpods-2-69-for-black-friday/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/153062/565706/9383?veh=aff&sourceid=imp_000011112222333344&u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-AirPods-with-Charging-Case-2nd-Generation%2F604342441"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Walmart kicked off its Black Friday sale with a major discount on AirPods 2, now available for &#36;69.00, down from &#36;129.00. Amazon briefly matched this price, but we haven't seen it return in two days. This is a new all-time low price on the 2019 earbuds, and a great Black Friday deal.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomePod</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/homepods-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922235" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;20 off HomePod mini and &#36;19 off HomePod (Gen 2)</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FApple%2F4Y5G2LLA%2F">OWC</a> and <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612">B&H Photo</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<em><div class="center-wrap"><strong>Note: These are in new condition but come in bulk packaging.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FApple%2F4Y5G2LLA%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>HomePod mini for &#36;78.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>HomePod (2nd Gen) for &#36;279.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Notable HomePod discounts have arrived for Black Friday, starting at &#36;78.99 for the HomePod mini at OWC in new condition but in bulk packaging and with a 90 day OWC fulfilled limited warranty. This is a solid record low price on the mini smart speaker.<br/>
<br/>
B&H Photo has the second generation HomePod for &#36;279.99, which is another match of an all-time low price that's available in all colors.<br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-11-10-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Black Friday Sales Introduce Big Discounts on AirPods, Apple Watch, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-black-friday-sales-introduce-big-discounts-on-airpods-apple-watch-and-more.2410599/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First Impressions: iPhone 15 Pro Spatial Videos on Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/spatial-videos-on-vision-pro-first-impressions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-impressions-iphone-15-pro-spatial-videos-on-vision-pro.2410602/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:28:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/spatial-videos-on-vision-pro-first-impressions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with iOS 17.2, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ios-17-2-public-beta-2/">currently in beta</a> and expected to be released in December, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-spatial-video-recording/">can record spatial video</a> with 3D depth for playback on Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset. When held in landscape orientation, the iPhone's main and ultra wide cameras combine to record 3D video.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
The feature can be toggled on in the Settings app under Camera → Formats, and when it is, an extra button to record spatial video appears in the Video section of the Camera app. Spatial videos are recorded in 1080p at 30 fps, and Apple says the iPhone needs to be in landscape orientation and stabilized for the best results. Apple says the toggle will be turned on automatically for future Vision Pro owners.<br/>
<br/>
When played on the iPhone, spatial videos are regular 2D videos without any extra depth effect.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Vision-Pro-Spatial-Video.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922277" /><br/>
While the Vision Pro does not launch until "early 2024" in the U.S., Apple invited some members of the press to record their own spatial videos on the iPhone 15 Pro and watch them on the headset this week. Apple is still not allowing the press to share photos or videos of the Vision Pro, so there are only written impressions for now.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://techthings.cmail19.com/t/d-e-vhlukdk-irijhkzjj-r/"><em>The Wall Street Journal</em>'s Joanna Stern</a>, in her <a href="https://www.wsj.com/newsletters?sub=486&mod=article_inline"><em>Tech Things</em> newsletter</a>:<blockquote>At the demo, I recorded a sushi chef holding a piece of sushi. When I watched it back in the Vision Pro, the sushi and the chopsticks really looked 3-D. They were clearly in the foreground, hovering closer to me than the rest of the imagery. Of course the lighting was perfect when recording—we'll have to see how it does in imperfect conditions.<br/>
<br/>
Apple showed me some other spatial videos. In one, a dad was telling his young kids a story in the back of an RV. It was so lifelike and cozy that it almost creeped me out. Why am I spying on this random family? That's obviously the big appeal here: spatial videos create intimacy in ways 2-D photos and videos don't.</blockquote><a href="https://www.thestreet.com/deals/apple-vision-pro-spatial-video-first-look-iphone-15-pro"><em>TheStreet</em>'s Jacob Krol</a>:<blockquote>Likely as Apple intended, capturing Spatial Video is simple and feels just as intuitive as shooting in another one of the modes on the iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max. You'll turn the phone into the landscape to unlock the recording mode, indicated by a headset icon, and see a level appear as you're filming.<br/>
<br/>
Horizon view and level are important, as an ultra-shaky video can be more jarring when playing back on the Vision Pro. In my experience, I captured a professional sushi chef creating a few standard rolls and rice balls, as well as the chef holding up the end product. I gradually approached, placing the roll while it was suspended in the air via chopsticks by about a foot and a half way. The iPhone did an excellent job of switching focus while I was moving around the piece of sushi and capturing the chef in the background. You can also manually click to focus if you'd like.</blockquote><a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/apple-iphone-spatial-video-arrives-in-beta-and-looks-amazing-on-vision-pro/"><em>CNET</em>'s Scott Stein</a>:<blockquote>The videos look great and the 3D is compellingly realistic. They're also easy to record, and can save as videos that will play back in 2D in a normal video format. But ultimately this feature is made for a 2024 product that, at &#36;3,500, it's safe to say most people won't buy anytime soon. Still, the experience is impressive.</blockquote>Stein noted that Apple's professional video editing app Final Cut Pro will be updated with spatial video editing support at some point next year.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial video recording on iPhone 15 Pro models was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-spatial-video-recording/">added in the second beta of iOS 17.2</a> seeded to developers yesterday and to public beta testers today.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/spatial-videos-on-vision-pro-first-impressions/">First Impressions: iPhone 15 Pro Spatial Videos on Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-impressions-iphone-15-pro-spatial-videos-on-vision-pro.2410602/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of iOS 17.2 With Journal App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ios-17-2-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-2-with-journal-app-and-more.2410594/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 10:15:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ios-17-2-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 updates to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to try out the software ahead of its release. The second iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 public betas come two weeks after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-1/">first public betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918853" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 adds the Journal app, designed to let <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users record their daily activities and thoughts. Apple offers prompts that can be used as inspiration, and journal entries can be outfitted with images, voice recordings, location tags, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Collaborative playlists are now available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> so you can create playlists that multiple people contribute to, and there's also now a Favorites playlist that has all the music you've favorited. Stickers can be used as tapback reactions in the Messages app, the Action Button on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models can now be set to a new Translate function, and Apple has implemented support for iMessage Contact Key Verification.<br/>
<br/>
There are new Weather and Clock widgets, tweaks to the TV app, updates to Message syncing across devices, new Memoji options, and more, with the full list of features we've found so far available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.2 beta features article</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ios-17-2-public-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of iOS 17.2 With Journal App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-2-with-journal-app-and-more.2410594/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/macos-14-2-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2.2410593/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 10:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/macos-14-2-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second public beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2 update, allowing non-developers to test out the software ahead of its release. The second public beta comes two weeks after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macos-sonoma-14-2-public-beta-1/">the first public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 adds Messages sticker reactions, which make it quicker to add a sticker or an emoji to an iMessage. It also includes support for collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists, allowing multiple people to add songs to a single playlist. <br/>
<br/>
There's a new Favorites &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; playlist as well, better support for Messages in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> syncing, and iMessage Contact Key Verification for people who face extraordinary digital threats. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/macos-14-2-public-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2.2410593/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Air Black Friday Deals Bring Massive &#36;200-&#36;300 Discounts to 13-Inch and 15-Inch Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/macbook-air-black-friday-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-black-friday-deals-bring-massive-200-300-discounts-to-13-inch-and-15-inch-models.2410581/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:58:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/macbook-air-black-friday-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is back with a few steep discounts on MacBook Air models today, including &#36;200 off the 13.6-inch MacBook Air and &#36;300 off the 15.3-inch MacBook Air. The best deals can be found if you're a <a href="https://howl.me/ckUf0uURy5j">My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total</a> member, with everyone else able to buy these notebooks at solid second-best prices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922226" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
If you don't have a membership, you can <a href="https://howl.me/ckUf0uURy5j">sign up for one on Best Buy's website</a>. They start at &#36;49.99 per year for My Best Buy Plus, providing you access to exclusive sales and events, free two-day shipping, extended 60-day return window on most products, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13.6-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Starting with the smaller model, Best Buy has the 256GB 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air at <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxabVFYOE"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,099.00. If you aren't a member, you can still get this notebook at a great price of &#36;949.00, which is &#36;150 off.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxabVFYOE"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, there's also the 512GB 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air at <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxehYyrkk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,399.00. Non-members can get this notebook for &#36;1,249.00, which is another &#36;150 discount on the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxehYyrkk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The My Best Buy Plus and Total member pricing represent the current best deals you can get on these MacBook Air models right now. For the 256GB notebook, this is also a match of the best price we've ever tracked.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>15.3-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Best Buy has the 256GB 15.3-inch M2 MacBook Air at <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,299.00, which is a new record low price at &#36;300 off. Non-members can get the computer for &#36;1,049.00, which is the typical sale price we track on this model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15.3-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There's also the 512GB 15.3-inch M2 MacBook Air at <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxm6NM1wV"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,499.00, which is another steep &#36;300 markdown on the 2023 MacBook Air. If you don't have a membership, you can again get this one at &#36;250 off the regular price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxm6NM1wV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15.3-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/macbook-air-black-friday-deals/">MacBook Air Black Friday Deals Bring Massive &#36;200-&#36;300 Discounts to 13-Inch and 15-Inch Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-black-friday-deals-bring-massive-200-300-discounts-to-13-inch-and-15-inch-models.2410581/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Is Apple Finally Taking Gaming Seriously? ft. TouchArcade</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-is-apple-finally-taking-gaming-seriously-ft-toucharcade.2410577/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:22:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>TouchArcade</category>
		<category>Mac Gaming</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://toucharcade.com"><em>TouchArcade</em></a>'s Jared Nelson and Eli Hodapp join us on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/is-apple-finally-taking-gaming-seriously-ft-toucharcade/id1602394741?i=1000634391855">The MacRumors Show</a> to talk through the current state of gaming in Apple's ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BqHmk7alzgA?si=R7446_2tro45SMmT" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
<a href="https://toucharcade.com"><em>TouchArcade</em></a> is <em>MacRumors</em>' sister site that focuses on iOS gaming. Jared is the website's Editor-in-Chief and host of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/the-toucharcade-show-an-iphone-games-podcast/id337015605">The TouchArcade Show podcast</a>, while Eli is Jared's predecessor, the founder of iOS gaming subscription service GameClub, and director of mobile publishing at GameMill Entertainment.<br/>
<br/>
We discuss Apple's recent gaming push prompted by the A17 Pro and M3 chip's hardware-accelerated ray-tracing, as well as the arrival of console-level games on Apple platforms like "Resident Evil Village." We look at where Apple has made progress with gaming in recent years and where it still faces limitations, what the company should address to bolster gaming experiences on its devices, and the direction of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>. We also consider the gaming potential of Apple's Vision Pro headset and how the new product line could evolve over time.<br/>
<br/>
Listen to more of Jared and Eli over on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/the-toucharcade-show-an-iphone-games-podcast/id337015605">The TouchArcade Show podcast</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so head over and subscribe to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">"Scary Fast" event</a> and the new Macs it introduced.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is now on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/toucharcade/">TouchArcade</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-gaming/">Mac Gaming</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">The MacRumors Show: Is Apple Finally Taking Gaming Seriously? ft. TouchArcade</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-is-apple-finally-taking-gaming-seriously-ft-toucharcade.2410577/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>8GB RAM in M3 MacBook Pro Proves the Bottleneck in Real-World Tests</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck-in-real-world-tests.2410564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:47:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new MacBook Pro models are powered by cutting-edge M3 Apple silicon, but the base configuration 14-inch model starting at &#36;1,599 comes with just 8GB of working memory. In 2012, Apple launched the first MacBook Pro with Retina display, which also started with 8GB of RAM. Of course, Apple now uses integrated chips with unified memory architecture, which is why the company feels confident in arguing that 8GB on a Mac is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/8gb-ram-m3-macbook-pro-like-16-gb-pc/">comparable to 16GB on rival systems</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hmWPd7uEYEY?si=zIgEy80AQutgE9Xj" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
But not everyone is convinced. Apple's decision not to equip base models with at least 16GB of RAM in late 2023 has proved incongruous to many users, including Vadim Yuryev, co-host of the YouTube channel <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hmWPd7uEYEY">Max Tech</a>. Yuryev decided to perform several real-world tests on two 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro models, one with 8GB and the other upgraded to 16GB of unified memory. The embedded video above has all the results.  <br/>
<br/>
Perhaps unsurprisingly, Yuryev saw significant performance improvements across the board using the 16GB machine under both middling and heavier workloads. The 8GB model suffered double-digit losses in Cinebench benchmarks, and took several minutes longer to complete photo-merging jobs in Photoshop as well as media exports in Final Cut and Adobe Lightroom Classic.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/max-tech-8gb-16gb-mbp2.jpg" alt="" width="2491" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922139" /><br/>
These tests were conducted as single operations with nothing else running, but also repeated with browser tabs, YouTube videos, spreadsheets, emails, and the like, open in the background to simulate typical real-world multi-tasking scenarios. As expected, the performance gap between the two machines widened further as the 8GB increasingly relied on its SSD swap file, while all-round responsiveness took a hit. Yuryev even reported crashes on the 8GB model during Blender rendering and a Final Cut export.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, Blender's raytracing acceleration was available as an option on the 16GB models, but was conspicuously absent on the 8GB MacBook Pro for an identical rendering job, suggesting the reduced memory pool actually prevents the GPU cores from utilizing certain features. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/max-tech-8gb-16gb-mbp1.jpg" alt="" width="2490" height="1401" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922142" /><br/>
Tests like these present a dilemma for customers looking to purchase a new MacBook Pro (or a new 8GB iMac, for that matter). Settling for 8GB appears to hinder the M3 chip's performance, but choosing 16GB or 24GB configuration options at checkout costs an extra &#36;200 and &#36;400, respectively, and Apple's machines cannot be upgraded at a later date because of their unified memory architecture. <br/>
<br/>
After factoring in the extra &#36;200 for 16GB on a 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro, an M3 Pro model with 18GB and several other extra features is only &#36;200 more at &#36;1,999. More galling perhaps is the fact that rival laptops at similar ballpark prices (Microsoft Surface or Lenovo Thinkpad, for example) come with at least 16GB of memory as standard. Apple customers are expected to pay &#36;200 extra each jump up, which surely includes a healthy markup, however much Apple pays its RAM suppliers.<br/>
<br/>
Is Apple's 8GB starting configuration for a &#36;1,599 MacBook Pro really acceptable in 2023? And has the company's memory pricing policy affected your own purchase options? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck/">8GB RAM in M3 MacBook Pro Proves the Bottleneck in Real-World Tests</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8gb-ram-in-m3-macbook-pro-proves-the-bottleneck-in-real-world-tests.2410564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
