<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 09:03:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 16 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 30+ Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16-buyers-guide-30-upgrades-compared.2419705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:35:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16&#038;post_date=1726079700/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus launch later this month, offering 35 changes and improvements over their predecessors. Here's everything that's different.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-15-vs-16-Feature-Yellow-Pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-936647" /></div><br/>
While Apple's latest models bring a variety of enhancements, the most significant change is support for Apple Intelligence, a new AI system that transforms how you interact with your device by offering smarter notifications, text summarization, and contextual information. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; also features the Action Button and Camera Control button, which provide more intuitive ways to access key functions.<br/>
<br/>
But beyond these headline features, how much of an improvement does the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; really offer? This guide breaks down the differences between the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models to help you understand all of the changes and determine whether these enhancements are enough to justify making the switch from an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
This guide focuses on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, but to learn about how the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> improves on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">see our other comparison guide</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design_and_displays">Design and Displays</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; introduces several design and display upgrades over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. The shift to vertically arranged cameras facilitates spatial video capture and looks more modern. Durability is also improved with the next-generation Ceramic Shield, which is twice as strong as the previous version. Additionally, the customizable Action Button replaces the traditional Ring/Silent switch and a new Camera Control button streamlines photography.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Diagonally arranged rear cameras</td><br/>
 <td>Vertically arranged rear cameras</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>~2–4 nits minimum brightness</td><br/>
 <td>1 nit minimum brightness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ceramic Shield front glass</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation Ceramic Shield front glass (2x stronger)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved thermal design for better heat dissipation</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Easier battery service</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action Button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Camera Control capacitive button with sapphire crystal cover</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Green, Blue, Pink, Black, and Yellow finishes</td><br/>
 <td>Available in Teal, Ultramarine, Pink, Black, and White finishes</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="artificial_intelligence">Artificial Intelligence</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; includes support for Apple Intelligence, a significant upgrade absent in the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. This artificial intelligence system enhances the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s ability to understand and process personal context, offering features like Visual Intelligence, which can recognize objects and scenes through the camera and provide relevant information, such as restaurant or product details.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Apple Intelligence (including priority notifications, text summarization, system-wide writing tools, audio transcription, Genmoji creation, personalized suggestions, and more)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Visual Intelligence, allowing users to pull up contextual information about objects or scenes in front of the camera (such as restaurant details or product info)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features like priority notifications, text summarization, and system-wide writing tools can significantly enhance the experience of using the device, making the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; a substantial upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; in this area. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_memory_and_connectivity">Chip, Memory, and Connectivity</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; brings notable improvements in performance and connectivity over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, driven by the A18 chip built with TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process, which is more efficient and powerful than the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s A16 chip. The 6-core CPU is up to 30% faster, while the upgraded 16-core Neural Engine is optimized for running generative models, doubling the speed of machine learning tasks. In terms of graphics, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;'s 5-core GPU delivers a 40% boost in performance and introduces hardware-accelerated ray tracing, enhancing gaming and visual effects.<br/>
<br/>
Memory and connectivity also see significant upgrades, with the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; offering 8GB of RAM, a 33% increase over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, and the introduction of Wi-Fi 7 and Thread networking for better wireless performance and smart home integration.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A16 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N4P" enhanced 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU (up to 30% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded 16-core Neural Engine optimized for generative models (runs ML models 2x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU (up to 40% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hardware-accelerated ray tracing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory (+33%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 7 (802.11be) with 2x2 MIMO</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thread networking technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The performance gains with the A18 chip and enhanced GPU are particularly meaningful for users who engage in gaming, video editing, or other graphics-heavy tasks. The hardware-accelerated ray tracing will greatly benefit gamers, making the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; capable of rendering more realistic lighting and shadows. Meanwhile, the Neural Engine upgrade doubles the speed of machine learning tasks such as Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
For everyday users, the jump from 6GB to 8GB of memory ensures better multitasking and future-proofing, while Wi-Fi 7 and Thread networking will improve connectivity speeds and compatibility with smart home devices. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;'s improvements are substantial for users who demand higher performance and future-ready wireless tech, though those who use their devices more casually might notice less immediate impact.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="camera">Camera</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; enhances the already impressive camera setup from the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. The Ultra Wide camera has been upgraded with an ƒ/2.2 aperture, providing better low-light performance compared to the ƒ/2.4 aperture on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; also introduces Macro photography and Macro video recording, enabling users to capture detailed close-up shots, while the Camera Control button brings new levels of ease and precision to shooting photos and videos.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Main camera with ƒ/1.6 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Fusion camera with ƒ/1.6 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera with ƒ/2.4 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture for improved-low light performance</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anti-reflective coating on Fusion camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Macro photography and Macro video recording, including slo‑mo and time‑lapse</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Photo­graphic Styles</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation Photo­graphic Styles</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Spatial video recording at 1080p at 30 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4K video recording at 24 fps, 25 fps, 30 fps or 60 fps</td><br/>
 <td>4K Dolby Vision video recording at 24 fps, 25 fps, 30 fps or 60 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1080p HD video recording at 25 fps, 30 fps or 60 fps</td><br/>
 <td>1080p Dolby Vision video recording at 25 fps, 30 fps or 60 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Cinematic mode up to 4K HDR at 30 fps</td><br/>
 <td>Cinematic mode up to 4K Dolby Vision at 30 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>QuickTake video</td><br/>
 <td>QuickTake video (up to 4K at 60 fps in Dolby Vision HDR)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Camera Control button features:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Launch the Camera App</strong>: Pressing the Camera Control button immediately opens the camera app.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Capture Photos</strong>: A single press of the button captures a photo, providing a quick and tactile way to take pictures.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Record Videos</strong>: A press and hold action allows you to start recording a video.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Half-Press for Focus and Exposure</strong> (upcoming feature): A light, half-press will lock focus and exposure, allowing you to reframe the shot without losing focus.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Trackpad-Like Control</strong>: The capacitive sensor on the button acts like a trackpad, enabling gestures to control zoom, cycle through filters, or switch between lenses by sliding your finger across the button.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Third-Party App Integration</strong>: The Camera Control button can also be used to trigger third-party camera apps, giving more flexibility to users who prefer other photography tools.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Camera Function Overlay</strong>: A light touch gesture reveals a clean preview and quick access to key camera controls like zoom or exposure settings.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Visual Intelligence Activation</strong>: The Camera Control button is integrated with Visual Intelligence, allowing users to pull up contextual information about objects or scenes in front of the camera.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="audio_recording">Audio Recording</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; brings several enhancements to audio recording over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. While the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; offers stereo recording, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; introduces Spatial Audio recording, providing a more immersive sound experience, particularly with playback on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset. Additional features like wind noise reduction and the new Audio Mix function further improve the quality and flexibility of recorded audio, making the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; a more capable device for capturing high-quality sound.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Stereo recording</td><br/>
 <td>Spatial Audio and stereo recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Wind noise reduction</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Audio Mix</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="battery_life_and_charging">Battery Life and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; brings noticeable improvements in battery life and charging efficiency compared to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. With up to 22 hours of battery life on the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 27 hours on the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, the new models offer a modest boost. In addition, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> wireless charging is now significantly faster, supporting up to 25W with a 30W adapter, a 66.67% increase over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s 15W limit.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15</strong>: Up to 20 hours of battery life<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Plus</strong>: Up to 26 hours of battery life</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: Up to 22 hours of battery life<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: Up to 27 hours of battery life</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wireless charging up to 15W with 20W adapter or higher</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wireless charging up to 25W with 30W adapter or higher <strong>(+66.67%)</strong></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="release_date">Release Date</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will be available for pre-order starting on Friday, September 13, 2024, with the official launch and availability in stores beginning Friday, September 20, 2024. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="is_it_worth_upgrading">Is It Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, while bringing some notable improvements, offer what might feel like an incremental upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus for most users. The most significant advancements come from Apple Intelligence and the introduction of the Action Button and Camera Control, both of which provide new ways to interact with the device. <br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence is arguably the most important new feature, as it enhances the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s ability to understand user context and assist in everyday tasks like prioritizing notifications, summarizing texts, and pulling real-time information through Visual Intelligence. For users who rely heavily on their phone for productivity and communication, this AI-driven functionality is a meaningful addition. The Action Button and Camera Control button are welcome hardware changes, offering customizable, quick access to key functions and improved control over photography and videography.<br/>
<br/>
Outside of these features, however, the upgrades feel more conservative. The performance gains with the A18 chip, new Neural Engine, and GPU architecture offer incremental improvements in speed and efficiency, which will benefit high-performance tasks like gaming, but may not be immediately noticeable for everyday users. The camera updates, including better ultra wide low-light performance and Macro photography, are valuable for photography enthusiasts, but they don't dramatically alter the overall camera experience for casual users. Similarly, the improvements in battery life and charging speeds are useful but relatively minor, providing a modest boost over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
For users with an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, the upgrade might not feel substantial unless you're looking to take full advantage of Apple Intelligence or the new buttons. If your phone usage revolves around basic tasks, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; remains an excellent device, and upgrading may not be necessary. However, if you're someone who is interested in AI or more intuitive camera controls, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; offers enough to justify the switch. Overall, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is a step forward, but the upgrades are relatively modest.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/">iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 16 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 30+ Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16-buyers-guide-30-upgrades-compared.2419705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Skipping the iPhone 16 Pro? Here&#039;s What&#039;s Rumored for iPhone 17 Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/iphone-17-pro-rumor-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/skipping-the-iphone-16-pro-heres-whats-rumored-for-iphone-17-pro.2435871/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:20:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/iphone-17-pro-rumor-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Will you be skipping the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-announces-iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and waiting another year to upgrade? If so, we already have some iPhone 17 Pro rumors for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-models-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964745" /><br/>
Below, we recap key new features rumored for the iPhone 17 Pro models so far:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>24MP front camera for all iPhone 17 models:</strong> All four iPhone 17 models will feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-rumor/">upgraded 24-megapixel front-facing camera</a>, according to Apple supply chain analysts Ming-Chi Kuo and Jeff Pu. For comparison, all four iPhone 16 models are equipped with a 12-megapixel front-facing camera.</li><br/>
<li><strong>48MP rear Telephoto camera for iPhone 17 Pro Max and maybe iPhone 17 Pro:</strong> An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/">upgraded 48-megapixel Telephoto camera</a> is rumored for the iPhone 17 Pro Max, compared to the 12-megapixel Telephoto camera on iPhone 16 Pro models. This change has not been ruled out for the iPhone 17 Pro too, but it might not come to the smaller Pro model until the iPhone 18 Pro.</li><br/>
<li><strong>12GB of RAM for iPhone 17 Pro Max:</strong> An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/">increased 12GB of RAM</a> is rumored exclusively for the iPhone 17 Pro Max, and this would benefit Apple Intelligence and multitasking performance. There is 8GB of RAM in the iPhone 16 Pro Max.</li><br/>
<li><strong>A smaller Dynamic Island for iPhone 17 Pro Max:</strong> Another change rumored exclusively for the iPhone 17 Pro Max is a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-rumor/">much narrowed Dynamic Island</a>," as a result of hardware changes to the Face ID system.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
iPhone 17 Pro models should launch in September 2025, so there is still plenty of time to go, and additional details will surface over the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>'iPhone 17 Air'</h2><br/>
There have been rumors from several credible sources about Apple planning to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-17-slim-everything-we-know/">redesigned, significantly thinner iPhone 17 model</a>, which could be called an iPhone 17 Air. There have been conflicting rumors about the design and specifications for this device, but most sources have agreed that it will have around a 6.6-inch display. Apple supply chain Ming-Chi Kuo said he expects the device to be equipped with a standard A19 chip, a Dynamic Island, a single rear camera, and an Apple-designed 5G modem.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/iphone-17-pro-rumor-recap/">Skipping the iPhone 16 Pro? Here&#039;s What&#039;s Rumored for iPhone 17 Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/skipping-the-iphone-16-pro-heres-whats-rumored-for-iphone-17-pro.2435871/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Big Savings on Portable Power Stations From Anker and Jackery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/amazon-savings-power-stations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-savings-on-portable-power-stations-from-anker-and-jackery.2435869/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:09:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/amazon-savings-power-stations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a big selection of discounts on <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1754-SOLIX-C800-Plus%2Fdp%2FB0C5CBDX2P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Anker's</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2_1726066202728">Jackery's</a> best portable power stations on Amazon, with as much as &#36;1,399 in savings on these devices. These accessories are high-capacity portable batteries that can provide backup power to a wide variety of devices, from laptops to RVs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/anker-jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958617" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For the Anker deals, you'll need to have a Prime membership in order to see some of these discounted prices, while others require an on-page coupon to be clipped before you see the final deal price. In regards to the Jackery discounts, all of these also require an on-page coupon in order to see the deal prices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2_1726066202728">Solar Generator with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;249.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QYH6YGJP7QXZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QYH6YGJP7QXZ_1726066280020">Solar Generator 300 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;419.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1Y4BIWHXTZ6QC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1Y4BIWHXTZ6QC_1726066047816">Explorer 1000 (2024 Model) Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;549.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2934EWK71TJ3A%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2934EWK71TJ3A_1726066103266">Expansion Battery Pack 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;999.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.YB2Y3VY6Z5QD%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.YB2Y3VY6Z5QD_1726066289607">Explorer 3000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;2,149.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;2,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DT4Q3X%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2934EWK71TJ3A%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2934EWK71TJ3A_1726066103267">Explorer Kit 4000 Plus (2X Portable Power Stations)</a> - &#36;2,999.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;3,799.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1754-SOLIX-C800-Plus%2Fdp%2FB0C5CBDX2P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C800 Power Station with Camping Lights</a> - &#36;499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;649.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Generator-UltraFast-Optional%2Fdp%2FB0C5C89QKZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;549.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Station-Generator-LiFePO4%2Fdp%2FB0CDGKRX4X%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C1000 Power Station with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;899.00 for Prime members, down from &#36;1,549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 for Prime members, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Generator-Portable-Batteries-Technology%2Fdp%2FB0CBB6HFMM%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station with 400W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;1,799.00 for Prime members, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-PowerHouse-Generator-Batteries%2Fdp%2FB0BX64LGFT%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station with 200W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;1,599.00 for Prime members, down from &#36;2,549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Batteries-Ultra-High-Generator-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0C5C9HMQ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F3800 Power Station</a> - &#36;2,999.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;3,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Station-Generator-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0CRB3MQT5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F3800 Power Station with 400W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;3,499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;4,899.00</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/amazon-savings-power-stations/">Amazon Introduces Big Savings on Portable Power Stations From Anker and Jackery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-savings-on-portable-power-stations-from-anker-and-jackery.2435869/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Full List of Over 250 New Features and Changes Coming With iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/apple-shares-full-list-of-ios-18-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-full-list-of-over-250-new-features-and-changes-coming-with-ios-18.2435859/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 07:16:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/apple-shares-full-list-of-ios-18-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following its iPhone 16 event on Monday, Apple shared a PDF on its website with a <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/ios-18/pdf/iOS_18_All_New_Features_Sept_2024.pdf">list of all new features</a> and changes coming with iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
The list includes many features that were already announced, including Apple Intelligence, new customization options for the Home Screen and Control Center, a redesigned Photos app, several enhancements to the Messages app, a Passwords app, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The first Apple Intelligence features won't be available <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/ios-18-1-available-in-october/">until iOS 18.1, which will be released in October</a>, according to Apple. Apple Intelligence requires an iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, or any iPhone 16 model with device and Siri language set to U.S. English, with support for additional languages to follow over the course of the next year.<br/>
<br/>
The list also includes some smaller features and changes that were lesser known or unannounced until now, such as the following:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>CarPlay now supports Spatial Audio in compatible vehicles. This works with Apple Music and select third-party apps.</li><br/>
<li>Spatial Audio is also now supported when using AirPlay to stream audio to a HomePod and select third-party AirPlay-compatible equipment.</li><br/>
<li>You can now add and locally control Wi-Fi-based Matter accessories in the Home app without needing a home hub.</li><br/>
<li>iOS 18 expands Live Voicemail to additional languages and countries, including English (U.K., Australia, India, Ireland, New Zealand, Singapore, South Africa, Puerto Rico), Spanish (U.S., Mexico, Spain, Puerto Rico), French (France), German (Germany), Japanese (Japan), Mandarin (China, Taiwan, Macao), Cantonese (China, Hong Kong, Macao), and Portuguese (Brazil).</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
A similar list of all new features is also <a href="https://www.apple.com/ipados/ipados-18/pdf/iPadOS_18_All_New_Features_Sept_2024.pdf">available for iPadOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 will be widely released to the public on Monday, September 16.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/11/apple-shares-full-list-of-ios-18-features/">Apple Shares Full List of Over 250 New Features and Changes Coming With iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-full-list-of-over-250-new-features-and-changes-coming-with-ios-18.2435859/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What&#039;s New With the iPhone 16 Displays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-display-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-new-with-the-iphone-16-displays.2435813/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-display-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple updated the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max with larger displays this year, increasing the size. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; has a 6.3-inch display, up from 6.1 inches, while the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max has a 6.9-inch display, up from 6.7 inches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-display.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965158" /><br/>
According to Apple, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models now have the thinnest borders on any Apple product, thanks to a reduction in bezels. Some of the increase in display size comes from the bezels, but the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are a little taller and a tiny bit wider than their predecessors.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong> - 6.42 inches tall, 3.06 inches wide, 8.25mm thick, 227 grams.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong> - 6.29 inches tall, 3.02 inches wide, 8.25mm thick, 221 grams.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong> - 5.89 inches tall, 2.81 inches wide, 8.5mm thick, 199 grams.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong> - 5.77 inches tall, 2.78 inches wide, 8.5mm thick, 187 grams.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Though the size has increased, there are actually few other changes to the display technology. Apple is still using its Super Retina XDR Display with ProMotion for the Pro models, and the brightness and peak brightness haven't changed. All models have 1000 nits max brightness, 1600 nits peak HDR brightness, and 2000 nits peak outdoor brightness.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong> - 2622x1206 resolution at 460 ppi</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong> - 2556x1179 resolution at 460 ppi</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong> - 2868x1220 resolution at 460 ppi</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong> - 2796x1290 resolution at 460 ppi</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
What is new is a 1 nit minimum brightness. Apple added this to the Apple Watch too, and said on that device that it would allow for a more frequently updated always-on display with a second hand. Some of that same benefit may be available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and it may be one of the reasons why Apple was able to increase battery life.<br/>
<br/>
While the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> display also supports 1 nit minimum brightness, it does not have an always-on display or support for ProMotion.<br/>
<br/>
Both models also have a new second-generation Ceramic Shield coating that Apple says is 50% tougher than the prior-generation Ceramic Shield coating used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-display-improvements/">What&#039;s New With the iPhone 16 Displays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-new-with-the-iphone-16-displays.2435813/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How Sleep Apnea Detection Works for Apple Watch Series 10, Series 9, and Apple Watch Ultra</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/sleep-apnea-detection-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-sleep-apnea-detection-works-for-apple-watch-series-10-series-9-and-apple-watch-ultra.2435810/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:47:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/sleep-apnea-detection-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is adding sleep apnea detection to the Apple Watch Series 10, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, and the Apple Watch Series 9. Given that sleep apnea is a breathing disturbance, it's easy to assume that it requires the blood oxygen sensor, but Apple actually uses an entirely different method to detect it. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/sleep-apnea-detection-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965154" /><br/>
Breathing Disturbances, the name for the new Apple Watch metric, uses the built-in accelerometer to detect small movements at the wrist that are associated with interruptions to normal respiratory patterns during sleep.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch collects 30 days of data and then analyzes it, alerting users if there are consistent signs of moderate to severe sleep apnea. Users will see Elevated or Not Elevated readings under the Breathing Disturbances section of the Health app, and the data can be used to share with a doctor to get information on the next steps for sleep apnea diagnosis and treatment. <br/>
<br/>
While aggregating data for sleep apnea detection requires 30 days of information, users can see an overall look at their nightly Breathing Disturbances in the Health app to assess the restfulness of sleep. Breathing patterns can be interrupted by alcohol, medications, and sleep position.<br/>
<br/>
With sleep apnea, breathing momentarily stops during sleep, which stops the body from getting adequate oxygen and often has the effect of waking a person up. It can be a difficult condition to diagnose because it occurs during sleep, and Apple says that more than 1 billion people are estimated to be impacted worldwide. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says that its sleep apnea notification algorithm was created using advanced machine learning and an extensive data set of clinical-grade sleep apnea tests, and then it was validated in a clinical study. Every participant identified by the algorithm had at least mild sleep apnea. <br/>
<br/>
Apple expects sleep apnea detection to get marketing authorization from the FDA and other global health authorities in the near future, and it will be available this month in more than 150 countries. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/sleep-apnea-detection-details/">How Sleep Apnea Detection Works for Apple Watch Series 10, Series 9, and Apple Watch Ultra</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-sleep-apnea-detection-works-for-apple-watch-series-10-series-9-and-apple-watch-ultra.2435810/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>A18 vs. A18 Pro: What&#039;s the Difference?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/a18-vs-a18-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/a18-vs-a18-pro-whats-the-difference.2435807/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/a18-vs-a18-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple introduced new second-generation 3-nanometer chips for both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models, bringing notable improvements in performance. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus have an A18 chip, while the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max have an A18 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/a18-chip.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965153" /><br/>
The chips are similar, but there are some differences to be aware of, along with differences in the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Pro thermal design.<br/>
<h2>A18 and A18 Pro Shared Features</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Built on second-generation 3-nm process with smaller transistors.</li><br/>
 	<li>6-core CPU with four performance cores and two efficiency cores.</li><br/>
 	<li>Upgraded 16-core Neural Engine optimized for running large generative models.</li><br/>
 	<li>Upgraded memory subsystem with 17 percent more memory bandwidth.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>A18/iPhone 16 Features</h2><br/>
The A18 has a 5-core GPU rather than the 6-core GPU in the A18 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models have a new thermal design. Apple says that it updated the main logic board, centralizing chip placement and optimizing the surrounding architecture. There's a recycled aluminum substructure that dissipates heat for 30 percent higher sustained performance for gaming.<br/>
<br/>
The A18 also adds hardware accelerated ray tracing, a feature that was available in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models with A17 Pro, but is new to the standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup. Hardware accelerated ray tracing is useful for gaming, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models can run all of the console-quality games that Apple touted for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models last year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A18 Pro/iPhone 16 Pro Features</h2><br/>
The A18 Pro has the same 6-core CPU as the A18, as well as the same Neural Engine, but it has one more GPU core for a 6-core GPU instead of a 5-core GPU.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; maximizes thermal capacity with a machined chassis that uses 100 percent recycled aluminum. It is bonded to the titanium frame using solid state diffusion, and it is combined with a graphite clad aluminum substructure. The new thermal architecture enables a 20 percent improvement in sustained gaming performance compared to the A17 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A18 Performance</h2><br/>
Compared to the A16 Bionic chip, the A18 Pro's CPU is 30 percent faster, and it offers the same performance while using 30 percent less power.<br/>
<br/>
The GPU is 40 percent faster than the A16 Bionic GPU, and it is also more efficient. It offers the same performance using 35% less power.<br/>
<br/>
The new Neural Engine is 2x faster for machine learning than the Neural Engine in the A16 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A18 Pro Performance</h2><br/>
The 6-core A18 Pro CPU is 15 percent faster than the A17 Pro CPU, and it delivers the same performance using 20 percent less power. Apple says that it is the fastest CPU in any smartphone, with next-generation ML accelerators that are directly programmable for high-efficiency, high throughput and low latency computations.<br/>
<br/>
The 6-core GPU is 20 percent faster than the GPU in the A17 Pro, and hardware accelerated ray tracing is 2x faster.<br/>
<br/>
The upgraded Neural Engine is faster and more efficient than the Neural Engine in the A17 Pro. Apple says that Apple Intelligence features run 15 percent faster on the A18 Pro than the A17 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
There is a new advanced display engine for ProMotion, a new video encoder, and a new image signal processor. Combined, they process twice the amount of data for fast video encoding and improved efficiency.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/a18-vs-a18-pro/">A18 vs. A18 Pro: What&#039;s the Difference?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/a18-vs-a18-pro-whats-the-difference.2435807/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Streamlines AirPods Lineup With Fourth-Generation Dual-Model Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/airpods-lineup-streamlined/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-streamlines-airpods-lineup-with-fourth-generation-dual-model-launch.2435805/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:54:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/airpods-lineup-streamlined/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a>, Apple discontinued the low-cost AirPods 2 and AirPods 3, making the AirPods lineup much less confusing. The &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; come in two variants, one with Active Noise Cancellation and one without, allowing Apple to hit two separate price points.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/02/airpods-4-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964768" /><br/>
The &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; without Active Noise Cancellation are priced at &#36;129, which is the same price that Apple used to sell the AirPods 2 for. The ANC version is priced at &#36;179, the same cost as the prior-generation AirPods 3. <br/>
<br/>
There wasn't notable difference between the AirPods 2 and AirPods 3 in terms of core functionality, which was undoubtedly confusing to the average consumer not familiar with Apple's products. The new lineup makes it very clear what's what, and what you get for the extra &#36;50. Apple has also eliminated the confusing charging case options, and both models use USB-C. <br/>
<br/>
Along with Active Noise Cancellation, there are a couple other differences between the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; and &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; with ANC. The ANC model has a case that supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> charging and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a>, and it also has ANC-related features that include Adaptive Audio, Transparency Mode, and Conversation Awareness. <br/>
<br/>
Other than these features, the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; and &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; ANC are identical in design and functionality. <br/>
<br/>
Apple rounds out the AirPods lineup with the &#36;249 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 and the &#36;549 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>. The latter headphones were just refreshed with USB-C charging and new color options, but are otherwise unchanged. The &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 were updated in September 2023, and we're expecting to see another refresh in 2025. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/airpods-lineup-streamlined/">Apple Streamlines AirPods Lineup With Fourth-Generation Dual-Model Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-streamlines-airpods-lineup-with-fourth-generation-dual-model-launch.2435805/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Models Get 50% Tougher Ceramic Shield for Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-ceramic-shield-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-models-get-50-tougher-ceramic-shield-for-display.2435802/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:33:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-ceramic-shield-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max feature a new version of the Ceramic Shield, which is the glass and ceramic hybrid material that protects the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-display.jpg" alt="" width="1780" height="1001" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965160" /><br/>
Apple says that its latest-generation Ceramic Shield features its most advanced glass ceramic formulation. It's 50 percent "tougher" than the first-generation ceramic shield, and two times tougher than "glass found in any other smartphone." It's not clear how Apple is defining tougher, but Apple has typically focused more on drop protection than scratch protection when marketing the material.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first started using the Ceramic Shield material in 2020 with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models, and at the time, Apple said that it was developed in partnership with Corning. Corning makes the Gorilla Glass that Apple competitors like Samsung use, including the new "Gorilla Armor" that Samsung included for the Galaxy S24 Ultra, but the ceramic infused glass appears to be an Apple exclusive.<br/>
<br/>
Once the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models launch, we're sure to see a variety of drop and scratch tests that will provide more insight into the benefits of the second-generation Ceramic Shield. Pre-orders for the new devices start this Friday, and an official launch will follow on September 20.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-ceramic-shield-improvements/">iPhone 16 Models Get 50% Tougher Ceramic Shield for Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-models-get-50-tougher-ceramic-shield-for-display.2435802/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple One-Ups 15W Qi2 Charging With 25W MagSafe Charging in iPhone 16 lineup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-obsoletes-qi2-wireless-charging/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-one-ups-15w-qi2-charging-with-25w-magsafe-charging-in-iphone-16-lineup.2435799/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:57:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-obsoletes-qi2-wireless-charging/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Third-party accessory makers <em>just</em> started releasing next-generation 15W Qi2 charging devices in the last few months, but Apple raised the wireless charging speed bar again with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/new-magsafe-charger.jpg" alt="" width="1764" height="992" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965150" /><br/>
With Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/iphone-16-25w-magsafe-charging/">newly updated MagSafe charger</a> and a 30W power adapter, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models can charge at up to 25W wirelessly over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, which is 10W faster than Qi2.<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 is great because it's an open standard that doesn't require accessory makers to pay Apple to license its technology, but companies that want to offer the fastest wireless charging speeds for the new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will once again need to turn to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
When &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; was first introduced in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12, it was a proprietary Apple charging standard that accessory makers could license. It was able to charge iPhones at up to 15W. The alternative was Qi charging, which was limited to 7.5W, but it didn't require using Apple technology.<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 brought 15W charging speeds that were on par with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, giving us charging speed parity for a short time. Accessory makers could design magnetic chargers that offered 15W charging without paying Apple a fee. That's over now, and we're back in the exact same situation we had when it was original &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; vs. original Qi.<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 chargers will only charge &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models at up to 15W, and 25W charging will be limited to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;. This time around, it's a wider difference because 25W charging is fast charging and can provide up to 50 percent power in 30 minutes.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released a new version of the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Charger alongside the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, so it doesn't look like existing &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; chargers are going to provide 25W. Apple says the 25W charging requires a "new" &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charger, which means accessory makers and customers alike will need new charging accessories to get the updated &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; speeds. Note that the new &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charger still charges older iPhones at 15W. <br/>
<br/>
While it's just the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models that support 25W charging now, this is a new baseline that will be added to future iPhones, and 15W Qi2 charging will soon be antiquated.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-obsoletes-qi2-wireless-charging/">Apple One-Ups 15W Qi2 Charging With 25W MagSafe Charging in iPhone 16 lineup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-one-ups-15w-qi2-charging-with-25w-magsafe-charging-in-iphone-16-lineup.2435799/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All the iPhone 16 Camera Upgrades</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/all-the-iphone-16-camera-upgrades/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-the-iphone-16-camera-upgrades.2435795/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:30:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/all-the-iphone-16-camera-upgrades/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple focused on camera improvements for its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, introducing a number of new features for every model. There's a Camera Control button for quickly taking a shot in landscape or portrait mode, new editing options, Ultra Wide lens improvements across the board, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iPhone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964515" /><br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models have a new dual-lens vertical camera rather than diagonally arranged lenses, plus there are updates to the Ultra Wide camera.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is now calling the Main lens the Fusion lens, but it doesn't seem to be upgraded over the prior version. It still enables either 1x or 2x zoom. The Ultra Wide lens did get an upgrade, though, and it appears to be the lens Apple used for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models. What's new compared to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>48-megapixel f/1.6 Fusion lens</li><br/>
 	<li>12-megapixel f/2.2 Ultra Wide lens</li><br/>
 	<li>Macro photos with Ultra Wide</li><br/>
 	<li>Spatial photos for Vision Pro</li><br/>
 	<li>QuickTake video up to 4K at 60 fps in Dolby Vision</li><br/>
 	<li>Spatial Audio sound recording</li><br/>
 	<li>Wind noise reduction for clearer audio quality when recording video</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The Pro models still have an edge when it comes to the Telephoto, Ultra Wide, flash, and image stabilization, as the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; has no Telephoto lens, a lower MP Ultra Wide, and no second-generation sensor-shift optical image stabilization. The Pro models also have ProRes and ProRAW.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and Pro Max both have 5x zoom this year, plus there's a new 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens that's the standout new addition for macro photography.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>48-megapixel Wide lens renamed "Fusion" lens. Same f/2.2 aperture.</li><br/>
<li>Second-generation quad pixel sensor for zero shutter lag for 48-megapixel RAW images</li><br/>
 	<li>New 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens</li><br/>
 	<li>5x Telephoto for both Pro models</li><br/>
 	<li>Better macro shots</li><br/>
 	<li>100 and 120 fps 4K Dolby Vision video recording</li><br/>
 	<li>120 fps 1080p Dolby Vision video recording</li><br/>
 	<li>120 fps 4K Dolby Vision Slo-mo video recording</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to change playback speed when editing</li><br/>
 	<li>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 120 fps (external SSD required)</li><br/>
 	<li>QuickTake video up to 4K at 60 fps in Dolby Vision</li><br/>
 	<li>Spatial audio recording</li><br/>
 	<li>New four-microphone array with more true-to-life sound</li><br/>
 	<li>Wind noise reduction for clearer audio quality when recording video</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>All iPhone 16 Models</h2><br/>
There are several features that have been added across the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Camera Control</h3><br/>
All of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/iphone-16-camera-control-button/">new Camera Control button</a> that's designed to make it easier to quickly get photos and videos. The button is touch and force sensitive, so it supports swipes and other gestures for swapping through camera options.<br/>
<br/>
A single click opens the camera, a second click snaps a photo, and a click and hold starts a video recording. A light press opens up control options like zoom, and you can swap tools with a double light press. Adjust parameters like zoom and exposure with a swipe. Later this year, Apple is adding an Apple Intelligence Camera Control feature that will let &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users point the camera at something and get more information about it.<br/>
<br/>
Pointing the camera at a restaurant, for example, will bring up hours and menu information, while pointing it at a plant will identify the plant.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>New Photographic Styles</h3><br/>
Photographic Styles have been an option for some time, but Apple overhauled the feature this year. There are new, more subtle styles to choose from, and Apple is enabling far more control over the way the style is applied.<br/>
<br/>
Photographic Styles can be previewed live before you make a change. You can shift the way a style looks with the control pad that lets you adjust tone and color. The intensity of specific colors and the tone can be changed, so you can make adjustments that don't affect the entire color scheme of an image.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that skin tone rendering is more advanced than before, so you can also create a style for dialing in your favorite look and then add it across all of the images that you take. You can also change the Photographic Style after an image is captured, which wasn't an option with prior models. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Audio Mix</h3><br/>
Audio Mix is a video feature that takes advantage of Spatial Audio capture. You can use it to adjust the way that voices sound in videos, and there are three different options.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>In-frame</strong> - Only captures the voices of people on camera, even if people off camera are talking.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Studio</strong> - Makes voices sound like the recording was done in a professional studio with sound-dampening walls. A recording will sound like the mic was close to the subject's mouth.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Cinematic</strong> - Captures all voices and consolidates them to the front of the screen, which is how sound is formatted for movies.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Pre-orders for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will kick off on Friday, September 13, with a launch to follow on Friday, September 20. We can expect to see media reviews ahead of the launch, and once we get the new iPhones at <em>MacRumors</em>, we'll do a deep dive into the camera capabilities.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/all-the-iphone-16-camera-upgrades/">All the iPhone 16 Camera Upgrades</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-the-iphone-16-camera-upgrades.2435795/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Battery Comparison: At Least 1+ Hour More for All Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-battery-comparison/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-battery-comparison-at-least-1-hour-more-for-all-models.2435788/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:34:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-battery-comparison/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, Apple has increased battery life for all models compared to the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models. Battery life is up at least an hour for each device for video playback, with bigger increases for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-colors-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964753" /><br/>
Streaming video can be played for two to four hours longer depending on device, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models also support longer audio playback. Note that in the comparison below, Apple lists the battery life as "up to" because the time the battery lasts will vary based on different usage habits.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16</strong> - 22 hours video playback, 18 hours streaming video, 80 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong> - 27 hours video playback, 24 hours streaming video, 100 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong> - 27 hours video playback, 22 hours streaming video, 85 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong> - 33 hours video playback, 29 hours streaming video, 105 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15</strong> - 20 hours video playback, 16 hours streaming video, 80 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15 Plus</strong> - 26 hours video playback, 20 hours streaming video, 100 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong> - 23 hours video playback, 20 hours streaming video, 75 hours audio.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong> - 29 hours video playback, 25 hours streaming video, 95 hours audio.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Apple is emphasizing battery life gains this year, and product pages for the new devices have a menu for seeing how much more battery life the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models have compared to older devices. Upgrading from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a>, for example, will get you a seven hour increase in battery life.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models support faster 25W <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> charging with one of Apple's new &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; chargers and a 30W power adapter or higher. It is the first time that fast charging has been available when charging wirelessly, and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users can expect to see a 50 percent charge in 30 minutes.<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 charging is also supported, but that is limited to 15W, the same as the prior-generation &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-battery-comparison/">iPhone 16 Battery Comparison: At Least 1+ Hour More for All Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-battery-comparison-at-least-1-hour-more-for-all-models.2435788/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 10 Reduces Wind Noise During Phone Calls</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-series-10-reduces-wind-noise-on-calls/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-reduces-wind-noise-during-phone-calls.2435784/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:10:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-series-10-reduces-wind-noise-on-calls/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-announces-apple-watch-series-10/">Apple Watch Series 10</a> launching next week includes a voice isolation feature that will make you sound better during phone calls.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Watch-Series-10-Jet-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965089" /><br/>
Apple says the Series 10's Neural Engine is able to suppress background noise during phone calls or FaceTime audio calls, so that your voice sounds more clear and crisp on the receiving end of the call. Apple says the feature even works in especially noisy environments, such as outdoors on a windy day or inside a crowded restaurant.<br/>
<br/>
This feature is not available on the Apple Watch Series 9 or older, but the Apple Watch Ultra 2 does already feature wind noise reduction.<br/>
<br/>
As for iPhones, there is already a voice isolation setting available for phone calls, but all four iPhone 16 models have gained wind noise reduction on top. Apple says machine learning algorithms reduce wind noise for better audio quality, but we'll have to wait for tests to see how much of an improvement there is over previous iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch Series 10 pre-orders began yesterday, and the device will begin arriving to customers on Friday, September 20.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-series-10-reduces-wind-noise-on-calls/">Apple Watch Series 10 Reduces Wind Noise During Phone Calls</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-reduces-wind-noise-during-phone-calls.2435784/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 in Black Gets First Discounts for Best Buy Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-in-black-gets-first-discounts-for-best-buy-members.2435781/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:47:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple yesterday <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-watch-ultra-satin-black-milanese-loop/">announced</a> a new black colorway for the Apple Watch Ultra 2, which will launch September 20. With this new color, there are a few new configurations of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 available to purchase, and <a href="https://howl.me/cm4biwLQPZs">Best Buy has the first discounts</a> available on these models for members.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-watch-ultra-2-new-black.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965050" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
If you're a My Best Buy Plus/Total member, you can get &#36;50 off the new Apple Watch Ultra 2 in black. This knocks the price of the watch down to <a href="https://howl.me/cm4bkMdSpAl"><strong>&#36;749.00</strong></a>, from &#36;799.00. Given that membership prices start at &#36;49.99/year, this deal is best for anyone who already has a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: My Best Buy Plus/Total membership required.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cm4bkMdSpAl"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Black) for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Configurations with the black color include the Black Ocean Band, Dark Green Alpine Loop, Black Trail Loop, and the new Black Titanium Milanese Loop. If you're shopping for the Milanese Loop model, shoppers should note that it's priced at <a href="https://howl.me/cm4bluPsqa7"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> with the member discount, down from &#36;899.00.<br/>
<br/>
The original natural finish of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 also has a few new band options that are part of Best Buy's discounts. Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-discounts/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 in Black Gets First Discounts for Best Buy Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-in-black-gets-first-discounts-for-best-buy-members.2435781/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Hands-On Videos: See the New &#039;Camera Control&#039; in Action</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-hands-on-videos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-hands-on-videos-see-the-new-camera-control-in-action.2435778/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-hands-on-videos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following its event on Monday, Apple allowed selected media and content creators to go hands-on with the iPhone 16 series and other new devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-capture-button.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964713" /><br/>
The iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max are all equipped with a new "Camera Control" button that allows you to quickly launch the camera, take a photo, start video recording, and more. Later this year, Apple says Camera Control will be updated with the ability to automatically lock focus and exposure on a subject with a light press.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we have rounded up some iPhone 16 hands-on videos, which offer a closer look at the Camera Control and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7x_85GAncko?si=S-EHIyjnPSh-HnOS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wKM7fLkByQE?si=pEL7NdG16VQOCLRA" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9lx11dy9J30?si=1cXdI791EMlJ-mVH" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fP8hAVvFiwY?si=aKHv6NrB7KqefLS1" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
There are also hands-on videos for the Apple Watch Series 10, AirPods 4, and USB-C AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QkVIKE_6q4I?si=rh4ilapt52x_Gato" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wPc1XWgvl7o?si=oIGL6Lds-heCp3nS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yPjTP5RjRWk?si=XD9czlmC04pa4MEo" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-hands-on-videos/">iPhone 16 Hands-On Videos: See the New &#039;Camera Control&#039; in Action</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-hands-on-videos-see-the-new-camera-control-in-action.2435778/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for Apple Pencil Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-pencil-pro-new-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-apple-pencil-pro.2435771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:45:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-pencil-pro-new-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro that launched alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models earlier this year. The new firmware has a version number of 0.1.40, up from the prior 0.1.33 firmware.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956283" /><br/>
There is no word on what features, fixes, or updates might be included in the new firmware, and Apple does not offer release notes for ‌&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;‌ software releases. You'll want to attach the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> to get it to initiate an update. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro is Apple's newest &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, and it adds several new features that were not available in prior models like squeeze gestures, barrel roll, haptic feedback, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> integration.<br/>
<br/>
The &#36;129 &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro is compatible with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models and the M4 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-pencil-pro-new-firmware/">Apple Releases New Firmware for Apple Pencil Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-apple-pencil-pro.2435771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2435770/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:40:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, including both the Lightning and USB-C versions. The firmware has a build number of 7A294, up from 6F8, and it is available for all &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 users. Apple has been beta testing this update, but it is launching ahead of when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> becomes available next Monday.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
There are multiple features that Apple is adding to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 as part of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, and these features are included in the firmware update.<br/>
<br/>
With head gestures, users can control <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with a shake or a nod of the head. If you get a phone call, for example, you can shake your head no if you don't want to answer it, or nod to accept the call. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interactions can be used for responding to incoming messages, calls, and notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is adding Voice Isolation to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to cut down on loud background sounds to make you easier to hear, and there is a new Personalized Spatial Audio feature specific to gaming. Game developers will be able to incorporate spatial audio into their games for a more immersive audio experience.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't have a way to manually upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air when the AirPods are in a charging case and connected to an iOS device or Mac. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-3/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2435770/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 10 Has Same Heart Sensor as Series 9</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-series-10-heart-rate-sensor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-has-same-heart-sensor-as-series-9.2435757/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:58:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-series-10-heart-rate-sensor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Though there were rumors that the Apple Watch Series 10 would get <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-10-upgraded-sensor/">a new heart and ECG sensor</a>, that does not appear to have happened. According to the technical specifications for the Apple Watch Series 10, it is equipped with a third-generation optical heart sensor, which is the same sensor that was used in the prior-generation Series 9.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-watch-series-10-silver.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964960" /><br/>
Apple also made no mention of the heart rate sensor during yesterday's event, and there is no information about any kind of upgrade on the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-watch-series-10/">Apple Watch Series 10 product page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The rumor, shared by <em>9to5Mac</em>, said the alleged upgraded heart sensor would "unlock new features and provide more accurate results." The site said that it would enable sleep apnea detection, but as Apple explained yesterday, sleep apnea detection actually uses the accelerometer. Sleep apnea detection did not require an upgrade to the heart sensor, and it is in fact also being added to the Apple Watch Series 9 and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, both of which have the same third-generation heart sensor as the Series 10.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was working on blood pressure monitoring for the Series 10, but the feature was not ready in time for the device's launch. Apple did not introduce health features other than the ability to detect sleep apnea.<br/>
<br/>
A new design is the main focus of the Series 10, and it is thinner and lighter than prior Apple Watch models. It does have a new water temperature sensor, depth sensor, Oceanic+ app for snorkeling, and Tides app, which brings it closer in functionality to the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There were rumors of improved water resistance that would allow the Series 10 to be used with high-speed water sports up to 20 meters deep, but Apple did not update the Apple Watch Series 10's water resistance. It continues to have a water resistance rating of 50 meters, and while it can be used for shallow-water activities like snorkeling or swimming in a pool, Apple still warns against using it for scuba diving, waterskiing, or other activities involving high-velocity water or submersion below shallow depth.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Series 10 models are available for pre-order right now and will begin arriving to customers on Friday, September 20.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-watch-series-10-heart-rate-sensor/">Apple Watch Series 10 Has Same Heart Sensor as Series 9</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-has-same-heart-sensor-as-series-9.2435757/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Apple Products Are Still Sold With Lightning After More AirPods Switch to USB-C</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-still-sells-these-lightning-products/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-apple-products-are-still-sold-with-lightning-after-more-airpods-switch-to-usb-c.2435744/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:11:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-still-sells-these-lightning-products/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Lightning</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has been gradually transitioning its products from Lightning to USB-C in recent years. For example, the charging cases for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-unveils-airpods-4/">both new AirPods 4 models</a> unveiled this week, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-announces-new-airpods-max/">revised AirPods Max</a>, are now equipped with a USB-C port. In addition, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-discontinues-iphone-15-pro-iphone-13/">discontinued the iPhone 13</a> this week, and that device has a Lightning port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/lightning-connector-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891738" /><br/>
The list of Apple devices and accessories that are still sold with the 12-year-old Lightning port or connector continues to shrink, and it is now as follows:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 14, iPhone 14 Plus, and iPhone SE</li><br/>
<li>Magic Keyboard (Mac)</li><br/>
<li>Magic Mouse</li><br/>
<li>Magic Trackpad<br/>
<li>First-generation Apple Pencil</li></ul>A new iPhone SE with a USB-C port is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/05/when-to-expect-iphone-se-4/">rumored to launch next year</a>, while the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus should be discontinued next September. The first-generation Apple Pencil will likely be discontinued at some point too, and the Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad trio of accessories for the Mac should be updated with USB-C ports eventually. Beyond legacy cables and adapters, the Lightning era will then finally be over at Apple.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lightning/">Lightning</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/apple-still-sells-these-lightning-products/">These Apple Products Are Still Sold With Lightning After More AirPods Switch to USB-C</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-apple-products-are-still-sold-with-lightning-after-more-airpods-switch-to-usb-c.2435744/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 45+ Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-buyers-guide-45-upgrades-compared.2419268/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:40:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro&#038;post_date=1725993600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max are Apple's latest flagship devices, offering over 45 changes and improvements compared to their predecessors. Here's everything that's changed.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iPhone-15-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature-Cyan-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-964953" /></div><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is an incremental update in some respects, but there are still some important improvements to consider. Key enhancements include larger displays with thinner borders, faster and more efficient chips, and camera advancements like the new Camera Control button. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; also boasts extended battery life, faster <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> charging, and improved audio recording capabilities. <br/>
<br/>
This comparison guides you through each area of improvement, from design changes to technical enhancements, helping you decide if the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is worth the upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design_and_displays">Design and Displays</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; builds on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>'s design by introducing several key enhancements, particularly in the display and materials. While both models feature a premium titanium frame, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; comes with a new blasted titanium finish that offers a more refined texture. One of the most noticeable changes is the larger display size, with the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; increasing to 6.3 inches and the Pro Max to 6.9 inches, while also reducing the borders by 30%. The minimum brightness has been improved to just 1 nit, making the display better suited for low-light environments.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; also features a next-generation Ceramic Shield front glass that's twice as strong as the one on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. Apple has improved thermal management in the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, leading to a 20% boost in heat dissipation, which helps sustain performance during demanding tasks. A new Desert Titanium color replaces the previous Blue Titanium option, and the other colors are slightly tweaked too.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Brushed titanium frame</td><br/>
 <td>Blasted titanium frame</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 6.1-inch display<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 6.7-inch display</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 6.3-inch display<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 6.9-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>30% thinner borders around the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>~2–4 nits minimum brightness</td><br/>
 <td>1 nit minimum brightness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More power efficient display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ceramic Shield front glass</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation Ceramic Shield front glass (2x stronger)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Camera Control capacitive button with sapphire crystal cover</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved thermal design for 20% improvement in heat management and better performance</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Black Titanium, White Titanium, Natural Titanium, and Blue Titanium finishes</td><br/>
 <td>Available in darker Black Titanium, brighter White Titanium, lighter Natural Titanium, and new Desert Titanium finishes</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Slimmer, fully recycled packaging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The design and display changes between the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; are subtle. The most significant difference is perhaps 30% thinner bezels, which enables a slightly larger screen without making the device feel significantly bigger. For everyday users, these design and display changes may not feel like a game-changer, but some may appreciate better durability, lower brightness for nighttime use, or the new Desert Titanium finish.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Dimensions</h4><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models introduces slight increases in height, width, and weight compared to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models. The changes in size are minimal, with the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; being 2.05% taller and 1.27% wider, while the Pro Max version sees similar small adjustments. The biggest change is in weight, where the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is 6.42% heavier than the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, which may be noticeable in hand, especially for users sensitive to weight.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Height</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 146.6 mm (5.77 inches)<br/>
 <strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 159.9 mm (6.29 inches)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 149.6 mm (5.89 inches) <strong>(+2.05%)</strong><br/>
 <strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 163 mm (6.42 inches) <strong>(+1.94%)</strong><br/>
 </td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Width</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 70.6 mm (2.78 inches)<br/>
 <strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 76.7 mm (3.02 inches)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 71.5 mm (2.81 inches) <strong>(+1.27%)</strong><br/>
 <strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 77.6 mm (3.06 inches) <strong>(+1.17%)</strong><br/>
 </td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 187 grams (6.60 ounces) <br/>
 <strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 221 grams (7.81 ounces)<br/>
 </td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 199 grams (7.03 ounces) <strong>(+6.42%)</strong><br/>
 <strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 227 grams (7.99 ounces) <strong>(+2.71%)</strong><br/>
 </td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The dimension changes are unlikely to be significant for most users, but those who prioritize portability and lightweight design may find the added 12 grams on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; more noticeable. That said, the slightly larger frame does accommodate a bigger display and better heat management, which could be worth the trade-off for users who value those enhancements. If you're upgrading from an older, smaller device, these changes may stand out more, but for &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; users, the physical differences are minor.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_and_connectivity">Chip and Connectivity</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s A18 Pro chip is a moderate upgrade over the A17 Pro in the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, thanks to its use of TSMC's N3E enhanced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process. This newer process improves both performance and power efficiency, making the A18 Pro 15% faster in CPU performance and 20% faster in GPU tasks. The real leap comes with hardware-accelerated ray tracing, which is now 2x faster, allowing for more realistic lighting and reflections in games and other graphic-intensive applications. Additionally, the 16-core Neural Engine in the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; benefits from 17% more memory bandwidth, improving AI tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A17 Pro chip (TSMC's "N3B" first-generation &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 Pro chip (TSMC's "N3E" second-generation, enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU (15% faster performance)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>6-core GPU (20% faster performance and 2x faster hardware-accelerated ray tracing)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine (17% more memory bandwidth)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced video encoding capabilities, supporting twice the data processing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6E</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 7 (802.11be) with 2x2 MIMO</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X70 5G modem</td><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X75 5G modem</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
In terms of connectivity, the jump to Wi-Fi 7 offers faster speeds and lower latency, especially in crowded networks, while the newer Snapdragon X75 5G modem improves signal strength and power efficiency, ensuring better connectivity in various conditions. <br/>
<br/>
The A18 Pro is built to handle more intensive tasks such as video encoding. While the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; remains extremely powerful for everyday use, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is simply more capable and future-proof for the demands of upcoming advancements in AI and connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="cameras">Cameras</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; brings a series of targeted improvements to its camera system, focusing on refining both hardware and software to enhance performance in specific areas. Key upgrades include faster sensor technology, increased ultra wide resolution, expanded video capabilities, and the dedicated Capture Control button.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Rear Cameras and Photography Capabilities</h4><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; takes photography to the next level with several significant enhancements over the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. While both models feature a 48-megapixel main camera, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; introduces a Fusion camera with a second-generation quad-pixel sensor, providing faster readout speeds and zero shutter lag for quicker, more responsive shooting. The biggest leap is in the Ultra Wide camera, which now matches the main sensor's resolution with 48 megapixels, offering better detail and low-light-performance, especially in macro shots.<br/>
<br/>
The optical zoom options have been standardized across both models with 5x zoom available on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; as well, not just the Pro Max. This benefits users who rely on long-range photography, providing more flexibility. New features like enhanced depth mapping improve overall image clarity and background separation, particularly in portrait photography and augmented reality experiences. For the first time, Apple has also introduced JPEG-XL format support, which provides higher-quality images with better compression.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Main camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Fusion camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation quad-pixel sensor</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation quad-pixel sensor with faster readout speeds and zero shutter lag</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: 0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 3x optical zoom options<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: 0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 5x optical zoom options </td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 5x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Macro photography</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel macro photography</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Support for new JPEG-XL format</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Photo­graphic Styles</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation Photo­graphic Styles</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Depth mapping for AR and portrait photography</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced depth mapping for AR and portrait photography, allowing for more accurate background and subject separation, more realistic bokeh, and better AR experiences.</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Visual Intelligence, allowing users to pull up contextual information about objects or scenes in front of the camera (such as restaurant details or product info)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Camera Control button features:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Launch the Camera App</strong>: Pressing the Camera Control button immediately opens the camera app.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Capture Photos</strong>: A single press of the button captures a photo, providing a quick and tactile way to take pictures.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Record Videos</strong>: A press and hold action allows you to start recording a video.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Half-Press for Focus and Exposure</strong> (upcoming feature): A light, half-press will lock focus and exposure, allowing you to reframe the shot without losing focus.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Trackpad-Like Control</strong>: The capacitive sensor on the button acts like a trackpad, enabling gestures to control zoom, cycle through filters, or switch between lenses by sliding your finger across the button.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Third-Party App Integration</strong>: The Camera Control button can also be used to trigger third-party camera apps, giving more flexibility to users who prefer other photography tools.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Camera Function Overlay</strong>: A light touch gesture reveals a clean preview and quick access to key camera controls like zoom or exposure settings.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Visual Intelligence Activation</strong>: The Camera Control button is integrated with Visual Intelligence, allowing users to pull up contextual information about objects or scenes in front of the camera</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The improvements in the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s camera system make it a compelling option for photography enthusiasts. The new Fusion camera and zero shutter lag will be particularly appreciated by users who need to capture fast-moving subjects or quickly switch between shots. The 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera brings much better low-light and macro capabilities. Features like the Camera Control button and Visual Intelligence add new levels of interactivity, letting users pull up information about objects in the scene and gain easier, more intuitive control over how they capture and frame their photos. For those who rely heavily on their camera, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; offers some meaningful upgrades, even though the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; remains highly capable.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Video Recording</h4><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; brings substantial upgrades to video recording, particularly in terms of frame rates and video quality. While the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; supports 4K recording at standard frame rates of 24, 30, and 60 fps, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; introduces 4K Dolby Vision video recording at up to 120 fps. This provides far smoother motion and more detailed slow-motion effects. For those who work with high-quality video content, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s ability to record in 4K ProRes at 120 fps (with external storage) offers a significant leap over the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s 4K at 60 fps.<br/>
<br/>
Another standout improvement is the support for slo-mo video at 4K Dolby Vision up to 120 fps, offering both sharper and more dynamic slow-motion footage. The 1080p slo-mo capabilities have also been improved to support frame rates up to 240 fps.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4K video recording at 24 fps, 25 fps, 30 fps, or 60 fps, with playback speed controls</td><br/>
 <td>4K Dolby Vision video recording at 24 fps, 25 fps, 30 fps, 60 fps, 100 fps (Fusion) or 120 fps (Fusion)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1080p HD video recording at 25 fps, 30 fps, or 60 fps</td><br/>
 <td>1080p Dolby Vision video recording at 25 fps, 30 fps, 60 fps, or 120 fps (Fusion)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 60 fps with external recording</td><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 120 fps with external recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Slo-mo video support for 1080p at 120 fps or 240 fps</td><br/>
 <td>Slo-mo video support for 1080p up to 240 fps and 4K Dolby Vision up to 120 fps (Fusion)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The video recording upgrades on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; are especially relevant for content creators and videographers. The addition of 4K at 120 fps allows for more professional-grade slow-motion and cinematic video effects, which is a significant improvement over the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. With the ability to shoot in Dolby Vision across a wider range of frame rates and resolutions, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is now an even more versatile video production tool. However, for casual users, these improvements may be less meaningful.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Front Camera</h4><br/>
While both the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; support 4K video recording at 24, 25, 30, and 60 fps, the latest model upgrades to 4K Dolby Vision recording across all frame rates, delivering more dynamic range and color accuracy for front-facing videos. This makes the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; a better option for users who frequently shoot high-quality video content like vlogs, video calls, or social media clips.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4K video recording at 24 fps, 25 fps, 30 fps, or 60 fps</td><br/>
 <td>4K Dolby Vision video recording at 24 fps, 25 fps, 30 fps, 60 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1080p HD video recording at 25 fps, 30 fps, or 60 fps</td><br/>
 <td>1080p Dolby Vision video recording at 25 fps, 30 fps, or 60 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>HDR video recording with Dolby Vision up to 4K at 60 fps</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Cinematic mode up to 4K HDR at 30 fps</td><br/>
 <td>Cinematic mode up to 4K Dolby Vision at 30 fps</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>QuickTake video</td><br/>
 <td>QuickTake video (up to 4K at 60 fps in Dolby Vision HDR)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="audio_recording">Audio Recording</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; introduces some significant upgrades in audio recording capabilities, designed to complement its camera system. While the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; offered stereo recording, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; elevates this with Spatial Audio support, which enhances sound depth and immersion, especially for playback in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>. Additionally, the inclusion of a studio-quality four-mic array improves overall sound clarity, making it a more capable device for capturing professional-level audio.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Stereo recording</td><br/>
 <td>Spatial Audio and stereo recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Studio-quality four-mic array</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Wind noise reduction</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Audio Mix</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="battery_and_charging">Battery and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; sees a meaningful increase in battery life compared to its predecessor, with the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; offering up to 27 hours of battery life, a 17.39% improvement over the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. The new Pro Max follows a similar trend, providing 33 hours, which is 13.79% more than its predecessor. In addition to extended battery life, &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wireless charging has been enhanced from 15W to 25W, delivering a 66.67% increase in charging speed when using a 30W adapter or higher.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong>: Up to 23 hours of battery life<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Pro Max</strong>: Up to 29 hours of battery life</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: Up to 27 hours of battery life <strong>(+17.39%)</strong><br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: Up to 33 hours of battery life <strong>(+13.79%)</strong></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wireless charging up to 15W with 20W adapter or higher</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wireless charging up to 25W with 30W adapter or higher <strong>(+66.67%)</strong></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will be available for pre-order starting on Friday, September 13, 2024, with the official launch and availability in stores beginning Friday, September 20, 2024. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="is_it_worth_upgrading">Is It Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
When comparing the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, it's clear that the upgrades are evolutionary rather than revolutionary. The changes, while meaningful in specific areas like display size, processing power, and camera capabilities, may not offer a compelling reason to upgrade for all users, particularly those who already own the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Many of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s improvements, such as the slightly larger display with thinner borders and more efficient A18 Pro chip, are beneficial but incremental. For users who are deeply invested in mobile gaming, AI, or content creation, the processing boost and video capabilities will be welcome, especially for future-proofing. Similarly, the addition of the Camera Control button offers more granular control and improved responsiveness in photography, making it a worthy upgrade for photography enthusiasts or professionals.<br/>
<br/>
However, for the average user who just relies on their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> for day-to-day tasks, these upgrades may feel less impactful. The increase in battery life and faster &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging are practical improvements, but likely not substantial enough to drive most users toward upgrading from the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
In essence, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is a solid refinement of an already exceptional device, but for users with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, the differences might not be significant enough to justify an upgrade. Those who will benefit most from the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; are users who are still using older models, content creators who need the best mobile video and audio tools, or those looking to future-proof their device for AI and graphics-heavy applications. For &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; owners, unless you fall into these categories, holding off for a more substantial leap in future models may be the more practical decision.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 45+ Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-buyers-guide-45-upgrades-compared.2419268/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
