<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 03:03:35 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>WWDC 2025 Preview: Apple&#039;s iOS 26 Design Overhaul, macOS Tahoe, and Much More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2025-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2025-preview-apples-ios-26-design-overhaul-macos-tahoe-and-much-more.2458312/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:32:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2025-what-to-expect&#038;post_date=1749252735/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 2025 Worldwide Developers Conference is just a few days away, with the keynote event set to take place on Monday, June 9. Ahead of Apple's big software debut, we've rounded up all of the rumors that we've heard so far about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, macOS 26, and Apple's other updates.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/p8ca2mQ6psc" title="Everything You Can Expect at Apple&#39;s WWDC 2025 Event!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="a_note_on_naming">A Note on Naming</h2><br/>
Apple is streamlining the way that it numbers operating system updates, so all of the software will be appended with a "26" instead of the number that would normally be expected in Apple's prior versioning scheme.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>iOS 19 -> &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>iPadOS 19 -> iPadOS 26</li><br/>
 <li>macOS 16 -> macOS 26</li><br/>
 <li>tvOS 19 -> tvOS 26</li><br/>
 <li>watchOS 12 -> watchOS 26</li><br/>
 <li>visionOS 3 -> visionOS 26</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The "26" used for each time reflects the launch season for each update, covering the period between September 2025 and September 2026. Apple is using year-ahead numbering going forward, so in September 2026, we'll get iOS 27.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/iOS-19-to-26-Thumb-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003962" /><br/>
Apple could have gone with the year of launch, which would be 25, but 26 also makes sense because there are more months in 2026 where we'll be running &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; and its sister updates than in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
With the streamlined naming that Apple is implementing, there won't be a need to remember separate numbers for each operating system, and it'll be clear which update came out in which year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ios_26">iOS 26</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; is going to get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">major design overhaul</a> that's been described as the biggest design update since iOS 7. Inside Apple, the design project is referred to as "Solarium," which hints at what we can expect. A solarium is an all-glass room that's designed to let in sunlight, and rumors suggest that &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; will adopt a more translucent, glass-inspired aesthetic that's loosely based on visionOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iOS-26-Mock-Rainbow-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003293" /><br/>
visionOS uses a semi-translucent interface to allow people to see their surroundings in AR or VR while also interacting with app menus and windows. visionOS windows blend into the background for an unobtrusive look, and on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple could adopt the same translucency, allowing content to shine through.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; is expected to get the floating on-screen windows and menus that are used in visionOS, with rounded pop-up navigation and menu bars that float above the content on the display. Apple may use shading, shadowing, and subtle lighting effects to give buttons and other interface elements a slight lift. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a> on the Lock Screen and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> will adopt the new design, but functionality won't change. <br/>
<br/>
App icons could see design tweaks, and notifications, menus in apps, search bars, card-style interfaces, and other parts of the iOS user interface could have more rounded corners than we're used to. The floating navigation bars are expected to be pill-shaped, for example, and Apple is going to use pop-out menu options to allow users to expand settings with a tap. One rumor suggested Apple is going to transition to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/ios-19-rounder-app-icons-video/">round app icons</a> on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> says that the icons are going to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns">keep the same general shape</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; has been described as having a glossy or glass-like look, which is also how visionOS looks. Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a> teaser images feature frosted glass with soft colors, and those images might give us a look at what's coming.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/WWDC-2025-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002300" /><br/>
Mockups that are allegedly based on real &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; designs were shared earlier this year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/ios-19-visionos-like-design-rumors/">by Front Page Tech</a>, demonstrating some of the design changes that might be in store. A mockup of the Camera app has translucent pop-out menus that better blend into the background to put the focus on the images, for example.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985937" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Alleged-iOS-19-Camera-App-Render.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="794" /><em>A render of &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;'s alleged redesigned Camera app, from Front Page Tech</em></div><br/>
Newer Apple apps like Apple Sports and Invites have simpler, translucent interface elements with expanding buttons, and could also serve as an example of the design language Apple is planning to unveil in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988149" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-invites-screenshots.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Apple will overhaul its built-in apps with the updated design, plus the company plans to provide developers with design guidelines and assets so that third-party apps can adopt the new aesthetic too.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="navigation_simplification_and_streamlining">Navigation Simplification and Streamlining</h3><br/>
Along with introducing new design language in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, Apple is streamlining navigation. Rumors suggest that Apple is tweaking menus, buttons, and navigation to make the operating system simpler to learn and navigate.<br/>
<br/>
Some of the design and interface changes will also extend to macOS, iPadOS, tvOS, and watchOS, improving design consistency and navigation across Apple's operating systems.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_intelligence_features">Apple Intelligence Features</h3><br/>
There are several new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features that are expected in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>AI Battery Management</h4><br/>
An AI-powered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/ios-19-ai-battery-management/">battery management tool</a> will analyze how you use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and make adjustments to maximize battery life. The option will be able to limit the power draw of apps and other system features based on device usage.<br/>
<br/>
Battery management will be particularly useful for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a> that will have a smaller battery than other iPhones, but it will be available on iPhones that are able to run &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;. It's not clear if Apple will announce the AI battery feature at &zwnj;WWDC 2025&zwnj;, as it could be held until the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; debut later in the year. <br/>
<br/>
<h4>Shortcuts App</h4><br/>
Apple plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/02/shortcuts-app-apple-intelligence-integration/">update the Shortcuts app</a> with &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;, allowing users to create actions that use &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; models. With this functionality, which Apple might call "Generative Shortcuts," Shortcuts will be easier to use. Even casual users will be able to create useful shortcuts using natural language and help from AI.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Google Gemini</h4><br/>
Apple and Google are close to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/ios-19-google-gemini-integration-likely/">establishing a deal</a> that will add Google Gemini to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as an alternative to ChatGPT, and that's a feature that we'll likely see in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;. Google Gemini would integrate with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> like ChatGPT, with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; able to hand requests over to Gemini for more in-depth AI-powered answers. Apple may not announce Gemini integration until it's ready, so this may not be a feature we see previewed at WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;</h4><br/>
Apple still hasn't launched the Apple Intelligence-powered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-ios-19-siri-delay/">personalized Siri features</a> that debuted at WWDC 2024. Those updates are expected to come at some point in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, but we're not quite sure when. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; may not be ready for the launch version of &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, and we're not expecting Apple to mention these &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features again until the functionality is ready.<br/>
<br/>
Here's what's coming, eventually:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Personal Context</strong> - &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to keep track of everything on your device, like emails, messages, files, and more, helping you complete tasks and find things.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Onscreen awareness</strong> - &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will know what's on your screen and will be able to complete actions involving whatever you're looking at.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Deeper App Integration</strong> - &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do more in and across apps, performing actions and tasks that are not possible with the personal assistant right now. This will be a feature available for Apple's apps and third-party apps.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="new_apps_and_app_features">New Apps and App Features</h3><br/>
Apple is planning to introduce a new Games app, plus some existing apps are getting new functionality.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Games</h4><br/>
Apple has a new pre-installed gaming app planned, and it'll replace Game Center and add more functionality than ever before. It's going to house the games section of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, so you'll be able to find and launch games from one convenient gaming-centric spot, but the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s games section isn't going away.<br/>
<br/>
Tabs in the Games app include Home, Arcade, Play Together, Library, and Search. The app will offer game suggestions from Apple's editorial team, and it has tools for playing with friends and family. It will also house achievements and leaderboards, replacing Game Center. <br/>
<br/>
<h4>Preview</h4><br/>
The Mac Preview app is coming to iOS and iPadOS, and like Games, it'll be pre-installed. It has the same functionality as the Mac version of the app, and it will let users view, edit, and annotate PDF documents. It's already possible to annotate PDFs using Markup tools in apps like Mail, but having a dedicated app will make the options easier to find.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Phone App</h4><br/>
The &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; Phone app will gain a unified view that shows favorite contacts, recent calls, and voicemails all in one window. The design will be opt-in, and Apple will provide a setting to use the existing design with separate tabs. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to bring new AI-based live translation features to the Phone app, for automatically translating conversations between people who speak two different languages. <br/>
<br/>
<h4>Safari</h4><br/>
To match the new systemwide iOS design, Safari is set to feature a more transparent, glass-looking address bar. <br/>
<br/>
<h4>Camera</h4><br/>
The Camera app's navigation will be redone to make it simpler to get to different settings and options. Apple will use pop-out menus that will make tweaking photo settings more intuitive. <br/>
<br/>
<h4>Messages</h4><br/>
The Messages app could gain support for polls in group chats and automatic translate. There's already an option to long press on a message to translate it to another language, but in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, messages that aren't in your specified language could be translated automatically.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/iOS-26-Messages-Background-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004705" /><br/>
Apple also plans to implement customizable backgrounds, allowing users to choose a background image for each conversation. Backgrounds will sync between devices and will be shared with other people that you're texting with. Users will be able to generate backgrounds for the Messages app using text-based descriptions, a feature that appears to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>. Generated backgrounds will be able to use &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; styles, including Animation, Illustration, and Sketch.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> is getting an update that will allow users to combine two existing emoji into a new emoji, a feature that Apple will call "Mixmoji." With Mixmoji, you will be able to combine two emoji such as cake and balloons into a new emoji that features a cake and a balloon for a celebration. <br/>
<br/>
<h4>Music</h4><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> app is expected to gain support for full screen animated art on the Lock Screen. The current Now Playing view tints the Lock Screen based on album art, but in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, album art could be even larger.<br/>
<br/>
<h4>Notes</h4><br/>
The Notes app could support exporting in Markdown.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="carplay_updates">CarPlay Updates</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> could get interface changes to match the design changes that are being introduced with &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also plans to bring new Accessibility features to &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; will gain a Large Text option and new Sound Recognition capabilities. Sound Recognition will recognize crying babies, sending a notification if a crying baby is detected inside the vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="new_airpods_features">New AirPods Features</h3><br/>
With an AirPods firmware update, &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; will allow the AirPods to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/13/airpods-live-translation-ios-19/">translate in-person conversations</a> from one language to another. If an English speaker with AirPods is conversing with someone who is speaking Spanish, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will detect the audio, translate the speech, and relay it back in English to the AirPods wearer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/airpods-pro-2-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984050" /><br/>
Apple also plans to add other new AirPods features:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>New head gestures</strong> - Apple could add new head gestures, such as a gesture for adjusting the volume of Conversation Awareness. Last year, Apple added a nod and a head shake to answer or decline calls.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Auto-pause for sleep</strong> - The AirPods could pause audio when the wearer falls asleep, presumably using sleep data gleaned from the Apple Watch, as the AirPods have no sleep detection functionality.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Camera trigger</strong> - Apple is planning to add trigger functionality to the AirPods, capturing an image on a linked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a press on the AirPods stem. It's possible this might work with a timer so the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user isn't touching an ear when the photo is taken.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Microphone enhancement</strong> - AirPods could get a "studio quality" microphone mode that's similar to the Audio Mix feature on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that lets users choose from sound recording options like studio and cinematic.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Better pairing</strong> - Apple is apparently working on a feature that would improve how AirPods pair with shared iPads for use in the classroom.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="connectivity_changes">Connectivity Changes</h3><br/>
Apple is adding a feature that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/ios-19-sync-captive-wi-fi-data-between-devices/">will synchronize</a> captive Wi-Fi portal login information across devices, so you'll only need to enter login details for a captive Wi-Fi network once, and it'll be available on all of your Apple products. Captive networks are common in hotels, airports, coffee shops, and other locations with shared or paid internet options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple might also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/ios-19-esim-android-transfer/">make it easier</a> for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to transfer an eSIM to an Android smartphone.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="stage_manager">Stage Manager</h3><br/>
There's a possibility that Apple will add a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a> feature for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models that have a USB-C port, with the feature activating when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is connected to an external display over USB-C.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj; would allow multiple apps to be opened at once, offering a more Mac-like experience when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is used with a display.<br/>
<h3 id="accessibility_features">Accessibility Features</h3><br/>
Apple previewed new Accessibility features coming to &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; earlier this year, and there are some interesting new additions.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Music Haptics</strong> - Music Haptics will get customization options so haptics can be enabled for an entire song or just vocals, plus there will be options to adjust the intensity of taps, textures, and vibrations.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>App Store Labels</strong> - &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; product pages will get Accessibility Nutrition Labels that highlight accessibility features in apps.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Accessibility Reader</strong> - Accessibility Reader is a systemwide reading mode that will make text easier to read thanks to customization features for adjusting font, color, spacing, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>CarPlay</strong> - &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; is getting support for Large Text and Sound Recognition that will alert drivers to the sound of a crying baby, horns, and sirens.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Background Sounds</strong> - Background Sounds will be customizable with new EQ settings, timers, and automation actions in Shortcuts.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Personal Voice</strong> - Personal Voice will let users preserve their voice faster and more easily. It will use on-device machine learning to create a smoother, more natural-sounding voice in under a minute.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Tracking</strong> - Head tracking and eye tracking are getting updates, plus Apple is adding support for Brain Computer Interface devices.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="developer_features">Developer Features</h3><br/>
Apple is planning to provide developers with tools to access Apple's large language models, so custom AI features can be integrated into apps. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="compatibility">Compatibility</h3><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; will not be available on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS, or the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS Max, but it will run on all other iPhones that support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a></li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro Max</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Plus</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 mini</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 Pro</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 Pro</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12-pro/">iPhone 12 Pro Max</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 Pro</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-11-pro/">iPhone 11 Pro Max</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; SE (2nd generation or later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
While these iPhones will support &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, advanced features may be limited to newer iPhones with faster processors. &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, for example, only runs on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipados_26">iPadOS 26</h2><br/>
iPadOS 26 is going to get the same design updates that are coming to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, so it will have the same glass-like, translucent look.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m3-ipad-air-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994860" /><br/>
Apple is also rumored to be working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/13/ipados-19-more-like-macos/">adding new features</a> that will make the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> experience more like using a Mac, introducing improved productivity, new multitasking features, and expanded window management options.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 26 may have a Mac-like menu bar when connected to a Magic Keyboard, plus Apple is adding a new reed calligraphy pen option for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> users that need to write Arabic script.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="macos_26_tahoe">macOS 26 Tahoe</h2><br/>
macOS is the only operating system that gets a special California landmark name along with its number. This year, Apple is going to go with "Tahoe," for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-26/">macOS 26 Tahoe</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003768" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/macOS-Tahoe-Render.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" /><br/>
Tahoe will join the other California landmark names that Apple has used, including Mavericks, Yosemite, El Capitan, Sierra, High Sierra, Mojave, Catalina, Big Sur, Monterey, Ventura, Sonoma, and Sequoia.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design">Design</h3><br/>
A lot of the rumors we've heard this year have focused on the design updates coming in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, but some of those same design changes will also debut in macOS 26. The changes won't be as dramatic, but Apple is aiming for a more cohesive look across its operating systems.<br/>
<br/>
macOS 26 could get the same glass-like design update, with more translucency, rounded menu elements, rounded app icons, and more depth through a play on light and shadow. The Mac design updates will focus on the menu bar and window buttons, with widgets also set to adopt the new look.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_intelligence_and_other_features">Apple Intelligence and Other Features</h3><br/>
Many of the &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features rumored for &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; will also come to macOS Tahoe. We'll get the same revamped Shortcuts app and perhaps Gemini integration, and eventually, all of the personalized &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features that Apple previewed at WWDC 2024 will come to iOS and macOS alike.<br/>
<br/>
The Mac is also going to get the new gaming app that Apple has in the works, and support for cross-device captive Wi-Fi network sharing. Xcode could also get a revamp, with Apple set to add support for third-party AI assistants like Claude and ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
Specific to the Mac, there's a new Magnifier accessibility feature that will let Mac users use their iPhones for zooming in on small text and anything else that's hard to read. It'll work using the Continuity Camera features that link the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
Macs are also going to get support for Vehicle Motion Cues, a feature that uses small dots at the edge of the display to match the feeling of movement with what the eyes are seeing, with the aim of cutting down on motion sickness.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="compatibility">Compatibility</h3><br/>
macOS Tahoe could drop support for the 2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, 2019 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, 2017 &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro, 2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, and the Intel-based 2020 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>. It's expected to be compatible with these Macs:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; (2019 and later)</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iMac&zwnj; (2020 and later)</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> (2019 and later)</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> and later)</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> (all models)</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (&zwnj;M1&zwnj; and later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="watchos_26">watchOS 26</h2><br/>
With watchOS 26, Apple plans to bring some of the same design updates that are coming to &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; to the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/watchOS-26-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003307" /><br/>
Floating menus, rounder buttons, and simplified navigation have been rumored, too. watchOS already uses round app icons and buttons, so it will fit right in. Apple could adopt the Solarium look for things like the app drawer, notifications, and Control Center.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim is a more consistent design across all of its software platforms.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="new_watch_faces">New Watch Faces</h3><br/>
If watchOS is getting a design update to match &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, Apple will likely add new watch faces that are designed with the new style.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_intelligence">Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
The Apple Watch doesn't have the processing power to run &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; on-device, but it is rumored to be getting some "powered by &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;" features that could rely on its link to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, features like ChatGPT &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; integration and Writing Tools don't extend to the Apple Watch, but these are options that Apple could add. The Apple Watch also doesn't support notification summaries or content summaries in general.<br/>
<br/>
It's possible Apple will bring the AI-powered battery management feature rumored for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the Apple Watch too.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="third-party_control_center_shortcuts">Third-Party Control Center Shortcuts</h3><br/>
watchOS 26 could introduce support for third-party shortcuts in Control Center, allowing third-party app settings to be accessed right alongside built-in options for doing things like toggling on Wi-Fi, turning on Airplane Mode, activating Do Not Disturb, and pinging the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Control Center could also get a new layout customization option that would be accessible through the Apple Watch app, with Apple allowing users to add new shortcuts and remove those that aren't necessary.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_sleep_detection">AirPods Sleep Detection</h3><br/>
The Apple Watch could integrate with the AirPods to pause content that's playing when the wearer falls asleep. It's a rumored feature for &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, but the AirPods have no sleep detection functionality, so the option would need to use Apple Watch data.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="compatibility">Compatibility</h3><br/>
watchOS 26 will run on all Apple Watch models that support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="visionos_26">visionOS 26</h2><br/>
The design that Apple used for visionOS is inspiring a new look for iOS and macOS, but Apple also plans to make some tweaks to the way that visionOS looks, too. The changes are likely to be small in scale, and we don't have a lot of detail, but at least some visual updates are coming.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionOS-26-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003304" /><br/>
<h3 id="eye-scrolling">Eye-Scrolling</h3><br/>
Apple is going to add a new eye-scrolling option to the Vision Pro, which will use the built-in eye tracking features. The Vision Pro already supports navigating through the OS by looking at something on the display and then using a hand gesture to "tap" it, so eye-based scrolling is a natural extension of that functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will add eye scrolling to the built-in Apple apps, and it will provide an API that will let developers integrate the capability into third-party apps as well.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="vr_controllers">VR Controllers</h3><br/>
The Vision Pro will gain support for third-party VR hand controllers like the hand controllers designed by Sony for the PlayStation VR console. VR controllers are better attuned to VR games than standard game controllers because they support gestures and magic wand functionality. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_intelligence">Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
Apple is planning to add new &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features to iOS, and it's possible anything that's added will also expand to visionOS. The AI battery management feature rumored for &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; would make sense for the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
At some point, Apple will introduce the &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; personalized &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features that were shown off at WWDC 2024, and those capabilities will almost certainly expand to the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="games_app">Games App</h3><br/>
The new cross-platform Games app that Apple has in the works should be available on the Vision Pro as well as the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Mac, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. The Games app will include all the content from the games section of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, along with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> content and Game Center features like achievements and leaderboards.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="accessibility">Accessibility</h3><br/>
In May, Apple announced upcoming Accessibility features that will be added to visionOS 26. visionOS is going to get new vision accessibility options for users who are blind or have low vision. Zoom will let users magnify anything that's in view using the main Vision Pro camera, while Live Recognition in VoiceOver will use on-device machine learning to describe surroundings, find objects, and read documents.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is developing a new API that will allow approved apps to use the main camera for providing live, person-to-person assistance for visual interpretation, a feature that will be useful for apps like Be My Eyes.<br/>
<br/>
For users with severe mobility disabilities, visionOS is gaining a new protocol that will support Switch Control for Brain Computer Interfaces, a technology that lets users control their devices with brain signals.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="tvos_26">tvOS 26</h2><br/>
The visionOS-style design update that's coming to iOS, iPadOS, and macOS will also extend to tvOS. tvOS 26 could adopt some of the same translucency for menus, app icons, buttons, and other parts of the interface, plus it could get the same floating look and more dramatically rounded edges for buttons and windows that are typical of visionOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/tvOS-26-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003300" /><br/>
Apple wants the experience of using its various platforms to feel more cohesive, which is why everything is getting some of the same design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="screensavers">Screensavers</h3><br/>
It's typical for Apple to introduce new screensavers with tvOS updates, so we can perhaps expect to see new aerial screensaver options, as well as screensavers that match the updated aesthetic. Last year, Apple came out with Snoopy screensavers, so we could get more of those too, or another partnership.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="games_app">Games App</h3><br/>
Apple's cross-platform Games app that will serve as a one-stop spot for discovering and launching games on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The Games app will essentially feature the entire games section of the tvOS &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. It's also expected to have features like achievements, leaderboards, and recommendations from Apple editors. There might also be new tools for communicating with other players.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="wi-fi_syncing">Wi-Fi Syncing</h3><br/>
If you're in the unusual situation of needing to connect your &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; to a captive network at a college or similar location, you'll be glad to hear that the captive Wi-Fi syncing option rumored for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will work across all platforms.<br/>
<br/>
With this feature, you'll only need to log into a captive network on one of your Apple devices, and the login information will sync to everything else signed into your Apple Account.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="compatibility">Compatibility</h3><br/>
tvOS 26 will run on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; HD from 2015 and later &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; models.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; HD (2015)</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K (1st generation, 2017)</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K (2nd generation, 2021)</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K (3rd generation, 2022)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="homepod_software">HomePod Software</h2><br/>
We don't have details about what's coming to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> in updated software, but Apple typically launches new software for its HomePods alongside other software updates. We do know that the forthcoming &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software is expected to run on all &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; models, including the original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-and-Mini-feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-882634" /><br/>
<h2 id="homeos">HomeOS</h2><br/>
For several years now, we've <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/tvos-17-4-homeos-mention/">been seeing hints</a> of a platform called "homeOS," which could be a new platform that's designed to run on upcoming Apple devices like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-command-center/">the smart home hub</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/homeOS2.jpg" alt="" width="1366" height="768" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801940" /><br/>
Apple appears to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/homeos-trademark-filings/">recently trademarked homeOS</a> in several countries around the world, so it's possible we'll see some hint of it at WWDC. It's more likely that Apple is preparing for some kind of product launch that will come later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
homeOS is distinct from the software that runs on the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="no_hardware_announcements">No Hardware Announcements</h2><br/>
Apple sometimes debuts new hardware at its developer events, but this year, there have been no rumors of products that are ready to come out around the June timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/apple-lineup-except-ipad-is-sad.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834959" /><br/>
We are not expecting any hardware-related announcements, with the focus set to be on Apple's updated software naming scheme and the design refresh that's rolling out across most of its updates.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="how_to_watch_the_wwdc_2025_keynote">How to Watch the WWDC 2025 Keynote</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;WWDC 2025&zwnj; keynote will take place on Monday, June 9 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time. Apple will live stream the event on its website, on YouTube, and in the TV app. We have a full list of when WWDC will take place in your timezone in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wwdc-2025-keynote-june-9/">How to Watch WWDC 2025 guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="WWDC 2025 -- June 9 Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0_DjDdfqtUE" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
If you're not able to watch live, we'll have a live blog and coverage of the announcements here at MacRumors, plus we'll be live tweeting the event <a href="https://x.com/macrumorslive">on the MacRumorsLive account</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="software_release_info">Software Release Info</h2><br/>
Apple will make the new versions of &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, iPadOS 26, macOS 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, and visionOS 26 available to developers for testing purposes just after the June 9 keynote event. Testing will continue for several months, with Apple likely planning to provide a public beta option starting in July. All of the updates will launch in the fall alongside new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2025-what-to-expect/">WWDC 2025 Preview: Apple&#039;s iOS 26 Design Overhaul, macOS Tahoe, and Much More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2025-preview-apples-ios-26-design-overhaul-macos-tahoe-and-much-more.2458312/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26 Getting Custom AI-Generated Message Backgrounds, Generative Shortcuts and &#039;Mixmoji&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-ai-backgrounds-mixmoji/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-getting-custom-ai-generated-message-backgrounds-generative-shortcuts-and-mixmoji.2458311/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:57:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-ai-backgrounds-mixmoji/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> Messages app is set to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-messages-and-phone-features/">gain support for customized backgrounds</a> for conversations, and it appears that AI will be an option for generating different looks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/iOS-26-Messages-Background-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004705" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://x.com/nicolas09F9/status/1931066422115057811">Nicolás Alvarez</a>, &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; code suggests that users will be able to generate backgrounds for the Messages app using text-based descriptions. The feature appears to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>, and there will be &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; style options that include Animation, Illustration, and Sketch.<br/>
<br/>
The Messages backgrounds will be customizable on a per-conversation basis, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac users will be able to set a different background for each of their message threads. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> previously said that the backgrounds will sync between all participants in a Messages conversation. So if you set a specific background for an iMessage chat with a friend, the friend will see the same background.<br/>
<br/>
Other messaging apps like WhatsApp support custom background options, so Apple is playing catch-up with the new Messages app background feature.<br/>
<br/>
The Messages app is also set to gain support for polls, automatic translation for incoming messages in other languages, and the option to create <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> by combining two existing standard emoji. Apple plans to call the &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; mixing feature "Mixmoji." With this feature, you will be able to combine two emoji such as cake and balloons into a new emoji that features a cake and a balloon for a celebration.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has other AI features in the works, such as an Apple Intelligence-powered version of the Shortcuts app. Apple could call the new Shortcuts option "Generative Shortcuts," and it appears it will use natural language to help users create powerful multi-step shortcut actions.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; and the new Messages features will be shown off at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a>, which is set to begin on Monday, June 9 with a 10:00 a.m. keynote event.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-ai-backgrounds-mixmoji/">iOS 26 Getting Custom AI-Generated Message Backgrounds, Generative Shortcuts and &#039;Mixmoji&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-getting-custom-ai-generated-message-backgrounds-generative-shortcuts-and-mixmoji.2458311/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Getting Yet Another Ban Delay as Trump Fails to Reach Deal With China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/tiktok-third-ban-delay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-getting-yet-another-ban-delay-as-trump-fails-to-reach-deal-with-china.2458310/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:42:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/tiktok-third-ban-delay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump plans to extend the looming <a href="https://tiktok.pxf.io/c/153062/2392239/27618">TikTok</a> ban for yet another 75 days, reports <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/politics/policy/trump-tiktok-ban-extension-f242c36a">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>. It will mark the third extension since Trump took office in January.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/TikTok-on-iPhone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986195" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/tiktok-75-day-ban-extension/">second extension</a> that Trump gave TikTok is set to expire on June 19, and there appears to be no progress made toward a deal with China, so TikTok needs a third reprieve to continue operating in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
TikTok was banned in the U.S. after the Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act went <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/17/tiktok-january-19-ban-imminent/">into law on January 19</a>, but Trump has ordered the U.S. Department of Justice not to enforce the law at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
Since January, Trump has been working to wrest TikTok's operations from Chinese control by establishing U.S. ownership. Trump's team has considered offers from Oracle, Perplexity, and Amazon, along with individuals like Jimmy Donaldson (known as MrBeast), Shark Tank host Kevin O'Leary, Employer.com founder Jesse Tinsley, and billionaire Frank McCourt.<br/>
<br/>
Trump needs to work with China to get the TikTok deal approved, and China is not cooperating due to ongoing trade tensions created by Trump's tariffs on Chinese goods.<br/>
<br/>
TikTok <a href="https://tiktok.pxf.io/c/153062/2392239/27618">continues to be available for download</a> as of now. It's not yet clear when the app might see a U.S. takeover, but with continued extensions, it is not in danger of being removed from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/tiktok-third-ban-delay/">TikTok Getting Yet Another Ban Delay as Trump Fails to Reach Deal With China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-getting-yet-another-ban-delay-as-trump-fails-to-reach-deal-with-china.2458310/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Father&#039;s Day Deals Arrive With Great Sales From Anker, Sonos, Samsung, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-6-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-fathers-day-deals-arrive-with-great-sales-from-anker-sonos-samsung-and-more.2458307/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:31:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-6-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week we saw some of the first Father's Day deals emerge online, with retailers like Anker, Sonos, and Samsung introducing notable discounts on numerous products ahead of the June 15 holiday. Below, you'll also find all-time low prices on the M3 iPad Air and Apple Watch Series 10.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/hero-new-blue-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961852" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Father's Day Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/sonos-fathers-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004557" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on popular Apple accessories for Father's Day</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/sonos-fathers-day-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Father's Day deals kicked off this week at numerous retailers, and they include great deals on everything from Sonos home audio equipment to Mophie charging accessories and more.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/JKo9Pa">Sonos</a> - Get up to &#36;250 off home audio equipment</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://logitech.cfzu.net/L7VEj">Logitech</a> - Get 20% off two or more items</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.nativeunion.com/">Native Union</a> - Get 20% off sitewide</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/c/153062/214281/3736">Belkin</a> - Get up to 30% off select purchase amounts</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a> - Get up to 50% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11043124-1465418060000">ZAGG</a> - Get 25% off sitewide</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/new-anker-fathers-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004562" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker's best charging accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F2A25B7A1-3EFE-419E-B3A6-3BD8FF119DAD%3Fingress%3D2%26visitId%3D01565566-936b-421a-87cc-5177e1654922%26store_ref%3Dbl_ast_dp_brandLogo_sto%26ref_%3Dast_bln">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/04/anker-fathers-day-sale-amazon/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F2A25B7A1-3EFE-419E-B3A6-3BD8FF119DAD%3Fingress%3D2%26visitId%3D01565566-936b-421a-87cc-5177e1654922%26store_ref%3Dbl_ast_dp_brandLogo_sto%26ref_%3Dast_bln"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">CHARGING SALE</div>Anker Father's Day Deals</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker this week introduced a big collection of discounts on numerous charging accessories on Amazon, with devices like MagSafe-compatible chargers and portable power stations that make perfect Father's Day gifts.<br/>
<br/>
It's also worth noting that MacRumors readers can still <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/anker-macrumors-readers-20-off/"><strong>get 20 percent off</strong></a> a collection of Anker's best charging accessories over on Anker's website. In order to get this deal, <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">head to Anker's website</a> and add an accessory to your cart, then enter the code <strong>Ankermacrumors2025</strong> at checkout to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D8PTGKSM%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1N0B3QBVY8SUN%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1N0B3QBVY8SUN_1749045473715">3-in-1 MagGo Foldable Travel Charger</a> - &#36;71.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.26QITUXI4DZD7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.26QITUXI4DZD7_1749045060729">3-in-1 MagGo Qi2 Charging Station</a> - &#36;82.49 for Prime Members, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S7WR00DALR1Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S7WR00DALR1Q_1749044767180">3-in-1 MagGo Charger Cube</a> - &#36;113.05 for Prime members, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/new-samsung-fathers-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004564" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get big discounts on Samsung monitors, TVs, and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/hzf0209qt54p9">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/02/samsung-summer-sale-2025/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/hzf0209qt54p9"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DISCOUNTS</div>Discover Samsung Summer Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/17yctwgf8s42i"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>32-inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung this week kicked off a new Discover Samsung sale, which includes savings on monitors, TVs, Galaxy products, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ipad-air-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004565" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;100 off M3 iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/01/m3-ipad-air-amazon-499/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week introduced discounts across nearly the entire M3 iPad Air lineup, offering &#36;100 off these tablets. Prices start at &#36;499.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch M3 iPad Air, down from &#36;599.00. <a href="https://bestbuy.7tiv.net/qz0Z15">Best Buy is matching</a> all of these deals on the iPad Air.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/apple-watch-series-10-new-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004566" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;100 Apple Watch Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/03/100-off-apple-watch-se-10/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the 42mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10 for &#36;299.00, down from &#36;399.00, as well as the 46mm GPS model for &#36;329.00, down from &#36;429.00. Both of these are record low prices on the Apple Watch Series 10, and they're available in about 5-6 case colors and band styles.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address" title="Email Address" /><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value="" title="form" /></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-6-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Father&#039;s Day Deals Arrive With Great Sales From Anker, Sonos, Samsung, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-fathers-day-deals-arrive-with-great-sales-from-anker-sonos-samsung-and-more.2458307/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Announces MLB Friday Night Baseball Schedule for July</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/apple-friday-night-baseball-july-schedule/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-announces-mlb-friday-night-baseball-schedule-for-july.2458306/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:24:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/apple-friday-night-baseball-july-schedule/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Major League Baseball this week <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-and-major-league-baseball-announce-july-friday-night-baseball-schedule/">announced</a> the July schedule for Friday Night Baseball, a weekly doubleheader of MLB games streamed on Apple TV+.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/MLB-Friday-Night-Baseball-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1103" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004669" /><br/>
Friday Night Baseball is included with an Apple TV+ subscription, at no additional cost. In the U.S., Apple TV+ costs &#36;9.99 per month or &#36;99 per year, and it is also included in all Apple One subscription bundles with other Apple services.<br/>
<br/>
The full July schedule is as follows:<blockquote><strong>Friday, 7/4</strong><br/>
St. Louis Cardinals at Chicago Cubs<br/>
2:20 p.m. ET<br/>
<br/>
Los Angeles Angels at Toronto Blue Jays<br/>
7:07 p.m. ET<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Friday, 7/11</strong><br/>
Seattle Mariners at Detroit Tigers<br/>
7:10 p.m. ET<br/>
<br/>
Arizona Diamondbacks at Los Angeles Angels<br/>
9:38 p.m. ET<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Friday, 7/18</strong><br/>
No games<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Friday, 7/25</strong><br/>
Philadelphia Phillies at New York Yankees<br/>
7:05 p.m. ET<br/>
<br/>
Cleveland Guardians at Kansas City Royals<br/>
8:10 p.m. ET</blockquote>Available in 60 countries, Apple says Friday Night Baseball provides enhanced production quality, expert commentary, and no local broadcast restrictions.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/apple-friday-night-baseball-july-schedule/">Apple TV+ Announces MLB Friday Night Baseball Schedule for July</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-announces-mlb-friday-night-baseball-schedule-for-july.2458306/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPad Air and Rock Paper Pencil From Astropad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/macrumors-giveaway-astropad-ipad-air-june/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-ipad-air-and-rock-paper-pencil-from-astropad.2458304/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:51:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/macrumors-giveaway-astropad-ipad-air-june/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://shop.astropad.com">Astropad</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro, and one of <a href="https://shop.astropad.com/collections/shop-astropad/products/rock-paper-pencil">Astropad's Rock Paper Pencil kits</a> to go along with it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/rock-paper-pencil-overview.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004654" /><br/>
Rock Paper Pencil is a product that's meant to make writing on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; feel like writing on a piece of paper rather than on a slippery display. Astropad <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/28/astropad-rock-paper-pencil-3/">just overhauled</a> Rock Paper Pencil to make it better than ever, so now is a good time to check it out.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://shop.astropad.com/collections/shop-astropad/products/rock-paper-pencil">&#36;45 kit</a> includes a NanoCling screen protector that goes on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s display, and an accompanying &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; tip that pairs with an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;. You can put the NanoCling screen protector on while you're using your &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, then take it off and tuck it away for later if you want to use your &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; without it. It takes just seconds to put the screen protector on and remove it again, and it doesn't leave a sticky residue on your &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/rock-paper-pencil-v3-screen-protector.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004657" /><br/>
The upgraded NanoCling screen protector has an improved feel, plus it's thinner. Writing on it is like writing on a stack of papers rather than just a single sheet, and it's a little softer and smoother than before. Using the NanoCling is a pleasant experience that makes note taking and sketching on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; feel more natural. Even though it has a unique microscopic texture that mimics the feel of paper, the screen protector doesn't interfere with the vivid colors of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/rock-paper-pencil-tip.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004659" /><br/>
Astropad also redesigned the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; tip that comes in the Rock Paper Pencil kit, and it's now made from solid stainless steel that won't wear down or chip over time. The size of the tip has also been increased, so it's now 1mm instead of 0.75mm. The larger tip balances out the friction and improves durability.<br/>
<br/>
If you dislike the slippery feeling of writing on a hard screen, the Rock Paper Pencil is worth checking out. It does a great job of making you forget that you're writing on a tablet because it both feels and sounds like using a pen on paper.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/rock-paper-pencil-demo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004658" /><br/>
Rock Paper Pencil is compatible with all of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>, M3, and M4 iPads, and many older models as well. It works with the 6th and 7th-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and the 7th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and later.<br/>
<br/>
We have a Rock Paper Pencil kit, an M3 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, and an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro for one lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/qTzEc/astropad-giveaway" rel="nofollow"><br/>
  Astropad Giveaway<br/>
</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script>The contest will run from today (June 6) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on June 13. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after June 13 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/macrumors-giveaway-astropad-ipad-air-june/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPad Air and Rock Paper Pencil From Astropad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-ipad-air-and-rock-paper-pencil-from-astropad.2458304/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence at WWDC 2025: Genmoji Upgrade Incoming Instead of Personalized Siri</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/genmoji-upgrade-for-ios-26/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-at-wwdc-2025-genmoji-upgrade-incoming-instead-of-personalized-siri.2458303/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:36:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/genmoji-upgrade-for-ios-26/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Genmoji</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A few smaller-scale Apple Intelligence enhancements will be announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wwdc-2025-keynote-june-9/">at WWDC 2025 next week</a>, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/genmoji-ad-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981739" /><br/>
One planned upgrade that had not been reported until now is the ability to create a Genmoji by combining a pair of existing standard emoji. For example, Gurman said that you will be able to turn separate basketball and trash can emoji into a single Genmoji that shows a basketball going into a trash can.<br/>
<br/>
He also expects iOS 26 to include an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/02/shortcuts-app-apple-intelligence-integration/">upgraded Shortcuts app powered by Apple Intelligence</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/ios-19-ai-battery-management/">new AI-powered battery mode</a>, as he previously reported.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, he said there will be system-wide Translate app capabilities on iOS 26. <em>9to5Mac</em> previously reported that the Messages app would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/03/ios-26-messages-app-rumors/">gaining live translation capabilities</a>, but Gurman said it will extend to the Phone app and other areas of the operating system. A live translation feature is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/13/airpods-live-translation-ios-19/">also expected for AirPods</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
Waiting on Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delayed personalized Siri features</a> to launch? Don't get your hopes up next week, as Gurman said that those features remain "far off." He does not expect any significant new Siri features to be announced at WWDC 2025.<br/>
<br/>
What happened to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/13/apple-announced-swift-assist-wwdc24-so-where-is-it/">Swift Assist</a>, the coding assistance tool that Apple announced at WWDC 2024? Gurman said it faced issues, so Apple instead plans to let developers use Xcode <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-anthropic-ai-coding-platform/">with third-party large language models</a> (LLMs).<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/genmoji-upgrade-for-ios-26/">Apple Intelligence at WWDC 2025: Genmoji Upgrade Incoming Instead of Personalized Siri</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-at-wwdc-2025-genmoji-upgrade-incoming-instead-of-personalized-siri.2458303/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Delays Two New iPhone Features Until iOS 27</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/two-features-delayed-to-ios-27/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-delays-two-new-iphone-features-until-ios-27.2458302/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:07:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/two-features-delayed-to-ios-27/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 26 is rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-rumored-design-details/">glassy design</a>, new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-games-app-details/">Games</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-and-ipados-26-preview-app/">Preview apps</a>, and more, but two other enhancements have reportedly been delayed until next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-teal.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964610" /><br/>
In his list of WWDC 2025 expectations today, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman today said</a> that Apple has postponed the launch of revamped Calendar and Health apps until iOS 27 or later, as it needs more time to develop these planned changes.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman did not reveal any specific changes planned for the Calendar app, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/09/apple-acquired-mayday-labs/">Apple's acquisition of Mayday Labs</a> in April 2024 could hint at the company's plans.<br/>
<br/>
Mayday Labs had developed an AI-powered calendar, task manager, and scheduling assistant for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac. The all-in-one app used AI to automatically schedule your events and tasks at ideal times, and it could learn your scheduling preferences and daily patterns over time to further optimize your calendar.<br/>
<br/>
Mayday's website said its app worked best when you used it with others. For example, it could automatically schedule a meeting at a time where both you and a co-worker were available. It also offered automatic rescheduling for flexibility.<br/>
<br/>
The app was shut down shortly after the acquisition.<br/>
<br/>
It would be reasonable to assume that some of Mayday's features and technologies could be added to Apple's Calendar app across the iPhone, iPad, and Mac, under the Apple Intelligence umbrella. But, it appears that will have to wait for iOS 27.<br/>
<br/>
As for the Health app, Gurman has previously reported that it will get a new AI-powered health coaching feature that offers personalized health recommendations. He initially expected the revamp to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/ios-19-4-revamped-health-app-rumor/">part of iOS 19.4</a> (now iOS 26.4), but it now appears that it will not be ready until at least iOS 27 as well. That update will arrive next year. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/two-features-delayed-to-ios-27/">Apple Reportedly Delays Two New iPhone Features Until iOS 27</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-delays-two-new-iphone-features-until-ios-27.2458302/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26&#039;s Digital Glass Design: Home Screen Widgets, Camera, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-rumored-design-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26s-digital-glass-design-home-screen-widgets-camera-and-more.2458298/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:32:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-rumored-design-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a lengthy report outlining his WWDC 2025 expectations today, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman shared more details</a> about iOS 26's rumored new design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/iOS-26-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004222" /><br/>
According to Gurman, iOS 26 will feature a "digital glass" design inspired by visionOS, the operating system for Apple's Vision Pro headset. That is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/ios-19-visionos-redesign-rumors/">well-known rumor by now</a>, but he goes on to provide some more specific details, as listed below:<ul><li>There will be more use of light and transparency.</li><br/>
<li>There will be redesigned app icons, but he does not expect them to be round.</li><br/>
<li>Toolbars and tabs will be redesigned, with a focus on pop-out menus.</li><br/>
<li>Home Screen widgets have been redesigned to match the new "digital glass" look.</li><br/>
<li>Safari will feature a more transparent, glassy address bar.</li><br/>
<li>The glass-like design changes should extend to the Camera app, which will be revamped with a focus on simplicity.</li></ul>The design changes are expected to extend to iPadOS 26, macOS 26, tvOS 26, and watchOS 26.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will announce iOS 26 and other software updates in just three days from now, during its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wwdc-2025-keynote-june-9/">WWDC 2025 keynote</a>, which kicks off on Monday, June 9 at 10 a.m. Pacific Time. The first iOS 26 beta should be seeded to developers shortly after the keynote, and the update will likely be released to the general public in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-rumored-design-details/">iOS 26&#039;s Digital Glass Design: Home Screen Widgets, Camera, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26s-digital-glass-design-home-screen-widgets-camera-and-more.2458298/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26&#039;s Rumored Games App Described in More Detail in New Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-games-app-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26s-rumored-games-app-described-in-more-detail-in-new-report.2458295/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:57:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-games-app-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 26 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-ios-19-gaming-app/">rumored to include a new Games app</a> on iPhones, and <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has now provided more details</a> about it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/Apple-Arcade-Sneaky-Sasquatch.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004601" /><br/>
In a lengthy report outlining his WWDC 2025 expectations today, Gurman revealed that the Games app will have five tabs: Home, Arcade, Play Together, Library, and Search. He said that the app will look like a games-centric version of the App Store, and it will give a bigger spotlight to both App Store games and Apple Arcade games.<br/>
<br/>
There will still be a Games tab in the App Store, according to Gurman, who described the new Games app as "underwhelming."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously said that the Games app will replace Apple's longstanding Game Center feature, which lets players track their in-game achievements and compete with others on leaderboards. Game Center used to be a preinstalled app on iPhones, but it was relegated to the Settings app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/06/14/game-center-removed-ios-10-beta/">starting with iOS 10</a> in 2016.<br/>
<br/>
The new Games app will be one of two new preinstalled apps on iOS 26, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-and-ipados-26-preview-app/">the other being Preview</a> for managing PDFs, according to Gurman.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-games-app-details/">iOS 26&#039;s Rumored Games App Described in More Detail in New Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26s-rumored-games-app-described-in-more-detail-in-new-report.2458295/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Has AirPods Pro 2 at &#36;169.99 and AirPods 4 at &#36;99.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/amazon-airpods-pro-2-at-169/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-airpods-pro-2-at-169-99-and-airpods-4-at-99-99.2458294/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:42:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/amazon-airpods-pro-2-at-169/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's steep discount on the AirPods Pro 2 is back today, with the earbuds available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1XD1ZV3"><strong>&#36;169.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. Free delivery options provide an estimated delivery date of around June 11, while Prime members should get the headphones sooner in most cases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895406" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Compared to past sales, this is a match of the best price we've tracked so far in 2025 and it's an overall solid second-best price on the AirPods Pro 2. Amazon also has the AirPods 4 available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.99</strong></a> during this sale, an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1XD1ZV3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address" title="Email Address" /><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value="" title="form" /></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/amazon-airpods-pro-2-at-169/">Amazon Has AirPods Pro 2 at &#36;169.99 and AirPods 4 at &#36;99.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-airpods-pro-2-at-169-99-and-airpods-4-at-99-99.2458294/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26: New Messages and Phone App Features Leaked Ahead of WWDC</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-messages-and-phone-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-new-messages-and-phone-app-features-leaked-ahead-of-wwdc.2458293/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:27:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-messages-and-phone-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to announce several new features for the Messages and Phone apps on iOS 26, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/General-Apps-Messages-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985161" /><br/>
In a lengthy report outlining his WWDC 2025 expectations today, Gurman said that the two main changes in the Messages app will be the ability to create polls, as well as the option to set a background image within a conversation.<br/>
<br/>
<em>9to5Mac</em> was first to report that the Messages app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/03/ios-26-messages-app-rumors/">would be gaining polls</a>, allowing users to vote on questions and topics. It is a feature that has long existed in other popular messaging apps, such as WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, and Telegram.<br/>
<br/>
Background images would add a personalized flair to conversations, and Gurman said that the images will automatically sync across Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
The new Messages features should extend to iPadOS 26 and macOS 26.<br/>
<br/>
For the Phone app, Gurman said that iOS 26 will introduce a new view that combines favorite contacts, recent calls, and voicemails into a single, scrollable window. He said this new design will be optional, with users able to revert to the legacy interface.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 26 and other software updates will be announced during Apple's WWDC 2025 keynote, which begins <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/02/apple-readies-wwdc-2025-live-stream/">on Monday, June 9 at 10 a.m. Pacific Time</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-messages-and-phone-features/">iOS 26: New Messages and Phone App Features Leaked Ahead of WWDC</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-new-messages-and-phone-app-features-leaked-ahead-of-wwdc.2458293/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Watch Apple&#039;s WWDC 2025 Keynote on June 9</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wwdc-2025-keynote-june-9/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-watch-apples-wwdc-2025-keynote-on-june-9.2458292/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:21:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wwdc-2025-keynote-june-9&#038;post_date=1749230472/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 2025 Worldwide Developers Conference will take place the week of June 9 to June 13, and like the last five years, it will be an online event, although select developers and students will be invited to Apple Park. To kick things off, Apple holds a keynote event on the Monday to announce new software, which is what makes it of interest to the general public.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/WWDC-2025-YouTube-Thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003917" /><br/>
During the keynote event on Monday, June 9, Apple is expected to unveil iOS 26, iPadOS 26, macOS 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, and visionOS 26. (Apple is changing the naming for its operating system updates –  the "26" represents the September 2025 to September 2026 release season.) The company may also preview its new homeOS operating system, the platform that powers its long-rumored smart home hub.<br/>
<br/>
You can watch the WWDC 2025 keynote event using one of the methods outlined below. The live stream is set to start at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time from ‌Apple Park‌ in Cupertino, California. We have a full list of when the event will begin in other time zones in the United States and around the world.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Honolulu, Hawaii -- 7:00 a.m. HAST</li><br/>
 	<li>Anchorage, Alaska -- 9:00 a.m. AKDT</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Cupertino, California -- 10:00 a.m. PDT</strong></li><br/>
 	<li>Phoenix, Arizona -- 10:00 a.m. MST</li><br/>
 	<li>Vancouver, Canada -- 10:00 a.m. PDT</li><br/>
 	<li>Denver, Colorado -- 11:00 a.m. MDT</li><br/>
 	<li>Dallas, Texas -- 12:00 noon CDT</li><br/>
 	<li>New York, New York -- 1:00 p.m. EDT</li><br/>
 	<li>Toronto, Canada -- 1:00 p.m. EDT</li><br/>
 	<li>Halifax, Canada -- 2:00 p.m. ADT</li><br/>
 	<li>Rio de Janeiro, Brazil -- 2:00 p.m. BRT (no DST)</li><br/>
 	<li>London, United Kingdom -- 6:00 p.m. BST</li><br/>
 	<li>Berlin, Germany -- 7:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li>Paris, France -- 7:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
 	<li>Cape Town, South Africa -- 7:00 p.m. SAST</li><br/>
 	<li>Helsinki, Finland -- 8:00 p.m. EEST</li><br/>
 	<li>Istanbul, Turkey -- 8:00 p.m. TRT</li><br/>
 	<li>Dubai, United Arab Emirates -- 9:00 p.m. GST</li><br/>
 	<li>Delhi, India -- 10:30 p.m. IST</li><br/>
 	<li>Jakarta, Indonesia -- 12:00 a.m. WIB next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Shanghai, China -- 1:00 a.m. CST next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Singapore -- 1:00 a.m. SGT next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Perth, Australia -- 1:00 a.m. AWST next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Hong Kong -- 1:00 a.m. HKT next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Seoul, South Korea -- 2:00 a.m. KST next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Tokyo, Japan -- 2:00 a.m. JST next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Adelaide, Australia -- 2:30 a.m. ACST next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Sydney, Australia -- 3:00 a.m. AEST next day</li><br/>
 	<li>Auckland, New Zealand -- 5:00 a.m. NZST next day</li><br/>
</ul><h2>Watch the Keynote on YouTube</h2><br/>
Watching the WWDC keynote on YouTube may be one of the quickest and easiest ways to catch the event because YouTube is generally available on most devices, including TV sets and consoles.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0_DjDdfqtUE?si=xq9tGiibA_awKnz4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The YouTube live stream above will be accessible on June 9 when the event kicks off.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Watch the Keynote on Mac, iPhone, iPad, or Vision Pro</h2><br/>
You can watch the WWDC keynote on any Mac, iPhone, iPad, or Vision Pro using Apple's native Safari browser or another browser. iOS devices must be running iOS 10 or later, and Macs need to be running macOS Sierra 10.12 or later to access the stream.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/WWDC-2025-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002300" /><br/>
Launch Safari from your chosen device and <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">follow this link to the WWDC 2025 Keynote</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Watch the Keynote Using the Apple TV App</h2><br/>
You can watch the WWDC keynote via Apple's TV app on Mac, iPhone, iPad, Vision Pro, and Apple TV, with the link in the TV app becoming available on the day of the event or just before.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open the <strong>TV</strong> app on your chosen device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Scroll down the <strong>Watch Now</strong> category and select <strong>WWDC 2025</strong>. Alternatively, type "WWDC" into the Search field and select <strong>WWDC 2025</strong> from the results.</li><br/>
 	<li>Click <strong>Play</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
The app may tell you to tune in at your local time to watch the event live prior to when the WWDC keynote begins.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Watch the Keynote on a Windows PC</h2><br/>
If you don't have an Apple device handy, you can still watch the WWDC 2025 keynote on a PC running Windows 10 or later. Open Microsoft Edge browser and follow <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">this link to the WWDC 2025 Livestream</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple offers no guarantees, other platforms may also be able to access the WWDC 2025 keynote using recent versions of Chrome or Firefox (MSE, H.264, and AAC codecs/extensions must be installed).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Watch in the Apple Developer App or Developer Website</h2><br/>
Apple also plans to stream the keynote in <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-developer/id640199958">the Apple Developer app</a>, and on the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/">Apple Developer website</a>, making it easier than ever for Apple fans and developers to catch the event.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacRumors Coverage</h2><br/>
For those unable to watch the live stream, or who prefer to read a text version of the announcements, we'll have live coverage both here on MacRumors.com and through our <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive?lang=en">MacRumorsLive X (Twitter) account</a>, so make sure to follow.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wwdc-2025-keynote-june-9/">How to Watch Apple&#039;s WWDC 2025 Keynote on June 9</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-watch-apples-wwdc-2025-keynote-on-june-9.2458292/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26: Apple&#039;s Preview App Rumored to Expand From Mac to iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-and-ipados-26-preview-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-apples-preview-app-rumored-to-expand-from-mac-to-iphone.2458291/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:14:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-and-ipados-26-preview-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 26 and iPadOS 26 will include a preinstalled Preview app from Apple, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-06-06/apple-wwdc-2025-preview-ios-26-macos-26-new-ai-features-ipados-26-redesigns"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/preview.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004554" /><br/>
In a lengthy report outlining his WWDC 2025 expectations today, Gurman said that the Preview app will provide iPhone and iPad users with an all-in-one, built-in solution for managing, editing, and annotating PDF documents.<br/>
<br/>
The app will look similar to Apple's longstanding Preview app on the Mac, he said:<blockquote>The software looks similar to the Mac version, and its launch screen is in the same style as apps like Pages and Keynote. It includes a big logo on the top portion of the screen advertising the Preview name and a gallery of document options below it.</blockquote>Gurman did not say if the Preview app on the iPhone and iPad will also offer basic image editing abilities, like it does on the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 26 and iPadOS 26 will be announced during Apple's WWDC 2025 keynote, which begins <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/02/apple-readies-wwdc-2025-live-stream/">on Monday, June 9 at 10 a.m. Pacific Time</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/ios-26-and-ipados-26-preview-app/">iOS 26: Apple&#039;s Preview App Rumored to Expand From Mac to iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-apples-preview-app-rumored-to-expand-from-mac-to-iphone.2458291/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Launching Later This Year With These 17 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/iphone-17-air-list-of-17-rumored-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-launching-later-this-year-with-these-17-new-features.2458290/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:17:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/iphone-17-air-list-of-17-rumored-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the so-called "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>" is not expected to launch until September, there are already plenty of rumors about the ultra-thin device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iPhone-17-Air-Size-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993585" /><br/>
Overall, the iPhone 17 Air sounds like a mixed bag. While the device is expected to have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/iphone-17-air-thinness-video/">impressively thin and light design</a>, rumors indicate it will have some compromises compared to iPhone 17 Pro models, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-17-air-battery-case-report/">worse battery life</a>, only a single rear camera, only a single speaker, and an A19 chip instead of an A19 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we recap 17 key rumors for the iPhone 17 Air as of June 2025:<ul><li>The thinnest iPhone ever, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">measuring just 5.5mm at its thinnest point</a>, but possibly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/iphone-17-air-9-5mm-thick-including-camera/">up to 9.5mm with the rear camera bump included</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">6.6-inch OLED display</a> with Face ID and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-metalens-rumor/">potentially smaller</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">Dynamic Island</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/ltpo-for-all-iphone-17-models-report/">ProMotion support</a> for up to a 120Hz refresh rate (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/03/iphone-17-promotion-rumors-disputed/">disputed</a> by one source)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">A19 chip</a> instead of A19 Pro chip</li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">single 48-megapixel rear camera</a> on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/17/iphone-17-air-front-page-tech-renders/">all-new elongated camera bar</a></li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">24-megapixel front camera</a></li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">single speaker</a> in the earpiece, no bottom speaker</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/">Apple-designed Wi-Fi 7 chip</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apples-c1-modem-iphone-17-air-lack-mmwave/">Apple-designed C1 modem for cellular connectivity</a></li><br/>
<li>eSIM only, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">no physical SIM card slot</a> worldwide</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/slimmer-iphones-without-usb-c-ports/">USB-C port</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/iphone-17-air-high-density-battery-rumor/">High-density battery</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-price-battery-life-more/">Camera Control button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-magsafe-action-button/">Action button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-magsafe-action-button/">MagSafe</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">12GB of RAM</a>, exceeding the 8GB minimum for Apple Intelligence</li><br/>
<li>Apple reportedly plans to release an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-17-air-battery-case-report/">iPhone 17 Air battery case</a></li></ul>Bookmark our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air roundup</a> to stay up to date with more rumors in the coming months.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/iphone-17-air-list-of-17-rumored-features/">&#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Launching Later This Year With These 17 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-launching-later-this-year-with-these-17-new-features.2458290/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>HomePod Software 26 to Support OG HomePod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/homepod-software-26-support-og-homepod/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-software-26-to-support-og-homepod.2458283/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:11:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/homepod-software-26-support-og-homepod/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming HomePod Software 26 update will support the original first-generation HomePod along with all succeeding HomePod models, according to a private account on X with a proven track record for upcoming software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/HomePod-White-on-Console.jpg" alt="" width="1120" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004423" /><br/>
Apple released the original HomePod eight years ago, so it's good to see that Apple's latest software will support it. As for what the new software will bring to the table in terms of new features, it's not yet clear, but hopefully improvements to the Siri experience are forthcoming.<br/>
<br/>
Rather than naming the next-generation version HomePod Software 19, Apple is likely to call it HomePod Software 26. All of the major software updates coming this year will be numbered "26," reflecting the September 2025 to September 2026 release cycle, so it'd be weird for the HomePod Software not to receive the same treatment.<br/>
<br/>
The HomePod family is expected to grow in size this year or next, with the arrival of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-command-center/">long-rumored smart home hub</a>. We're hoping that Apple provides an early preview of the home hub at WWDC, based on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/homeos-trademark-filings/">recent trademarking activity</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's WWDC 2025 keynote will begin on Monday, June 9 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time. Apple will live stream the event on its website, on YouTube, and in the TV app. If you're not able to watch live, we'll have a live blog and coverage of the announcements here at MacRumors, plus we'll be live tweeting the event on the <a href="https://x.com/macrumorslive">MacRumorsLive account</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/homepod-software-26-support-og-homepod/">HomePod Software 26 to Support OG HomePod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-software-26-to-support-og-homepod.2458283/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 26 to Support These Apple TV Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/tvos-26-support-these-apple-tv-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-26-to-support-these-apple-tv-models.2458282/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:38:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/tvos-26-support-these-apple-tv-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming tvOS 26 software update will support all Apple TV models that are compatible with tvOS 18, according to a private account on X with a proven track record for upcoming software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/tvOS-26-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003300" /><br/>
If this rumor is accurate, and we have high confidence that it is, then tvOS 26 will be compatible with the Apple TV HD – released in 2015(!) – and beyond:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Apple TV HD (2015)</li><br/>
  <li>Apple TV 4K (1st generation, 2017)</li><br/>
  <li>Apple TV 4K (2nd generation, 2021)</li><br/>
  <li>Apple TV 4K (3rd generation, 2022)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Rather than naming the next-generation version tvOS 19, Apple is going to call it tvOS 26, our source confirmed. All of the software updates coming this year will be numbered "26," reflecting the September 2025 to September 2026 release cycle.<br/>
<br/>
The visionOS-inspired design coming to iOS, iPadOS, and macOS will also extend to tvOS. While tvOS typically receives less attention and specific details are scarce, we can infer some changes based on iOS rumors.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 26 is expected to feature a visionOS-like interface with translucent elements, floating menus and windows, and softer, rounded visuals. The design uses light and shadow to create a glass-like effect, as seen in Apple's WWDC promotional imagery, so expect these to appear.<br/>
<br/>
We're also expecting new screensavers, a new cross-platform Games app, Wi-Fi syncing, and potential new AI-powered features. For everything we know, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/tvos-26-what-to-expect/">WWDC roundup for tvOS 26</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/tvos-26-support-these-apple-tv-models/">tvOS 26 to Support These Apple TV Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-26-to-support-these-apple-tv-models.2458282/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 26 to Support These Apple Watch Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/watchos-26-support-these-apple-watch-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-26-to-support-these-apple-watch-models.2458281/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:22:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/watchos-26-support-these-apple-watch-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming watchOS 26 software update will support all Apple Watch models that are compatible with watchOS 11, according to a private account on X with a proven track record for upcoming software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/watchOS-26-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003307" /><br/>
If this rumor is accurate, and we believe it is, watchOS 26 will be compatible with the Apple Watch Series 6 and beyond:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch SE (2nd generation)</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch Series 6</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch Series 7</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch Series 8</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch Series 9</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 10</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch Ultra</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch Ultra 2</li><br/>
</ul>Rather than naming the next-generation version watchOS 12, Apple is going to call it watchOS 26, our source confirmed. All of the software updates coming this year will be numbered "26," reflecting the September 2025 to September 2026 release cycle.<br/>
<br/>
The overhauled design that Apple is introducing for iOS 26 will also extend to the Apple Watch, though the changes to watchOS may not be as dramatic as the iOS 26 refresh. Apple will likely add new watch faces that are designed with the new style.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's upcoming watchOS 26 update could also introduce support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/apple-watch-control-center-third-party/">third-party shortcuts in Control Center</a>. For more details on what to expect for Apple Watch at WWDC next week, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/04/wwdc-2025-watchos-26/">check out our roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/watchos-26-support-these-apple-watch-models/">watchOS 26 to Support These Apple Watch Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-26-to-support-these-apple-watch-models.2458281/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Use Your iPhone As a Webcam for Nintendo Switch 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/use-iphone-webcam-nintendo-switch-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/use-your-iphone-as-a-webcam-for-nintendo-switch-2.2458279/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 02:37:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/use-iphone-webcam-nintendo-switch-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Nintendo Switch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Nintendo Switch 2 includes a new built-in social feature called GameChat that allows up to 12 users to engage in video chats simultaneously, even if they're playing in different games. To facilitate this, Nintendo offers an official Switch 2 Camera that connects via USB-C, but it turns out that an iPhone does the job just as well, if not better.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wGH_VF-Gx4Y?si=Q8OVgQyJ3TF6qOFe" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Niles Mitchell has thoughtfully <a href="https://youtu.be/wGH_VF-Gx4Y">shared a demo</a> of the Switch-iPhone configuration that explains how to set it up. You'll need a HDMI to USB-C cable and a HDMI converter cable to connect them, which should cost around &#36;30 in total. <br/>
<br/>
If you aren't lucky enough to own a Switch 2, you can always <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-continuity-camera-iphone-mac/">use your iPhone as a webcam for a Mac</a>. Click the link to learn how it works.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nintendo-switch/">Nintendo Switch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/06/use-iphone-webcam-nintendo-switch-2/">Use Your iPhone As a Webcam for Nintendo Switch 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/use-your-iphone-as-a-webcam-for-nintendo-switch-2.2458279/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WWDC 2025: What to Expect From tvOS 26</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/tvos-26-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2025-what-to-expect-from-tvos-26.2458271/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:38:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/tvos-26-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[tvOS is probably the Apple operating system that gets the fewest updates each year, and that's not going to change in 2025. But thanks to the design overhaul that Apple is introducing across all of its software platforms, tvOS is set to get some interesting new features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/tvOS-26-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003300" /><br/>
<h2>Naming</h2><br/>
As we've noted several times this week, Apple is changing the naming for its operating system updates. After tvOS 18, we're getting tvOS 26 instead of tvOS 19. The "26" represents the September 2025 to September 2026 release season for tvOS, with Apple planning to use the same numbering across iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, and visionOS too.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Updated Design</h2><br/>
The visionOS-style design update that's coming to iOS, iPadOS, and macOS will also extend to tvOS. tvOS tends to get little attention comparatively so we don't have specific details on what's changing, but we can extrapolate a bit from the iOS rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> will adopt an interface that riffs on visionOS, with a focus on translucency, floating menus and windows, and more rounded design elements. It's been described as using light and shadow to give off a glass-like effect, which we can see in the imagery that Apple is using to promote WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 26 could adopt some of the same translucency for menus, app icons, buttons, and other parts of the interface, plus it could get the same floating look and more dramatically rounded edges for buttons and windows that are typical of visionOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple wants the experience of using its various platforms to feel more cohesive, which is why everything is getting some of the same design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Screensavers</h2><br/>
It's typical for Apple to introduce new screensavers with tvOS updates, so we can perhaps expect to see new aerial screensaver options, as well as screensavers that match the updated aesthetic. Last year, Apple came out with Snoopy screensavers, so we could get more of those too, or another partnership.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Games App</h2><br/>
Apple plans to debut a new cross-platform Games app that will serve as a one-stop spot for discovering and launching games. On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, it will feature a range of games that can run on the device, including third-party games and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> games.<br/>
<br/>
The Games app will essentially feature the entire games section of the tvOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. It's also expected to have features like achievements, leaderboards, and recommendations from Apple editors. There might also be new tools for communicating with other players.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wi-Fi Syncing</h2><br/>
If you're in the unusual situation of needing to connect your &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; to a captive network at a college or similar location, you'll be glad to hear about a new captive Wi-Fi syncing option that's coming to Apple's platforms.<br/>
<br/>
With this feature, you'll only need to log into a captive network on one of your Apple devices, and the login information will sync to everything else signed into your Apple Account.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Recommendations</h2><br/>
There's no rumor about tvOS adopting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, but Apple is expanding AI across its platforms. tvOS could benefit from AI features that better learn from user preferences to make more tailored content recommendations on what to watch next.<br/>
<br/>
If and when Apple introduces major &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; updates to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, we could see some of those features available on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>WWDC 2025 Keynote</h2><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a> keynote will begin on Monday, June 9 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time. Apple will live stream the event on its website, on YouTube, and in the TV app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="WWDC 2025 -- June 9 Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0_DjDdfqtUE" width="1674" height="807" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
If you're not able to watch live, we'll have a live blog and coverage of the announcements here at MacRumors, plus we'll be live tweeting the event <a href="https://x.com/macrumorslive">on the MacRumorsLive account</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/05/tvos-26-what-to-expect/">WWDC 2025: What to Expect From tvOS 26</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2025-what-to-expect-from-tvos-26.2458271/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
