<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:03:31 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Plans Split iPhone Launch Strategy: Pro and Foldable in Fall 2026, Standard in Spring 2027</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/apple-split-iphone-launch-strategy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-plans-split-iphone-launch-strategy-pro-and-foldable-in-fall-2026-standard-in-spring-2027.2456436/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:32:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/apple-split-iphone-launch-strategy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting in 2026, Apple plans to change the release cycle for its flagship <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup, according to <em><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-plans-iphone-release-schedule-shakeup-new-styles">The Information</a></em>. Apple will release the more expensive &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 Pro models in the fall, delaying the release of the standard &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 until the spring.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Iridescent-Search.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995557" /><br/>
The shift may be because Apple plans to debut a foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in 2026, which will join the existing &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup. The fall release will include the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 Pro, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 Pro Max, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 Air, and the new foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Later, in spring 2027, Apple will release the standard &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 18 and an updated version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a>. The less expensive &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models will undergo manufacturing trials in India as Apple expands efforts to reduce its reliance on Chinese manufacturing.<br/>
<br/>
Shifting the release schedule will make it easier for Apple to manage an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup that has six devices instead of five, as <em>The Information</em> suggests that a staggered launch would cut down on the number of manufacturing workers that Apple needs to employ at one time.<br/>
<br/>
The 2026 Pro &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models could have under-display <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> for the first time, with the hardware needed for facial recognition embedded underneath the display. A pinhole would remain for the front-facing camera.<br/>
<br/>
The foldable 2026 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will have a book-style design with a 5.7-inch outer display when closed and an inner display close to eight inches when open.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/apple-split-iphone-launch-strategy/">Apple Plans Split iPhone Launch Strategy: Pro and Foldable in Fall 2026, Standard in Spring 2027</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-plans-split-iphone-launch-strategy-pro-and-foldable-in-fall-2026-standard-in-spring-2027.2456436/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Air Expected to Have Battery Case Due to &#039;Worse&#039; Battery Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-17-air-battery-case-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-expected-to-have-battery-case-due-to-worse-battery-life.2456433/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:24:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-17-air-battery-case-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's rumored iPhone 17 Air model will have "worse" battery life compared to previous iPhone models, according to a <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-plans-iphone-release-schedule-shakeup-new-styles">paywalled <em>The Information</em></a> report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iPhone-17-Air-Size-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993585" /><br/>
In internal testing, Apple determined that the percentage of users who will be able to use the iPhone 17 Air for a full day without needing to recharge the device throughout the day will be between 60% and 70%, according to the report. For other iPhone models, the report said that metric is apparently between 80% and 90%.<br/>
<br/>
The reduced battery life is due in part to the iPhone 17 Air's ultra-thin 5.5mm design, which would make it the thinnest iPhone ever.<br/>
<br/>
To mitigate this problem, the report said that Apple is planning to release a battery case as an optional accessory for the iPhone 17 Air.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last released battery cases <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/11/20/apple-new-iphone-11-battery-cases/">for the iPhone 11 lineup</a>, followed by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo/">since-discontinued MagSafe Battery Pack</a> for iPhone 12 models and newer. A battery case both protects an iPhone and provides additional battery life as necessary.<br/>
<br/>
The report added that Apple's supply chain is uncertain about how much demand there will be for the iPhone 17 Air, given it will be an all-new model with a unique form factor. As a result, the suppliers are initially only dedicating about 10% of production capacity for the iPhone 17 series to the iPhone 17 Air, according to the report.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-17-air-battery-case-report/">iPhone 17 Air Expected to Have Battery Case Due to &#039;Worse&#039; Battery Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-expected-to-have-battery-case-due-to-worse-battery-life.2456433/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 Available for Lowest Price of the Year so Far at &#36;169, Plus AirPods 4 at &#36;99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/airpods-pro-2-for-lowest-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-available-for-lowest-price-of-the-year-so-far-at-169-plus-airpods-4-at-99.2456430/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 06:44:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/airpods-pro-2-for-lowest-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon has the AirPods Pro 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1XD1ZV3"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a> this weekend, down from &#36;249.00. Free delivery options provide an estimated delivery date of around May 8, while Prime members should get the headphones sooner in most cases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Blue-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895402" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Compared to past sales, this is a match of the best price we've tracked so far in 2025 and it's an overall solid second-best price on the AirPods Pro 2. Amazon also has the AirPods 4 available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a> during this sale, an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1XD1ZV3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Other Amazon discounts include record low prices on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/11-gen-ipad-50-discounts/">11th generation iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/apple-watch-series-10-299-amazon/">Apple Watch Series 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/amazon-150-off-m4-macbook-air/">M4 MacBook Air</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/m3-ipad-air-at-100-off/">M3 iPad Air</a>. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/airpods-pro-2-for-lowest-price/">AirPods Pro 2 Available for Lowest Price of the Year so Far at &#36;169, Plus AirPods 4 at &#36;99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-available-for-lowest-price-of-the-year-so-far-at-169-plus-airpods-4-at-99.2456430/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Epic Games Victory Over Apple, iPhone 17 Rumors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/top-stories-epic-games-victory/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-epic-games-victory-over-apple-iphone-17-rumors-and-more.2456427/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/top-stories-epic-games-victory/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There's a major shakeup for the App Store in the U.S. this week, with Epic Games winning a major victory that is forcing Apple to make immediate changes in how it works with developers seeking to offer alternative methods for purchasing in-app content and subscriptions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/top-stories-2025-05-03.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000430" /><br/>
This week also saw fresh rumors about the iPhone 17 lineup, while Dan and Hartley talked through all of the current Apple Watch rumors on this week's episode of The MacRumors Show, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Epic Games Wins Major Victory as Apple is Ordered to Comply With App Store Anti-Steering Injunction</h2><br/>
In a sharp rebuke, Judge Yvonne Gongalez Rogers ruled this week that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-anti-steering-injunction-violation/">Apple has been in "willful violation" of her 2021 ruling</a> in the court battle between Apple and Epic Games, with Apple continuing to engage in anti-competitive behavior by limiting how developers can link to alternative to Apple's in-app purchasing system and charging significant fees even on purchases made outside of Apple's ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite_apple_featured.jpg" alt="" width="2140" height="1204" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-754674" /><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-rule-change-appeal/">going to appeal</a>, but in the meantime it must immediately cease charging commissions or fees on purchases made outside of apps and may not restrict developers' abilities to promote alternatives to users.<br/>
<br/>
Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney says the company intends to bring Fortnite back to the U.S. App Store next week, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/epic-games-apple-peace-proposal/">has offered a "peace proposal"</a> that would see Epic drop additional litigation on the issue if Apple extends the changes required by the ruling worldwide. Epic is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/epic-games-webshops-ios-developers/">going to launch Epic Games Store Webshops</a> that will allow other developers to deploy digital storefronts outside of the Apple's App Store.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Pro's Scratch Resistant Anti-Reflective Display Coating Canceled</h2><br/>
While Apple was reportedly aiming to bring an anti-reflective display coating to the iPhone 17 Pro models this year, a reliable source now tells <em>MacRumors</em> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/iphone-17-anti-reflective-coating-canceled/">the plan has been canceled</a> for now as Apple ran into difficulties scaling up the process for the millions of devices it will need to produce.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-display.jpg" alt="" width="1780" height="1001" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965160" /><br/>
Apple has brought anti-reflective nano-texture display options to several recent products like the MacBook Pro and iPad Pro, but so far the iPhone has been limited to a fingerprint-resistant oleophobic coating that still leaves the glass fronts of the devices susceptible to glare.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>All iPhone 17 Models Again Rumored to Feature 12GB of RAM</h2><br/>
We're expecting at least some iPhone 17 models to see an increase in RAM to 12GB from the current 8GB, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/all-iphone-17-models-feature-12gb-of-ram/">new rumor claims that the increase will extend to all four models in the lineup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-on-Desk-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998158" /><br/>
Apple had originally been thought to only include the higher RAM amount in the iPhone 17 Pro Max, though analyst Ming-Chi Kuo indicated last week that it will extend to not only the iPhone 17 Pro and the "iPhone 17 Air," but potentially even the base iPhone 17 if supply chain issues can be overcome. This week's rumor from Digital Chat Station on Weibo claims this will indeed be possible.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Google CEO Suggests iOS 19 Will Feature Built-In Gemini Integration</h2><br/>
While ChatGPT is currently the only third-party AI service integrated into Apple Intelligence on iPhones, Apple has reportedly been open to adding other services, with Google Gemini regarded as the most likely future addition.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/google-gemini.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941761" /><br/>
As part of an ongoing antitrust trial against Google, its CEO Sundar Pichai confirmed that he has held discussions with Apple CEO Tim Cook about Gemini integration and he hopes a deal will be reached by the middle of this year. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/ios-19-google-gemini-integration-likely/">That timing would set the stage for the inclusion of Gemini in iOS 19</a>, set to be introduced at WWDC next month ahead of a public launch in September.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The MacRumors Show: Apple Watch Series 11, Ultra 3, and SE 3 Rumors</h2><br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/the-macrumors-show-series-11-ultra-3-se-3/">latest episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, Dan and Hartley discuss what to expect from the 2025 Apple Watch lineup when new models launch in the fall, with updates for the standard Apple Watch, high-end Apple Watch Ultra, and low-end Apple Watch SE all expected.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/TMRS-144-2025-Apple-Watch-Lineup-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000416" /><br/>
They also look at the latest rumors about iPadOS 19, where a macOS-style menu bar is expected to appear on-screen when the iPad is connected to a Magic Keyboard. The iPhone could also be getting a Stage Manager-like feature when connected to an external display.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/may-1-2025">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/top-stories-epic-games-victory/">Top Stories: Epic Games Victory Over Apple, iPhone 17 Rumors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-epic-games-victory-over-apple-iphone-17-rumors-and-more.2456427/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17: What&#039;s New With the Cameras</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/iphone-17-camera-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-whats-new-with-the-cameras.2456405/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 15:52:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/iphone-17-camera-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We've still got months to go before the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> models come out, but a combination of dummy models and leaks have given us some insight into what we can expect in terms of camera changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-Blue-Feature-Tighter-Crop.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999328" /><br/>
Apple is adding new camera features, and changing the design of the camera bump for some models. You might be skeptical of dummy models, but over the years, they've proven to be a highly accurate reflection of Apple's design changes. It's case makers who suss out the info used for these dummy models, because there's big money in being the first to market with a case for a new device.<br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up everything that we've heard so far about Apple's upcoming camera tweaks.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>All iPhones</h2><br/>
All four of the iPhones coming in 2025 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-more/">are expected to have</a> an upgraded 24-megapixel front-facing camera, which marks a major improvement over the current 12-megapixel front camera.<br/>
<br/>
You'll be able to crop in further on selfies without a loss of quality with that size increase, plus we can also expect better low light performance and more detail in images.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Pro</h2><br/>
For the first time, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a> and Pro Max will have a trio of 48-megapixel lenses, with a 48-megapixel Fusion lens, a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, and a new 48-megapixel Tetraprism Telephoto lens. The new Ultra Wide lens was introduced in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, and the upgraded Telephoto lens will be 2025's standout camera feature.<br/>
<br/>
With 48 megapixels, it will be possible to crop in further on Telephoto images without losing detail, for even closer shots.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-in-Hand-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998328" /><br/>
Apple plans to focus camera marketing on video this year, and the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; models could support 8K video recording, up from 4K in the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models. There might also be support for dual video recording, which would let users record video with both the front and rear cameras at the same time for sharing on social media.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors suggesting the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; models might have a mechanical aperture that will let users adjust the amount of light reaching the lens. Apple has only used fixed apertures to date, but a variable aperture would allow for more customizable images with a shallower depth-of-field.<br/>
<br/>
Along with all of these camera improvements, it looks like there's going to be a major camera redesign. Instead of a square camera bump, Apple's going to turn it into a rectangle. There will be a horizontal camera bar across the back of the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; Max, and it'll house the cameras.<br/>
<br/>
The lenses are still going to be in the same general orientation, apparently, with a triangular setup that packs them close together. The flash, microphone, and the LiDAR sensor will be moved further to the right at the other end of the rectangle. It's not clear why Apple is making this design change.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Air</h2><br/>
Because of interior space constraints, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a> will have just one 48-megapixel Fusion camera. It won't have the room for an Ultra Wide lens or a Telephoto lens, because Apple is making the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; super thin. Rumors suggest it'll be just 5.5mm thick.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Air-Pastel-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999629" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; is getting the same horizontal rear camera bar as the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj;, but it won't be as tall since it only needs to accommodate one lens. The camera lens will be on the left, and the flash and microphone will be on the right.<br/>
<br/>
With just one camera, the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; won't be able to capture spatial video or spatial photos, unless Apple has a new method for using a single-lens camera to capture that kind of footage.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17</h2><br/>
Aside from that 24-megapixel front-facing camera improvement, we haven't heard anything about the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;. The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;'s rear camera seems to look the same as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>'s rear camera, with two lenses in a vertical arrangement at the left side of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-teal.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964610" /><br/>
It doesn't look like the standard &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; will get the same horizontal camera bar that Apple is introducing for the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
We also haven't heard anything about sensor improvements, but that doesn't mean it's not a possibility. The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; is expected to continue to feature a 48-megapixel Fusion lens and a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide lens.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Read More</h2><br/>
For more on all of the features that are coming to the 2025 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup, we have dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a> roundups.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/iphone-17-camera-rumors/">iPhone 17: What&#039;s New With the Cameras</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-whats-new-with-the-cameras.2456405/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Absorbs Tariff Costs While Electronics Prices Surge, But How Long Will It Last?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-future-tariff-costs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-absorbs-tariff-costs-while-electronics-prices-surge-but-how-long-will-it-last.2456401/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:54:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-future-tariff-costs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[During yesterday's earnings call, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that the company's March quarter hadn't been impacted by Trump's tariffs because it was able to build up supply, but it will take a hit in the current quarter that ends in June. While Cook said that Apple had no updates to make on pricing at the current time, it's not clear how long Apple will be able to absorb tariff costs, especially if there are policy changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="2632" height="1480" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965161" /><br/>
<h2 id="apples_current_tariffs">Apple's Current Tariffs</h2><br/>
U.S. President Donald Trump has levied tariffs on almost every country, but there have been so many pauses and so much back and forth on tariff policy that it's tough to keep track of.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, there is a 145 percent total tariff on goods imported from China into the United States. 20 percent of that was put into place earlier this year (the fentanyl tariff), and the other 125 percent is a direct result from "Liberation Day" and retaliatory tariffs put in place in the ongoing trade war with China.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been paying the 20 percent tariff on all products that it imports from China since that tariff was put in place, but Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/apple-tariff-exemptions/">has been exempted</a> from the 125 percent additional tariff. In April, the Trump administration exempted most of Apple's devices, along with computer components, displays, TVs, and more.<br/>
<br/>
There are some Apple products, such as accessories, that are not exempt from the extra 125 percent tariff in China, and Apple is paying the full 145 percent for those.<br/>
<br/>
For all other countries except for China, Trump put a 10 percent tariff in place, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-stock-trump-tariffs/">higher "reciprocal" tariffs</a> on multiple countries where Apple sources device components. Those tariffs ranged from 20 percent to 46 percent, but have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/apple-stock-up-tariff-pause/">subject to a 90-day pause</a> since April 9. The pause does not apply to the baseline 10 percent tariff, so Apple would be paying a 10 percent tariff on goods imported from countries like India, Thailand, Vietnam, and the EU were it not exempt. Apple <em>is</em> exempt from the 10 percent tariff, and it is not paying the reciprocal tariff rates at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>In a nutshell:</strong> Apple is paying a 20 percent tariff for most of the products that it imports from China. For others, like accessories, Apple is paying 145 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's exemption is not a permanent status and the 90-day pause is temporary, so it's unclear how policies might change in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="how_apple_has_mitigated_tariffs_so_far">How Apple Has Mitigated Tariffs So Far</h2><br/>
For the March quarter, Cook said that Apple saw a limited impact from tariffs because the company was able to optimize its supply chain and inventory.<br/>
<br/>
Basically, Apple knew the tariffs were coming, and stockpiled devices in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
Cook said Apple already sources approximately half of the iPhones sold in the United States from India, and the company expects the majority of the iPhones sold in the U.S. in the coming months to have India as their country of origin. Almost all iPads, Macs, Apple Watches, and AirPods sold in the U.S. will be sourced from Vietnam. Sourcing devices from India and Vietnam means Apple doesn't currently have to pay the 20 percent tariff for goods from China, minimizing tariff impact.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="june_quarter_impact">June Quarter Impact</h2><br/>
Apple isn't able to precisely estimate the impact from tariffs in the current quarter because it is "uncertain of potential future actions prior to the end of the quarter" in June.<br/>
<br/>
Cook said that if the current global tariff rates do not change, policies remain the same, and no new tariffs are added, the tariffs will add &#36;900 million to the company's costs. Cook cautioned that this was not an estimate that could be used for future quarters because of "unique factors" benefitting the June quarter, which suggests the impact could be more severe going forward.<br/>
<br/>
If there are policy changes and additional tariffs introduced, it could cost Apple more than &#36;900 million. Cook said that much of the &#36;900 million estimate is from the 20 percent tariff that Apple is paying for goods coming from China. &#36;900 million is less than one percent of Apple's quarterly revenue and under two percent of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales, which is why Apple is able to absorb the current costs. <br/>
<br/>
Cook said that Apple didn't know what would happen with tariffs, and he wasn't able to provide insight beyond June. He did say that Apple would continue to source U.S. devices outside of China, and that Apple's operations team has done "an incredible job around optimizing the supply chain and the inventory," which Apple will continue to do.<br/>
<br/>
Starting today, the U.S. has removed the de minimus exemption that meant goods with a value under &#36;800 were not subject to tariffs. That will impact the refurbished components that Apple receives from China for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> repairs, and Apple will need to tweak its supply chain and procedures to avoid it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="the_section_232_investigation">The Section 232 Investigation</h2><br/>
In mid-April, the Trump administration <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/04/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-ensures-national-security-and-economic-resilience-through-section-232-actions-on-processed-critical-minerals-and-derivative-products/">initiated a Section 232 investigation</a> that will focus on recommendations to reduce dependence on foreign suppliers, and it covers rare earth metals, magnets, semiconductors, and other products that Apple uses.<br/>
<br/>
Depending on the outcome of the Section 232 investigation, Trump could levy additional fees on semiconductors and equipment for manufacturing semiconductors, along with critical minerals. New tariffs on semiconductors would impact Apple.<br/>
<br/>
The Section 232 investigation spans several months and we may not see any outcome from it until December 2025, after which Trump will need to decide on a solution. So we could be looking at 2026 for any kind of dedicated semiconductor tariff.<br/>
<br/>
The 90-day tariff pause is shorter term, and Apple's exemption could end at any point.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="manufacturers_already_raising_prices">Manufacturers Already Raising Prices</h2><br/>
Other tech companies and electronic manufacturers that have not been exempted from the current tariffs give us some insight into what might happen if Apple is hit with new tariffs. Several companies have already raised prices, and there's undoubtedly more to come.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>Xbox</strong> - The Xbox Series X is 20 percent more expensive, and it costs &#36;600 instead of &#36;500. Microsoft has also raised prices on other devices.</li><br/>
<li><strong>PlayStation</strong> - The PlayStation 5 Pro is priced at &#36;700, up from &#36;590.</li><br/>
<li><strong>MSI Claw 8</strong> - MSI's handheld PC is &#36;1,000, up from &#36;900. Other products have also gone up in price.</li><br/>
<li><strong>DJI</strong> - DJI's Osmo Pocket 3 camera is now &#36;799, up from &#36;519.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Legion Go S</strong> - Lenovo's Legion Go S is &#36;549, up from &#36;500.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Segway</strong> - Segway upped the price of the Ninebot F3 to &#36;1,000. It was &#36;850 before the tariffs.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Bambu</strong> - The X1 Carbon 3D printer is &#36;1,500, up from &#36;1,200. The new H2D printer, announced right around when tariffs hit, is &#36;2,400, up from &#36;1,900 when it was introduced.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Anycubic Kobra S</strong> - Now &#36;700, up from &#36;550.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Temu and Shein</strong> - Chinese retailers are adding tariff fees to purchases. These companies will be hit hard with the end of the de minimis exemption.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="how_much_could_prices_go_up">How Much Could Prices Go Up?</h2><br/>
When tariffs were first announced, there were a slew of stories suggesting the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/2300-dollar-iphone/">could cost hundreds to thousands of dollars more</a>, but it's doubtful prices would actually increase that much. Consumers wouldn't be willing to pay those kinds of fees, plus Apple has plans to mitigate some of the tariff impact. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is sourcing some components in the United States, including chips from a TSMC factory in Arizona, and it has diversified enough that if Trump lowers tariffs in India, Vietnam, Thailand, and other countries, prices won't increase as much. Apple is also sizable enough that it can negotiate some of its costs down.<br/>
<br/>
Apple can certainly absorb some of the tariff impact as it is doing now, but that's not sustainable long term. With no relief, Apple will need to raise prices, and the question isn't if, but when. It's not likely that we'll see price increases mid-cycle on existing devices, but it is possible we could see a jump in cost with the debut of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> models. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-future-tariff-costs/">Apple Absorbs Tariff Costs While Electronics Prices Surge, But How Long Will It Last?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-absorbs-tariff-costs-while-electronics-prices-surge-but-how-long-will-it-last.2456401/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Available Apple Intelligence Features Highlighted in New Ad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-intelligence-features-ad-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/available-apple-intelligence-features-highlighted-in-new-ad.2456400/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:24:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-intelligence-features-ad-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a "Hands-On with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>" video that walks through all of the current &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features and how to use them.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Hands on with Apple Intelligence Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GGMhQkHCjxo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The video shies away from the unavailable &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features like personalized <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> replies, and instead focuses on what's available now.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Clean Up in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a></li><br/>
 	<li>Mail Summaries</li><br/>
 	<li>Writing Tools</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a></li><br/>
 	<li>ChatGPT integration</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
After delaying the personalized &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features, Apple took down its &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; ads that had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/apple-pulls-iphone-16-ad-more-personal-siri/">highlighted the functionality</a>. Apple originally published ads with unavailable &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features when the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> launched, and now it's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/20/apple-intelligence-siri-lawsuit/">facing lawsuits as a result</a> from customers who expected the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features on their new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; devices.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-intelligence-features-ad-2/">Available Apple Intelligence Features Highlighted in New Ad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/available-apple-intelligence-features-highlighted-in-new-ad.2456400/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Partners With Anthropic for Claude-Powered AI Coding Platform</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-anthropic-ai-coding-platform/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-partners-with-anthropic-for-claude-powered-ai-coding-platform.2456396/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:10:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-anthropic-ai-coding-platform/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Anthropic</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working with Anthropic on an updated version of Xcode that will support AI code writing, editing, and testing, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-02/apple-anthropic-team-up-to-build-ai-powered-vibe-coding-platform">Bloomberg</a></em>. Anthropic is best known for its "Claude" large language model and chatbot that competes with OpenAI's ChatGPT. Claude is well-known for its coding capabilities, beating out other LLMs on programming tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/iu-2-1.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="537" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-755800" /><br/>
The new version of Xcode integrates the Claude Sonnet model, and Apple is slowly rolling it out internally for employees to use. Many companies have started adopting AI coding tools to speed up product development, and Apple can't afford to be behind. <em>Bloomberg</em> says that Apple was initially hesitant to use AI to create software for Apple customers, but advancements in LLMs have made the company more comfortable with expanded AI tools.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's internal version of Xcode has a chat interface for programmers to request code or help with coding, and it is able to test user interfaces and help engineers locate and address bugs.<br/>
<br/>
There's no word yet on whether Apple will eventually launch the software publicly, but if the company's internal testing is successful, it's possible the tool could be provided to third-party developers. Last year, Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/apple-empowers-developers-and-fuels-innovation-with-new-tools-and-resources/">announced Swift Assist</a>, an AI-powered coding companion for Xcode. Swift Assist was supposed to come out in 2024, but like the personalized <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/13/apple-announced-swift-assist-wwdc24-so-where-is-it/">it never materialized</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As it turns out, Apple engineers testing Swift Assist found that it was making up information and could slow down app development in some situations. Apple's work with Anthropic could help with Swift Assist and future tools.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has inked deals with several AI companies. OpenAI's ChatGPT is already integrated into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is working with Google to add support for Gemini, and now there is a partnership with Anthropic. In China, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/14/apple-intelligence-plan-for-china-report/">also working with</a> Baidu and Alibaba on AI.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anthropic/">Anthropic</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-anthropic-ai-coding-platform/">Apple Partners With Anthropic for Claude-Powered AI Coding Platform</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-partners-with-anthropic-for-claude-powered-ai-coding-platform.2456396/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple Watch Series 11, Ultra 3, and SE 3 Rumors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/the-macrumors-show-series-11-ultra-3-se-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-watch-series-11-ultra-3-and-se-3-rumors.2456388/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:27:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/the-macrumors-show-series-11-ultra-3-se-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/2025-apple-watch-lineup-rumors/id1602394741?i=1000705847230">The MacRumors Show</a>, we look at what to expect from the 2025 Apple Watch lineup when new models launch in the fall.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xp2bvRA_0Cs?si=NBR9me9Iqg5NFxFx" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
The Apple Watch Series 11 is anticipated to offer hypertension detection as the device's next major health monitoring advancement, potentially with AI-powered health-coaching features. It is also rumored to offer a new chip and, on cellular models, 5G RedCap connectivity. <br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 is expected to receive these new capabilities, as well as features that came to last year's Series 10 model such as a brighter display with a faster refresh rate and a redesigned metal back to facilitate faster charging. However, iPhone-like satellite connectivity features are rumored to be the biggest upgrade for this year's new Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
The third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> is rumored to feature a "new look," perhaps with an all-new plastic casing to bring down the device's cost. It is also likely to feature different size options, either by reducing the bezels around the display or enlarging the screens similar to the Apple Watch Series 7. It should also feature a new chip and a lower price point.<br/>
<br/>
We also look at the latest rumors about iPadOS 19, where a macOS-style menu bar is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ipados-19-mac-like-menu-bar-rumor/">expected to appear on-screen</a> when the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> is connected to a Magic Keyboard. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> could also be getting a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/ios-19-iphone-stage-manager-rumor/">Stage Manager-like feature</a> when connected to an external display. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> also has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/the-macrumors-show-ipados-19-and-iphone-17-air/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up to hear our discussion about the rumored look of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> "Air" and iPadOS 19's major productivity update.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/18/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-apple-intelligence/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/the-macrumors-show-series-11-ultra-3-se-3/">The MacRumors Show: Apple Watch Series 11, Ultra 3, and SE 3 Rumors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-watch-series-11-ultra-3-and-se-3-rumors.2456388/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Updates iPhone App With Out-of-App Payment Options in U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/spotify-out-of-app-payment-options/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-updates-iphone-app-with-out-of-app-payment-options-in-u-s.2456375/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:57:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/spotify-out-of-app-payment-options/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/spotify-ios-update-web-purchase-link/">planned</a>, Spotify has updated its iPhone app in the U.S. with out-of-app pricing and subscription options for its Premium plans. The latest version of the app is <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spotify-music-and-podcasts/id324684580">now available in the App Store</a>, and the added pricing information is rolling out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Spotify-Premiumer-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000361" /><br/>
Spotify users in the U.S. can now view pricing information for its Individual, Duo, Family, and Student plans directly in the iPhone app, and there are buttons that lead to Spotify's website, where users can complete the payment process.<br/>
<br/>
For many years, Spotify has not allowed users to subscribe to Premium plans directly in its iPhone app, as the company does not want to pay Apple's 30% commission on in-app purchases. That remains the case as of today, but Spotify is now permitted to show buttons and links pertaining to out-of-app payment options, without any limitations.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2025-05-01/following-landmark-court-ruling-spotify-submits-new-app-update-to-apple-to-benefit-u-s-consumers/">shared</a> the following statement today:<blockquote>In a victory for consumers, artists, creators, and authors, Apple has approved Spotify's U.S. app update. After nearly a decade, this will finally allow us to freely show clear pricing information and links to purchase, fostering transparency and choice for U.S. consumers. We can now give consumers lower prices, more control, and easier access to the Spotify experience. There is more work to do, but today represents a significant milestone for developers and entrepreneurs everywhere who want to build and compete on a more level playing field. It's the opening act of a new era, and we could not be more ready for the show.</blockquote>This monumental change comes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-anti-steering-injunction-violation/">after a U.S. judge ordered Apple</a> to immediately allow apps to show this sort of information, as part of a lawsuit filed by Fortnite maker Epic Games. Apple is also no longer permitted to collect a 27% commission on those out-of-app purchases that are initiated through the App Store. Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-updates-u-s-app-review-guidelines-epic/">complied with the order</a>, but the company said it disagrees with the decision and plans to appeal.<br/>
<br/>
The judge enforced these requirements after finding Apple violated a 2021 injunction by imposing too many barriers on out-of-app payment options.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/patreon-ios-app-update-in-app-purchases/">Many other popular iPhone apps</a> will likely be updated with out-of-app subscription buttons and information in the U.S. over the coming days.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/spotify-out-of-app-payment-options/">Spotify Updates iPhone App With Out-of-App Payment Options in U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-updates-iphone-app-with-out-of-app-payment-options-in-u-s.2456375/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Amazon&#039;s Biggest Sale of the Year so Far Has Low Prices on AirPods, iPads, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-2-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-amazons-biggest-sale-of-the-year-so-far-has-low-prices-on-airpods-ipads-and-more.2456373/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:21:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-2-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week had a huge sale across a number of Apple products, offering the best prices of the year so far on AirPods Pro 2, AirPods 4, 11th generation iPad, M3 iPad Air, Apple Watch Series 10, and M4 MacBook Air. All of these record low prices are still live today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Best-Apple-Deals-Feature-0007-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990218" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/airpods-pro-2-pinnk.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000365" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;80 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/airpods-4-99-99-on-amazon/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One of the best deals of the week is on the AirPods Pro 2, which have hit &#36;169.00 on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00, the best price we've tracked so far in 2025. You can also find low prices on AirPods 4 right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/apple-watch-series-10-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000368" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;100 off Apple Watch Series 10 and SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/apple-watch-series-10-299-amazon/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ2NM9S%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Series 10 is available for &#36;100 off this week on Amazon, while the Apple Watch SE is on sale for &#36;80 off. These are both record low prices for each model of the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/11th-gen-ipad-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000370" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off 11th generation iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75TN5F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/11-gen-ipad-50-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75TN5F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ773FRV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ77SG5C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>512GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;599.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon introduced &#36;50 discounts on nearly every 11th generation iPad this week, all hitting new all-time low prices in the process. Prices start at &#36;299.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/m3-ipad-air-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000371" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;100 off M3 iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/m3-ipad-air-at-100-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You'll also find new all-time low prices on nearly every M3 iPad Air this week on Amazon, with &#36;100 off these tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/m4-macbook-air-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000372" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;150 off M4 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/amazon-150-off-m4-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul> <br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZD9NV7L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDDTFLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for a new notebook, Amazon has the M4 MacBook Air available from &#36;849.00 for the 256GB 13-inch model. All of these computers are hitting &#36;150 off across the board, and like the rest of the deals from Amazon this week, they're new all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-2-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Amazon&#039;s Biggest Sale of the Year so Far Has Low Prices on AirPods, iPads, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-amazons-biggest-sale-of-the-year-so-far-has-low-prices-on-airpods-ipads-and-more.2456373/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights Three Benefits of Apple Watch for Kids Without iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-watch-for-your-kids-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-three-benefits-of-apple-watch-for-kids-without-iphones.2456371/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:02:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-watch-for-your-kids-ads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/09/15/apple-watch-se-series-6-family-setup/">watchOS 7 in 2020</a>, parents have been able to pair their iPhone to their child's Apple Watch. Formerly known as Apple Watch Family Setup, and now marketed as <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-watch-for-your-kids/">Apple Watch For Your Kids</a>, this option allows kids to use an Apple Watch with a cellular plan for texting, calling, and location sharing, even if they do not own an iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-2022.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866330" /><br/>
For children, a cellular Apple Watch can be a stepping stone towards an iPhone, and Apple has now marketed that idea in a series of new ads.<br/>
<br/>
On its YouTube channel in Canada, Apple has shared <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pYHxcbocHAE">three</a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAaz1jcwWgs">short</a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9X1NqZAOkBo">videos</a> advertising the benefits of the Apple Watch For Your Kids feature. In each video, a child uses their cellular Apple Watch to text their parents. And in one of the videos, a parent reminds their child who is secretly at a shopping mall that they can see their child's location.<br/>
<br/>
Three key benefits of a cellular Apple Watch for kids: texting, calling, and location sharing.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple Watch with cellular lets your kids text, call and location share, all without their own phone," says each video's description.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pYHxcbocHAE?si=Ahv1hO9QFXL9Y6Ca" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PAaz1jcwWgs?si=7EJ1jHemvuFhwP7P" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9X1NqZAOkBo?si=GMTCRdIB1HNtdU9m" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Apple Watch For Your Kids requires a child to have an Apple Watch Series 4 or newer with watchOS 7 and later, while the parent must have an iPhone XS or later. A cellular Apple Watch is recommended for full functionality, but a limited set of features are available on Apple Watch models with Wi-Fi only.<br/>
<br/>
More details are available on the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-watch-for-your-kids/">Apple Watch For Your Kids page</a>, and in a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109036">support document</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/apple-watch-for-your-kids-ads/">Apple Highlights Three Benefits of Apple Watch for Kids Without iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-three-benefits-of-apple-watch-for-kids-without-iphones.2456371/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 18 Rumors: What to Expect From Apple Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/iphone-18-rumors-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-rumors-what-to-expect-from-apple-next-year.2456362/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:01:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/iphone-18-rumors-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's is continually working with suppliers on successive iPhone models simultaneously, which is why we often get rumored features so far ahead of launch. The iPhone 18 series is no different, and we already have a picture forming of what to expect from Apple's 2026 smartphone lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-ghost-hand.jpg" alt="" width="1785" height="1004" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966100" /><br/>
If you're skipping this year's upcoming iPhone 17 series, or just plain curious about Apple's plans further out, here are the rumored features that we are expecting to see in the iPhone 18 lineup next year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Variable Aperture</h2><br/>
Apple's iPhone 18 Pro models may feature a main camera with a variable aperture, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-18-pro-rumored-camera-upgrade/">according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. This would be a first for the iPhone lineup and could give users more control over how their photos look. Current iPhones  including the iPhone 14 Pro, 15 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro  use a fixed aperture of /1.78 for the 48-megapixel main camera, meaning the lens opening doesn't change and is always fully open when capturing photos.<br/>
<br/>
A variable aperture would allow users to manually adjust how much light enters the lens, similar to how traditional cameras work. This could help in bright lighting conditions, reduce overexposure, and offer more flexibility with depth of field  allowing backgrounds to appear more or less blurred depending on the aperture setting.<br/>
<br/>
That said, iPhones use relatively small image sensors, so the practical impact on depth of field may be limited compared to larger-sensor cameras. Still, the feature could give advanced users more creative control, especially in challenging lighting environments.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>C2 Modem</h2><br/>
Apple plans to include its next-generation C2 modem in the iPhone 18 Pro models, according to supply chain analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/iphone-18-pro-c2-modem-rumor/">Jeff Pu</a>. The chip will succeed the C1 modem, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-unveils-c1/">debuted</a> in the lower-cost iPhone 16e as Apple's first in-house cellular modem. The C2 is expected to bring faster speeds, improved power efficiency, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apples-second-5g-modem-said-to-support-mmwave/">support for mmWave 5G</a> in the United States  a feature missing from the C1.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's modem roadmap is part of a long-term strategy to reduce reliance on Qualcomm, which currently supplies 5G modems for the rest of the iPhone lineup. The company has been working on developing its own cellular chips for years, aiming for deeper integration and greater control over power management and performance.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A20 Chip</h2><br/>
Apple's upcoming A20 Pro chip, set to power the iPhone 18 Pro models, will reportedly be built using TSMC's third-generation 3nm process  the same node expected for the A19 Pro chip in this year's iPhone 17 Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/a19-and-a19-pro-n3p-rumor/">according to analyst Jeff Pu</a>. This suggests that year-over-year performance gains between the A19 Pro and A20 Pro may be modest, at least in terms of raw CPU and GPU improvements.<br/>
<br/>
However, Pu notes that the A20 Pro will feature a more advanced packaging method known as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/a20-chip-still-3nm-rumor/">CoWoS (Chip on Wafer on Substrate)</a>. This technology enables tighter integration between the processor, unified memory, and the Neural Engine, which could potentially enhance performance in AI-related tasks. The shift could be part of Apple's broader push to support on-device Apple Intelligence features in future iPhones, as the company ramps up its machine learning capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Camera Image Sensor</h2><br/>
Samsung is working on a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-18-samsung-camera-sensor-report/">three-layer stacked image sensor</a>, reportedly intended for the iPhone 18. The sensor, referred to as PD-TR-Logic, integrates three layers of circuitry, which would improve camera responsiveness, reduce noise, and increase dynamic range. The leak comes from a source known as "<a href="https://x.com/Jukanlosreve/status/1874358213011005628">Jukanlosreve</a>," who claims the sensor is being developed specifically for Apple's 2026 iPhone lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Sony has long been Apple's sole image sensor supplier, so Samsung's entry would be a big shift in the iPhones camera supply chain. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo in 2024 said he expected Samsung to begin shipping <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/2026-iphone-48mp-camera-sensor-samsung/">48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera sensors</a> to Apple for iPhones as early as 2026, which is when the iPhone 18 Pro models are expected to be released.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Under-Screen Face ID</h2><br/>
Apple may finally introduce under-display Face ID with the iPhone 18 Pro and iPhone 18 Pro Max in 2026, according to updated information from display analyst Ross Young. Young originally said in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/under-display-face-id-to-debut-on-iphone-17-pro/">April 2023</a> that the feature would arrive with the iPhone 17 Pro lineup, but revised that timeline in <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1786098652420911128">May 2024</a>, pushing the expected debut back by a year.<br/>
<br/>
Even with Face ID sensors hidden beneath the display, the Dynamic Island is still expected to remain  though it could shrink in size. Another possibility is that Apple will move to a single punch-hole cutout for the front-facing camera, similar to designs seen on Android flagships like the Pixel 9 or Galaxy S25. The exact implementation remains unclear, and plans could shift again as development continues.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/02/iphone-18-rumors-what-to-expect/">iPhone 18 Rumors: What to Expect From Apple Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-rumors-what-to-expect-from-apple-next-year.2456362/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates U.S. App Review Guidelines Following Epic Games Ruling</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-updates-u-s-app-review-guidelines-epic/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-u-s-app-review-guidelines-following-epic-games-ruling.2456351/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:08:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-updates-u-s-app-review-guidelines-epic/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>App Store Review Guidelines</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the wake of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-anti-steering-injunction-violation/">yesterday's court ruling</a> in the dispute between Apple and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> over Apple's policies restricting developers' ability to inform users about alternatives to making purchases through Apple's in-app purchasing system, Apple has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=9txfddzf">updated</a> its <a href="https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/">App Review Guidelines</a> to comply with the ruling.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Sqaure-Complement.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833993" /><br/>
Apple summarized the changes in an email to developers today:<blockquote>3.1.1: Apps on the United States storefront are not prohibited from including buttons, external links, or other calls to action when allowing users to browse NFT collections owned by others.<br/>
<br/>
3.1.1(a): On the United States storefront, there is no prohibition on an app including buttons, external links, or other calls to action, and no entitlement is required to do so.<br/>
<br/>
3.1.3: The prohibition on encouraging users to use a purchasing method other than in-app purchase does not apply on the United States storefront.<br/>
<br/>
3.1.3(a): The External Link Account entitlement is not required for apps on the United States storefront to include buttons, external links, or other calls to action.</blockquote>Judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers ruled that Apple must immediately comply with the ruling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-rule-change-appeal/">even as the company moves to appeal</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The changes are currently limited to the United States given the scope of the court case, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/epic-games-apple-peace-proposal/">Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney offered a "peace proposal"</a> pledging to drop all remaining litigation against Apple over the issue if Apple were to implement the required U.S. changes on a worldwide basis. Apple has so far given no indication that it is interested in accepting that proposal.<br/>
<br/>
Following the court ruling and with Apple's policy changes, major app developers are already moving to make it easier for users to purchase or subscribe to content outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/spotify-ios-update-web-purchase-link/">Spotify already submitting an app update</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/patreon-ios-app-update-in-app-purchases/">Patreon indicating that it will do so</a>, and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; saying that it will bring Fortnite back to the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store-review-guidelines/">App Store Review Guidelines</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-updates-u-s-app-review-guidelines-epic/">Apple Updates U.S. App Review Guidelines Following Epic Games Ruling</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-u-s-app-review-guidelines-following-epic-games-ruling.2456351/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Submits iOS App Update With Out-of-App Purchase Options</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/spotify-ios-update-web-purchase-link/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-submits-ios-app-update-with-out-of-app-purchase-options.2456338/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:37:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/spotify-ios-update-web-purchase-link/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify today submitted an app update to Apple that will include information on Spotify plan costs and options to subscribe through weblinks without using the in-app purchase system. Spotify will not need to pay a fee to Apple when customers subscribe to the service using alternate payment methods in the Spotify app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/General-Spotify-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810756" /><br/>
In a blog post <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2025-05-01/following-landmark-court-ruling-spotify-submits-new-app-update-to-apple-to-benefit-u-s-consumers/">announcing the changes</a>, Spotify said that yesterday's ruling "delivers the benefits that all consumers deserve around the world," calling it a great day for Spotify users in the United States. Here's what Spotify says consumers will be able to do in the updated Spotify app:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Can finally see how much something costs in our app, including pricing details on subscriptions and information about promotions that will save money;</li><br/>
 	<li>Can click a link to purchase the subscription of choice, upgrading from a Free account to one of our Premium plans;</li><br/>
 	<li>Can seamlessly click the link and easily change Premium subscriptions from Individual to a Student, Duo, or Family plan;</li><br/>
 	<li>Can use other payment options beyond just Apple's payment system--we provide a wider range of options on our website; and</li><br/>
 	<li>Going forward, this opens the door to other seamless buying opportunities that will directly benefit creators (think easy-to-purchase audiobooks)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Spotify said that it's "absurd" that it hasn't been able to offer these "basic services" to customers prior to now, and that "meaningful parts of Apple's anticompetitive barriers" have now been addressed, a change that is "long overdue."<br/>
<br/>
According to Spotify, the decision could "unlock real opportunities for creators building their business and sharing their art with fans through Spotify." Publishers will soon be able to sell their audiobooks through the Spotify platform, for example.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, Patreon, and other app developers are submitting updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> with external purchase options. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-anti-steering-injunction-violation/">has been ordered</a> to allow developers to add links to external purchase options with no fee, "effective immediately."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/spotify-ios-update-web-purchase-link/">Spotify Submits iOS App Update With Out-of-App Purchase Options</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-submits-ios-app-update-with-out-of-app-purchase-options.2456338/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Q2 2025 Earnings Call Takeaways</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-earnings-call-q2-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-q2-2025-earnings-call-takeaways.2456336/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:09:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-earnings-call-q2-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple held its earnings call for the second fiscal quarter of 2025 today (second calendar quarter), announcing revenue of &#36;95.4 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;24.8 billion. During the call, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> spoke about tariffs, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> changes Apple is facing, device sales, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834994" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/Apple-Logo-Cash-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2676" height="1504" /><br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up the most interesting tidbits from the Q2 2025 earnings call below.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>U.S. App Store Changes</h2><br/>
Cook was asked about some of the high-profile legal cases that Apple is facing right now, including the U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes that Apple was ordered to make yesterday, and how those legal cases might impact Apple's services business.<br/>
<br/>
Cook repeated Apple's statement about complying and appealing, and didn't add much more beyond saying that the outcome is unclear.<br/>
<blockquote>The case yesterday, we strongly disagree with it. We've complied with the court's order, and we're going to appeal. In the DoJ case you referenced with Google, that case is ongoing, and I don't really have anything to add beyond that.<br/>
<br/>
We're monitoring these closely. But as you point out, there's risk associated with them. And the outcome is unclear.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tariffs</h2><br/>
Cook said that tariffs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/tim-cook-tariffs-apple/">had a limited impact</a> on the March quarter because Apple was able to optimize its supply chain and inventory. Apple is unable to entirely estimate the impact of tariffs on the June quarter because policies could change, but if everything stays as it is now, the tariffs will add &#36;900 million to Apple's costs.<br/>
<br/>
Cook declined to speak on pricing or whether elevated costs will be passed along to consumers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>US Investment</h2><br/>
Cook said that Apple is sourcing glass and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> modules from the United States, along with purchasing 19 billion chips from 12 states.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Siri Features</h2><br/>
Cook said that Apple is "making progress" on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-intelligence-siri-features-progress/">the personal Siri features</a> that the company announced at WWDC 2024. "We are making progress, and we look forward to getting these features into customers' hands," said Cook.<br/>
<br/>
"It's just taking a bit longer than we thought," Cook added.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Impacting iPhone Sales</h2><br/>
Cook said that during the March quarter, Apple saw year over year performance in countries with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> that was stronger than those countries where &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; was not available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac</h2><br/>
Mac revenue grew 6.7 percent year over year, thanks to the new M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> that came out during the quarter. The Mac install base grew to an all-time high, and Apple saw growth for upgraders and customers new to the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> revenue grew 15.2 percent year over year, with growth in every geographic segment. More than half of customers who purchased an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; were new to the product. Apple debuted the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 11 during the quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wearables, Home and Accessories</h2><br/>
Wearables revenue dropped 4.9 percent year over year due to a difficult compare against the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> in the year-ago quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Services</h2><br/>
Apple's services revenue was up 11.6 percent year over year, an all-time revenue record, with strong performance across all categories. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ set a new record for viewership during the quarter, and paid accounts and paid subscriptions grew double digits year over year. Apple now has more than 1 billion total paid subscriptions.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-earnings-call-q2-2025/">Apple&#039;s Q2 2025 Earnings Call Takeaways</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-q2-2025-earnings-call-takeaways.2456336/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook Explains How Tariffs Are Impacting Apple&#039;s Business</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/tim-cook-tariffs-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-explains-how-tariffs-are-impacting-apples-business.2456334/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:35:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/tim-cook-tariffs-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> today provided some insight into how the tariffs levied by U.S. president Donald Trump have affected its business, and the future impacts that Apple is expecting should tariffs continue.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-16e-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990895" /><br/>
Cook said that tariffs had a limited impact on the March quarter as Apple was able to optimize its supply chain and inventory. Apple can't entirely estimate the impact of tariffs on the June quarter due to uncertainties, but with no changes, the tariffs will add &#36;900 million to Apple's costs. From Apple's earnings call:<blockquote>Now let me walk you through the impacts of tariffs in the March quarter, and give you some color on what we expect for the June quarter. For the March quarter, we had a limited impact from tariffs as we were able to optimize our supply chain and inventory.<br/>
<br/>
For the June quarter, currently, we are not able to precisely estimate the impact of tariffs, as we are uncertain of potential future actions prior to the end of the quarter. However, for some color, assuming the current global tariff rates, policies and applications do not change for the balance of the quarter, and no new tariffs are added, we estimate the impact to add &#36;900 million to our costs. This estimate should not be used to make projections for future quarters, as there are certain unique factors that benefit the June quarter.</blockquote><br/>
Apple is already sourcing more than half of iPhones sold in the United States from India, while Macs, iPads, AirPods, and the Apple Watch come from Vietnam. For the June quarter, Cook said that Apple expects the majority of iPhones sold in the U.S. to have India as a country of origin, while Apple will continue sourcing other products from Vietnam. Apple will source devices from China for the rest of the world.<br/>
<br/>
Cook said that Apple's operational team has "done an incredible job around optimizing the supply chain and the inventory," and that Apple plans to continue to do those things to the degree that it is able to.<br/>
<br/>
The 20 percent tariffs that Trump put in place earlier this year are the tariffs that are primarily impacting Apple, as many Apple products have been exempted from the 125 percent reciprocal tariffs. Some products, though, such as accessories, are subject to the total 145 percent tariffs.<br/>
<br/>
Cook said that he doesn't know what will happen with the Section 232 investigation that will eventually see tariffs applied to semiconductors, a change that will impact Apple.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/tim-cook-tariffs-apple/">Tim Cook Explains How Tariffs Are Impacting Apple&#039;s Business</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-explains-how-tariffs-are-impacting-apples-business.2456334/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook: Apple is &#039;Making Progress&#039; on Apple Intelligence Siri Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-intelligence-siri-features-progress/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-apple-is-making-progress-on-apple-intelligence-siri-features.2456331/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:20:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-intelligence-siri-features-progress/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[During today's earnings call covering the second fiscal quarter of 2025, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> acknowledged the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features that have been delayed. Cook said that Apple needs more time to ensure &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; meets its quality bar, but progress is being made.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Sad-Siri-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994723" /><br/>
<blockquote>With regard to the more personal Siri features we announced, we need more time to complete our work on these features, so they meet our high quality bar. We are making progress, and we look forward to getting these features into customers' hands.</blockquote><br/>
Apple first unveiled the more personalized &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features at WWDC 2024, and rumors suggested that the plan was to introduce them with an update to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. That didn't happen, and Apple earlier this year said that there would be a delay because more time was needed for development.<br/>
<br/>
At this point, the new &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features will be held for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>, and it is not yet clear if they will be in the first &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; release or held for a later update. Apple's delay wording suggested that we could be waiting until 2026 for the functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Behind the scenes, Apple made a number of changes to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; leadership, moving AI chief John Giannandrea <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/siri-management-team-overhaul/">off of the project</a> and instead turning to Mike Rockwell, who handled Vision Pro development.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-intelligence-siri-features-progress/">Tim Cook: Apple is &#039;Making Progress&#039; on Apple Intelligence Siri Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-apple-is-making-progress-on-apple-intelligence-siri-features.2456331/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reports 2Q 2025 Results: &#36;24.8B Profit on &#36;95.4B Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-2q-2025-earnings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reports-2q-2025-results-24-8b-profit-on-95-4b-revenue.2456328/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:36:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-2q-2025-earnings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Jordan Golson</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/apple-reports-second-quarter-results/">announced</a> financial results for the second fiscal quarter of 2025, which corresponds to the first calendar quarter of the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/aapl-2q25-line.jpg" alt="" width="1732" height="784" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000297" /><br/>
For the quarter, Apple posted revenue of &#36;95.4 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;24.8 billion, or &#36;1.65 per diluted share, compared to revenue of &#36;90.8 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;23.6 billion, or &#36;1.53 per diluted share, in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-2q-2024-earnings/">year-ago quarter</a>. Services revenue reached an all-time high during the quarter, while earnings per share set a March quarter record.<br/>
<br/>
Gross margin for the quarter was 47.1 percent, compared to 46.6 percent in the year-ago quarter. Apple's board of directors also authorized an additional &#36;100 billion for share repurchases and declared an increased dividend payment of &#36;0.26 per share, up from &#36;0.25 per share. The dividend is payable May 15 to shareholders of record as of May 12.<blockquote>"Today Apple is reporting strong quarterly results, including double-digit growth in Services," said Tim Cook, Apple's CEO. "We were happy to welcome iPhone 16e to our lineup, and to introduce powerful new Macs and iPads that take advantage of the extraordinary capabilities of Apple silicon. And we were proud to announce that we've cut our carbon emissions by 60 percent over the past decade."</blockquote>As has been the case for over five years now, Apple is once again not issuing guidance for the current quarter ending in June.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/aapl-2q25-pie.jpg" alt="" width="2338" height="1148" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000298" /><br/>
Apple will <a href="http://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">provide live streaming</a> of its fiscal Q2 2025 financial results conference call at 2:00 pm Pacific, and <em>MacRumors</em> will update this story with coverage of the conference call highlights.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Conference call recap ahead...</b><br/>
<!--more--><br/>
<b>1:37 pm</b>: "Our March quarter business performance drove EPS growth of 8 percent and &#36;24 billion in operating cash flow, allowing us to return &#36;29 billion to shareholders," said Kevan Parekh, Apple's CFO. "And thanks to our high levels of customer loyalty and satisfaction, our installed base of active devices once again reached a new all-time high across all product categories and geographic segments."<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:38 pm</b>: Apple's share price is down around 2.5% in after-hours trading following the earnings release, after rising about 0.4% in regular trading earlier today.<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:41 pm</b>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> revenue was up 15.2% year-over-year while Services revenue was up 11.6%, Mac revenue was up 6.7%, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> revenue was up 1.9%. Wearables, Home, and Accessories was the only product category to see a year-over-year revenue decline, dropping 4.9%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:44 pm</b>: On a geographic basis, Japan led the way in revenue increase at 16.5% year-over-year, the rest of Asia Pacific excluding Greater China saw an 8.4% increase, the Americas saw an 8.2% increase, and Europe saw a 1.4% increase. Greater China was the only geographic segment to see a decline at 2.3%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:00 pm</b>: Apple's earnings call should be begining momentarily. On the call should be Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and CFO Kevan Parekh.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:01 pm</b>: The call is opening with an introduction from Suhasini Chandramouli, Apple's head of investor relations, giving the standard notices about forward-looking statements.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:02 pm</b>: Tim is taking over for introductory remarks.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:03 pm</b>: "We are reporting &#36;95.4 billion in revenue, up 5% from a year ago and at the high end of the range we provided last quarter. Diluted earnings per share were &#36;1.65, up 8% year over year and a March quarter record. Services achieved an all-time revenue record, growing 12% over the prior year. Quarterly records were also set in the UK, Spain, Finland, Brazil, Chile, Turkey, Poland, India and the Philippines.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:04 pm</b>: He is also touting the impact Apple is making in the United States, including plans to spend &#36;500 billion over the next four years and expanding facilities in a number of states. A new factory for advanced server manufacturing in Texas will open later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:05 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; revenue was &#36;46.8 billion, up 2% year over year. During the quarter, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> was launched, including Apple's newest in-house designed modem. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and 16 Pro "continue to be a hit with our users."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:06 pm</b>: Mac revenue was &#36;7.9 billion, up 7% year over year. New updates during the quarter included M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> is "the most powerful Mac we've ever shipped."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:06 pm</b>: For &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, revenue was &#36;6.4 billion, up 15% from a year ago. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lineup "continues to help users learn, work, play and go wherever their imaginations take them. The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> with M3 combines powerful performance and exceptional portability." Tim is touting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> across all the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:08 pm</b>: Wearables, Home and Accessories revenue was &#36;7.5 billion, down 5% from a year ago. Apple Watch Series 10 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a> with Active Noise Cancellation, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 with the new hearing health features are some of the flagship items of the category, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> getting a shoutout as well, with that product now a year old.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:08 pm</b>: Two retail stores were opened in the quarter, with a new store in the UAE and India coming during this quarter, plus the online store in Saudi Arabia.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:08 pm</b>: Services reached an all-time revenue record of &#36;26.6 billion, up 12% and reflecting strong performance across all categories.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:09 pm</b>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ set a record for viewership in the quarter, and the new F1 movie starring Brad Pitt hits theaters this summer. &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ has earned more than 2,500 award nominations and 560 wins.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:10 pm</b>: He mentions sports with Friday Night Baseball, MLS Season Pass and Formula 1 on the Apple Sports app.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:10 pm</b>: iOS 18.4 brings &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; to more languages including French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Spanish, Japanese, Korean and Simplified Chinese, as well as localized English in Singapore and India.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:11 pm</b>: "AI and machine learning are core to so many profound features we've rolled out over the years to help our users live a better day. It's why we designed Apple silicon with a neural engine that powers so many AI features across our products and third-party apps. It's also what makes Apple products the best devices for generative AI."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:12 pm</b>: He's touting &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; extensively, but he's also noting that the "more personal <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features" need more time to complete "so they meet our high quality bar. We are making progress and we look forward to getting these features into customers' hands."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:12 pm</b>: Apple continues to make progress on achieving carbon neutrality across the supply chain.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:13 pm</b>: Now he's addressing tariffs. "We had a limited impact in the March quarter, due to optimizations of our supply chain and inventory."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:14 pm</b>: For the June quarter, currently, we are not able to precisely estimate the impact of tariffs, as we are uncertain of potential future actions prior to the end of the quarter. <br/>
<br/>
However, for some color, assuming the current global tariff rates, policies, and applications do not change for the balance of the quarter, and no new tariffs are added, we estimate the impact to add &#36;900 million to our costs. This estimate should not be used to make projections for future quarters, as there are certain unique factors that benefit the June quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:14 pm</b>: "As we look ahead, we remain confident, confident that we will continue to build the world's best products and services, confident in our ability to innovate and enrich our users' lives, and confident that we can continue to run our business in a way that has always set Apple apart."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:15 pm</b>: CFO Kevan Parekh is taking over, noting that there was a headwind of 2.5 percentage points from FX challenges, growing in the majority of markets.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:16 pm</b>: Gross margin was 47.1%, up 20 basis points sequentially, primarily driven by favorable mix. Product gross margin was 35.9%, while services gross margin was 75.7%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:16 pm</b>: Net income was &#36;24.8 billion, diluted earnings per share was &#36;1.64, up 8% year over year and a March quarter record.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:17 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; active install base grew to an all-time high in total and across every geographic segment. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was the top-selling model in the US, urban China, UK, Germany, Australia and Japan. 97% customer satisfaction.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:17 pm</b>: Mac revenue was &#36;7.9 billion, up 7% year over year, with every geographic segment growing year over year. Mac install base grew to an all-time high, with growth for both upgraders and customers new to the Mac. Customer satisfaction was 95% in the US.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:17 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue was &#36;6.4 billion, up 15% year over year, with a new all-time high in user base and more than half of customers purchasing an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; new to the product. Customer satisfaction was 97% in the US.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:18 pm</b>: Wearables, Home and Accessories revenue was &#36;7.5 billion, down 5%, against a difficult compare last year with the launch of the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:19 pm</b>: Services revenue was &#36;26.6 billion, up 12% year over year, comparable to the December quarter's growth rate when negative impact from FX is removed. Paid accounts grew double digits year over year, as did paid subscriptions. More than 1 billion total paid subscriptions.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:19 pm</b>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> active users reached an all-time record, up double digits year over year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:20 pm</b>: In the enterprise, KPMG rolled out &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; for all US employees. Strong Mac performance in enterprise. &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is standard computer for Nubank's thousands of employees.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:21 pm</b>: Regarding cash position, Apple ended the quarter with &#36;133 billion in cash and marketable securities. &#36;98 billion in total debt, with a net cash position of &#36;35 billion. Returned &#36;29 billion to shareholders, including &#36;3.8 billion in dividends and equivalents, and &#36;25 billion through open market repurchases of 108 million Apple shares. &#36;100 billion in share repurchases have been authorized, with dividend increasing to 4% to 26 cents per share, with plans for annual increases in the dividend going forward.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:22 pm</b>: The color provided assumes that global tariff rates remain in effect as of this call, and that the global macro outlook doesn't worsen from today. Color at the total company level is still being provided. June quarter will grow low to mid single digits year over year. Gross margin between 45.5% and 46.5%, which includes estimated &#36;900 million in tariff-related costs. OpEx to be between &#36;15.3 and &#36;15.5 billion. Tax rate around 16%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:22 pm</b>: The Q&A session with analysts is beginning.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:26 pm</b>: Q: Re &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sourcing, you said 50% of US iPhones are currently sourced from India. Is your goal to expand that to 100%? How should we expect that to trend?<br/>
<br/>
A: The existing tariffs that apply to Apple are based on the product's country of origin. For the June quarter, we expect the majority of iPhones sold in the US will have India as their country of origin, and Vietnam to be the country of origin for almost all &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Mac, Apple Watch and AirPods sold in the US. China would continue to be the country of origin for the vast majority of total product sales outside the US.<br/>
<br/>
For the June quarter, most of the tariffs that apply to us, relate to the February IEEPA related tariffs at 20%, for imports to the US of products with China as their country of origin. For 120% tariff, that covers certain categories including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> and some accessories. That brings the total rate in China for those products to 145%.<br/>
<br/>
The vast majority of our products including &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Mac, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Apple Watch and Vision Pro, are currently not subject to the global reciprocal tariffs from April. The Commerce Department has initiated a Section 232 investigation into imports of semiconductors and semiconductor manufacturing equipment and downstream products that contain semiconductors.<br/>
<br/>
For June, we estimate the impact, assuming that the current global tariff rates, policies and applications don't change, to be &#36;900 million. I don't want to predict the mix of production, but wanted to give you clarity for the June quarter on country of origin so you can use that for your modeling.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:27 pm</b>: Q: There were reports that Apple had pulled forward sales into the channel to get ahead of tariffs. Were sell-in and sell-through in the March quarter? Should they be aligned in the March quarter, and do you see any acceleration in hardware purchases or was behavior normal?<br/>
<br/>
A: In terms of pull-forward in demand, if you look at the March quarter, we don't believe that we saw obvious evidence of a significant pull forward in demand in March due to tariffs. If you look at channel inventory from the beginning of the quarter to the end, unit channel inventory was similar, not only for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; but for the balance of our products. You will see that we did build ahead inventory and that's reflected in manufacturing purchase obligations that you'll see on the quarterly filing. I hope that answers all your questions.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:29 pm</b>: Q: If you'd told me on April 2 that your impact of tariffs was only &#36;900 million, that'd be a pretty good outcome given the panic that ensued. I'm surprised it's that low, and I know that you gave a comment about the impact after the June quarter  can you give us an idea, is that a multiple? Can you give any guidance on if it's bigger or smaller or what.<br/>
<br/>
A: I tried to give some information on country of origin which is currently the key factor in determining the tariffs that we're paying. I don't want to predict the future because I'm not sure what will happen with the tariffs, and there is this Section 232 investigation going on. June has the assumptions in it that I mentioned earlier.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:32 pm</b>: Q: With regards to China down 2%, you intuitively would have thought that there would have been an increased nationalism and perhaps it would have been worse than that. The trajectory there improving with subsidies benefited your competitors too. Can it keep improving given the geopolitical tensions?<br/>
<br/>
A: Down 2% in the March quarter, we were roughly flat when you remove headwinds from foreign exchange. Channel inventory at the end of March was similar to where we started the quarter. The subsidies played a favorable impact on the results, it's difficult to estimate the precision as to how much but I think it was positive. Some products are included, some are not. Generally on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, if something is priced above 6,000 RMB, it's not eligible and other products have different rules. I do think it helped, and it's helping others as well I'm sure.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was the key driver of the improvement sequentially. Hopefully that provides some color. The Mac, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Watch are attracting a majority of customers new to that product. That continues to look quite good in China and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was the top two models in urban China, and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; was the top two tablets in urban China. Some positive nuggets there.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:33 pm</b>: Q: Appreciated the transparency around building ahead with inventory, will you continue to do that until we get clarity on the Section 232 investigation, and what's your philosophy on pricing and elevated costs that come through, whether to resellers or end consumers?<br/>
<br/>
A: We are engaged on tariff discussions. We believe in engagement and we will continue to engage. On pricing, we have nothing to announce today, and the operational team has done an incredible job around optimizing the supply chain and the inventory, and we'll continue to do those things to the degree that we can.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:34 pm</b>: Q: On product gross margin, can you provide some color on factors that might have impacted product GM in the quarter, down sequentially on seasonal factors, but year over year decline as well. Any additional color would be helpful.<br/>
<br/>
A: On sequential, we had decrease by 340 basis points sequentially driven by mix, seasonal loss of leverage, and foreign exchange, partially offset by cost savings. Year over year, down 70 BP, driven by a different mix and FX.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:35 pm</b>: Q: Talked about &#36;900 million hit to product sales, what are the benefits to the June quarter and what would the impact be without them?<br/>
<br/>
A: Wouldn't want to go through all of them, but the build-ahead in the manufacturing purchase obligations were helpful.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:36 pm</b>: Q: Do you expect Services growth to remain in the double digit range thorugh the back half of the year and how does Services stack up in the June quarter? <br/>
<br/>
A: Low to mid single-digit improvement year over year, with FX to improve sequentially, but a slight headwind to revenue year over year, but we aren't providing category-levels of color today.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:39 pm</b>: Q: How should investors think about the gross margin trajectory as you source more from the US or other supply chain changes, including in India, how should those go into the cost structure?<br/>
<br/>
A: We're excited about bringing more production to the US, as you know we've been very key in the TSMC project in Arizona and are the largest and first customer getting product out of that. That's the SoC that's coming out of there. We also have glass coming out of the US and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> module. And loads of chips, some 19 billion coming out across 12 states, down to the resistor and capacitor level. Some of that is already built into the margins that Kevan has quoted and we don't forecast beyond the current quarter.<br/>
<br/>
Re margin going forward, every product cycle is different. We've managed gross margin well, we've made good decisions. As we launch new products, they tend to have a higher cost structure than the products they replace. As we introduce new features and technologies, we have a track record of reducing cost structures over the life of the product.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:40 pm</b>: Q: Could you share color around what you have seen in developer behavior in Europe where there has been emergency of alternate app stores for a little more time, anecdotally or in your data, in terms of dev behavior large or small? Any color on what has actually happened?<br/>
<br/>
A: It's embedded in our results. Embedded in the overall company color that was provided. As you know, the digital markets act went into effect in March of last year, so the DMA has been enacted for a bit over a year and there's been alternate app stores for some period of time of that. At this point, in Europe, it's embedded in the actuals. There may be more to come and so forth, but I don't want to predict beyond the current quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:43 pm</b>: Q: Can you update us on your thoughts about your resiliency and redundancy following the changes you've talked about on the supply chain? Where's the supply chain 2-3 years from now and is there risk of export control issues? You quantified a &#36;900 million hit from tariffs, but is there a hit from how you're thinking about demand backdrop holistically?<br/>
<br/>
A: In terms of resiliency and risk, we have a complex supply chain, there's always risk in the supply chain and I wouldn't tell you anything different from that. What we learned some time ago, having everything in one location had too much risk with it. We have, over time, with certain parts of the supply chain, opened up new sources of supply. You could see that kind of thing continuing in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Our best thinking is captured in the outlook we've provided. But the assumptions we made, assume that the global tariff rates and policies remain the same, and that the global macro outlook doesn't worsen from today.<br/>
<br/>
Q: No quantifiable impact on demand to date, where we are over the last month?<br/>
<br/>
A: Our best thinking is reflected in the range we provided.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:44 pm</b>: Q: You made a comment on &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; making an impact on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales in the countries where it was available. Has that continued to play out in the broader number of countries as you've rolled that out?<br/>
<br/>
A: During the March quarter, we saw year over year performance in countries with &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;, it was stronger than those countries where &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; was not available. Many of the upgrades you're referring to rolled out in April, which is Q3.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:45 pm</b>: Q: You've had opinions of consumers reacting to overall macro, and prefaced your guidance with macro remaining consistent... what's the reaction in how consumers are reacting to the macro at this point?<br/>
<br/>
A: I'm not an economist so I start by saying that. From a total company point of view, our results accelerated sequentially to the 5% level and the US is the vast majority of the Americas segment and you can see how the Americas performed during the quarter. I don't want to try to predict what happens in the months from now but I'm quite pleased with the results from Q2.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:47 pm</b>: Q: How should we think about how much CapEx is in R&D, how much is in TSMC, Texas server, any color on the &#36;500 billion in investment?<br/>
<br/>
A: There's lots in all of it, but we're not giving out the exact split. As we expand facilities in different states, Michigan, Texas, California, Arizona, Nevada, Iowa, Oregon, North Carolina, Washington, there will be CapEx and OpEx involved in all of it. Standing up our server manufacturing in Texas will be through a partner, as we do with manufacturing, putting a fair amount in cost of goods sold to do that, some OpEx, some CapEx, so it's a bit of all of it.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:48 pm</b>: Q: A longer term philosophical question, you've spoken about AI on the edge, from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac angle, looking at AI on the edge, are the current smartphone and silicon specs good enough to reach LLM inference, how should we think about the evolution of edge devices here?<br/>
<br/>
A: As you know, we're shipping an LLM on the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; today. There are some of the queries used by our customers are on-device, and others are going to the private cloud where we mimic the security and privacy in the device into the cloud. Others, for world knowledge, use the integration with ChatGPT. We continue to be very excited about the opportunities here, we're very excited about the roadmap, and we are pleased with the progress that we're making.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:51 pm</b>: Q: I won't ask about tariffs. Given that you said new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is taking longer than you thought to deliver, what are some of the learnings you had from those delays, are they related to legacy software stack, organizational factors, or a matter of R&D spending? What are factors investors should look for at WWDC or beyond that Apple can deliver on the promises that it's made?<br/>
<br/>
A: At WWDC, we've talked about a number of different features that would launch with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, we've released a slew of those from writing tools to seamlessly connecting to ChatGPT to image playground, image wand, visual intelligence, making movies of your memories with a prompt, AI-powered photo search, smart replies, priority notifications, the list goes on. Recently, we expanded it into different languages including French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Spanish, Japanese, Korean, Simplified Chinese... but with regard to more personal &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, we just need more time to complete the work so it meets our quality bar. There's not a lot of other reason for it, it's just taking a bit longer than we thought. We are making progress and are extremely excited to get the more personal features out there. <br/>
<br/>
We make significant investments in our R&D, and we are making all the investments we think we need to enable our roadmap.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:52 pm</b>: Q: Hard to ignore some of the very high profile legal cases that touch on Apple, Google antitrust, Epic injunction, do you have ample ways to mitigate some of the negative impacts on Apple Services business that might come about in legal rather than commercial pressures?<br/>
<br/>
A: The case yesterday, we strongly disagree with it. We've complied with the court's order and we're going to appeal. In the Google case, that's ongoing so I don't have anything to add. But as you point out, there is risk associated with them and the outcome is unclear.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:55 pm</b>: Q: I want to go back to the AI strategy a little bit. You talked about building your own foundational models, how important do you think it is for Apple to have its own models and dovetailed with that, how do you think about your data center footprint with Apple spending &#36;3 billion a quarter relative to companies spending multiples of that? How does the strategy play out in your opinion?<br/>
<br/>
A: On the data center side, we have a hybrid strategy. We utilitize third parties in addition to the data center investments that we're making. As I mentioned, in the &#36;500 billion, there's a number of states that we're expanding in, some of those are data center investments. We do plan on making investments in that area and we're not gating it. We invest in the business first. We want to have certain models and we'll partner as well, so I don't view it as an all of one or all of the other, what's on device or what's in the Private Cloud Compute.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:56 pm</b>: Q: With the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; e, internalizing your C1 modem, how do you see that modem strategy playing out?<br/>
<br/>
A: We're excited to ship the first one and get it out there, we love to ship better products from a point of view of focusing on battery life and other things customers want. We've just started on that journey is how I would put it.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:56 pm</b>: The call is concluded!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/apple-2q-2025-earnings/">Apple Reports 2Q 2025 Results: &#36;24.8B Profit on &#36;95.4B Revenue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reports-2q-2025-results-24-8b-profit-on-95-4b-revenue.2456328/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Patreon Planning iOS App Update to Skirt In-App Purchases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/patreon-ios-app-update-in-app-purchases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/patreon-planning-ios-app-update-to-skirt-in-app-purchases.2456324/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 12:56:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/patreon-ios-app-update-in-app-purchases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Patreon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Patreon plans to update its iOS app with new functionality that will allow creators to accept payments from followers without having to pay Apple's in-app purchase fees, a Patreon spokesperson told <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/news/659754/patreon-update-iphone-ios-app-apple-payment-system-ruling">The Verge</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/patreon.jpg" alt="" width="761" height="428" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000288" /><br/>
<blockquote>This is a huge moment for creators and their businesses. The iOS app is the number one platform for fan engagement on Patreon, and we believe this ruling allows creators to get paid without giving Apple 30 percent. As a first step, we will submit an app update for review by Apple to enable payments outside of IAP so creators keep more from iOS based fan payments.</blockquote><br/>
In 2024, Apple forced Patreon to adopt support for the in-app purchase system, which meant that Apple started <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/patreon-in-app-purchase-fees/">taking a 30 percent cut</a> of all payments made to creators. Patreon gave creators the option of increasing their prices in just the iOS app, or absorbing the fee to keep prices the same across all platforms. Creators had to raise prices in the iOS app, lose money to pay Apple's cut, or encourage customers to subscribe on the web.<br/>
<br/>
As of right now, Apple is still collecting a 30 percent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> fee for all memberships purchased via Patreon for iOS, and for other digital goods purchased from Patreon shops.<br/>
<br/>
Patreon does not have a timeline for when it plans to submit its app update with out-of-app payment options, and Apple also hasn't outlined exactly when it will change its &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-anti-steering-injunction-violation/">has been ordered</a> to stop restricting developers from informing customers about purchase options outside of an app in the U.S., and from collecting fees for out-of-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
The court said that it "will not tolerate further delays" and that the ruling, which was issued yesterday, was effective immediately.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patreon/">Patreon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/01/patreon-ios-app-update-in-app-purchases/">Patreon Planning iOS App Update to Skirt In-App Purchases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/patreon-planning-ios-app-update-to-skirt-in-app-purchases.2456324/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
