<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 03:00:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: 10 New Home Screen and Lock Screen Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-home-screen/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-10-new-home-screen-and-lock-screen-features.2430567/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:45:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-home-screen&#038;post_date=1719971135/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple overhauled the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a>, introducing design changes that allow for more customization and personalization. You can put icons where you want, change their size, and give them new colors, plus you can hide apps and swap out your Lock Screen buttons.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Home-Screen-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957461" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything new coming to the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; and Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rearranging_icons">Rearranging Icons</h2><br/>
With &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can rearrange app icons and widgets on your &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; and app pages with space between them, providing a wealth of new layout options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-home-screen-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957464" /><br/>
Apple stuck with a grid system so you can only move app icons within the grid locations, but an icon can be placed anywhere in the grid with empty space around it. That sounds complicated, but with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, if you added a new app to your &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;, it would automatically go to the next open spot.<br/>
<br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can choose where to put it. You can have app icon-sized spaces between apps, full empty rows, and full empty columns. You can't put icons and widgets in places with uneven spacing because of the invisible grid limitation, so keep that in mind.<br/>
<br/>
You can put a single app in the middle of a page, have a row of apps at the top and a row of apps at the bottom, create a column of apps, and more. Apple created this design to allow you to place apps and widgets around wallpapers and arrange them into more useful layouts.<br/>
<br/>
Here's how to move your icons:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or on an app page to initiate wiggle mode.</li><br/>
 <li>Move apps into the desired positions.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on done.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
<h2 id="increase_icon_size">Increase Icon Size</h2><br/>
You can make your app icons bigger in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; by removing the app names. With app names in place, Apple needs space to display them, but removing them opens up a lot of area for a larger icon and folder size. Changing the app size does not change the number of apps that are visible, it simply removes text and uses up that empty space.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/hide-app-labels-home-screen-ios-18.jpg" alt="Home Screen" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954852" /><br/>
With larger icons, you still get a maximum of six icon rows with four icons each, the same that you're limited to when icon names are turned on. To change icon size, follow these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or an app page.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Edit."</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Customize."</li><br/>
 <li>Choose Small to turn on app names, or Large to turn them off.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Note that this setting is universal, so you cannot have small icons on one app page and large icons on a different app page.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="change_widget_size">Change Widget Size</h2><br/>
You can change the size of widgets directly from the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; without having to go into the customization options. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a> now have a white rounded bar in the corner, which you can drag to make them larger or smaller.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-resize-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957465" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or an app page to get into wiggle mode.</li><br/>
 <li>Use a finger to resize the widget to be smaller or larger.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
You are limited to the minimum and maximum size available with any given widget. For example, the Battery widget can be the size of four app icons, six horizontal app icons in two rows, or a square shape that's four icons wide by four icons tall. When you resize the Battery widget, you are limited to those size options, but you don't need to go into the full widget settings to change the size.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Widgets&zwnj; are still added to your &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; and app pages in the same way, though some of the labeling has shifted. Long press and tap on "Edit," then choose the "Add Widget" option. It's one more tap than it was before due to the new customization options.<br/>
<br/>
If an app has a widget, you can also long press on its icon to see widget options right there, turning the app's icon into a widget instead.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_widgets">New Widgets</h2><br/>
Apple added a new Health widget in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; that shows information from the new Vitals feature that's both in the Health app and on Apple Watch. It provides an overview of daily vitals or weekly vitals, plus there's also a new widget for cycle tracking.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-new-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957466" /><br/>
Vitals aggregates information from the Apple Watch to provide a daily readout of how your heart rate, sleep patterns, respiration, and blood oxygen change from day to day and week to week.<br/>
<br/>
There is a new Journal widget as well, with options that provide a writing prompt that you can tap on to open up the app to answer. You can also select a Streaks widget that keeps track of how many days in a row you've used the Journal app.<br/>
<br/>
For the new Training Load feature on Apple Watch, Apple has added a corresponding widget in the Fitness widget section.<br/>
<br/>
In the Home widget section, there are new widgets for electricity usage and electricity rates (a feature coming to select users in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; later this year).<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="dark_mode_icons">Dark Mode Icons</h2><br/>
Apple's built-in apps have both Light and Dark color options in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, which allows you to change the color of your icons when you have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a> turned on. The Dark icons are all redesigned with a black background rather than a white or colored background, which makes them blend in better with the &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; setting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-dark-mode-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956931" /><br/>
You can turn on Dark icons independently of having &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; enabled, so you can leave Light mode on while using the Dark icon option. You can also set icons to an automatic mode, which means they'll change color depending on whether &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; or Light Mode is active.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, it's only Apple's apps that have a Dark option, but third-party developers will presumably also be able to include two color options for their icons when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; launches.<br/>
<br/>
To go along with the &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; icons, Apple also introduced a toggle that makes your wallpaper darker. Here's how to change your icon and wallpaper color:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or an app page.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Edit."</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Customize."</li><br/>
 <li>Select Automatic, Dark, Light, or Tinted, an option described below. This is also the interface used to change app icon size, and darken your wallpaper (the sun icon).</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
The wallpaper option makes your chosen wallpaper a bit darker in color, dimming bright shades when enabled. Tapping toggles Light and Dark modes, with Light being your standard wallpaper color.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="icon_tints">Icon Tints</h2><br/>
In addition to choosing a &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; for your app icons, you can opt to put a tint over all of them, which is an aesthetic that's useful if you want to match a wallpaper.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Home-Screen-Feature-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957459" /><br/>
You cannot change icon colors individually, and the tint changes the shade of <em>all</em> of the icons en masse. You can use an eyedropper to choose a color from your wallpaper, or you can use the two bars to tweak both hue and saturation. Tinting works with all icons because it desaturates and then places a color over the desaturated icon, so you do lose individual colors in app icons and widgets. It's a very monochromatic look.<br/>
<br/>
As with icon size, this is a universal setting so you cannot have different tints for different app pages. Tinting affects not only your app pages and &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;, but also the App Library. To change an icon tint:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or an app page.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Edit."</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Customize."</li><br/>
 <li>Select Tinted and use the sliders to adjust the tint to your ideal color.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
To turn off a tint, follow these same steps and then choose "Light" or "Dark" to get back to the standard app icon colors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hiding_and_locking_apps">Hiding and Locking Apps</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; includes a security feature for locking apps or even hiding them entirely from your &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; and app pages. A locked app requires a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> scan to open, so if someone is using your unlocked <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, they still won't be able to open apps you've disabled.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-lock-apps.jpg" alt="" width="5560" height="3128" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954703" /><br/>
Hiding an app does the same thing as locking it, but goes a step further and removes it from view entirely. You'll only see it in a Hidden folder in the App Library, which also requires authentication to access. Locked and Hidden apps do not show up in searches on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, they're not accessible by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> without authentication, and notifications and alerts like calls from the app are disabled, so they're entirely private without authentication.<br/>
<br/>
The option to lock and hide apps is useful for when you need to hand your phone over to someone for viewing photos, playing games, or similar situations.<br/>
<br/>
For a locked app, there is no sign that it's locked until someone attempts to open it, at which point there's a &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; authentication prompt. For hidden apps, they simply don't show up anywhere except the App Library.<br/>
<br/>
Apps <em>do</em> show up in your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> purchase/download list, but they don't show up in the Settings app. Settings for hidden apps can be accessed in a separate "Hidden Apps" folder that does require authentication to open up. How to lock or hide an app:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the icon of the app that you want to lock or hide.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on "Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;."</li><br/>
 <li>If you want to simply lock an app, tap on "Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;" again. If you want to hide it, choose "Hide and Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;."</li><br/>
 <li>Authenticate with a &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; scan.</li><br/>
 <li>For a locked app, that's it. For a hidden app, you'll see a screen letting you know that you won't get notifications or calls from the app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap "Hide App."</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
To remove the lock on an app, long press again on the icon on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or app page and choose "Don't Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;." You will need to authenticate to turn it off.<br/>
<br/>
To unhide an app, go to the App Library, select the Hidden section, authenticate with &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;, long press on the app icon, and choose "Don't Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or "Unhide App." The first option turns off the lock and keeps the app off of the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;, while the second both turns off the authentication requirement and adds it back to the first available opening on an app page.<br/>
<br/>
If you turn off the lock and do not add it back to the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;, you'll need to find it in the App Library to put it back on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="lock_screen_updates">Lock Screen Updates</h2><br/>
Apple didn't make major changes to the Lock Screen because it was just overhauled with &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, but there are a few updates worth noting.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="rainbow_time_and_other_new_lock_screen_widget_options">Rainbow Time and Other New Lock Screen Widget Options</h3><br/>
With &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, Apple added an option to customize the font and the color of the time on the Lock Screen, and in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, there's a new rainbow color option that adds a variegated rainbow shade for the time. There are no other changes to font or color options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-rainbow-lock-screen-time.jpg" alt="" width="2320" height="1305" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957467" /><br/>
Above the time, you can add a new Journal widget that presents a journaling prompt and opens the app when you tap it.<br/>
<br/>
For widget options, there are new Health app Vitals widgets, and new entries for electricity usage and rates. These match the new &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; widgets.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="quick_buttons">Quick Buttons</h3><br/>
For the first time, you can change the Flashlight and Camera icons on the Lock Screen, picking something more useful or turning them off entirely.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-lock-screen-buttons.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954622" /><br/>
You can choose any Control Center option for the Lock Screen buttons, including Shortcuts, &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj;, Airplane Mode, Remote, Alarm Calculator, Translate, and more. This change ties into a redesign of the Control Center, and it gives you a lot more possibilities for what you can launch from the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is allowing third-party apps to add Control Center icons, so you can also choose from those. Depending on what you pick, you may need to use &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; to authenticate before being able to access an app from the Lock Screen in order to preserve user privacy and keep sensitive data from being easily accessible.<br/>
<br/>
To change your Lock Screen buttons, follow these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press on the Lock Screen after authenticating.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Customize.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Lock Screen.</li><br/>
 <li>From this interface, tap on the "-" icon to remove any apps that are already assigned to those buttons. If you're doing this for the first time, you'll have the Flashlight and Camera apps set to the default, which need to be removed.</li><br/>
 <li>From there, tap on the "+" button and choose a new control to add.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Done in the upper right corner.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="ios_18_wallpaper">iOS 18 Wallpaper</h3><br/>
There are four new &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; wallpaper options in pink, yellow, azure, and purple with a matching darker colored swoop. These all have a Light Mode and a &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; shade customized by Apple, with the &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; featuring a background glow for the darker part of the design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-wallpaper.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957469" /><br/>
You can find the new wallpapers by long pressing on the Lock Screen, and choosing Customize to modify an existing wallpaper or "+" to add a new one entirely.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
More on all of the new features that were added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-home-screen/">iOS 18: 10 New Home Screen and Lock Screen Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-10-new-home-screen-and-lock-screen-features.2430567/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Phil Schiller to Serve as OpenAI Board Observer as Part of iOS 18 AI Agreement</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-schiller-openai-board-observer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-phil-schiller-to-serve-as-openai-board-observer-as-part-of-ios-18-ai-agreement.2430565/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:14:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-schiller-openai-board-observer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Fellow and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> chief <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phil-schiller/">Phil Schiller</a> will take on a board observer position at OpenAI, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-07-02/apple-to-get-openai-board-observer-role-as-part-of-ai-agreement">Bloomberg</a></em>. Apple has been granted an observer role as part of its agreement with OpenAI, which will see ChatGPT integrated into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, and Schiller has been selected for the role.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" /><br/>
A board observer is an informal board position where the participant is able to attend and contribute to board meetings, but is not allowed to vote and has no control. OpenAI has also given a board observer role to Microsoft, so Apple and Microsoft will be on even footing with Schiller's new position.<br/>
<br/>
Given Microsoft's relationship with OpenAI, future board meetings could cover new arrangements between OpenAI and Microsoft, which <em>Bloomberg</em> suggests could cause tension if Schiller is present. Microsoft can request that Schiller be excluded from these meetings, however.<br/>
<br/>
Schiller has not yet attended any OpenAI board meetings and is not set to do so until later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and OpenAI's deal will see <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> able to hand complicated user requests over to ChatGPT with explicit user permission. OpenAI is not paying Apple to integrate ChatGPT in its operating systems, nor is Apple paying OpenAI. No money is being exchanged under the terms of the arrangement at the current time.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-schiller-openai-board-observer/">Apple&#039;s Phil Schiller to Serve as OpenAI Board Observer as Part of iOS 18 AI Agreement</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-phil-schiller-to-serve-as-openai-board-observer-as-part-of-ios-18-ai-agreement.2430565/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Former Apple Lawyer Fined &#36;1.15 Million After Insider Trading Conviction</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/former-apple-lawyer-sec-fine/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/former-apple-lawyer-fined-1-15-million-after-insider-trading-conviction.2430564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:47:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/former-apple-lawyer-sec-fine/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>SEC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Former Apple director of corporate law Gene Levoff has been ordered to pay the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission &#36;1.15 million for insider trading, reports <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/apple-ex-lawyer-ordered-pay-115-million-sec-fine-insider-trading-2024-07-02/">Reuters</a></em>. Late last year, Levoff was sentenced to four years of probation and a fine, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/former-apple-lawyer-insider-trading-no-prison/">avoiding a possible two-year jail sentence</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-767473" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/apple-logo-cash-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1430" height="805" /><br/>
At the time, the fine had not been determined, but the judge presiding over the case handed down a ruling on Tuesday. The judge said that Levoff's violations were "especially egregious" even though he had not been "living excessively."<br/>
<br/>
At Apple, Levoff's role included making sure Apple employees were compliant with the company's insider trading policies, which is why the judge decided that his violation was of particular concern.<br/>
<br/>
Because Levoff was meant to prevent insider trading at Apple, he had access to Apple's earnings results before they were made available to the public. He used the information that he learned to buy Apple shares ahead of better-than-expected results, and to sell shares when there were weaker-than-expected earnings. Levoff's shady stock dealings earned him approximately &#36;277,000, while helping him avoid losses of around &#36;377,000.<br/>
<br/>
In July 2015, for example, Levoff knew Apple would not meet analysts' third quarter estimates for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales, so he sold &#36;10 million in Apple stock between July 17 and July 21, which is when Apple's earnings information went live. After the announcement, Apple stock dropped more than four precent.<br/>
<br/>
Levoff worked at Apple from 2011 to 2018, but he abused his insider information between 2011 and 2016. Apple fired him in September 2018 after the authorities contacted the company about Levoff's dealings. In June 2022, Levoff <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/01/former-apple-lawyer-pleads-guilty-insider-trading/">pleaded guilty</a> to six counts of securities fraud for insider trading. Federal prosecutors pushed for jail time to deter other corporate executives from insider trading, but the judge did not feel that it was necessary because Levoff was fired and is no longer be able to practice law.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sec/">SEC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/former-apple-lawyer-sec-fine/">Former Apple Lawyer Fined &#36;1.15 Million After Insider Trading Conviction</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/former-apple-lawyer-fined-1-15-million-after-insider-trading-conviction.2430564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second macOS Sonoma 14.6 Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta.2430550/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 10:13:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming macOS 14.6 update to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its launch. Today's public beta comes two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/">released the first public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
No new Mac features were found in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 developer betas, so it is not clear what might be included. With Apple now working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, development on &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; is beginning to wrap up so it's likely a bug fix update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta-2/">Apple Releases Second macOS Sonoma 14.6 Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta.2430550/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second Public Beta of iOS 17.6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-6.2430549/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 10:12:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to public beta testers, with the betas coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-6/">initial iOS and iPadOS 17.6 developer betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
The new additions Apple promised for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented at this point, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no features were discovered in the developer betas.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple now shifting its focus to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also seeded the second public betas of upcoming watchOS 10.6 and tvOS 17.6 updates. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-2/">Apple Releases Second Public Beta of iOS 17.6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-6.2430549/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Leak Confirms Four iPhone 16 Models With Same A18 Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-models-a18-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leak-confirms-four-iphone-16-models-with-same-a18-chip.2430548/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:48:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-models-a18-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Code discovered in Apple's backend by <a href="https://x.com/nicolas09F9">Nicolás Alvarez</a> and shared with <em>MacRumors</em> confirms Apple's plans to release four <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models this year, and it indicates that the devices will all have the same A-series chip. There are mentions of new model numbers that are not associated with existing iPhones, and that have the numbering scheme Apple uses for its flagship devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935160" /><br/>
The code includes the following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> identifiers:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>iPhone17,1</li><br/>
 	<li>iPhone17,2</li><br/>
 	<li>iPhone17,3</li><br/>
 	<li>iPhone17,4</li><br/>
 	<li>iPhone17,5</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
All five start with the same number, which suggests that Apple plans to use the same chip for them. With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, which have different chips, the internal identifiers have separate numbers.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; - &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;,4</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus - &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;,5</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> - &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;,1</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max - &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;,2</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models have the A16 Bionic chip that was first used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro models, which had corresponding model numbers of &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;,2 for the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;,3 for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max have the A17 Pro chip, hence the 16,x identifier.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's iPhones typically tie identifier to chip. Everything with the A16 chip has an identifier that starts with 15, and prior devices that had an A15 chip all had an identifier starting with 14. The same goes for the 13,x identifier (A14), and the 12,x identifier (A13).<br/>
<br/>
So if Apple sticks with the identifier numbering scheme it has used for years, all four &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have the same chip, and that's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">in line with rumors</a> and prior leaks. We've heard several rumors that the devices will share a chip, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed/">earlier code leak in March</a> also confirmed the shared identifiers.<br/>
<br/>
Note that there are five model numbers listed, and only four are likely to be associated with the upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup. The fifth could potentially be a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, but there's no way to determine what that device is at this time.<br/>
<br/>
While we do expect all four &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models to use a new A18 chip, Apple could still differentiate between the standard models and the Pro models, even giving the chips separate A18 and A18 Pro names. Apple could use A18 chips with a smaller number of GPU cores (either binned or disabled) for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, while saving chips with a better GPU for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> lineup.<br/>
<br/>
It would make sense for all four &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models and a future &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; to all have the same A18 chip because of the Apple Intelligence features set to debut in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. Apple Intelligence requires a high-powered chip for the AI features to run on-device. At this time, only the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max are able to use Apple Intelligence, and Apple likely wants to make sure all future devices have the power required for machine learning and artificial intelligence tasks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-models-a18-chip/">Apple Leak Confirms Four iPhone 16 Models With Same A18 Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leak-confirms-four-iphone-16-models-with-same-a18-chip.2430548/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Resident Evil 7 Debuts on iPhone 15 Pro, iPad, and Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/resident-evil-7-iphone-15-pro-ipad-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/resident-evil-7-debuts-on-iphone-15-pro-ipad-and-mac.2430545/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:14:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/resident-evil-7-iphone-15-pro-ipad-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Capcom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of its effort to embrace Apple's latest chips, <a href="https://www.capcom-games.com/apple/en-us/">Capcom</a> today released <em>Resident Evil 7 biohazard</em> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, and all iPads and Macs with M-series Apple silicon chips. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/resident-evil-7-biohazard/id1640629241">App Store</a>]<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dxfivQCE42o?si=cRywGOpQzC2L-78J" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The game runs natively on Apple silicon with support for cross-progression and universal purchase, letting Apple users play the game across <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac with a single purchase and transfer their saved games between devices.<br/>
<br/>
Capcom notes that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; version of <em>Resident Evil 7 biohazard</em> includes enhanced controls with a new Auto Fire option to assist with touchscreen usability. Hardware controller support is also included for those who want a more console-like experience.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the main <em>Resident Evil 7 biohazard</em> game, the download also includes the <em>Not A Hero</em> DLC add-on, and a Gold Edition upgrade is available with additional DLC content.<br/>
<br/>
The game is a free download that allows for a portion of the game to be played free of charge, with the full main unlock priced at &#36;19.99. The Gold Edition DLC upgrade costs an additional &#36;20.00.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Resident Evil 7 biohazard</em> joins <em>Resident Evil 4</em> and <em>Resident Evil Village</em> as titles from the series available on &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and Mac, with <em>Resident Evil 2</em> also in development.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/capcom/">Capcom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/resident-evil-7-iphone-15-pro-ipad-mac/">Resident Evil 7 Debuts on iPhone 15 Pro, iPad, and Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/resident-evil-7-debuts-on-iphone-15-pro-ipad-and-mac.2430545/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Could Feature Advanced Camera Sensor From Samsung</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-could-feature-samsung-advanced-sensor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-could-feature-advanced-camera-sensor-from-samsung.2430541/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:35:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-could-feature-samsung-advanced-sensor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is testing advanced CMOS image sensors (CIS) from Samsung that could debut in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> later this year, <a href="https://www.thelec.net/news/articleView.html?idxno=4899"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/iphone_12_pro_sensor_shift.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1118" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-764639" /><br/>
Apple is currently conducting a final quality assessment on CMOS image sensors provided by Samsung System LSI, the logic business unit of Samsung, according to the report. These sensors are slated for use in the main camera of the upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;. Historically, Apple has exclusively sourced CIS for its iPhones from Sony, but recent developments are said to indicate a strategic pivot away from the Japanese supplier due to concerns about reliability and the need to incorporate new technologies into its camera system.<br/>
<br/>
The decision to engage Samsung is said to stem from issues Apple faced with Sony last year. Apple requested that Samsung begin the development of new image sensors in 2023 after Sony failed to deliver them in a sufficiently timely manner, which contributed to difficulties in setting a launch date for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>. If Samsung passes the ongoing quality tests, it will be the first time the company supplies an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> CIS. <br/>
<br/>
The new image sensor developed by Samsung features a more advanced three-wafer stack design. These three wafers each house distinct elements: the photodiode, transistors, and analog digital converter logics. In contrast, current and previous &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; image sensors have a two-stack design that combines the photodiode and transistors on a single wafer.<br/>
<br/>
In a CIS, the photodiode converts light into electrical signals, while four transistors are responsible for transferring, amplifying, reading, and erasing these signals. The separation of these components into three wafers allows for higher pixel density, reduced noise, and smaller pixel sizes.<br/>
<br/>
The new technology employs wafer-to-wafer hybrid bonding, which attaches these wafers directly through a copper pad, eliminating the need for signal-transferring bumps. This enables the CIS to be smaller and increases data transfer speeds. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is widely expected to be announced in the fall with new camera features such as a dedicated "Capture" button, a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-could-feature-samsung-advanced-sensor/">iPhone 16 Could Feature Advanced Camera Sensor From Samsung</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-could-feature-advanced-camera-sensor-from-samsung.2430541/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 3: Everything We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know-so-far.2430530/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:14:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know&#038;post_date=1719936885/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Ultra 3, likely to be released in September 2024 alongside the iPhone 16, is expected to offer fewer upgrades compared to its predecessor, the Apple Watch Ultra 2. Keep reading to learn what the rumored changes are.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-blorange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911679" /><br/>
When Apple Watch Ultra 2 debuted last year, key new features included a 50% brighter display, a faster S9 chip, a "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watch without touching the screen, on-device Siri, and increased internal storage. Unfortunately, the next version of the device is unlikely to reach those lofty heights. Here's what the rumors say.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="display_technology">Display Technology</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-night-mode.jpg" alt="" width="1598" height="953" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866222" /><br/>
Initially, it was believed that Apple was working on an Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display, which would provide increased brightness, better contrast, and improved battery efficiency. However, these plans appear to have been postponed indefinitely. Apple worked on microLED display technology for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-still-dedicated-microled-apple-watch-ultra/">several years</a>, but the project was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">scrapped in 2024</a> and there are no current plans for a microLED Apple Watch in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
On the flip side, Apple is rumored to be adopting new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/09/2024-apple-watch-more-power-efficient-display/">low-energy OLED panel technology</a> in new Apple Watch models to further reduce the power consumption of its always-on display. If that's the case, it's unlikely that Apple would use the technology in its latest Series model without also bringing it to its latest Apple Watch Ultra model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-Orange-Alpine-Loop-Action-button-220907_big.jpg.large_.jpg" alt="" width="980" height="402" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862625" /><br/>
The design of the Apple Watch Ultra 3 is likely to remain largely unchanged. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4">recently said</a> that this year's third-generation Apple Watch Ultra will have "roughly the same look as the original." He has previously suggested a totally redesigned "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>" with a thinner case and magnetic bands is coming, but this is likely to be a different model to the Ultra, and he said it would be released "in 2024 or 2025."<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_features">New Features</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-sandy.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864665" /><br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 is likely to include improved health tracking capabilities such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/2024-apple-watch-blood-pressure-sleep-apnea/">blood pressure monitoring and sleep apnea detection</a>, aligning with the rumored features of the Apple Watch Series 10 / X. <br/>
<br/>
The blood pressure monitoring featuring will let users know if their blood pressure is trending upward, and will provide an option for users to note what they were doing when hypertension occurred. Specific blood pressure numbers will not be provided, though. Meanwhile, sleep apnea detection will use sleep history and breathing patterns to estimate whether someone suffers from sleep apnea, with the watch suggesting that users contact a doctor if so.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hardware_updates">Hardware Updates</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-1-1.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866346" /><br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 is expected to have "almost no" new hardware upgrades compared to the Apple Watch Ultra 2, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/kuo-on-apple-watch-ultra-3-hardware/">Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. His phrasing suggests that the rumored blood pressure and sleep apnea detection features will be machine learning / software-based, relying on existing sensors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="colors">Colors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/Apple-Watch-Ultra-Black-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905396" /><br/>
Apple currently offers the Apple Watch Ultra 2, released in September 2023, in the same natural titanium color as the first-generation model. Prior to launch of the second-generation model, some rumors suggested Apple could release a new darker color option. It didn't happen.<br/>
<br/>
However, we know that Apple originally designed a first-generation Apple Watch Ultra with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-apple-watch-ultra-black-prototype-images/">dark ceramic back</a> that was never launched. Moreover, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman in 2023 said it was "theoretically" possible the finish could be released for a later model. Previously, the high-end Edition model of the Apple Watch Series 7 was available with a Space Black titanium case.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="watchos_11">watchOS 11</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Thumb-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955941" /><br/>
One thing we can be sure of is that Apple Watch Ultra 3 will run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, the latest version of the Apple Watch operating system. Apple previewed the software during WWDC in June, and users can expect a range of updates and improvements, such as additional Smart Stack widgets, Check In for Messages and workouts, a Vitals app to view key health metrics, a Translate app, a new Apple Pay feature called Tap to Cash, training load for workouts, additional workout types, more customizable Activity rings, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know/">Apple Watch Ultra 3: Everything We Know So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know-so-far.2430530/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are the macOS Sequoia Features Intel Macs Won&#039;t Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support.2430519/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:24:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When Apple released macOS Monterey in 2021, some key features required a Mac with Apple silicon. The same scenario played out with macOS Ventura in 2022, and then again the following year with the release of macOS Sonoma. With macOS Sequoia set to arrive in the fall, which new features can Intel Mac owners expect to be unavailable to them this time around?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-macOS-Sequoia-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954631" /><br/>
Apple says that macOS Sequoia is compatible with the same Macs as macOS Sonoma, but Apple's fine print reveals that certain new features won't work on Intel machines. If you're still on an Intel Mac, here's what you won't have access to.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954498" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence</a>, a deeply integrated, personalized AI feature set for Apple devices that uses cutting-edge generative artificial intelligence to enhance the user experience, won't be available on Intel Macs. Apple says the advanced features require its M1 chip or later, so if your Mac was released before November 2020, you're out of luck.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-siri-improvements-coming-2025/">These Apple Intelligence Features Won't Be Ready Until 2025</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Live Audio Transcription</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-notes-live-audio-transcription.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957406" /><br/>
Live audio transcription lets you record audio sessions within notes in Apple Notes, and generate live audio transcriptions that can be searched through or combined with other documents, checklists, or documents. According to Apple, support for live audio transcription in the Notes app is limited to machines powered by Apple silicon. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>What Else?</h2><br/>
Surprisingly, nothing! Apple is not withholding any other new features in macOS Sequoia, meaning users with supported Intel Macs will be able to enjoy things like the ability to schedule messages to send later, Reminder integration with Calendars, a new standalone Passwords app, window tiling, and more. Even Apple's latest continuity feature, iPhone Mirroring, works on Intel-based Mac computers that have a T2 Security Chip. For all the details, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS 15 roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
On that note, let's review which Mac models that macOS Sequoia supports. As mentioned above, macOS 15 works with the same Macs as macOS Sonoma. They include:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>MacBook Air (2020 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>MacBook Pro (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Mini (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac Pro (2017 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Pro (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Studio (2022 and later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can check your Mac's model by clicking the Apple in the menu bar and choosing About This Mac. macOS Sequoia is currently in developer beta, with a public beta expected later this month, before Apple's latest Mac software gets a general release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support/">Here Are the macOS Sequoia Features Intel Macs Won&#039;t Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support.2430519/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Boosts A18 Chip Orders in Anticipation of High iPhone 16 Demand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-increases-a18-chip-orders-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-boosts-a18-chip-orders-in-anticipation-of-high-iphone-16-demand.2430516/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:03:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-increases-a18-chip-orders-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is said to have upped its order of next-generation chips from TSMC to between 90 million and 100 million units, following heightened demand expectations for its iPhone 16 series. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Update-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953750" /><br/>
Last year's initial chip order volume for the iPhone 15 series launch is believed to have been in the region of 80-90 million units, suggesting Apple is anticipating higher demand for its 2024 devices in the region of 10 million units, according to Taiwanese outlet <em><a href="https://www.ctee.com.tw/news/20240701700050-430501">CTEE</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
The arrival of Apple Intelligence in iOS 18 is expected to boost initial sales of the devices. One of the reasons is that Apple Intelligence requires at least an iPhone 15 Pro to run, which means owners of last year's iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus will miss out on Apple's new AI features unless they upgrade to an iPhone 15 Pro or plump for one of the iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus were equipped with the A16 Bionic chip – the same chip that was in the iPhone 14 Pro models – whereas the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max featured an A17 Pro chip manufactured using TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, also known as "N3E." N3E is less expensive and has improved yield compared to the previous-generation N3B, according to TSMC.<br/>
<br/>
This year, all four models in the iPhone 16 lineup are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/iphone-16-jump-from-a16-to-a18-chip-rumor/">expected to use A18-branded chips</a> manufactured using the N3E process. Despite switching to N3E, the A18 chip in the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus is likely to adopt the A17 Pro design that was used in the iPhone 15 Pro models. Meanwhile, the iPhone 16 Pro and ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max will likely use a chip branded as an "A18 Pro," which could feature an upgraded Neural Engine with more cores enabling improved AI/machine learning performance. <br/>
<br/>
The standard iPhone 16 models could also be upgraded with 8GB of RAM, up from 6GB in the iPhone 15 models. That would see all four iPhone 16 models offering 8GB of RAM, which Apple has suggested is a minimum requirement for running large-language models (the algorithms that power AI) locally on device, rather than in the cloud.<br/>
<br/>
Based on previous years, Apple is expected to release the iPhone 16 series in the fall, around mid-September. For more information, be sure to check our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> roundups.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-increases-a18-chip-orders-iphone-16/">Apple Boosts A18 Chip Orders in Anticipation of High iPhone 16 Demand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-boosts-a18-chip-orders-in-anticipation-of-high-iphone-16-demand.2430516/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Owners With Faulty Butterfly Keyboards to Get Payouts Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard-payout/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-owners-with-faulty-butterfly-keyboards-to-get-payouts-soon.2430485/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:09:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard-payout/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Butterfly Keyboard Issues</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Two years after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/19/apple-butterfly-keyboard-lawsuit-settlement/">paid &#36;50 million to settle a class-action lawsuit</a> over faulty MacBook butterfly keyboards, funds from the settlement will be going out to affected customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-790219" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1955" height="1100" /><br/>
An update on the <a href="https://www.keyboardsettlement.com">MacBook Keyboard Litigation Settlement website</a> says that the court issued a payment order on June 27, 2024, with payments set to be issued for approved claims by August 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Emails about the lawsuit were sent out in December 2022 to MacBook owners eligible for a payment. MacBook owners who had at least two topcase replacements from Apple within four years of purchase are set to receive a maximum of &#36;395, while customers who had one topcase repair will receive up to &#36;125. Those who had keycap replacements are eligible for up to &#36;50.<br/>
<br/>
Claims were accepted through March 6, 2023, and the settlement was ultimately approved on May 25, 2023. There is no word on why there has been more than a year's delay getting payments sent out to customers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple used butterfly keyboards in Macs between 2015 and 2019, and while the design was updated several times during that four-year period, the butterfly mechanism was prone to failure. Thousands of customers had issues with repeating keys, sticking keys, and keyboard failures due to crumbs, dust, and other issues.<br/>
<br/>
Apple launched <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/06/22/apple-macbook-pro-keyboard-repair-program/">a repair program</a> in June 2018 covering the MacBook, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, and MacBook Pro models manufactured from 2015 on, but it only covered machines for four years after purchase and because butterfly keyboards were replaced with another butterfly keyboard, no permanent fix was available.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the major failure of the butterfly keyboard, Apple swapped back to a scissor switch mechanism. Macs manufactured since late 2019 have had the much more reliable scissor switch keyboard that is able to stand up to wear and tear.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/butterfly-keyboard-issues/">Butterfly Keyboard Issues</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard-payout/">MacBook Owners With Faulty Butterfly Keyboards to Get Payouts Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-owners-with-faulty-butterfly-keyboards-to-get-payouts-soon.2430485/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers.2430470/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:13:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 update to developers, with the second software coming two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-1/">released the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/macOS-Sonoma-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-957372" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what might be included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.6, and no new features were discovered in the first beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers.2430470/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers.2430465/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:08:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the second betas coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-1-to-developers/">first iOS and iPadOS 17.6 betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The features Apple promised for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no major new additions were discovered in the first beta.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers.2430465/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2430467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.3 update to developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The second &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 beta comes over two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may make further improvements to Personas, EyeSight, and other features with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3, as well as implement additional bug fixes. No new features were found in the first &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Releases Second Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2430467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2430466/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:03:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.6 update to developers for testing purposes, with the second beta coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-1-to-developers/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.6 update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.6 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what's included in watchOS 10.6, and with Apple's focus shifting to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, it likely features bug fixes and other minor improvements. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2430466/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers.2430468/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.6 to developers for testing purposes, with the second beta coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.6 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.6.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers.2430468/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone and Apple Watch Likely to Support NFC Multi-Purpose Tap in the Future</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-and-apple-watch-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap-in-the-future.2430457/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:43:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>NFC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhones and Apple Watches could support multiple actions via NFC simultaneously in the future, the NFC Forum today suggested.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/apple-card-via-apple-pay.jpeg" alt="" width="1524" height="909" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-843215" /><br/>
The NFC Forum, the leading standards body for Near Field Communication (NFC) technology, <a href="https://nfc-forum.org/news/2024-07-nfc-forum-defines-next-generation-of-contactless-user-experience-with-multi-purpose-tap/">today published</a> its first overview of NFC Multi-Purpose Tap. The technology, which supports multiple actions with one tap, is designed to bring more convenience to various NFC use cases such as point-to-point receipt delivery, loyalty programs, identification, and total-journey transit ticketing.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is a prominent member of the NFC Forum and likely contributed to the development of the technology. The company first introduced NFC in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6 and original Apple Watch, initially focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, allowing users to make contactless payments. <br/>
<br/>
NFC Multi-Purpose Tap would allow &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to perform multiple transactions with a single tap. For instance, consumers could make payments, log loyalty points, and receive receipts instantaneously. The potential applications are considerable, from retail payments to public transportation, where users could tap their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to pay for a journey, apply discounts, and get travel receipts all at once.<br/>
<br/>
Since Apple is a member of the NFC Forum, it seems highly likely that NFC Multi-Purpose Tap will come to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch at some point in the future. The company often adds support for new NFC functionalities, such as reading NFC tags and facilitating more interactions with a broader range of NFC devices. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nfc/">NFC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/">iPhone and Apple Watch Likely to Support NFC Multi-Purpose Tap in the Future</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-and-apple-watch-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap-in-the-future.2430457/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reclassifies iPhone X, HomePod, and Original AirPods as &#039;Vintage&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reclassifies-iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-as-vintage.2430454/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:52:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>iPhone X</category>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today reclassified the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> X, first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, and first-generation AirPods as "vintage" products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/homepod-feature-blue2.jpg" alt="" width="2144" height="1206" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-788875" /><br/>
The products appeared on Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage and obsolete products list</a> earlier today. Products are considered vintage when Apple stopped distributing them for sale more than five and less than seven years ago. Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers continue to offer repairs for vintage products for up to two more years, subject to parts availability.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X, announced on September 12, 2017 and released on November 3, 2017, represented a significant leap forward in Apple's smartphone design and feature-set. Marking the 10th anniversary of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it introduced several significant changes such as the removal of the home button, allowing for an edge-to-edge 5.8-inch Super Retina OLED display. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, a facial recognition system, replaced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> for authentication, utilizing a TrueDepth camera system in a "notch" that also enabled Animojis. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X was powered by the A11 Bionic chip, featuring the company's first dedicated Neural Engine for enhanced machine learning capabilities, and it supported wireless charging for the first time. Its stainless steel frame and glass back design marked a return to a more premium aesthetic.<br/>
<br/>
The original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was announced on June 5, 2017, at the Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) and released on February 9, 2018. Initially priced at &#36;349, the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was designed to deliver high-quality audio and integrate closely with Apple's ecosystem, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>. It featured a custom-engineered high-excursion woofer and an array of seven beamforming tweeters. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was powered by the Apple A8 chip, enabling real-time acoustic modeling, audio beamforming, and multi-channel echo cancellation. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> came built-in, allowing users to control music playback, manage smart home devices, and access information and services via voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced the original AirPods on September 7, 2016 and officially released them on December 13, 2016, with a retail price of &#36;159. The wireless earbuds were groundbreaking due to their seamless integration with Apple's ecosystem, facilitated by the custom-designed W1 chip. The chip enabled effortless pairing with Apple devices, long battery life, and efficient wireless connectivity. The AirPods also featured optical sensors and motion accelerometers, allowing them to detect when they were in the user's ears, automatically pausing playback when removed. Their unusual, compact design, combined with the convenience of a portable charging case, set a new standard for wireless earphones, making them highly popular and influential in the audio accessory market.<br/>
<br/>
Sometime after becoming "vintage," an Apple product will be reclassified as "obsolete." Apple says it considers a product obsolete once seven years have passed since the company last distributed it for sale. When this happens, Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers no longer offer repairs or other hardware service for it. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/">Apple Reclassifies iPhone X, HomePod, and Original AirPods as &#039;Vintage&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reclassifies-iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-as-vintage.2430454/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fortnite and Epic Games Store Submitted to Apple for iOS Launch in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-and-epic-games-store-submitted-to-apple-for-ios-launch-in-eu.2430446/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 05:37:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Epic Games says it has <a href="https://x.com/epicnewsroom/status/1806819627181219995">submitted</a> the Epic Games Store to Apple for notarization under Apple's alternative app marketplace policy in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite-apple-logo-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-756080" /><br/>
The ‌Epic Games‌ Store will include popular game Fortnite, which means ‌iPhone‌ users in the EU will be able to install and play the title without having to use a cloud gaming service. Epic said it was "targeting the next couple months for the store and Fortnite on iOS in the EU." An ‌iPad‌ version of Fortnite is expected to follow this year.<br/>
<br/>
Fortnite has been banned from the iOS App Store for the last several years due to the legal dispute between Apple and ‌Epic Games‌. An avenue for its return was only made possible after Apple made it possible for iPhone‌ users in the EU to download apps from alternative app marketplaces rather than the App Store, as well as directly from developer websites.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is charging a 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee per year for apps installed outside of the ‌App Store‌ (and in the ‌App Store‌ for developers who opt in to the new terms and also still choose to use Apple's system), but there are no ‌App Store‌ commissions or in-app fees. While Apple is waiving fees for the first one million installs, the 0.50 per user fee will cost app developers like ‌Epic Games‌ a notable amount of money, especially given that Epic will often be charged twice – once for its app marketplace and once again for every Fortnite install. <br/>
<br/>
Epic CEO Tim Sweeney has been critical of Apple's App Store changes to bring its policies in line with the Digital Markets Act (DMA). Sweeney has <a href="https://x.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1750589570880516402">described</a> the changes as a "devious new instance of malicious compliance," and called Apple's charges "junk fees." The European Commission last week formally announced its preliminary view that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">Apple's App Store policies are in breach of the DMA</a>. The Commission also said it would open a new non-compliance procedure against Apple over concerns that its contractual requirements for third-party app developers and app marketplaces, including its Core Technology Fee, "fall short of ensuring effective compliance with Apple's obligations under the DMA."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/">Fortnite and Epic Games Store Submitted to Apple for iOS Launch in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-and-epic-games-store-submitted-to-apple-for-ios-launch-in-eu.2430446/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
