<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:11:44 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 M4 Mac Mini: What We Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m4-mac-mini-what-we-know.2427154/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:28:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini&#038;post_date=1716424106/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>M4 Mac mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working to refresh the entire Mac lineup with chips in the M4 series, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> could get an update as soon as late 2024. Apple is expected to skip the M3 chip, going straight from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> to M4.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946149" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Mini-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything that we know about the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; refresh so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple hasn't changed the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; design in many years, and there are no rumors of a design update coming in 2024. Apple did make the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; a little bit thicker and lighter when it was refreshed in 2023, and that same design will likely be used for the 2024 model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said in January that the "next new &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;" will have the same "form factor design." Back in 2021, there were rumors that Apple was working on a &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; with a plexiglass top and other design changes, but that device never materialized.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; is Apple's smallest, most portable desktop machine, measuring in at 7.75 inches square and 1.41 inches thick. The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; is meant to be connected to a standalone display, keyboard, and mouse, and it does not ship with those accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="m4_chip">M4 Chip</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be equipped with Apple's M4 and M4 Pro chips, with Apple skipping the M3 line entirely and going from &zwnj;M2&zwnj; to M4.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the M4 chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, and the chip is built on a second-generation 3-nanometer technology. Compared to the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, the M4 chip offers 50 percent faster CPU performance and up to 4x faster rendering performance.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 chip features a 10-core CPU and a 10-core GPU. There is a variant of the M4 with a 9-core CPU, but Apple is unlikely to use it in the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, instead reserving it for the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There is also a more advanced 16-core Neural Engine and the GPU supports hardware-accelerated ray tracing, a feature not available with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;. According to Apple, the Neural Engine in the M4 chip is an "absolute powerhouse for AI."<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know details on the M4 Pro because that chip is not expected to come out until later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be refreshed alongside the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/when-to-expect-the-first-m4-macs/">in late 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; was last refreshed in January 2023, so it will be close to two years old when it is updated. Apple often does Mac refreshes in October or November, so we could see the M4 &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; sometime in that timeframe.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/">Apple&#039;s 2024 M4 Mac Mini: What We Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m4-mac-mini-what-we-know.2427154/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Anker&#039;s Latest 3-in-1 Power Bank is a Versatile On-the-Go Powerhouse</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/anker-3-in-1-power-bank/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ankers-latest-3-in-1-power-bank-is-a-versatile-on-the-go-powerhouse.2427150/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:11:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/anker-3-in-1-power-bank&#038;post_date=1716423106/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Anker</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular accessory brand Anker has just launched a new <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1637%3Fvariant%3D43609981550742">10K version of its 3-in-1 power bank</a> that offers up to 30 watts of charging power, a convenient display to quickly view exact charge status, an integrated USB-C cable for both input and output, and built-in folding prongs to recharge directly from a power outlet. I've recently been testing one of these Anker power banks out, and it has become a must-have accessory for my gear bag.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-front.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951991" /><br/>
Competitively priced at &#36;44.99, the 10,000 mAh capacity means I can charge up my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max more than one and a half times while on the go, which is plenty for a long day out or even a weekend trip where easy access to power might be iffy. And the 30-watt charging speed means it'll charge my devices up quickly, meaning spending less time with my phone awkwardly tethered to a power bank while I'm out and about. A quick charge during a lunch or dinner  is more than enough to keep my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> topped off for the remainder of the day.<br/>
<br/>
The integrated USB-C cable is only 10 inches (0.25 meters) long, which feels just about right for hooking things up without having to deal with excess cable. And the fact it's integrated into the power bank means there's no chance of losing or forgetting the cable.<br/>
<br/>
As with some other recent Anker power banks with integrated cables, the cable on this one also serves as a convenient lanyard for the power bank that cleverly uses the USB-C connector to hold things together. It will let you keep the power bank on your wrist if needed, or clipped to a bag or other item to help make it easier to find. While I do have some concerns over the long-term stress of using the USB-C cable in this way, so far in my testing on this bank and similar ones from Anker, the cable and connector have proven durable enough and Anker claims the cable has been tested to withstand at least 10,000 bends over its lifetime.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-prongs.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952002" /><br/>
That integrated cable not only provides for rapid charging of a connected device, but it can also be used to quickly recharge the power bank itself, so if you've got a convenient USB-C power adapter or a laptop available, you can easily charge off of one of those. But even more conveniently, folding prongs allow the power bank to be recharged straight from most power outlets in the U.S., Canada, Japan, and anywhere else that uses Type A/B plugs and sockets. The folding prongs also allow the power bank to easily offer passthrough charging, recharging both the power bank and a connected device simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the integrated USB-C cable and the folding prongs, there's a third power option on this power bank, and that's a dedicated USB-C port that can support both input and output. This of course requires you to bring along a separate cable, but it offers the ability to charge multiple devices simultaneously. Both the integrated cable and the USB-C port support up to 30 watts input and output, although that output will be split if you have multiple devices charging simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-side.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951992" /><br/>
In my testing, it took about two hours to charge the power bank to full from empty, regardless of whether I used the built-in prongs or a USB-C power source of at least 30 watts. Going in the opposite direction, the power bank took about two hours to charge my &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max from 10% up to full, although it reached 80% within 50 minutes with the final 20% taking around 70 minutes at a slower rate to prevent overcharging. Anker's ActiveShield 2.0 temperature monitoring also helps protect devices from damage during charging.<br/>
<br/>
After delivering that 90% charge to my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, the power bank still had 47% of its own battery charge left, so I can get around 1.75 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charges out of a fully charged power bank. With the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max carrying a 4,441 mAh battery and the power bank including a 10,000 mAh battery, you might think it could recharge the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at least twice, but energy loss within the battery cells and circuitry and during the transfer process reduces that figure as is true of any power bank.<br/>
<br/>
Anker has been integrating status displays into a number of recent charging products, and this 3-in-1 power bank is no exception. When it's off, the display is invisible below the glossy surface of the power bank, but while charging other devices, being charged itself, or at the press of a button on the side of the bank, it lights up to show the exact percentage of charge remaining in the power bank. When the power bank  is charging, a green LED next to the display flashes, letting you know at a glance that power is flowing to the bank's battery. The display is easily readable indoors, but does get tougher to read outdoors in bright sunlight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951993" /><br/>
The power bank's overall design is a relatively simple plastic brick shape but with some visual interest in the form of a glossy front with some Anker branding and the display hidden beneath the surface, a matte back with a substantial amount of small regulatory and informational text, and ribbed sides.<br/>
<br/>
Along those sides, you'll find the folding prongs on one side, the attachment point for the integrated cable, the USB-C port, and a button to manually activate the display on the opposite side, and a small bracket where the integrated cable loops through to create the lanyard on the top. The power bank measures approximately 4.25 x 2.0 x 1.2 inches (10.8 x 5.1 x 3.0 cm) and weighs approximately 8.8 ounces (250 grams), so it's reasonably pocketable but a bit on the thick side, so some may feel more comfortable carrying it in a bag rather than in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
The Anker 10K 3-in-1 power bank is available in five colors: Truffle Black, Pastel Pink, Ice Lake Blue, Classic White, and Lilac Purple. It's priced at &#36;44.99 at both <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX4992Z8%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1716409644147">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1637%3Fvariant%3D43609981550742">Anker's own site</a>, with a promo currently offering 15% off the purchase of two select charging accessories. A <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1636%3Fvariant%3D43449917210774">smaller 5K version</a> featuring a similar design but with a slightly different layout of the various features is available for &#36;39.99.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Anker provided MacRumors with the 3-in-1 Power Bank for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anker/">Anker</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/anker-3-in-1-power-bank/">Review: Anker&#039;s Latest 3-in-1 Power Bank is a Versatile On-the-Go Powerhouse</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ankers-latest-3-in-1-power-bank-is-a-versatile-on-the-go-powerhouse.2427150/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Disney Shares Trailer for Immersive Vision Pro Marvel Story</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-marvel-immersive-story/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-shares-trailer-for-immersive-vision-pro-marvel-story.2427144/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:49:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-marvel-immersive-story/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Disney</category>
		<category>Disney Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Disney today shared a trailer for the hour-long interactive and immersive Disney+ Marvel story that is set to come to the Vision Pro on Thursday, May 30.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Marvel Studios' What If...? - An Immersive Story Official Trailer ILM Immersive &amp; Disney+" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lLk-IkPktMo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The Disney+ original from Marvel Studios is connected to the "What If...?" animated series and it will be released as a standalone app for the Vision Pro.<blockquote>What If... You Were Chosen? Step into the Multiverse and harness the power of the Infinity Stones in this reality-bending story from Marvel Studios, ILM Immersive, and Disney+.<br/>
<br/>
The Multiverse is in danger and The Watcher needs your help. Dangerous variants are hunting Infinity Stones and altering the fate of not only their realities, but yours as well. To save the fate of the Multiverse, you'll need to use your own hands to learn mystic spells, defend your allies in epic battles, and more. But, be careful... everything might not be all that it seems.</blockquote>What If...? reimagines events from the Marvel Cinematic Universe in unexpected ways, and on the Vision Pro, fans will be able to step into the lead role of an immersive story that transforms the space around them.<br/>
<br/>
There are multiversal variants of key Marvel characters, chances to learn mystic arts, and an opportunity to harness the power of the Infinity Stones. Marvel says that users will "cross between augmented and virtual reality" while going through the narrative adventure, interacting with the world using their hands and eyes.<br/>
<br/>
The What If...? experience features new and iconic "breathtaking environments" from the Marvel Cinematic Universe, with impressive visuals and support for spatial audio.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro immersive story is set to come out on Thursday, May 30.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney/">Disney</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney-plus/">Disney Plus</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-marvel-immersive-story/">Disney Shares Trailer for Immersive Vision Pro Marvel Story</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-shares-trailer-for-immersive-vision-pro-marvel-story.2427144/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What the Golf on Apple Vision Pro Gains New Levels</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-what-the-golf-levels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-the-golf-on-apple-vision-pro-gains-new-levels.2427133/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 11:00:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-what-the-golf-levels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> game What the Golf? for the Vision Pro is being updated with a slew of new content, with Apple adding 15 new areas with more than 100 spatial levels and 200 challenges to complete.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LaJ5yzmlNYs" title="WHAT THE GOLF? - Apple Vision Pro Launch Trailer" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen data-thumb-size="hqdefault"></iframe></div><br/>
What the Golf? is, as the name suggests, a mini golf game aimed at people who hate golf. The goal is to get the ball to the hole, and every hole has a twist with different game mechanics to overcome.<br/>
<br/>
The game has been around on iOS, iPadOS, and macOS since 2019, plus it launched on Vision Pro in February, but there is new content to play on the Vision Pro this week. Apple says players will experience more cowboys, portals, eggs, crabs, sneaky cardboard boxes, and more.<br/>
<br/>
On the Vision Pro, a pinch of the fingers lets users set up the perfect shot, with the golf course able to be played anywhere in the home. What the Golf? can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> on the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
Other &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; titles getting updates this week include Ridiculous Fishing EX, Tamagotchi Adventure Kingdom, Solitaire Stories, and Fruit Ninja Classic.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-what-the-golf-levels/">What the Golf on Apple Vision Pro Gains New Levels</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-the-golf-on-apple-vision-pro-gains-new-levels.2427133/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;189 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-for-just-189-on-amazon.2427121/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 08:33:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is just &#36;10 higher compared to the all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-gen-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-865510" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's also available in all three aluminum colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This model of the Apple Watch SE launched in September 2022 and remains Apple's most affordable Apple Watch. The Apple Watch SE lacks some of the upgraded features you'll find in some Series 9 or Ultra 2 models, like temperature sensing and ECG functionality, but it will otherwise provide you with all key Apple Watch features, and at the cheapest price possible.<br/>
<br/>
Finally, we're also tracking a solid deal on one model of the Apple Watch Ultra 2. You can get the model with the Green/Grey Trail Loop (S/M) for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;714.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;799.00. Discounts on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 have been rare over the past few weeks, and this deal beats the average discounted price by about &#36;15.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/">Get the 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;189 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-for-just-189-on-amazon.2427121/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>T-Mobile Announces Price Increases for Some Older Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/tmobile-raising-prices-of-some-older-plans/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-announces-price-increases-for-some-older-plans.2427116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:43:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/tmobile-raising-prices-of-some-older-plans/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile today revealed that it will be increasing the monthly prices of some of its older plans in the U.S. by &#36;2 to &#36;5 per line.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/T-Mobile-Generic-Feature-Pink-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951944" /><br/>
Affected customers will receive a text message from T-Mobile if their plan will be receiving a price increase, which will take effect next month. Affected plans appear to include certain T-Mobile ONE, Simple Choice, and Magenta plans.<br/>
<br/>
In its text message to customers, T-Mobile said this is the first time that it has changed the prices of some of its monthly plans in "nearly a decade."<br/>
<br/>
"We're adjusting prices to respond to rising costs, but we are committed to offering low prices and the best value in postpaid wireless," <a href="https://x.com/TMobileHelp/status/1793280595076005912">said T-Mobile</a>, in response to a customer inquiry on social media platform X. "We offer customers more for every dollar they spend than ever before, especially when you consider taxes & fees included."<br/>
<br/>
In an <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tmobile/comments/1cxyp7k/tmobile_to_raise_the_cost_of_older_rate_plans_by/">alleged memo</a> shared with T-Mobile employees today, the carrier said "costs and inflation have risen over the past decade," but touted that it still offers the "lowest prices versus AT&T and Verizon" after the price increases. T-Mobile also ensured that customers on these older plans will retain all of their "benefits and perks."<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile did not immediately respond to our request for more information.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/tmobile-raising-prices-of-some-older-plans/">T-Mobile Announces Price Increases for Some Older Plans</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-announces-price-increases-for-some-older-plans.2427116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M1 MacBook Air Drops to Low Price of &#36;699 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops-to-low-price-of-699-on-amazon.2427113/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:09:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is selling the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5KWB9H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;699.00</a>, down from the original price of &#36;999.00. This is an overall solid second-best price on this version of the MacBook Air, and it's the first time the computer has been in stock at a steep discount in weeks.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850533" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/M1-MacBook-Air-Deals-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2125" height="1195" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The model that Amazon has for &#36;699.00 is the entry-level version with 8GB Unified Memory, an 8-core CPU, a 7-core GPU, and a 256GB SSD. You can get both the Gold and Silver colorways at this price, with delivery as soon as May 24 if you have Amazon Prime.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5KWB9H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple discontinued the M1 MacBook Air back in March, which is why we're seeing such low prices on remaining inventory. The M1 MacBook Air first came out in 2020, so it is four years old at this point, but the Apple silicon chip is still more than adequate for day-to-day tasks. As the M1 MacBook Air is no longer being manufactured, available supply is likely to dry up soon. <br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops/">Apple&#039;s M1 MacBook Air Drops to Low Price of &#36;699 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops-to-low-price-of-699-on-amazon.2427113/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best M4 iPad Pro Cases Currently Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/m4-ipad-pro-cases-covers-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-m4-ipad-pro-cases-currently-available.2427109/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:45:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/m4-ipad-pro-cases-covers-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/m4-ipad-pro-hands-on/">launched</a> its new 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro models on May 15, and there's still a notable lack of cases available for the device. For new owners wanting to protect their pricey investment from scuffs or an accidental drop, we've shortlisted a handful of options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m4-iPad-Pro-Horizontal-Feature-Purple-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950742" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><br/>
<br/>
We would have included the popular <a href="https://www.zugucase.com">Zugu brand</a> in this shortlist, but the company says it is still working on new cases for the M4 iPad Pro and plans to make them available in June or July. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Burton Goods Magnetic Leather Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/burton-goods-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951869" /><br/>
A full-grain leather case with a soft microfiber lining, Burton Goods' slim but pricey case props up to offer multiple viewing angles, and the front flap supports the iPad Pro's sleep/wake function. Equipped with "rare-earth magnets," it also includes a magnetic tab that folds back when not in use and secures an Apple Pencil Pro during transit. There's an internal leather pocket for storing a few documents, and it's topped off with a hand-stitched French hem. The <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-11?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">11-inch</a> model costs &#36;169.95, while the <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-13?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">13-inch</a> version comes in at &#36;179.95. Burton Goods is the recent new venture of Brian Holmes, former Pad & Quill president. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-11?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Burton Goods 11" Magnetic Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-13?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Burton Goods 13" Magnetic Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>Torro Leather Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/torro-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951870" /><br/>
Handcrafted using cowhide leather, Torro's case offers one of the more elegant finishes out of the cases listed here. The inner frame is designed for optimal shock absorption to protect against drops and impacts, while flexible sides aim to make it easy to insert and remove the iPad. It offers three adjustable standing angles, the highest angle for watching videos and the lowest for a stable surface to type or use your Apple Pencil. It also includes an indented groove on the side of the frame for charging Apple Pencil Pro, as well as the USB-C, and 2nd Gen Apple Pencils. Lastly, the front cover supports the iPad's sleep/wake feature. Pre-orders are open for the <a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-11-leather-case-5th-gen">11-inch</a> (&#36;74.99) and <a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-13-leather-case">13-inch</a> (&#36;89.99) versions, and the cases ship by May 30.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-11-leather-case-5th-gen"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Torro 11" Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-13-leather-case"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Torro 13" Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>Otterbox Statement Series Studio Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/otterbox-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951871" /><br/>
The Statement Series Studio Case is slim and features a soft, durable fabric finish. The adjustable stand offers a range of viewing angles for typing, streaming, drawing, or video calls. Its front detaches to save space while working or commuting. There's also decent corner protection to save the screen in the event of a drop, and it includes a dedicated space to store your Apple Pencil. It's a pricey option though: The <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHB2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-blue">11-inch</a> model is &#36;89.95, while the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHC2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-gray">13-inch</a> version is &#36;99.95. Color options are limited to Blue and Gray.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHB2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-blue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Otterbox 11" Studio Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHC2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-gray"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Otterbox 13" Studio Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>UAG Metropolis SE Series Folio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/uag-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951872" /><br/>
The Metropolis SE Series is foremost designed for protection, and has a robust and durable design. Constructed with a lightweight composite material and a soft, impact-resistant core, this case is engineered to withstand significant drops. The corners also provide additional defense against scratches and dents in the event of accidental falls. The folio cover doubles as a stand, and the case also features a smooth PU exterior that's easy to wipe clean, while the Apple Pencil holder supports Apple Pencil pairing and charging. UAG says the case has been tested for medical environments, and can be sanitized with medical-grade wipes and disinfectants repeatedly without compromising its integrity. Available in Cloud Blue, Black, Bordeaux, and Olive colors, the Metropolis SE comes in <a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-11-5th-gen-2024-folio-case/">11-inch</a> (&#36;69.95) and <a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-13-7th-gen-2024-folio-case/">13-inch</a> (&#36;79.99) versions. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-11-5th-gen-2024-folio-case/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">UAG 11" Metropolis SE Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-13-7th-gen-2024-folio-case/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">UAG 13" Metropolis SE Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>ESR Rebound Magnetic Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/esr-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951875" /><br/>
Essentially a cheap version of Apple's Smart Folio, this could serve as an interim option until more quality cases become available. The front trifold cover supports sleep/wake mode and can be folded into two stand positions, one for viewing and another for writing. Unlike Apple's case, the ESR alternative includes a magnetic flap that secures and charges your Apple Pencil while you're on the move. Constructed entirely from TPU (a flexible, rubber-like plastic), it has strong magnets that securely hold the iPad Pro in place. While it may not have the premium feel of higher-end cases, it is lightweight, sturdy, and provides easy access to the tablet's ports and buttons. Both <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHHTHNF">11-inch</a> (&#36;19) and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHKJYVX%2F">13-inch</a> (&#36;24) versions are available.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHHTHNF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">ESR 11" Rebound Magnetic Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHKJYVX%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">ESR 13" Rebound Magnetic Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>Apple Smart Folio Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-smart-folio-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951881" /><br/>
Apple's Smart Folio has been a staple accessory for quite some time, and is known for its elegant design rather than its protective capabilities. It's not cheap, but thanks to some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/new-ipads-added-magnets-smart-folio-case/">additional magnets</a>, the latest version boasts a wider range of viewing angles. The front cover offers sleep/wake functionality and can fold to create a convenient stand. It attaches magnetically to the back, eliminating the need for snaps and providing minimal edge protection. Available in three colors — black, white, and denim blue — the Smart Folio is available in both <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW983ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-black">11-inch</a> (&#36;79) and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWK23ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-white">13-inch</a> (&#36;99) variants.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW983ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-black"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Apple 11" Smart Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWK23ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-white"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Apple 13" Smart Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/m4-ipad-pro-cases-covers-available/">Best M4 iPad Pro Cases Currently Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-m4-ipad-pro-cases-currently-available.2427109/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Speed Up Text Editing With iPhone&#039;s Hidden Trackpad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-text-navigation-iphone-hidden-trackpad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/speed-up-text-editing-with-iphones-hidden-trackpad.2427101/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:52:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-text-navigation-iphone-hidden-trackpad&#038;post_date=1716393160/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Navigating and editing text on your iPhone can sometimes feel cumbersome, especially when trying to precisely place the cursor. Fortunately, Apple has integrated a hidden feature in the virtual keyboard that can make this task much easier. Here's how to unlock and utilize this powerful tool to streamline your text editing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iphone-hidden-trackpad-tip.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951898" /><br/>
The next time you are writing something a little more lengthy and need to go back and change something, simply long-press the space bar, and the on-screen keyboard will transform into a trackpad that you can use to control the cursor. This allows you to navigate quickly through your text, moving the cursor to any desired spot with ease.<br/>
<br/>
But that's not all. If you tap the trackpad with another finger while in this mode, you can also select chunks of text. This dual-functionality makes editing and tweaking text on your iPhone a breeze. Give it a try next time you're typing a message or note.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/hidden-trackpad.jpg" alt="notes" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874097" /><br/>
If you're looking to cut down on the amount of time you spend performing certain actions on your iPhone, there's usually a solution hidden in Apple's mobile operating system. Check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/time-saving-iphone-tips/">20 quick iOS tips</a> that once you start using will make you a lot more time-efficient in the long run.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-text-navigation-iphone-hidden-trackpad/">Speed Up Text Editing With iPhone&#039;s Hidden Trackpad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/speed-up-text-editing-with-iphones-hidden-trackpad.2427101/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Reveals Top 10 Albums of All Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums-of-all-time.2427098/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:28:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums-of-all-time-on-100-best-list/">today unveiled</a> its list of the top 10 albums of all time, with Lauryn Hill's "The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill" securing the number one spot.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-music-100-best-albums.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-950376" /><br/>
The announcement is part of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/apple-music-100-best-albums/">10-day countdown event</a> culminating in a special finale featuring discussions with prominent artists and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; hosts. "The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill," released in 1998, was praised for its impact and relevance. Hill was given an award made of blasted anodized aluminum sourced from recycled Apple products. The top 10 albums list is as follows:<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>1.</strong> The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill (1998), Lauryn Hill</li><br/>
<li><strong>2.</strong> Thriller (1982), Michael Jackson</li><br/>
<li><strong>3.</strong> Abbey Road (1969), The Beatles</li><br/>
<li><strong>4.</strong> Purple Rain (1984), Prince & The Revolution</li><br/>
<li><strong>5.</strong> Blonde (2016), Frank Ocean</li><br/>
<li><strong>6.</strong> Songs in the Key of Life (1976), Stevie Wonder</li><br/>
<li><strong>7.</strong> good kid, m.A.A.d city (2012), Kendrick Lamar</li><br/>
<li><strong>8.</strong> Back to Black (2006), Amy Winehouse</li><br/>
<li><strong>9.</strong> Nevermind (1991), Nirvana</li><br/>
<li><strong>10.</strong> Lemonade (2016), Beyoncé</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The selection process involved &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; experts and a group of artists, songwriters, producers, and industry professionals. This ranking is described as a modern, 21st-century evaluation of the greatest records ever made, created independently of streaming statistics. <br/>
<br/>
In addition to the top 10 list, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; has created 100 audio vignettes to accompany each album on the list, providing context and stories behind the records. These vignettes, along with additional content, are available across &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, <a href="http://apple.co/100BestRadio">Apple Podcasts</a>, and Apple Books.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums/">Apple Music Reveals Top 10 Albums of All Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums-of-all-time.2427098/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Little Snitch 6 Released for macOS Sonoma With DNS Encryption, Integrated Blocklists, New Traffic Chart, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/little-snitch-6-released-macos-sonoma/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/little-snitch-6-released-for-macos-sonoma-with-dns-encryption-integrated-blocklists-new-traffic-chart-and-more.2427091/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 03:31:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/little-snitch-6-released-macos-sonoma/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Austrian developer Objective Development has announced <a href="https://www.obdev.at/products/littlesnitch/index.html">Little Snitch 6</a>, the latest evolution of its popular firewall and network monitoring utility on the Mac. Whenever an app attempts to connect to a server on the internet, Little Snitch shows a connection alert, allowing you to decide whether to allow or deny the connection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/little-snitch-6.jpg" alt="" width="3072" height="1920" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951856" /><br/>
The key new features include DNS encryption, easier access to blocklists, a redesigned interactive traffic chart, a new Control Center in the menu bar, new hierarchical grouping options in the connection list, new sound notifications, and an overhauled user interface. The full advertised features list is as follows:<blockquote><ul><br/>
    <li>DNS Encryption: Let Little Snitch encrypt your server name queries to shield your online activities from prying eyes.</li><br/>
    <li>Integrated Blocklists: Effortlessly select from a curated list of blocklists. Install them with a single click to add an extra layer of protection against unwanted connections.</li><br/>
    <li>Control Center in Menu Bar: Quickly access essential network information, recent activity charts, and recently blocked connections at a glance, directly from the menu bar.</li><br/>
    <li>Interactive Traffic Chart: Enjoy a redesigned, intuitive real-time traffic chart for a clearer visualization and analysis of network activity.</li><br/>
    <li>Hierarchical Connection Grouping: Group connections by application, domain, server, or country to gain deeper insights into network traffic.</li><br/>
    <li>Advanced Search and Filters: Swiftly locate specific connections or firewall rules with enhanced search capabilities.</li><br/>
    <li>Usage Statistics: Track and optimize your firewall rules based on usage frequency.</li><br/>
    <li>Sound Notifications: Stay informed about network activities through customizable acoustic notifications, just by listening. Make connections not only visible but also audible!</li><br/>
    <li>Rule Groups: Organize firewall rules by topic to conveniently turn related rules on or off together.</li><br/>
    <li>Enhanced Web Application Support: Gain better and more precise control over external connections initiated by websites.</li><br/>
    <li>Improved Firewall Rules: Use of cryptographic code signing identifiers for better process identification, resistant to renaming or moving of apps.</li><br/>
    <li>Simplified Setup: Automatically create rules for installed applications to streamline initial configuration.</li><br/>
    <li>Enhanced Xcode Simulator Support: Enjoy smoother development experiences with improved handling of processes in Xcode's Simulator app.</li><br/>
</ul></blockquote>Little Snitch 6 supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> and is available from the <a href="https://www.obdev.at/products/littlesnitch/index.html">Objective Development website</a> for &#36;59 per single license. Existing users can upgrade at a discounted price starting at &#36;39. <br/>
<br/>
Licenses that have been purchased after January 1, 2024, are already valid for Little Snitch 6 at no additional cost. A free demo mode is also included, which offers full functionality for three hours per session and can be reactivated as often as desired.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/little-snitch-6-released-macos-sonoma/">Little Snitch 6 Released for macOS Sonoma With DNS Encryption, Integrated Blocklists, New Traffic Chart, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/little-snitch-6-released-for-macos-sonoma-with-dns-encryption-integrated-blocklists-new-traffic-chart-and-more.2427091/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Adds Support for Live Activities to Shazam</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/shazam-adds-support-for-live-activities/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-support-for-live-activities-to-shazam.2427090/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 03:21:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/shazam-adds-support-for-live-activities/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Shazam</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added support for Live Activities in Shazam, its free music discovery and identification app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/shazam-for-mac.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-857861" /><br/>
Shazam's Live Activities keep the user updated when searching for music in the background, which is particularly useful when multitasking or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/06/shazam-app-song-identification-apps/">identifying songs in other apps</a>. The last <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/shazam-identifies-songs-other-apps-headphones/">significant update to Shazam</a> arrived in January, allowing users to identify songs from other apps while listening with headphones.  <br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/09/24/apple-shazam-acquisition-finalized/">acquired</a> Shazam in 2018, and has been gradually bringing the app into closer alignment with ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>‌ ever since, offering trials to the streaming service through the app and the ability to sync Shazams directly to ‌&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;‌. <br/>
<br/>
Shazam can be downloaded from the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/shazam-music-discovery/id284993459">App Store for free</a>. It can be accessed through the Control Center on ‌‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>‌‌ and ‌‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>‌‌, through ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>‌ commands, or on the Mac, as well as via widgets. Version 17.11 of Shazam is now available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple opened up its Live Activities API to third-party &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps with the release of iOS 16.1 in 2022, and many developers have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-activities/">since made good use of the feature</a>. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shazam/">Shazam</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/shazam-adds-support-for-live-activities/">Apple Adds Support for Live Activities to Shazam</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-support-for-live-activities-to-shazam.2427090/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next Emoji Coming to iOS Could Include Face With Eye Bags, Shovel, Fingerprint, Splatter and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-emoji-characters/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-emoji-coming-to-ios-could-include-face-with-eye-bags-shovel-fingerprint-splatter-and-more.2427059/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:13:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-emoji-characters/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Emoji</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple adds new emoji to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, and other devices regularly based on updates made to the emoji catalog by the Unicode Consortium, and there are seven new emoji that we could see sometime in late 2024 or early 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Unicode-16-Emoji-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951831" /><br/>
The next emoji characters <a href="https://www.unicode.org/emoji/charts-16.0/emoji-released.html">being considered</a> include face with bags under eyes, fingerprint, leafless tree, root vegetable, harp, shovel, and splatter.<br/>
<br/>
The Unicode Consortium today opened <a href="https://blog.unicode.org/2024/05/unicode-160-beta-review-open.html">the beta review period</a> for Unicode 16, which includes the new emoji characters. The beta period lasts until July 2, and after that, Unicode 16 will see a release and the new characters will be officially approved.<br/>
<br/>
It often takes smartphone makers like Apple several months to create artwork for new emoji characters that are approved, so it is likely we won't see these new emoji until after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> launches. Apple will likely add the new characters sometime around March 2025, around when iOS 18.4 comes out.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last introduced new emoji <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">with the iOS 17.4 update</a> that was released in March 2024. Characters added in iOS 17.4 include lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emoji/">Emoji</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-emoji-characters/">Next Emoji Coming to iOS Could Include Face With Eye Bags, Shovel, Fingerprint, Splatter and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-emoji-coming-to-ios-could-include-face-with-eye-bags-shovel-fingerprint-splatter-and-more.2427059/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Apple Music App to Get Smarter Song Transitions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-apple-music-song-transitions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-apple-music-app-to-get-smarter-song-transitions.2427049/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 14:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-apple-music-song-transitions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> app will gain smarter song transitions, reports <em><a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/05/21/new-music-audio-enhancements-plus-a-mysterious-passthrough-feature-are-coming-at-wwdc">AppleInsider</a></em>. Apple is reportedly testing a new feature called "smart song transitions" that would be an improvement to the current crossfade option that comes into play when transitioning from one song to the next.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-813608" /><br/>
With smart song transitions, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; users will be able to adjust the crossfade duration from 1 to 12 seconds. As it stands, crossfade bridges the gap between songs by lowering the volume of the song that's ending while increasing the volume of the new song, creating a successful transition without the music ever coming to an end.<br/>
<br/>
<em>AppleInsider</em> says that Apple is also working on a new feature called "Passthrough" for &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; and QuickTime Player, but there is no information on what this feature is. The site suggests that it is related to Spatial Audio with Dolby Atmos.<br/>
<br/>
Similarly, Apple is said to be working on a "Spatial Gaming" feature internally, but there are also no details on what this might be.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is set to be unveiled at the Worldwide Developers Conference that will kick off on Monday, June 10.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-apple-music-song-transitions/">iOS 18 Apple Music App to Get Smarter Song Transitions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-apple-music-app-to-get-smarter-song-transitions.2427049/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New &#039;Parkour&#039; Immersive Video Coming to Vision Pro on Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/parkour-immersive-video-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-parkour-immersive-video-coming-to-vision-pro-on-friday.2427043/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:48:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/parkour-immersive-video-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is set to release a new immersive video on the Vision Pro on Friday, with "Parkour" <a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/episode/parkour/umc.cmc.no9u63y3wpn8xl7s23jfia46">labeled as episode two</a> in the "Adventure" series. Episode one is the "Highlining" video that shows highliner Faith Dickey walking across a tightrope 3,000 feet above Norway's fjords.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-adventure-parkour.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951827" /><br/>
A description of the Parkour episode invites Vision Pro wearers to join the "world's leading parkour athletes" as they go on a "gravity-defying trek across the streets and rooftops of Paris."<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that its Adventure series is aimed at immersing Vision Pro users in the world of adventure "like never before." Apple works with pioneering athletes facing extraordinary challenges across the world.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Immersive Video is an entertainment format that features 180-degree 3D 8K video recordings captured with spatial audio. The Vision Pro launched with several Immersive Videos, including Prehistoric Planet, Wild Life, and Alicia Keys: Rehearsal Room, and Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/apple-immersive-video-mls-playoffs/">since added a video</a> highlighting the best of the 2023 MLS Cup Playoffs.<br/>
<br/>
The latest "Parkour" video is set to launch on Friday, May 24.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/parkour-immersive-video-vision-pro/">New &#039;Parkour&#039; Immersive Video Coming to Vision Pro on Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-parkour-immersive-video-coming-to-vision-pro-on-friday.2427043/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Beats Pill Appears in FCC Database Ahead of Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/beats-pill-fcc-database/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-appears-in-fcc-database-ahead-of-launch.2427035/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 10:48:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/beats-pill-fcc-database/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Multiple celebrities have been spotted with a new version of the Beats Pill speaker, and today the device showed up in an FCC database, suggesting that we're getting closer to a potential launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/beats-pill-f1-daniel-ricciardo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949043" /><br/>
FCC filings typically happen just weeks ahead of when a product launches, so we could see this new Beats Pill speaker sometime in June. Apple plans to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">Solo Buds earphones</a> in June, so the Pill could launch around the same timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has clearly provided these Beats Pill speakers to a number of sports stars and celebrities to create hype for it, and the speaker has been seen with basketball star LeBron James, F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo, soccer star Lionel Messi, and Kim Kardashian. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/New-Beats-Pill-iOS-17.5-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949655" /><br/>
Apple has shared no details on the speaker, but it has a pill-shaped design that's similar to the Beats Pill that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">discontinued in 2022</a>. It also includes a lanyard that was not available on prior models, and that's been heavily promoted in the celebrity leaks. Colors will include gold, red, and black, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-beats-pill-ios-17-5/">according to leaked images</a> found when iOS 17.5 was being beta tested. <br/>
<br/>
The new Beats Pill speaker will likely feature USB-C charging, improved Bluetooth, and other similar improvements.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/beats-pill-fcc-database/">New Beats Pill Appears in FCC Database Ahead of Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-appears-in-fcc-database-ahead-of-launch.2427035/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Asks Judge to Dismiss U.S. Antitrust Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-dismiss-antitrust-lawsuit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-asks-judge-to-dismiss-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit.2427033/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 10:36:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-dismiss-antitrust-lawsuit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>DOJ</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Apple vs. DoJ</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today filed a pre-motion letter seeking to dismiss the antitrust case that the United States Department of Justice (DoJ) levied against Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/">back in March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-vs-DOJ-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943221" /><br/>
In the pre-motion letter, Apple says that the government's lawsuit is flawed in multiple ways, and has not successfully alleged that Apple is a monopoly power in the relevant market, proven anticompetitive conduct, or demonstrated consumer harm. From Apple's filing:<br/>
<blockquote>This case lies well beyond the outer limits of antitrust law. A Section 2 Sherman Act claim can move past the pleadings only if the complaint alleges (1) monopoly power in a relevant market; (2) anticompetitive conduct; and (3) anticompetitive effects. [...]<br/>
<br/>
This complaint fails on all three fronts. The Supreme Court has repeatedly held that the type of conduct at the core of this case--namely, Apple's decisions about how and whether to grant third parties access to its platform--does not give rise to Section 2 liability as a matter of law.<br/>
<br/>
The complaint also nowhere connects the restrictions it challenges to any anticompetitive effects in the smartphone market. And regardless, far from being a monopolist, Apple faces fierce competition from well-established rivals, and the complaint fails to allege that Apple has the ability to charge supra-competitive prices or restrict output in the alleged smartphone markets, let alone that it has the market share necessary to establish or infer market power.</blockquote><br/>
The DoJ's lawsuit attempts to establish a narrow market category by arguing that Apple dominates in the U.S. smartphone market and the U.S. "performance smartphone" market, but it's going to be tough to win even with that definition. Apple has 65 percent market share in the U.S. smartphone market and 70 percent in the "performance" category, but a designation of monopoly power typically requires a company to have a higher share of the market. Apple has argued that it should be judged based on its global market share, which is at 20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Apple points out that Supreme Court precedent favors allowing businesses to set the terms and prices of agreements that are entered into with third parties, and these agreements are what the DoJ has targeted in its complaint. The DoJ argues that Apple has restricted messaging apps, digital wallet development, and smart watch integration with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, among other things, and Apple says that historically, courts have rejected antitrust claims involving third party platform access.<br/>
<br/>
Further, Apple suggests that the DoJ has not demonstrated that Apple's conduct has had "anticompetitive effects" on the smartphone market. While the lawsuit claims that Apple design decisions lock consumers into the Apple ecosystem, Apple says that it does not have allegations establishing "a factual link between those decisions and consumers' smartphone purchasing behavior."<br/>
<br/>
Judge Neals, who is overseeing the case, required Apple to file its pre-motion letter to dismiss by today, and the DoJ's response is due on May 30. From there, the two parties will have a conference with Neals. After that, the full motion to dismiss will be filed, but this is not expected until mid-June at the earliest.<br/>
<br/>
The government will need to respond 35 days after Apple files a motion to dismiss, and Apple will need to submit a reply brief 21 days after that. At that point, there may be a hearing, which is not expected to take place until September or later, and a ruling on the motion to dismiss will come late in 2024 or early 2025.<br/>
<br/>
The lawsuit on the whole is going to be a multi-year process with Apple's answer to the initial complaint, discovery, trial, and additional appeals coming if the judge does not grant Apple's motion to dismiss the case at this point. It is unclear how the antitrust case will play out, because the DoJ's aim is to secure a ruling that does not fit with antitrust precedent in order to push antitrust law into new areas.<br/>
<br/>
We have a complete <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/"><strong>Apple vs. the U.S. Department of Justice guide</strong></a> that breaks down the case, the DoJ's argument, and what consumers can expect as the lawsuit progresses.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/doj/">DOJ</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">Apple vs. DoJ</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-dismiss-antitrust-lawsuit/">Apple Asks Judge to Dismiss U.S. Antitrust Lawsuit</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-asks-judge-to-dismiss-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit.2427033/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases tvOS 17.5.1 to Fix Photos Corruption Bug Causing Deleted Images to Reappear</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-releases-tvos-17-5-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-tvos-17-5-1-to-fix-photos-corruption-bug-causing-deleted-images-to-reappear.2427032/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 10:13:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-releases-tvos-17-5-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released tvOS 17.5.1, a minor update to the tvOS 17 operating system that came out last September. tvOS 17.5.1 comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/apple-releases-tvos-17-5/">release of tvOS 17.5</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850424" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/apple-tv-4k-red-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
tvOS 17.5.1 can be downloaded using the Settings app on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>‌. Go to System &gt; Software Update to get the new software. ‌&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;‌ owners who have automatic software updates activated will be upgraded to tvOS 17.5.1 automatically.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to other operating system updates, tvOS updates are often minor in scale, focusing on bug fixes and other small improvements. According to Apple's release notes, the update addresses a bug with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app that could cause deleted images to reappear. <blockquote>This update addresses a rare issue where photos that experienced database corruption could reappear in the Photos library even if they were deleted.</blockquote>Apple fixed the same bug on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">iOS 17.5.1 and iPadOS 17.5.1 updates</a> that came out yesterday.<br/>
<br/>
We don't know what's new in the update, but it may address the same &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; bug that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">fixed in iOS 17.5.1 yesterday</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-releases-tvos-17-5-1/">Apple Releases tvOS 17.5.1 to Fix Photos Corruption Bug Causing Deleted Images to Reappear</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-tvos-17-5-1-to-fix-photos-corruption-bug-causing-deleted-images-to-reappear.2427032/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad 10 vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: Is the &#36;250 Difference Worth It?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide-is-the-250-difference-worth-it.2366555/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 09:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1716319800/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>No Top Comments</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the same design, display size, camera systems, and more, the entry-level <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> is now a formidable rival to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> at a markedly lower &#36;349 price point. With &#36;250 between these two &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lines, how different are they and which should you buy?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/iPad-10-vs-Air-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-870500" /><br/>
Upon the discontinuation of the ninth-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Apple dropped the price of the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; from &#36;449 to &#36;349. This means that the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is now &#36;250 less than the &#36;599 starting price of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; that Apple just released.<br/>
<br/>
The 10th-generation model completes the transformation of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; product lineup toward a flat look with squared-off edges, no home button, and an all-screen design with curved corners. With the exact same display size and identical features like a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> top button, USB-C port, and 5G connectivity, many prospective customers may now be considering a purchase of the standard &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; instead of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; – but there are more differences between the devices than immediately meets the eye. <br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip and double the amount of memory make the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; much more powerful than the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. Combined with a more advanced display in two size options, support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> hover and the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro, a thinner and lighter design, and even a different selection of color options, many users still have good reasons to prefer the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
So should you consider buying the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to save money, or do you need the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; instead? This breakdown serves as a clear way to see all the differences between the two devices.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad&zwnj; (10th Generation, 2022)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; (Sixth Generation, 2024)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>10.9-inch display</td><br/>
 <td>11- or 13-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>sRGB color</td><br/>
 <td>P3 wide color</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Fully laminated display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anti-reflective coating</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A14 Bionic chip</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>8-core CPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>10-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Media Engine<br/>
Hardware-accelerated H.264 and HEVC<br/>
Video decode engine<br/>
Video encode engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 3 for photos</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4 for photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Supports &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; (USB‑C) and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; (first generation)</td><br/>
 <td>Supports &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; (USB‑C) and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Supports Magic Keyboard Folio</td><br/>
 <td>Supports Magic Keyboard</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7mm depth</td><br/>
 <td>6.1mm depth</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;349</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;599</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>477 gram weight</td><br/>
 <td>462 gram or 617 gram weight</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Silver, Pink, Blue, and Yellow</td><br/>
 <td>Available in Space Gray, Starlight, Blue, and Purple</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>64GB or 256GB storage</td><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, or 1TB storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;349</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;599</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
A key difference between the devices is their chips and amount of memory, so if you plan on using your &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; for more demanding tasks like 3D graphic design, advanced photo editing, and gaming, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be the better choice by far. The &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip's dedicated media engine is also be particularly helpful when video editing, and supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a>, Apple's multitasking system for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s display lacks P3 wide color, full lamination, and an anti-reflective coating. While these aspects are unlikely to be major reasons to preference the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, they are worth bearing in mind when trying to justify the &#36;250 leap to the more expensive device. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is also available in an all-new 13-inch size option, which is more suitable for multitasking and using the device as a laptop-replacement, but this pushes the price difference up to &#36;450 – more than the cost of the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; itself. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is marginally thinner and lighter, with differences that are so minor as to be unimportant to most customers, but the more muted tones of its color options may make it more or less appealing based on your personal preferences.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; support is also a key consideration. While the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; supports the first-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with USB-C is a better choice due to easier charging. However, this lacks advanced features like pressure sensitivity, haptic feedback, and barrel roll that you get with the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;'s &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro support. People who plan to use the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; heavily for tasks like note-taking and illustration will undoubtedly have a significantly better experience with the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which supports both the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with USB-C and the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro.<br/>
<br/>
While both devices support external keyboards, they have different strengths. The 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s Magic Keyboard Folio will be better for table-typers, those who prefer function keys, and those who want to easily detatch the keyboard but keep the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; propped up on a surface, while the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;'s Magic Keyboard is better for lap-typers and those who want backlighting.<br/>
<br/>
In theory, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is a more compelling overall package with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, 4GB of additional memory, a dedicated media engine, &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj; for multitasking, a better display, and a much better &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; experience, but in practice, users with basic requirements are unlikely to notice a massive amount of difference between the devices. Unless you have specific need for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;'s added features or its larger display size option, it may be worth saving the &#36;250 and buying the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air/">iPad 10 vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: Is the &#36;250 Difference Worth It?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide-is-the-250-difference-worth-it.2366555/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wallet App Gaining Support for Transit Cards in Paris and Toronto</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-wallet-app-transit-cards-paris-toronto/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-gaining-support-for-transit-cards-in-paris-and-toronto.2427030/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 09:28:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-wallet-app-transit-cards-paris-toronto/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-and-ile-de-france-mobilites-introduce-navigo-for-iphone-and-apple-watch/">announced</a> that the Navigo transit card can be added to the Wallet app starting today, allowing iPhone and Apple Watch users to simply tap their devices to pay for rides on the metro, trains, buses, and more in the Paris, France area.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-Wallet-Paris-Navigo-Transit-Card.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951808" /><br/>
With the Navigo card in the Wallet app, a rider no longer needs to visit a ticket vending machine, or reload the card at retailers. Instead, passes can be purchased directly in the Wallet app on the iPhone, or in the Île-de-France Mobilités app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also announced that real-time transit information for the Paris area will be available in Apple Maps starting this week. This feature will allow riders to view detailed schedules, live departure and arrival times, delays, outages, and any connections required to complete a trip across multiple transit systems.<br/>
<br/>
In related news, it was recently <a href="https://x.com/PRESTOcard/status/1791248521334546928">announced</a> that the PRESTO transit card in the Toronto, Canada area will soon support the Wallet app too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-Wallet-PRESTO-Transit-Card-Toronto.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="574" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951809" /><br/>
In both cities, the transit cards will support Express Mode, meaning that riders can simply hold their iPhone or Apple Watch near a payment reader to pay for their ride, without needing to unlock or wake the device. Express Mode continues to work for up to five hours after an iPhone has run out of battery power.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Thanks, <a href="https://mastodon.social/@apollozhao">Apollo Zhao</a>!</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-wallet-app-transit-cards-paris-toronto/">Apple Wallet App Gaining Support for Transit Cards in Paris and Toronto</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-gaining-support-for-transit-cards-in-paris-and-toronto.2427030/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
