<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 03:04:14 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Offers Safari Design Choices in iOS 26, Learning from Past Criticism</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-ios-26-safari-design/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offers-safari-design-choices-in-ios-26-learning-from-past-criticism.2458696/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:32:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-ios-26-safari-design/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple introduced a new, compact design for Safari in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> that serves as the default layout, but there are two other design options available if you don't like it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-safari-options.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005460" /><br/>
In the Safari section of the Settings app, you can select Compact (the default), Bottom, or Top. The latter two are the options in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, so &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; uses that same layout, but with a tweaked design to match the Liquid Glass aesthetic.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-safari-design-light-mode.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005461" /><em>The three Safari Tab options in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, Light Mode</em></div><br/>
Functionally, the Bottom and Top Tabs operate in the same way as the Safari Tab bars in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, so you don't need to change anything about how you use Safari. The Compact option hides the share, bookmark, and tab settings behind the three-dot button on the left of the URL bar.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-18-safari-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005466" /><em>Safari in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
The Liquid Glass translucent design blends the URL bar and buttons into the background of the webpage you're looking at regardless of what layout you choose. The effect is similar in both Light and Dark mode, with the color of the bar determined by the webpage's content.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-safari-design-dark-mode.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005463" /><em>The three Safari Tab options in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a></em></div><br/>
When you scroll down with any of the Tab settings, the URL bar and buttons collapse down into a single, small bar with just the webpage address listed. The collapsible bar allows you to see more of the webpage without distractions.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-safari-menu-collapsed.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005464" /><em>Collapsed Tab Bar in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
Back when iOS 15 was in beta testing, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/17/apple-safari-design-changes-ios-15-beta-6/">changed the design of Safari</a> and did not initially provide different layout options for the URL bar. Apple received negative feedback throughout the beta testing process, and ultimately implemented options to revert to the original design. This time around, Apple has learned its lesson, and has provided users with more choice for the Safari layout.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/tab-bar-safari-ios15.jpg" alt="safari" width="3260" height="762" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803945" /><em>The iOS 15 Safari Tab Bar</em></div><br/>
Apple has actually offered design choices for several of the &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; design updates that could be controversial. The Phone app offers a unified view, for example, but by default, it's not implemented. There are also glass-like icons that can be selected, but they're also not the default option.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-ios-26-safari-design/">Apple Offers Safari Design Choices in iOS 26, Learning from Past Criticism</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offers-safari-design-choices-in-ios-26-learning-from-past-criticism.2458696/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Personalized Siri Features Shown at WWDC Last Year Were &#039;Real&#039; and &#039;Working&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-says-personalized-siri-was-working/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-personalized-siri-features-shown-at-wwdc-last-year-were-real-and-working.2458695/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:52:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-says-personalized-siri-was-working/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Craig Federighi</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi and marketing chief Greg Joswiak are on a media tour this week, following the WWDC 2025 keynote.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
The latest interview comes from <a href="https://www.wsj.com/video/series/joanna-stern-personal-technology/apple-executives-defend-apple-intelligence-siri-and-ai-strategy/A7F62EE4-E4F5-4E5D-969A-22644536A47B"><em>The Wall Street Journal</em>'s Joanna Stern</a>, who sat down with Federighi and Joswiak to discuss Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delayed personalized Siri features</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Stern asked the executives if Apple had a working version of the more personalized Siri when the company demonstrated the features during its WWDC 2024 keynote.<br/>
<br/>
According to Federighi, it did.<br/>
<br/>
"We were filming real working software, with a real large language model, with real semantic search, that's what you saw," said Federighi.<br/>
<br/>
"There's this narrative out there that it was demoware only," added Joswiak. "No."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NTLk53h7u_k?si=k83fhbZgD1CqTHES" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Federighi also gave the same answer about why the personalized Siri features were delayed as he did <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-explains-personalized-siri-delay/">in another interview</a>. In short, there were quality issues, and Apple is shifting to a newer underlying architecture for Siri to overcome that.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced the personalized Siri features during its WWDC 2024 keynote. The new capabilities will include better understanding of a user's personal context, on-screen awareness, and deeper per-app controls. For example, Apple showed an iPhone user asking Siri about their mother's flight and lunch reservation plans based on info from the Mail and Messages apps. Apple said it currently plans to release the features in 2026.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/craig-federighi/">Craig Federighi</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-says-personalized-siri-was-working/">Apple Says Personalized Siri Features Shown at WWDC Last Year Were &#039;Real&#039; and &#039;Working&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-personalized-siri-features-shown-at-wwdc-last-year-were-real-and-working.2458695/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26 Wallet App Will Let You Track All Your Packages</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-wallet-app-package-tracking/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-wallet-app-will-let-you-track-all-your-packages.2458691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:09:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-wallet-app-package-tracking/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is integrating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> in the Wallet app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, with the aim of powering a new package tracking feature. Apple Wallet will be able to automatically scan your emails to find messages from merchants or delivery carriers, and tracking numbers will be added to the Wallet app so you can keep an eye on upcoming deliveries. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-wallet-order-tracking.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005429" /><br/>
Package tracking is already a feature in the Wallet app, but at the current time, it only works with purchases made using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>. Going forward, you won't need to buy something with &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; for it to show up in the order tracking section of the Wallet app. <br/>
<br/>
If you're running &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, package tracking can be enabled by opening up the Wallet and &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; section of the Settings app, tapping on &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; Defaults, selecting Order Tracking, and toggling on Orders Found in Mail. Note that the feature has a beta label, which means Apple is still working out bugs. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; is limited to developers right now, but Apple plans to release a public beta in July. The update will launch to the public in September alongside new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-wallet-app-package-tracking/">iOS 26 Wallet App Will Let You Track All Your Packages</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-wallet-app-will-let-you-track-all-your-packages.2458691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WWDC 2025 Proved That Apple Learned a Valuable Lesson</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-learned-from-siri-mishap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2025-proved-that-apple-learned-a-valuable-lesson.2458690/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:40:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-learned-from-siri-mishap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At its WWDC 2024 keynote last year, Apple previewed a more personalized version of Siri that has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-explains-personalized-siri-delay/">since been delayed until next year</a>. Subsequently, Apple was hit with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/">class action lawsuits</a> that accuse the company of false advertising, and well-known Apple commentator John Gruber <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/gruber-says-something-is-rotten-at-apple/">strongly criticized the company</a> over the situation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/WWDC-2025-Apple-Logo.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004059" /><br/>
Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/23/apple-removes-2024-from-next-gen-carplay-page/">missed its promised 2024 timeframe</a> for launching next-generation CarPlay, which it first announced all the way back at WWDC 2022. The company finally <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apples-carplay-ultra-now-available/">announced the launch of CarPlay Ultra</a> last month, with the software system rolling out in high-end Aston Martin vehicles in the U.S. and Canada to start.<br/>
<br/>
It appears that Apple learned a valuable lesson.<br/>
<br/>
During its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/wwdc-2025-live-coverage/">WWDC 2025 keynote</a>, there was a noticeable lack of new software features that Apple promised as coming later this year. The company did say that Apple Intelligence will be gaining support for additional languages later this year, but most of those languages had already been announced months ago. Over the past several years, on the other hand, there were typically quite a few "later this year" labels on Apple's software pages.<br/>
<br/>
Still, not every new feature announced at WWDC 2025 is available in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-ios-26-developer-beta/">first betas</a> of Apple's latest software releases. The lack of "later this year" phrasing suggests that those features will be ready by time iOS 26 and the other updates are released in September, however, as opposed to subsequent versions like iOS 26.1 or iOS 26.2.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, it is clear that Apple is being more cautious, as was expected. In a report last month about Apple's artificial intelligence shortcomings, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman and Drake Bennett cited sources who said that Apple planned to mostly stop announcing new features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/18/apple-to-cut-down-on-early-announcements/">more than a few months before they are ready to launch</a>. Based on the WWDC 2025 keynote, that does appear to be the company's approach for now.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-learned-from-siri-mishap/">WWDC 2025 Proved That Apple Learned a Valuable Lesson</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2025-proved-that-apple-learned-a-valuable-lesson.2458690/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Image Playground in iOS 26 Gets ChatGPT Integration for Anime-Style Images</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-image-playground-chatgpt/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/image-playground-in-ios-26-gets-chatgpt-integration-for-anime-style-images.2458683/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:42:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-image-playground-chatgpt/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you've seen the anime-style Studio Ghibli images that people have been making with ChatGPT, you might be interested to know that Apple has integrated this feature into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, iPadOS 26, and macOS Tahoe.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-anime-image-playground-style.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005471" /><em>ChatGPT's anime-style output in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
&zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; doesn't add new art styles designed by Apple, but it does support several ChatGPT Styles. Options include oil painting, watercolor, vector, anime, and print, which complement the existing Apple-created Animation, Illustration, and Sketch styles.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-image-playground-styles-set-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005472" /><em>Anime, oil painting, and water color styles in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
The ChatGPT options are similar to what you can get if you use ChatGPT 4o for image creation, and the anime style in particular is one that's been popular on social media. In ChatGPT, you can type in any style you want, and Apple has a similar feature with the "Any Style" option. You can select "Any Style" and then add the descriptors that you want, even asking for a realistic image.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-image-playground-realistic-image.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005473" /><em>This was an image of a cat, and ChatGPT was asked to add a bird and make it realistic.</em></div><br/>
You can create images based on text descriptions, or you can upload a photo to have it converted into the style of your choice. When using the ChatGPT option, you will need to give the okay for your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to send the image to ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-image-playground-styles-set-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005562" /><em>Vector, print, and any styles (specified as Van Gogh) in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;</em></div><br/>
As with standard &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; image generation, you can add in additional phrases to tweak the result that you get from ChatGPT. ChatGPT is fairly slow compared to Apple's own on-device image generation capabilities in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;, so expect to wait for the end result.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-image-playground-text-combo.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005475" /><em>A photo combined with a text-based request</em></div><br/>
Unlike Apple's &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; default styles, ChatGPT has no problem with copyrighted content. It will make an image that uses the Studio Ghibli style, or that features Elmo. You're also welcome to include violence, so Elmo can be bloody and hold a knife. Technically, ChatGPT isn't supposed to make violent images featuring children's characters either, but there are simple wording tricks to get around that. Apple does warn before sending any images to ChatGPT, and it is made clear that it's ChatGPT creating the images. ChatGPT has far fewer guardrails than Apple's standard &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; tools, which is something to be aware of. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-chatgpt-image-playground-copyright.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005482" /><br/>
It is worth noting that creating images with ChatGPT uses up tokens, and if you have a free account, you won't be able to create more than one or two. You'll need a paid account to use the feature more frequently.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/chatgpt-limit-ios-26-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005478" /><br/>
There is no limit on the number of images that you can generate using the built-in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; options, and it is worth noting that Apple has one other new feature you can use, and that's the "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>" option. You can combine multiple emoji into a single &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj;, a feature that's new in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, or describe an emoji character to create something new. &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; does not work with photos, and it is a description-only setting. The &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; that you create can be added to your emoji keyboard so you can use them in Messages. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-genmoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005476" /><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; is available for developers right now, but Apple plans to release a public beta in July. The software will see a public launch in September alongside new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-image-playground-chatgpt/">Image Playground in iOS 26 Gets ChatGPT Integration for Anime-Style Images</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/image-playground-in-ios-26-gets-chatgpt-integration-for-anime-style-images.2458683/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains Why Personalized Siri Features Have Still Yet to Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-explains-personalized-siri-delay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-why-personalized-siri-features-have-still-yet-to-launch.2458681/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:11:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-explains-personalized-siri-delay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Craig Federighi</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://www.tomsguide.com/ai/apple-intelligence/wwdc-interview-apples-craig-federighi-and-greg-joswiak-on-siri-delay-voice-ai-as-therapist-and-whats-next-for-apple-intelligence">WWDC interview</a> with <em>Tom's Guide</em> editor-in-chief Mark Spoonauer, and <em>TechRadar</em> editor-at-large Lance Ulanoff, Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi explained why the more personalized version of Siri has still yet to launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
Federighi admitted that the first-generation architecture that Apple was developing for the personalized Siri features was too limited, which prevented the features from reaching the company's high quality standards. By spring 2025, Apple decided that it needed to fully shift Siri to a second-generation architecture that it had been planning, in order for the personalized features to reach a quality level that meets customer expectations. That decision led Apple to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delay the features</a> for up to another year.<br/>
<br/>
Even with the second-generation architecture, Federighi said that Apple is still working to perfect the Siri features. In the interview, Apple's marketing chief Greg Joswiak confirmed that the "coming year" refers to 2026, so it is likely that the company is currently planning to launch the features as part of iOS 26.4 next spring.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Pt3qAWxIbrU?si=f7yARPFuA3jkUKpy" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Multiple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/">class action lawsuits</a> were filed against Apple in the U.S. and Canada over the delayed Siri features, which were heavily advertised by the company last year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced the personalized Siri features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">during its WWDC 2024 keynote</a>. Specifically, Apple said that Siri would gain improved understanding of a user's personal context, on-screen awareness, and deeper per-app controls. For example, Apple showed an iPhone user asking Siri about their mother's flight and lunch reservation plans based on info from the Mail and Messages apps. At the time, Apple said that the capabilities would be available within a year, but evidently it was overconfident and had to return to the drawing board.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/craig-federighi/">Craig Federighi</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-explains-personalized-siri-delay/">Apple Explains Why Personalized Siri Features Have Still Yet to Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-why-personalized-siri-features-have-still-yet-to-launch.2458681/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPadOS 26 Multitasking Update Gets Rid of Split View and Slide Over</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ipados-26-no-split-view-slide-over/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-26-multitasking-update-gets-rid-of-split-view-and-slide-over.2458678/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:50:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ipados-26-no-split-view-slide-over/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iPadOS 26, Apple is introducing major changes to the way that multitasking works, and part of that update will see the removal of Split View and Slide Over, two multitasking interface options that have long existed on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ipados-26-multitasking.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005023" /><br/>
iPadOS 26 allows for multiple app windows, each of which can be resized freely on the display. The feature works on all &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models able to run iPadOS 26, though there are limitations on how many apps can be open at once. On older iPads, for example, you're limited to four apps. Newer iPads can have more open app windows.<br/>
<br/>
You can change the size of &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app windows, move them on top of each other, and rearrange them as desired, much like on the Mac. There are also tiling options so that you can see two to four apps side-by-side, a feature that's similar to Split View. <br/>
<br/>
Windows retain their positions even when you shut off your &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or close an app, and you can see all of your open apps with a swipe up gesture that activates an Exposé-style view. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app windows feature the Mac traffic-light controls, and these can be used for resizing and closing apps. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps also have Mac-style menu bars for tweaking settings, and there's a feature for running system-intensive tasks in the background.<br/>
<br/>
The new multitasking feature that replaces Slide Over and Split View is much more robust, so it is unlikely that most &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users are going to miss these options.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ipados-26-no-split-view-slide-over/">iPadOS 26 Multitasking Update Gets Rid of Split View and Slide Over</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-26-multitasking-update-gets-rid-of-split-view-and-slide-over.2458678/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 26 Removes These Apple Watch Faces</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/watchos-26-removes-these-apple-watch-faces/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-26-removes-these-apple-watch-faces.2458677/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:30:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/watchos-26-removes-these-apple-watch-faces/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AppleWatch/comments/1l854fa/toy_story_and_other_faces_are_removed_in_26/">has removed</a> several Apple Watch faces that are options in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, nixing the Fire/Water, Gradient, Liquid Metal, Vapor, and Toy Story watch faces, according to a post on Reddit.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/watchos-26-removed-faces.jpg" alt="" width="1892" height="1064" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005505" /><br/>
Apple tends to quietly remove some watch face options when it launches a new version of iOS, so it is not a huge surprise to see these go missing. It is not clear why Apple picked these watch faces in particular, but it could be because they were used less often.<br/>
<br/>
Apple didn't add new watch faces with watchOS 26, but some watch faces have new Liquid Glass-inspired design options.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/watchos-26-removes-these-apple-watch-faces/">watchOS 26 Removes These Apple Watch Faces</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-26-removes-these-apple-watch-faces.2458677/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26 to Bring Severe Weather Alerts and Widgets for Predicted Travel Destinations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-severe-weather-predicted-destinations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-to-bring-severe-weather-alerts-and-widgets-for-predicted-travel-destinations.2458670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:42:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-severe-weather-predicted-destinations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Steve Moser</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expanding the Weather app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> with a new feature: Severe Weather Alerts and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a> for Predicted Travel Destinations. This enhancement offers proactive notifications for locations you may soon visit, leveraging Apple's "Proactive Intelligence" to keep you informed before you arrive.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/watchos-26-weather-predicted-location.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005457" /><br/>
The new feature builds on the existing severe weather notification system, which currently supports alerts for a user's current location. &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; uses on-device processing to estimate where you might be traveling soon if the Significant Locations & Routes permission setting is turned on.<br/>
<br/>
This will be particularly useful for travelers, commuters, or anyone planning a day trip or overnight stay, ensuring users are not caught off guard by incoming extreme weather events at their destinations.<br/>
<br/>
To enable this feature, users will need to:<br/>
<ul><li>Enable Significant Locations & Routes in Location Services.</li><br/>
<li>Set Weather app location access to “Always”.</li><br/>
<li>Turn on Severe Weather notifications in the Weather app settings.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If these conditions are met, the Weather app can access predicted destinations and deliver timely alerts relevant to those areas. Importantly, Apple states that it may associate the region of your possible travel destinations with your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, similar to how it handles alerts for your current location.<br/>
<br/>
This feature also integrates with Smart Stacks in watchOS 26 and Widget Suggestions. When enabled, the Weather app can automatically display a destination-specific widget in your Smart Stack, providing at-a-glance weather updates for places you're likely to visit.<br/>
<br/>
Finally, it appears &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; will extend the satellite connectivity for Emergency SOS and Messages introduced in earlier releases to Weather data. This ensures users without Wi-Fi or cellular access can still receive critical weather warnings even when out of range of terrestrial networks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-severe-weather-predicted-destinations/">iOS 26 to Bring Severe Weather Alerts and Widgets for Predicted Travel Destinations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-to-bring-severe-weather-alerts-and-widgets-for-predicted-travel-destinations.2458670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26 Includes These 100 New Features and Changes for Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-includes-these-100-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-includes-these-100-new-features-and-changes-for-your-iphone.2458664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:59:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-includes-these-100-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-announces-ios-26/">announced iOS 26</a>, and the upcoming software update includes a long list of new features and changes for iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/iOS-26-on-Three-iPhones.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005324" /><br/>
The first iOS 26 developer beta is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-ios-26-developer-beta/">now available</a>, and a public beta will follow next month. The update will be released later this year.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 26 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/ios-26-supports-iphone-11-and-newer/">compatible with the iPhone 11 and newer</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we have provided a high-level overview of 100 new features and changes that are coming with iOS 26, in no particular order:<ol><li>A new Liquid Glass design with shimmery app icons and a translucent interface that reflects and refracts the surrounding colors</li><br/>
<li>There is a redesigned tab bar in apps</li><br/>
<li>A new "Clear" option for Home Screen app icons and widgets, alongside the existing "Light" and "Dark" options</li><br/>
<li>On the Lock Screen, the clock dynamically adapts to fill empty space</li><br/>
<li>On the Lock Screen, there is an option to view full-screen album artwork</li><br/>
<li>Polls in group chats in the Messages app</li><br/>
<li>Add a custom background to any conversation in the Messages app</li><br/>
<li>You can now send and receive Apple Cash in group chats in the Messages app</li><br/>
<li>Typing indicators are now visible in group chats in the Messages app</li><br/>
<li>There is a new "Add Contact" button in group chats in the Messages app</li><br/>
<li>A new "Select" option in the Messages app lets you select a portion of text within a message bubble</li><br/>
<li>Messages app can screen messages from unknown senders, placing them into an Unknown Senders folder</li><br/>
<li>Messages app has gained natural language search</li><br/>
<li>Hold Assist can wait on hold for you during a phone call, and notify you when the live agent is ready for you</li><br/>
<li>Call Screening automatically answers unknown callers, and asks for their name and the reason for their call, before your iPhone rings</li><br/>
<li>Live Translation for calls and texts across the Phone, FaceTime, and Messages apps</li><br/>
<li>A preinstalled Apple Games app lets you discover games, in-game events, and compete with friends with new challenges</li><br/>
<li>A preinstalled Preview app lets you create, edit, annotate, markup, and export PDFs, plus crop, flip, rotate, and resize images</li><br/>
<li>Photos app is now split into Library and Collections tabs</li><br/>
<li>Relevant video thumbnails are now shown in search results in the Photos app</li><br/>
<li>In the Photos app, you can create 3D spatial versions of photos, which was previously only possible using the Apple Vision Pro</li><br/>
<li>Camera app has a simpler design with Video and Photo tabs</li><br/>
<li>In the Camera app, you will receive an alert if a camera lens needs to be cleaned, so long as "Lens Cleaning Hints" is toggled on in the Settings app</li><br/>
<li>The screenshot editing interface has been slightly redesigned</li><br/>
<li>In the Settings app, you can now turn off CarPlay screenshots under General → Screen Capture, so that taking a screenshot on your iPhone does not also generate a CarPlay screenshot while the device is connected to CarPlay</li><br/>
<li>In the Settings app, can now turn off iCloud Drive syncing via cellular data</li><br/>
<li>Phone app now has an optional all-in-one layout that combines Favorites, Recents, and Voicemails</li><br/>
<li>Phone app now supports screen sharing and SharePlay during phone calls</li><br/>
<li>Phone app offers new Monogram styles for contacts</li><br/>
<li>A new Focus mode lets you silence an individual SIM</li><br/>
<li>Journal app now lets you create multiple journals</li><br/>
<li>Journal app entries can now be viewed on a map</li><br/>
<li>Journal app now lets images be added inline with text</li><br/>
<li>Passwords app now shows password history</li><br/>
<li>Safari now has three layouts: Compact, Bottom, and Top</li><br/>
<li>Safari now offers advanced fingerprinting protection for all browsing by default</li><br/>
<li>Tips app now offers step-by-step guides for troubleshooting common iPhone issues</li><br/>
<li>You can now test AirPods beta firmware directly via the Settings app</li><br/>
<li>You can start recording video in the Camera app by pressing and holding on the stem of AirPods 4 or AirPods Pro 2</li><br/>
<li>AirPods 4 and AirPods Pro 2 now offer studio-quality audio recording</li><br/>
<li>AirPods can now detect when you fall asleep and automatically pause audio</li><br/>
<li>You are now notified when your AirPods are fully charged</li><br/>
<li>You can be reminded to charge your AirPods when their battery life is low</li><br/>
<li>AirPods audio can now automatically switch to CarPlay as necessary</li><br/>
<li>You can now set a custom snooze duration of 1 to 15 minutes in the Clock app</li><br/>
<li>Visual Intelligence now works with on-screen content, so you can ask ChatGPT questions about what you are looking at</li><br/>
<li>Visual Intelligence can now read aloud and summarize screenshots with text</li><br/>
<li>Genmoji can now combine two standard emoji into one custom one</li><br/>
<li>Image Playground offers new ChatGPT image styles, including Oil Painting, Watercolor, Vector, Anime, and Print</li><br/>
<li>In the Shortcuts app, there is a new set of shortcuts powered by Apple Intelligence</li><br/>
<li>Apple Music lets you pin playlists, albums, and artists at the top of the Library tab</li><br/>
<li>Apple Music lets you create playlist folders</li><br/>
<li>Lyrics translation for Apple Music songs</li><br/>
<li>AutoMix for Apple Music can seamlessly mix from one song to the next like a DJ</li><br/>
<li>Live Activities support for boarding passes in the Apple Wallet app</li><br/>
<li>Wallet app now displays relevant information below the boarding pass, such as Apple Maps directions to the appropriate airport terminal, and a shortcut to the Find My app's baggage tracking feature</li><br/>
<li>Create a digital ID in the Wallet app using your U.S. passport, for age and identity verification in supported apps, and at select stores and TSA checkpoints</li><br/>
<li>In participating U.S. states, "Verify with Wallet on the Web" enables you to present your driver's license or state ID in the Wallet app to websites for age and identity verification, starting with Chime, Turo, Uber Eats, and U.S. Bank, as well as the Arizona MVD, Georgia DDS, and Maryland MVA</li><br/>
<li>You can now manage AutoFill credit cards in the Wallet app</li><br/>
<li>When toggled on, a new Adaptive Power mode can make small adjustments to extend battery life, such as by slightly lowering display brightness or allowing certain background activities to take longer</li><br/>
<li>In the Settings app, you can see how long it will take for your iPhone's battery to achieve a full charge when the device is charging</li><br/>
<li>The entire Battery section of the Settings app was overhauled</li><br/>
<li>A new "Keep Audio in Headphones" setting prevents audio from automatically switching to newly connected devices, like car speakers or Bluetooth speakers, when you are already listening through AirPods or other headphones<br/>
<li>You can now access a list of blocked contacts via the Settings app</li><br/>
<li>Safety Check is now an option when blocking a contact</li><br/>
<li>Apple News+ subscribers in the U.S. and Canada can play a new Emoji Game</li><br/>
<li>A new set of Background Sounds include Babble, Steam, Airplane, Boat, Bus, Train, Rain on Roof, and Quiet Night</li><br/>
<li>The so-called Home bar at the bottom of the screen is now hidden more often</li><br/>
<li>Weather via satellite will allow you to receive the latest forecast information while outside of Wi-Fi or cellular range</li><br/>
<li>In the Notes app, notes can be exported as a Markdown file</li><br/>
<li>With Apple Intelligence, the Reminders app can suggest tasks, grocery items, and follow-ups based on emails or other text on your device</li><br/>
<li>Apple Intelligence can automatically categorize reminders in the Reminders app</li><br/>
<li>You can now create reminders in the Reminders app via the Action button</li><br/>
<li>Apple Maps can now learn your commute between home and work, and notify you if there are any significant delays along your typical route, and offer alternate routes if available</li><br/>
<li>Apple Maps can intelligently detect and save the places that you frequently visit and spend time in, such as restaurants or stores</li><br/>
<li>Apple Maps now lets you choose from additional types of incidents on the "Report an Incident" screen</li><br/>
<li>You can use an iPhone as a wireless microphone for the Apple Music Sing feature on the Apple TV 4K (3rd generation)</li><br/>
<li>In the Apple Podcasts app, there are now a wider range of playback speed options, from 0.5x to 3x</li><br/>
<li>In the Apple Podcasts app, an Enhance Dialogue option lets you hear speech more clearly over background sounds</li><br/>
<li>In the Apple Wallet app, Apple Intelligence can now automatically identify, summarize, and display order tracking details from emails sent from merchants or delivery carriers</li><br/>
<li>Apple Pay now lets you use rewards and installments for in-store purchases</li><br/>
<li>Custom Plans in Apple Fitness+ now automatically create a personalized schedule based on users' workout and meditation preferences</li><br/>
<li>New accessibility features, such as Accessibility Reader and Braille Access</li><br/>
<li>Personal Voice can now create a smoother, more natural-sounding replication of your voice in less than a minute, using only 10 recorded phrases</li><br/>
<li>Vehicle Motion Cues has gained new options to further help reduce motion sickness</li><br/>
<li>Parents can now create or move kids into Child Accounts even more easily</li><br/>
<li>Parents can grant an exception for their child to download an app with an age rating that exceeds the app content restriction they set</li><br/>
<li>Enhancements across Communication Limits, Communication Safety, and the App Store include parental approvals for contact requests from kids, and blurring out sensitive content in FaceTime calls and photos in Shared Albums</li><br/>
<li>There is a new "Transfer From Android" option during eSIM setup</li><br/>
<li>Wi-Fi Aware is now supported</li><br/>
<li>You can now sync captive Wi-Fi portal login information across Apple devices</li><br/>
<li>Arabic calculator</li><br/>
<li>Multiscript keyboard for Arabic/English</li><br/>
<li>You can now specify spelling while using the Dictation feature</li><br/>
<li>Liquid Glass design extends to CarPlay when using an iPhone running iOS 26</li></li><br/>
<li>CarPlay now can now show Live Activities on the Dashboard screen</li><br/>
<li>CarPlay can now display widgets for things like calendar appointments and Home app accessory controls (previously CarPlay Ultra only)</li><br/>
<li>CarPlay now has a compact view for incoming phone calls</li><br/>
<li>CarPlay now shows pinned conversations in the Messages app</li><br/>
<li>CarPlay now lets you respond to messages with the standard set of Tapbacks in the Messages app</li></ol><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-includes-these-100-changes/">iOS 26 Includes These 100 New Features and Changes for Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-includes-these-100-new-features-and-changes-for-your-iphone.2458664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;AirPods Pro 3&#039; Referenced in iOS 26 Code</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-code-airpods-pro-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-3-referenced-in-ios-26-code.2458653/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:59:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-code-airpods-pro-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> suggests that Apple is indeed working on a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> that could be coming in the not too distant future. Code in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; discovered by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://x.com/stevemoser">Steve Moser</a> references the "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-pro-3/">AirPods Pro 3</a>" alongside the "&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;" and the "&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/AirPods-Pro-3-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999276" /><br/>
There is no &zwnj;AirPods Pro 3&zwnj; at the current time, but rumors suggest that Apple plans to introduce a new model this fall. The reference is buried in a headphone-related UI framework, so Apple appears to be preparing for the upcoming product launch behind the scenes.<br/>
<br/>
This isn't actually the first time Apple has hinted at &zwnj;AirPods Pro 3&zwnj;. Last month, Apple <a href="https://x.com/aaronp613/status/1922731957890232570">changed a reference</a> to the second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to the "&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 or later," even though there is no "later" right now.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;AirPods Pro 3&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-pro-3/">will have a new look</a> for the earbuds and the case, with Apple perhaps slimming down the case like it did for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a>. We're also counting on a faster audio chip that brings improved Active Noise Cancellation and audio quality, plus the updated earbuds might offer heart rate monitoring functionality and temperature sensing.<br/>
<br/>
For more on what's expected for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro 3&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-pro-3/">we have a dedicated guide</a> that's updated with new rumors regularly.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-code-airpods-pro-3/">&#039;AirPods Pro 3&#039; Referenced in iOS 26 Code</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-3-referenced-in-ios-26-code.2458653/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expands Digital ID Support to Web Browsers in iOS 26</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-digital-id-web-browser-support-ios-26/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-digital-id-support-to-web-browsers-in-ios-26.2458651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:22:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-digital-id-web-browser-support-ios-26/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is adding a "Verify with Wallet on the Web" option in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> that can use a state-issued license <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-passport-wallet-identity-verification/">or Digital ID</a> to verify age and identity in a private and secure way. This is already an option in apps, but Apple is expanding it to the web through support for the W3C Digital Credentials API and the FIDO CTAP protocol.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-id-verify-on-web.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005413" /><br/>
Right now, purchasing alcohol, renting a car, or similar activities online can require users to upload a picture of their ID, but Apple's new system will replace that. Websites will be able to request digital credentials like name and date of birth without receiving unnecessary information. End users will be informed of how the data will be used, and whether it will be stored by the website asking for identity verification.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's new web-based ID verification feature will work seamlessly in Safari on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac, but it will also work with other browser apps and other operating systems that implement support. You can use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to scan a QR code in any browser on any system to share digital ID information with a website using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> authentication.<br/>
<br/>
Verify with Wallet on the web works with state-issued IDs and licenses, and passports added through the new &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; Digital ID feature could support online verification. Apple is also adding support for third-party apps that store licenses. Some states have digital ID systems that do not integrate with Apple Wallet, but licenses stored in these apps will still be able to be used for identity and age verification on the web. When initiating the verification process on a website, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will be able to select the Wallet app or a third-party app.<br/>
<br/>
The process is end-to-end encrypted, so other parties are not able to read identity data, including browsers and operating systems. IDs are cryptographically signed, preventing the use of fake IDs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the first websites that will support the Verify with Wallet on the Web feature include Chime, Turo, Uber Eats, and U.S. Bank. The Arizona MVD, Georgia DDS, and Maryland MVA will add support for their digital ID apps.<br/>
<br/>
The web verification process for IDs will launch this fall when &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; debuts.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-digital-id-web-browser-support-ios-26/">Apple Expands Digital ID Support to Web Browsers in iOS 26</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-digital-id-support-to-web-browsers-in-ios-26.2458651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26 Will Let You Add Your U.S. Passport to Wallet for Identity Verification</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-passport-wallet-identity-verification/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-will-let-you-add-your-u-s-passport-to-wallet-for-identity-verification.2458648/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:35:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-passport-wallet-identity-verification/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, Apple is implementing a new Digital ID feature that builds on integration for Driver's Licenses in the Wallet app. Starting this fall, Apple Wallet will allow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users to add a U.S. passport that can be used in lieu of a physical passport for domestic travel.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ios-26-digital-id-passport-wallet.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005400" /><br/>
The Digital ID can be stored on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or the Apple Watch, and it can be used at select TSA checkpoints throughout the United States. It is Real ID compliant, as a passport can be presented instead of a Real ID when traveling.<br/>
<br/>
Digital IDs do not replace physical passports, and Apple warns that they cannot be used for international travel or border crossings. In these situations, a physical passport will be required, but for domestic travel, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users won't need to pull out a passport and can instead pass through TSA checkpoints quicker.<br/>
<br/>
As with state driver's licenses and IDs, Digital IDs will work for age and identity verification in apps, retail store locations, and new in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, websites. The option to add a passport to Wallet for use as an ID option will expand digital identification features to many more &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users.<br/>
<br/>
U.S. states and territories have been slowly rolling out support for IDs in the Wallet app, but it is still limited to Arizona, California, Colorado, Georgia, Hawaii, Iowa, Maryland, New Mexico, Ohio, and Puerto Rico.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is adding other travel-friendly features to the Wallet app. There's an overhauled boarding pass experience that provides users with a Live Activity overview of their flight and real-time updates. Boarding passes also offer options to go to Maps for an airport overview, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> for tracking luggage.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is partnering with airlines to implement the updated boarding passes, and these airlines will be the first to support the feature: Air Canada, American Airlines, Delta Air Lines, JetBlue, Jetstar, Lufthansa Group, Qantas, Southwest Airlines, United Airlines, and Virgin Australia.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-passport-wallet-identity-verification/">iOS 26 Will Let You Add Your U.S. Passport to Wallet for Identity Verification</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-will-let-you-add-your-u-s-passport-to-wallet-for-identity-verification.2458648/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warning: Apple Says macOS 27 Won&#039;t Support AirPort Time Capsule Backups</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/macos-27-wont-support-airport-time-capsule/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-apple-says-macos-27-wont-support-airport-time-capsule-backups.2458637/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:23:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/macos-27-wont-support-airport-time-capsule/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPort Time Capsule</category>
		<category>Time Machine</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Throughout the 2000s and 2010s, Apple offered a line of Wi-Fi routers that it referred to as AirPort base stations. There was a standard AirPort Express, a higher-end AirPort Extreme with more advanced networking features, and an AirPort Time Capsule that doubled as an external storage drive for backing up a Mac with Time Machine.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-AirPort-Routers.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983152" /><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/04/26/apple-officially-discontinues-airport-wireless-router-lineup/">discontinued the AirPort line</a> in 2018, and this week it shared more sad news that will impact the AirPort Time Capsule specifically.<br/>
<br/>
As noticed <a href="https://x.com/StellaFudge/status/1932449171572998310">by @StellaFudge</a>, and by other users who have installed the first macOS Tahoe beta, the Time Machine page in the System Settings app now indicates that the next major version of macOS — aka macOS 27 — will no longer support the AirPort Time Capsule or any other storage drives that use the Apple Filing Protocol (AFP).<br/>
<br/>
Apple already announced that its AFP client had been deprecated, in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/121011">enterprise release notes for macOS Sequoia 15.5</a> last month.<br/>
<br/>
Starting with macOS 27, Time Capsule backups will require a storage drive that supports more current file-sharing protocols like SMBv2 and SMBv3.<br/>
<br/>
macOS 27 will be released next year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airport-time-capsule/">AirPort Time Capsule</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/time-machine/">Time Machine</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/macos-27-wont-support-airport-time-capsule/">Warning: Apple Says macOS 27 Won&#039;t Support AirPort Time Capsule Backups</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-apple-says-macos-27-wont-support-airport-time-capsule-backups.2458637/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Phase Out Rosetta 2 Starting With macOS 28 as Intel Era Ends</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-to-phase-out-rosetta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-phase-out-rosetta-2-starting-with-macos-28-as-intel-era-ends.2458631/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:41:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-to-phase-out-rosetta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		<category>Intel</category>
		<category>Rosetta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/wwdc-2025-live-coverage/">WWDC keynote</a> on Monday, Apple updated a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/apple-silicon/about-the-rosetta-translation-environment">developer document</a> to indicate that Rosetta 2 will remain available through macOS 27.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-silicon-1-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1422" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924673" /><br/>
Rosetta 2 enables Macs with Apple silicon (Arm architecture) to run apps that were built for Macs with an Intel processor (x86 architecture), by translating code.<br/>
<br/>
Starting with macOS 28, Apple said that only a limited version of Rosetta 2 will remain available for older games that rely on Intel-based frameworks:<blockquote>Rosetta was designed to make the transition to Apple silicon easier, and we plan to make it available for the next two major macOS releases – through macOS 27 – as a general-purpose tool for Intel apps to help developers complete the migration of their apps. Beyond this timeframe, we will keep a subset of Rosetta functionality aimed at supporting older unmaintained gaming titles, that rely on Intel-based frameworks.</blockquote>The document also reiterates that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/intel-macs-no-more-updates/">macOS Tahoe will be the final macOS release that supports Intel-based Macs</a>. However, Apple said that Intel-based Macs will continue to receive security updates for an additional three years.<br/>
<br/>
macOS Tahoe is compatible with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/macos-tahoe-compatible-macs/">only a handful of Intel-based Macs</a>, including the 16-inch MacBook Pro (2019), 13-inch MacBook Pro (2020, Four Thunderbolt 3 Ports), 27-inch iMac (2020), and Mac Pro (2019).<br/>
<br/>
macOS 28 will be released in 2027.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/intel/">Intel</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rosetta/">Rosetta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/apple-to-phase-out-rosetta-2/">Apple to Phase Out Rosetta 2 Starting With macOS 28 as Intel Era Ends</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-phase-out-rosetta-2-starting-with-macos-28-as-intel-era-ends.2458631/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Get the iOS 26 Developer Beta on Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-26-developer-beta-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-get-the-ios-26-developer-beta-on-your-iphone.2458630/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:38:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-26-developer-beta-iphone&#038;post_date=1749577105/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has released the first iOS 26 beta to developers, but even non-developers have the opportunity to download beta software updates on their iPhones for free. Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/Apple-WWDC25-iOS-26-hero-250609.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005070" /><br/>
Traditionally, when Apple announced a major new operating system update, the first wave of betas would only be available to download by paying subscribers to <a href="https://developer.apple.com">Apple's Developer Program</a>, which costs &#36;99 a year. Public betas would then become available to users enrolled in <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/welcome">Apple's Public Beta Software Program</a> after a delay of a few days or weeks after the developer beta has been released. That all changed in 2023, and these days iPhone users no longer have to wait for a publicly released beta to test what's new.<br/>
<br/>
Indeed, anyone who signs in to Apple's developer account website with their Apple Account credentials gets access to developer beta releases as well, even if they are not a paying member of Apple's Developer Program. This means anyone with an Apple Account can download and install the new iOS 26, iPadOS 26, and macOS Tahoe betas without waiting for the public betas to launch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Is My iPhone Compatible With iOS 26?</h2><br/>
 iOS 26 is compatible with the iPhone 11 series and newer. In other words, the following models are supported:<ul><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16e</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone SE (2nd generation and later)</li><br/>
</ul><h2>Should I Install iOS 26 Developer Beta?</h2><br/>
Great question! Before downloading the update, it's worth noting that Apple does not recommend installing iOS 26 beta updates on your main iPhone, so if you have a secondary device, use that. This is beta software, which means there are often bugs and issues that pop up that can prevent software from working properly or cause other problems. Apple undoubtedly has plenty of fixes to make before the final release.<br/>
<br/>
<div id="backup"></div><h2>Make an Archived Backup of Your Device First</h2><br/>
Before installing the beta, make sure to <strong>back up your iOS device</strong> before installing the software using the following method, otherwise you won't be able to revert back to iOS 18 if things go wrong.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Plug your iPhone into your Mac using the supplied cable.</li><br/>
<li>Allow the accessory to connect by clicking <strong>Allow</strong> in the dialog prompt.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open a <strong>Finder</strong> window by clicking the Finder icon in the Dock.</li><br/>
 	<li>Click your iOS device's name in the sidebar.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/archived-backup2.jpg" alt="finder" width="2264" height="1592" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901467" /><br/>
 	<li>If this is the first time connecting your device to your Mac, click <strong>Trust</strong> in the Finder window.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/archived-backup1.jpg" alt="finder" width="2030" height="1408" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901468" /><br/>
 	<li>Tap <strong>Trust</strong> on your device when prompted, then enter your passcode to confirm.</li><br/>
 	<li>In the General tab, click the circle next to where it says <strong>Back up all of the data on your iPad to this Mac</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>If you want to encrypt the backup, check the box next to <strong>Encrypt local backup</strong>, then enter a password to protect your data.</li><br/>
 	<li>If you don't want to create an encrypted backup, or you've already set up encrypted backups, click <strong>Back Up Now</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/archived-backup3.jpg" alt="finder" width="1990" height="1364" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901469" /><br/>
</ol><br/>
When the backup is finished, you can find the date and time of the last backup in the <strong>General</strong> tab, just above the Manage Backups button. Remember that this backup will not be overwritten when you manually or automatically back up your iPhone in the future, so you can restore it at any time by using the <strong>Restore Backup...</strong> option in the same Finder screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Download iOS 26 Developer Betas</h2><br/>
The option to download and install the iOS 26 Developer Beta is immediately available for users who have previously enrolled on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's Beta Software Program</a>. If you're currently enrolled to receive Public Betas, you can skip to step 6, otherwise follow these steps.<br/>
<ol><li>Open Safari on your iPhone and visit <a href="https://developer.apple.com">developer.apple.com</a>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the menu icon in the top-left corner of the page, then tap <strong>Account</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Under "Sign in to Apple Developer," enter and submit your Apple Account credentials using the arrow buttons, then enter the two-factor authentication code sent to your devices.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/sign-in-developer-account.jpg" alt="safari" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005331" /><br/>
<li>Tap the top-left menu icon again, then tap <strong>Account</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Accept the legal terms of the Apple Developer Agreement by scrolling down the page, checking the box, and tapping <strong>I Agree</strong>. You'll then be directed to a payment screen, but you can quit out of your browser from here – you don't need to pay anything.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/install-ios-beta-2.jpg" alt="dev program" width="5108" height="2999" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899063" /><br/>
<li>Make sure your iPhone is running iOS 16.4 or later by going to <strong>Settings -> General -> Software Update</strong>. If it is, and you have just completed steps 1-5 to register a developer account, restart your iPhone. If it isn't, download and install the latest update to your device, then wait for it to restart.</li><br/>
<li>Now go back to <strong>Settings ➝ General ➝ Software Update</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Beta Updates</strong>. If you don't see the option, try switching off Download iOS Updates (<strong>Automatic Updates ➝ Download iOS Updates</strong>), then tap <strong>Back</strong> and it should appear.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>iOS 26 Developer Beta</strong> in the list, then tap <strong>Back</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Wait for the Software Update screen to check Apple's servers. When the iOS 26 Developer Beta appears, tap <strong>Download and Install</strong>, then follow the instructions and wait for installation to complete.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/install-ios26-developer-beta.jpg" alt="settings" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005325" /></ol><h2>iOS 26 Features</h2><br/>
iOS 26 introduces a striking system-wide redesign built around Liquid Glass, a translucent material that reflects and refracts ambient content and dynamically responds to user input. The new aesthetic applies across the Lock Screen, Home Screen, toolbar controls, navigation elements, app icons, and widgets.<br/>
<br/>
The update also brings new Apple Intelligence features. With Live Translation available in Messages, FaceTime, and Phone, conversations across languages are now seamless and entirely on-device to ensure privacy. New Visual Intelligence capabilities mean you can ask questions about screen content. There are also smarter Shortcuts with intelligent actions to make automation easier.<br/>
<br/>
Communication apps gain smart upgrades too. The revamped Phone app now combines Favorites, Recents, and Voicemails in one view, adds Call Screening, and includes a clever Hold Assist feature. Messages gains filtered inboxes for unknown senders, typing indicators in group chats, custom backgrounds and polls, and Apple Cash transfers.<br/>
<br/>
CarPlay gets a visual refresh aligned with the Liquid Glass design and now includes compact call notifications, tappable Message reactions, pinned conversations, widgets, and Live Activities support.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also updated some of its key apps: Apple Music adds Lyrics Translation and Pronunciation plus AutoMix DJ-style transitions; Maps introduces privacy-protected "Visited Places" and smarter route preferences; Wallet supports installment/rewards payments, refreshed boarding passes with Live Activities, and deeper integrations with Maps and Find My. Lastly, a new Games app debuts as a central hub for mobile gaming, featuring a unified library, Apple Arcade support, event tracking, and friend status updates.<br/>
<br/>
For a full breakdown of what's new, be sure to check out our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26 roundup</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-26-developer-beta-iphone/">How to Get the iOS 26 Developer Beta on Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-get-the-ios-26-developer-beta-on-your-iphone.2458630/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;100 Off Nearly Every M3 iPad Air, Starting at &#36;499</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/amazon-ipad-air-499/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-100-off-nearly-every-m3-ipad-air-starting-at-499.2458625/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:20:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/amazon-ipad-air-499/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week has discounts across nearly the entire M3 iPad Air lineup, offering &#36;100 off these tablets. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;499.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch M3 iPad Air, down from &#36;599.00. <a href="https://bestbuy.7tiv.net/qz0Z15">Best Buy is matching</a> all of these deals on the iPad Air.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/ipad-air-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004565" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Every deal has been automatically applied and does not require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final sale price. We've rounded up every discount available on Amazon in the lists below, and they include both 11-inch and 13-inch models. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our list below focuses on Wi-Fi models, but you'll also find many cellular models on sale at &#36;100 off right now. The 128GB cellular 11-inch iPad Air is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ73LCP8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;649.00</strong></a> and the 128GB cellular 13-inch iPad Air is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ754K11%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a>, both &#36;100 discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11-inch M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76RM7P%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;599.00, down from &#36;699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ7466KC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74CF3K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>13-inch M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;699.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75R957%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74RTQD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74L1N7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address" title="Email Address" /><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value="" title="form" /></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/amazon-ipad-air-499/">Amazon Takes &#36;100 Off Nearly Every M3 iPad Air, Starting at &#36;499</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-100-off-nearly-every-m3-ipad-air-starting-at-499.2458625/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 26 Adds These New Features to Your Apple TV</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/tvos-26-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-26-adds-these-new-features-to-your-apple-tv.2458619/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:28:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/tvos-26-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-tv-brings-a-beautiful-redesign-and-enhanced-home-entertainment-experience/">announced</a> tvOS 26, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-ios-26-developer-beta/">now available in developer beta</a>. The upcoming software update includes a handful of new features for the Apple TV, although some of the changes are only available on newer models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/tvOS-26.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="899" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005308" /><br/>
The most obvious change is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-announces-liquid-glass/">new Liquid Glass design</a>, which was also introduced across iOS 26, iPadOS 26, macOS 26, and watchOS 26. The new design language includes shimmery app icons, and translucent elements that reflect colors. The new design is only visible on the Apple TV 4K (2nd generation) and Apple TV 4K (3rd generation).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/tvOS-26-Liquid-Glass.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005304" /><br/>
In the TV app, movies and TV show posters are now shown in vertical cards, which take up less space on the screen than the previous horizontal cards.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/tvOS-26-Movie-Posters.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005312" /><br/>
With an optional new setting, tvOS 26 can automatically display profiles when your Apple TV wakes, so that you can quickly access your watchlist and personalized recommendations in the TV app, as well as your Apple Music playlists.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/tvOS-26-Profiles.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005305" /><br/>
tvOS 26 will link login information to your Apple Account for supported apps, making it easier for you to sign in to apps when setting up an Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
On the Apple TV, Apple Music subscribers have access to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-apple-music-sing-karaoke-feature/">Apple Music Sing</a> karaoke feature that lowers the volume of the song's vocals so that you can sing along to the on-screen lyrics. tvOS 26 takes Apple Music Sing a step further by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/tvos-26-iphone-karaoke-mic-apple-music-sing/">allowing you to use your iPhone as a wireless microphone</a>, with your voice amplified through the TV's speakers. Plus, your friends and family can use their iPhones to queue up songs, or react with on-screen emoji.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/apple-music-sing-tvos26.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005240" /><br/>
In order to use an iPhone as a microphone for Apple Music Sing, you will need to have the latest Apple TV 4K (3rd generation) running tvOS 26.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Music Sing has also gained lyrics translation for select songs in select languages.<br/>
<br/>
FaceTime has received some enhancements on tvOS 26, including incoming call notifications, Contact Posters when starting a call, and Live Captions in French, German, Japanese, Korean, Mandarin, and Spanish.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 26 lets you designate any AirPlay speaker as the permanent speaker for your Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
The update also adds new Aerial screen savers captured across India.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/tvOS-26-Aerial-Screen-Saver-India.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005306" /><br/>
These are only the new features that Apple highlighted in its tvOS 26 press release, so expect more changes to be uncovered in the betas.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 26 will be released to the general public later this year. The update is compatible with all Apple TV HD and Apple TV 4K models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/tvos-26-new-features/">tvOS 26 Adds These New Features to Your Apple TV</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-26-adds-these-new-features-to-your-apple-tv.2458619/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 26 Brings the Notes App to Apple Watch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/watchos-26-notes-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-26-brings-the-notes-app-to-apple-watch.2458601/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:53:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/watchos-26-notes-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-announces-watchos-26/">watchOS 26</a>, the Notes app is available on the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/Apple-Watch-Notes.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005272" /><br/>
With the Notes app on the Apple Watch, you can finally view your notes right on your wrist. You can also create new notes with Siri, or by using the on-screen keyboard, and they will sync to your iPhone, iPad, and Mac via iCloud.<br/>
<br/>
Other available functions in the Notes app on the Apple Watch include pinning notes, unlocking notes, and completing checklist items.<br/>
<br/>
This is a smaller yet very useful change coming with watchOS 26, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/09/apple-ios-26-developer-beta/">now available in beta</a>. The update will be released to all users later this year for the Apple Watch Series 6 and newer, Apple Watch SE 2, and all Apple Watch Ultra models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/watchos-26-notes-app/">watchOS 26 Brings the Notes App to Apple Watch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-26-brings-the-notes-app-to-apple-watch.2458601/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 26 Tweaks Back Gesture to Make Navigation Easier on Bigger iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-tweaks-swipe-back-gesture/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-tweaks-back-gesture-to-make-navigation-easier-on-bigger-iphones.2458596/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:43:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-tweaks-swipe-back-gesture/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 26 beta 1, Apple has seemingly tweaked the swipe-to-go-back gesture to make it easier to navigate screens on bigger iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/swipe-to-go-back-gesture-ios-26.jpg" alt="" width="5472" height="3078" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005254" /><br/>
In iOS 18, many apps allow you to navigate back to the previous screen by swiping with your thumb from the left edge of the display. This is generally easier than tapping a back button in the top-left corner, especially if you're navigating with one hand. <br/>
<br/>
However, to trigger the gesture, you need to start swiping from the very edge of the screen, which is harder if you have small hands or you're using a larger device like an iPhone 16 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
To make things easier in iOS 26, you no longer have to start the rightward swipe at the very edge of the screen. Now you can start the gesture from anywhere, like the middle of the display. Providing you're not thumbing an interactive UI element, the swipe-to-go-back gesture will still be triggered.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/06/swipe-to-back-gesture-music.jpg" alt="" width="2778" height="2736" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1005263" /><br/>
Currently the gesture works in many system apps including Settings, Contacts, Music, and the App Store. It also seems to work in some third-party apps, although support is likely to expand once developers update their apps in time for the release of iOS 26 in the fall.<br/>
  <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/06/10/ios-26-tweaks-swipe-back-gesture/">iOS 26 Tweaks Back Gesture to Make Navigation Easier on Bigger iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-26-tweaks-back-gesture-to-make-navigation-easier-on-bigger-iphones.2458596/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
