<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:01:23 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s AirPods Lineup to Get These Updates in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/apple-airpods-lineup-updates-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-lineup-to-get-these-updates-in-2024.2433764/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:52:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/apple-airpods-lineup-updates-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to upgrade its entire AirPods lineup this year in one form or another, with a combination of new model launches and upcoming software updates for existing devices. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/airpods-school.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905460" /><br/>
Whether you're holding out for the next generation of AirPods or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, or just want to know what new features are on the way for your current earbuds, keep reading for the full lowdown on what to expect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 3</h2><br/>
Fourth-generation AirPods are expected to arrive in late 2024, with Apple planning to release two versions at different price points. Both models will feature a redesigned look, including a USB-C port instead of a Lightning port, shorter stems similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, along with an updated fit and enhanced audio quality.<br/>
<br/>
The higher-end version is expected to include Active Noise Cancellation (ANC), making ANC available at a lower price point for the first time. They are also likely to have a speaker in the charging case that can play a sound for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> location tracking. This model will be more affordable than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; (&#36;249) but will not include features like silicone ear tips. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/AirPods-Fourth-Generation-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905655" /><br/>
One of the key aspects the next-generation AirPods are likely to bring over from the second-generation ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌ is the H2 chip. Both the second- and third-generation AirPods currently feature the H1 chip. The H2 chip is accompanied by Bluetooth 5.3 connectivity, which offers faster and more reliable connectivity with Bluetooth accessories, as well as improved power efficiency, which can contribute to longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the H2 chip provides an "exceptional acoustic experience" when paired with a new low-distortion audio driver and custom amplifier in the ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌. The ‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌ offer richer bass and clearer sound across a wider range of frequencies partly due to the computational audio improvements facilitated by the H2 chip, so similar enhancements seem highly likely to come to the fourth-generation AirPods. <br/>
<br/>
The launch of the two <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a> models is expected in September or October 2024, which will also see the current AirPods 2 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a> discontinued.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro</h2><br/>
Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> update introduces several enhancements for the current second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, leveraging machine learning and AI. New head gestures will allow users to control &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; hands-free—nodding to answer a call or shaking their head to decline. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> Interactions will also enable hands-free management of calls, messages, and notifications without speaking.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; adds Voice Isolation to &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, improving call clarity by filtering out background noise and focusing on your voice, similar to an existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> feature. Additionally, the Adaptive Audio feature, which adjusts sound and noise cancellation based on your environment, will now offer a customizable setting for finer control.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862208" /><br/>
According to Apple, the ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌ provide the best wireless audio latency ever for mobile gaming, thanks to improvements coming in ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;‌. Improved latency means that you'll see little to no delay when taking an action in the game and hearing the resulting sound, making for a more responsive experience.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will introduce a "hearing aid mode" to &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;. Although they already have a Conversation Boost feature, this update further positions them as a potential hearing aid device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected introduce a redesigned third-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; in 2025, with refined design and better audio quality, along with a faster processor.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
&zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are the oldest current-generation AirPods product still in Apple's lineup. It's been over three years since Apple launched &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in December 2020, and only recently have we begun hearing rumors about Apple's plans for a new-generation model that is coming later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will replace the Lightning port found on the current-generation &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; for a USB-C port. This will ensure the headphones comply with European regulations, and will bring consistency across the company's AirPods lineup. This of course means &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; 2 will come supplied with a USB-C to USB-C charging cable, rather than a Lightning to USB-C cable. Apple will also need to offer a USB-C to 3.5mm audio accessory cable so that users can plug &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; 2 into 3.5mm audio ports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Dark-Red-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877636" /><br/>
The Bluetooth 5.3 specification can already be found in the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, and the latest Apple Watch models. It is also supported by all Mac models released in 2023. Therefore it's almost inevitable that the second-generation ‌&zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;‌ will similarly feature the latest Bluetooth standard.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to offer second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in fresh colors, although what those colors might be remains unknown. &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are currently available in Space Gray, Silver, Green, Sky Blue, and Pink, although interchangeable ear cushions allow for many color combinations.<br/>
<br/>
While there are no rumors that claim &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; 2 will feature the H2 chip, it would seem reasonable to expect them to do so. Apple's custom silicon chip is designed specifically for earbuds and headphones, and enables improved computational audio to enhance sound quality on the current-generation ‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌ and improves battery life with better energy efficiency. Without the H2 chip, &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; would also miss out on Adaptive Audio features including Personalized Volume and Conversation Awareness.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Coming to All AirPods Models</h2><br/>
Personalized Spatial Audio is a feature that already exists for movies, TV shows, and music. It uses the TrueDepth camera on your ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ to scan your face and ears, developing a personal profile that customizes Spatial Audio just for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Spatial-Audio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1698" height="978" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-787199" /><br/>
With ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;‌, Apple is expanding Personalized Spatial Audio to gaming, with the aim of delivering more immersive sound for gameplay. Personalized Spatial Audio for Gaming will support &zwnj;AirPods 3&zwnj; and 4, &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, and &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/apple-airpods-lineup-updates-this-year/">Apple&#039;s AirPods Lineup to Get These Updates in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-lineup-to-get-these-updates-in-2024.2433764/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games Store Launches on iPhone in EU, Brings Fortnite Back to iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/epic-games-store-launches-ios-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-store-launches-on-iphone-in-eu-brings-fortnite-back-to-ios.2433762/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:40:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/epic-games-store-launches-ios-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After a four-year absence, <em>Fortnite</em> is making its return to iPhones – but only for users in the European Union. This comeback is part of the broader launch of the <a href="https://store.epicgames.com/en-US/mobile/ios">Epic Games Store for iPhone</a>, which went live today in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/epic-games-store.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1350" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961828" /><br/>
The return of <em>Fortnite</em> to iOS comes as a result of the EU's Digital Markets Act, which has forced Apple to allow third-party app marketplaces on its platform. Users in the EU can now download the Epic Games Store by <a href="https://store.epicgames.com/en-US/mobile/ios">visiting Epic's website</a> on their iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Fortnite</em>'s availability is undoubtedly the headline feature of the Epic Games Store launch. The popular battle royale game was removed from the App Store in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">2020</a> following a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">dispute between Epic and Apple</a> over in-app purchase systems. Prior to that, <em>Fortnite</em> on iOS made more than &#36;700 million over two years, while Apple collected more than <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/19/apple-earned-over-100-million-from-fortnite/">&#36;100 million in revenue</a> from the 30 percent cut that it took from <em>Fortnite</em> in-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
Otherwise, the current game catalog in the iOS Epic Games Store is limited, featuring only a handful of Epic's own titles such as <em>Fortnite</em> and <em>Rocket League Sideswipe</em>. However, the company says it plans to expand the library over time and is in discussions with third-party mobile developers. <br/>
<br/>
Going forward, Epic will have to deal with navigating Apple's new fee structure, including a "Core Technology Fee" of €0.50 per install per year after the first million installs. This fee applies to both the Epic Games Store itself and the games within it, effectively doubling the charge for popular titles like <em>Fortnite</em>. The EU commission is currently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">investigating</a> whether Apple's new fee structure complies with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
The Epic Games Store is only available on iPhones running iOS 17.4 or later, while iPad users will have to wait until the release of iPadOS 18 to access the store on their devices. Epic says it plans to expand the availability of its store to other regions where regulations permit, with Japan slated for a 2025 launch. The company has set a goal of reaching 100 million mobile downloads of its store by the end of the year, made up of combined game installs across both iOS and Android.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/epic-games-store-launches-ios-eu/">Epic Games Store Launches on iPhone in EU, Brings Fortnite Back to iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-store-launches-on-iphone-in-eu-brings-fortnite-back-to-ios.2433762/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All Four iPhone 16 Pro Colors Revealed in New Image</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-four-iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed-in-new-image.2433761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:14:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Leaker <a href="https://x.com/sonnydickson/status/1824381930579824739?s=46">Sonny Dickson</a> is back today with a new dummy unit image showing all four <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> color variants, including the rose gold or "bronze" unit that replaces Blue Titanium in the existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/sonny-iphone-16-pro-colors.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961824" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to come in black, white or silver, gray or "Natural Titanium," and a rose or rose gold color replacing Blue Titanium, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <a href="https://x.com/VNchocoTaco/status/1772522408144191732">other leakers</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Dickson's image shows what we can expect, particularly in terms of the rose gold variant, which was recently described by one leaker as having more of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/">bronze-like hue</a>. Apple did not include a gold option in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, so a similar variant could see heightened demand.<br/>
<br/>
One <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/iphone-16-pro-new-polished-titanium-finish/">rumor</a> suggests that Apple is using an improved process for finishing and coloring titanium, which will result in a glossier look than the brushed aluminum finish of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models. The glossy finish could look much more like the stainless steel that Apple used in prior years, but it will be more resistant to scratches.<br/>
<br/>
We don't actually know the official color names yet, but Apple may choose to stick with the Titanium colorway branding it used for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models. The next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is due to arrive around mid-September, so we will know for sure soon. Dickson revealed the colors for the standard (non-Pro) &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/">last month</a>. What do you think of the new colors? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/16/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/">All Four iPhone 16 Pro Colors Revealed in New Image</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-four-iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed-in-new-image.2433761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These New Macs Are Coming in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024.2433739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:34:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's almost September, but Apple still has multiple new product launches planned for 2024. New <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models and Apple Watches are coming in September, and we're also going to get at least three Mac updates with M4 chips this year, according to rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Silver-Ortho-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961274" /><br/>
Here's what's on the horizon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
Apple plans to refresh both the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models, adding M4 chips. The MacBook Pro lineup was last updated in October 2023, so the machines are due for a yearly refresh.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did away with the 13-inch MacBook Pro last year, so there's now an entry-level 14-inch model, and that's what's going to get the standard M4 chip that was used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Middle tier and higher-end 14-inch models will get the M4 Pro and M4 Max chips, as will the 16-inch models. The M4 chips are built on the 3-nanometer process, but compared to the M3 chips, they have improved performance, efficiency, and AI capabilities. Apple introduced a new, more powerful Neural Engine.<br/>
<br/>
There are no design updates expected for the MacBook Pro models this year, with Apple focusing on internal improvements. Specifically, the M4 chip will be the star of the upgrade, and Apple is aiming to get its entire Mac lineup on the same M4 chip series across 2024 and 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac mini</h2><br/>
Unlike the MacBook Pro, Apple does have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/">design refresh planned</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be Apple's smallest computer to date, even smaller than the prior-generation version.<br/>
<br/>
It is expected to be around the size of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, though it will be thicker than the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; and the current &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, which is 1.4 inches tall. The machine will continue to be made from aluminum, just in an overall smaller package.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has tested &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models that have at least three USB-C ports, along with an HDMI port and a power cable.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to use the M4 and M4 Pro chips for the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models, and since these never got an M3 update, they'll go from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> to M4 and will see some notable performance improvements.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMac</h2><br/>
The 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> is also expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/m4-macbook-pro-mac-mini-imac-2024/">see an update</a> this year, going from the M3 chip to the M4 chip. Design changes are not rumored for the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, so we can expect to see the same 24-inch display with multiple color options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is still exploring a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/apple-still-working-on-larger-imac/">version of the iMac</a> with a larger ~30-inch display, but an &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with a bigger display is not expected in 2024, and it's not clear if it will come in 2025, either.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Possible Launch Timeline</h2><br/>
Apple does not typically unveil Macs at its September events, which focus on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the Apple Watch. We're expecting Apple to hold an event around September 10 to unveil new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, but Macs will likely come later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
When Apple has Macs to unveil around fall, it often introduces the machines in October or November. Last year, for example, Apple held a Mac-centric event in October to refresh the MacBook Pro and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;. October/November events aren't as consistent as &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; events, so nailing down a target date is tougher. Apple has held second fall events on these dates in the past:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 30, 2023</strong> - Scary Fast event with MacBook Pro and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 18, 2021</strong> - Unleashed event with new MacBook Pro models and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>November 10, 2020</strong> - One More Thing event with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, and MacBook Pro.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 30, 2018</strong> - Apple refreshed the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>October 27, 2016</strong> - Apple unveiled a new MacBook Pro and &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Apple could also skip an event and unveil the new Macs with a press release, though the small event we got last year for the M3 MacBook Pro and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; models could be repeated in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Macs Coming in 2025</h2><br/>
While the MacBook Pro, &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, and &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; are expected to get the M4 chip before the end of the year, M4 updates for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> won't be happening until 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/">These New Macs Are Coming in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024.2433739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Will Require Users to Update Screen Recording App Permissions Monthly</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/macos-sequoia-screen-recording-app-permissions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-will-require-users-to-update-screen-recording-app-permissions-monthly.2433732/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/macos-sequoia-screen-recording-app-permissions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, Apple is requiring users to regularly reauthorize permissions for screen recording apps, a move that has not been popular with some Mac users. Popups for screen recording app permissions have been showing weekly up throughout the beta testing process, but Apple has tweaked the frequency in response to user feedback.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-6/">latest macOS Sequoia beta</a> prompts users to review their screen recording app permissions once a month, an update over the more frequent weekly popups. The prompt reminds users that screen recording apps have access to their screens and audio.<br/>
<blockquote>[App Name] is requesting to bypass the system private window picker and directly access your screen and audio. This will allow [App Name] to record your screen and system audio, including personal or sensitive information that may be visible or audible.</blockquote><br/>
When the popup shows up, there's now an option to "Allow For One Month" to let the app function as normal, or to open System Settings to get to the screen recording options. &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; was also requiring users to approve screen recording apps after restarting their Macs, and this requirement has been removed.<br/>
<br/>
It does not appear that there is a way for users to permanently give screen recording access to recording functionality, but a monthly popup is at least more convenient than a weekly popup.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/macos-sequoia-screen-recording-app-permissions/">macOS Sequoia Will Require Users to Update Screen Recording App Permissions Monthly</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-will-require-users-to-update-screen-recording-app-permissions-monthly.2433732/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.6, Downgrading No Longer an Option</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6-downgrading-no-longer-an-option.2433728/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:20:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 17.6, preventing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from downgrading to that version of iOS. The update is no longer being signed after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/apple-releases-ios-17-6-1/">released iOS 17.6.1 on August 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" /><br/>
Apple regularly stops signing older version of iOS, typically within a week or two after a new version is released. When Apple stops signing an update, it can no longer be installed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; due to a server-side software verification check, so those who have updated to the latest version of iOS cannot downgrade.<br/>
<br/>
Preventing downgrading encourages users to keep their operating systems up to date with the latest security fixes.<br/>
<br/>
This policy encourages users to keep their operating systems up to date, ensuring they have the latest security enhancements.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.6 focused on introducing security fixes, while iOS 17.6.1 added a fix for a bug that could prevent the enabling or disabling of Advanced Data Protection.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.5.1 addressed a corruption bug that could cause <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">deleted photos to reappear on an iPhone</a>. There were no notable features in the iOS 17.6 update, with Apple adding unspecified bug fixes and security updates.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.6, Downgrading No Longer an Option</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-6-downgrading-no-longer-an-option.2433728/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>United States Fines T-Mobile &#36;60 Million for Failing to Prevent Unauthorized Access to Sensitive Customer Data</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/t-mobile-60-million-data-breach-fine/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/united-states-fines-t-mobile-60-million-for-failing-to-prevent-unauthorized-access-to-sensitive-customer-data.2433723/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:32:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/t-mobile-60-million-data-breach-fine/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile was fined &#36;60 million by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the US (CFIUS) for negligence surrounding data breaches, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-14/us-watchdog-cfius-discloses-60-million-fine-against-t-mobile">Reuters</a></em>. CFIUS penalized T-Mobile for failing to prevent or disclose unauthorized access to sensitive customer data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/T-Mobile-Generic-Feature-Pink-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951944" /><br/>
When T-Mobile merged with Sprint, it signed a national security agreement with CFIUS, which is what led to the fine earlier this year. T-Mobile is owned by German company Deutsche Telekom, and T-Mobile agreed to protect consumer data as part of the Sprint acquisition. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/16/t-mobile-data-breach/">Back in 2021</a>, T-Mobile suffered a major breach that impacted over 100 million of its users, just a year after it acquired Sprint.<br/>
<br/>
CFIUS does not typically name the companies that it fines, but T-Mobile has been called out in an effort to push companies to comply with national security rules associated with acquisitions.<blockquote>In 2024, following an initial Notice of Penalty issued in 2023, CFIUS resolved an enforcement action against T-Mobile US, Inc. ("T-Mobile"), a telecommunications company, resulting in a &#36;60 million penalty. As publicly disclosed by T-Mobile, the company entered into a National Security Agreement ("NSA") with CFIUS in 2018 in connection with T-Mobile's merger with Sprint and the foreign ownership of the resulting entity. CFIUS determined that between August 2020 and June 2021, in violation of a material provision of the NSA, T-Mobile failed to take appropriate measures to prevent unauthorized access to certain sensitive data and failed to report some incidents of unauthorized access promptly to CFIUS, delaying the Committee's efforts to investigate and mitigate any potential harm. CFIUS concluded that these violations resulted in harm to the national security equities of the United States. T-Mobile has worked with CFIUS to enhance its compliance posture and obligations and has committed to working cooperatively with the U.S. Government to ensure compliance with its obligations going forward.</blockquote>T-Mobile told <em>Reuters</em> that it experienced technical issues when integrating with Sprint, which affected information from "a small number of law enforcement information requests." T-Mobile claims to have swiftly dealt with the issue and reported it "in a timely manner."<br/>
<br/>
CFIUS said that T-Mobile's lack of timely reporting prevented CFIUS from investigating and mitigating potential harm to U.S. national security.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/t-mobile-60-million-data-breach-fine/">United States Fines T-Mobile &#36;60 Million for Failing to Prevent Unauthorized Access to Sensitive Customer Data</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/united-states-fines-t-mobile-60-million-for-failing-to-prevent-unauthorized-access-to-sensitive-customer-data.2433723/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Gaining Support for Analytics, Scheduling Posts, Multiple Drafts and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/threads-analytics-post-scheduling/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-gaining-support-for-analytics-scheduling-posts-multiple-drafts-and-more.2433721/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:25:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/threads-analytics-post-scheduling/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Threads, Meta's social network that's meant to rival X, today announced <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2024/08/new-threads-features-for-creators-and-businesses/">several new features</a> that are available or coming soon. For creators, Threads is launching analytics for performance measurement.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
Users can see view numbers, replies, reposts, and quotes, along with follower count over time and follower demographics like age, location, and gender.<br/>
<br/>
Threads on the web is gaining support for writing and saving multiple drafts of posts before sharing them with an audience. Up to 100 ideas can be saved in the new Drafts section. To go along with drafts, Threads plans to add scheduling, so Threads can be created and scheduled to go up at a later date and time. Multiple posts can be scheduled per day, multiple days in advance.<br/>
<br/>
While these features are available only on the web at the current time, Threads plans to bring them to the mobile versions of the app in the future. Insights and multiple drafts are rolling out now, and scheduling posts will be coming soon.<br/>
<br/>
It has now been just over a year since Threads launched, and it has over 28 million daily active users. Meta has been regularly adding new features to the social network to put it on par with X (formerly Twitter).<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/threads-analytics-post-scheduling/">Threads Gaining Support for Analytics, Scheduling Posts, Multiple Drafts and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-gaining-support-for-analytics-scheduling-posts-multiple-drafts-and-more.2433721/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Display Panels for M4 MacBook Pro Shipping Ahead of Q4 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/display-panels-for-m4-macbook-pro-shipping-ahead-of-q4-launch.2433715/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Display panels destined for the 14-inch and 16-inch M4 models are shipping to Apple in July and August, timing that makes sense for a launch in the fourth quarter, according to display analyst Ross Young.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/M4-Real-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950311" /><br/>
Young shared the information <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1824130598975443363">in a tweet</a> for subscribers, confirming rumors that new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4 chips will come out before the end of the year. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said earlier this month that Apple will update the MacBook Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> lines with M4 chip technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/">in late 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models will get M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max chips. The entry-level 14-inch model will have the M4, while higher end 14-inch models and 16-inch models will get the M4 Pro and M4 Max, which have not yet been unveiled. Apple first introduced the M4 in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> in May.<br/>
<br/>
No redesign is expected, but Apple will overhaul the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; that's expected to be refreshed alongside the MacBook Pro models. The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will feature a smaller footprint, and it will be Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">smallest ever computer</a>. It could be around the size of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, though a little taller.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 chip is built on TSMC's 3-nanometer process, much like the M3, but there are performance and efficiency improvements. Apple also included a new, more powerful Neural Engine for AI workloads.<br/>
<br/>
With new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch models planned for Apple's annual September event, new Macs could come out at a second event in October or November or they could be unveiled through a press release.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/">also plans to refresh</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> with M4 chips, but those updates will not happen until 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/">Display Panels for M4 MacBook Pro Shipping Ahead of Q4 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/display-panels-for-m4-macbook-pro-shipping-ahead-of-q4-launch.2433715/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Rolling Out Soon in California</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-rolling-out-soon-in-california.2433707/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:17:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		<category>California</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[California will <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/drivers-licenses-and-state-ids-in-apple-wallet-are-coming-soon-to-california/">soon start rolling out support</a> for digital driver's licenses and IDs in the Apple Wallet app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch, becoming the sixth state to implement the feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-california-drivers-license.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961769" /><br/>
Wallet app integration is part of California's mobile driver's license effort, which kicked off a year ago. More than 500,000 people have already added a driver's license or ID to the California DMV Wallet app, where California tested the option before rolling it out to the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>"We're excited to be working with the state of California to bring IDs in Apple Wallet to Apple's home state soon, and provide residents with an easy, secure, and private way to present their California driver's license and state ID in person and in app using Apple Wallet," said Jennifer Bailey, Apple's vice president of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet. "Whether using IDs in Apple Wallet to breeze through travel, or to securely verify age or identity at businesses, California driver's licenses and state IDs in Apple Wallet make ID presentment seamless -- all with the security built into iPhone and Apple Watch."</blockquote><br/>
IDs and licenses stored in the Wallet app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> can be used for TSA screenings at select airports and for age verification at select stores. Right now, California's mobile wallet support is still in a pilot stage, and only 1.5 million participants are able to sign up.<br/>
<br/>
California requires people to continue to carry a physical license or ID card because the digital license is not accepted by law enforcement, state government agencies, and most businesses.<br/>
<br/>
Evidence that Apple Wallet integration was coming to California first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/iphone-drivers-license-support-coming-california/">surfaced earlier in August</a> when a hidden landing page on the DMV website was discovered, but California and Apple are officially announcing the feature today.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced a new Wallet app that supported digital IDs back in 2022, but states have been slow to adopt the feature. So far, only Arizona, Colorado, Georgia, Maryland, and Ohio have implemented support. Apple said in 2022 that Connecticut, Iowa, Kentucky, Oklahoma, and Utah are also working on support.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/california/">California</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/">iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Rolling Out Soon in California</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-rolling-out-soon-in-california.2433707/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Primate Labs Debuts New Geekbench Suite for AI-Centric Workloads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/primate-labs-geekbench-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/primate-labs-debuts-new-geekbench-suite-for-ai-centric-workloads.2433705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/primate-labs-geekbench-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Geekbench</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following extended testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/geekbench-ml-macos/">under the "Geekbench ML" name</a>, Primate Labs is officially launching its new benchmarking suite optimized for AI-centric workloads under the name <a href="https://www.geekbench.com/ai/">Geekbench AI</a>. The tool seeks to measure hardware performance under a variety of workloads focused on machine learning, deep learning, and other AI-centric tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/geekbench-ai.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961692" /><br/>
Geekbench AI 1.0 examines some of the unique workloads associated with AI tasks and seeks to encompass the variety of hardware designs employed by vendors to tackle these tasks, delivering a three-score summary as part of its benchmarking results to reflect a range of precision levels: single-precision, half-precision, and quantized data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/geekbench-ai-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961693" /><br/>
In addition to these performance scores, Geekbench AI also includes an accuracy measurement on a per-test basis, allowing developers to improve efficiency and reliability while assessing the benefits and drawbacks of various engineering approaches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/geekbench-ai-mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961694" /><br/>
Finally, the 1.0 release of Geekbench AI includes support for new frameworks and more extensive data sets that more closely reflect real-world inputs, improving the accuracy evaluations in the suite.<br/>
<br/>
Geekbench AI is <a href="https://www.geekbench.com/ai/download/">available for an array of platforms</a>, including iOS, macOS, Windows, Android, and Linux.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/geekbench/">Geekbench</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/primate-labs-geekbench-ai/">Primate Labs Debuts New Geekbench Suite for AI-Centric Workloads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/primate-labs-debuts-new-geekbench-suite-for-ai-centric-workloads.2433705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Developers Must Share Phone Number and Address on EU App Store to Meet &#039;Trader&#039; Requirement Starting in October</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-must-share-phone-number-and-address-on-eu-app-store-to-meet-trader-requirement-starting-in-october.2433704/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:54:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=a0nevv65">today reminded developers</a> who plan to distribute apps in the European Union to submit <a href="https://developer.apple.com/help/app-store-connect/manage-compliance-information/manage-european-union-digital-services-act-trader-requirements/">their trader status</a>, a requirement that will see the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> sharing the address, phone number, and email address of each developer. The information will be displayed on a developer's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; page.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/app-store-trader-requirement-dsa.jpg" alt="" width="1538" height="865" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961762" /><br/>
The Digital Services Act (DSA) in the European Union requires Apple to verify and display trader contract information for all "traders" who are distributing apps on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the European Union. Developers who make money from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; through an upfront cost or through in-app purchases are considered traders, regardless of size.<br/>
<br/>
Contact information for each developer that is classified as a trader will be publicly available, and many developers are unhappy with the requirement. Independent developers and small companies may not have business addresses and phone numbers to provide, and are understandably reluctant to provide their personal contact information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will require trader status to submit app updates starting on October 16, 2024. Trader information must be provided before an app can be submitted for review. On February 17, 2025, apps without trader status will be removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the EU until trader status is provided and verified.<br/>
<br/>
As displaying trader status is a Digital Services Act requirement in the European Union, Apple does not have a choice on implementing the feature. Developer contact information will be displayed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; product page when an app is distributed in any of the 27 territories in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
More information on determining who is a trader and who needs to provide contact details can be <a href="https://developer.apple.com/help/app-store-connect/manage-compliance-information/manage-european-union-digital-services-act-trader-requirements/">found on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/">Developers Must Share Phone Number and Address on EU App Store to Meet &#039;Trader&#039; Requirement Starting in October</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-must-share-phone-number-and-address-on-eu-app-store-to-meet-trader-requirement-starting-in-october.2433704/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Watch Ultra More Popular Than Apple Watch SE</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-se/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-apple-watch-se.2433700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:57:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-se/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Ultra is considerably more popular than the entry-level <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> despite its high price point, according to a <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/apple-watch-models-trend-toward-the">new report</a> from Consumer Intelligence Research Partners (CIRP).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-1-1.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-866346" /><br/>
The report provides a detailed look at how the various Apple Watch models are performing in the market. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, introduced in September 2023 alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, is the most popular model in the lineup as of the June 2024 quarter. It captured 43% of total Apple Watch sales in the United States, making it the top choice among customers. The Series 8, which Apple no longer sells directly but is still available through various retailers, followed with a 19% share. Combined, these two models accounted for nearly two-thirds of all Apple Watch sales during the period.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra and Ultra 2, which represent the high-end segment of the lineup, contributed 20% of total sales. Despite their advanced features and premium positioning, the Ultra models have a smaller market share compared to the high-end variants of other Apple products like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. For instance, premium models in these categories typically account for a quarter or more of total sales. The CIRP report indicates that the Ultra 2 had a slightly higher share than the original Ultra during the June 2024 quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/cirp-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="827" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-961744" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; held a 12% market share. This model continues to attract buyers who are looking for a more affordable entry point into the Apple Watch, yet its market presence is significantly smaller than that of the higher end models. The Nike-branded version of the Apple Watch, which is essentially a variant of the Series 8 and 9, accounted for a modest 5% of the market.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's strategy of offering a range of models at different price points appears to mirror its approach with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. However, there are some notable differences in consumer behavior across these product lines. While the premium models of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; often capture a larger share of sales, the Apple Watch lineup sees stronger performance in its mid-range models. The CIRP report suggests that the Series 8 and Series 9, positioned as a mid-tier option in terms of pricing and features, is particularly attractive to consumers, while the Ultra models, despite their higher price and more advanced capabilities, appeal to a smaller segment of the market. The low-cost &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; and Nike models appeal to an even smaller segment of the market.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-se/">Report: Apple Watch Ultra More Popular Than Apple Watch SE</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-watch-ultra-more-popular-than-apple-watch-se.2433700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;200 Off M4 iPad Pro, Starting at &#36;899</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-200-off-m4-ipad-pro-starting-at-899.2433698/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:33:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a large collection of discounts on the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2024 M4 iPad Pro</a> at Amazon, which includes multiple all-time low prices on both 11-inch and 13-inch models. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
For the smaller 11-inch M4 iPad Pro, Amazon has an all-time low price on the entry-level 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. Amazon has every model of the 11-inch iPad Pro on sale right now, including both Wi-Fi and cellular versions.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;899.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,484.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6RX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J89FYD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,899.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JBX6ML%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;2,099.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-Inch</h3><br/>
Similar to the 11-inch models, Amazon has every Wi-Fi and cellular version of the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro on sale this week. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J98W75%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,197.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, and totals up to &#36;200 off these devices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J98W75%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,197.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J776JL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,379.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6S6LS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,839.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,099.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J85MZM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,287.92, down from &#36;2,399.00</li></ul>  Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-ipad-pro-starting-899/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;200 Off M4 iPad Pro, Starting at &#36;899</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-200-off-m4-ipad-pro-starting-at-899.2433698/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card Named Best in Customer Satisfaction for Fourth Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-for-fourth-year.2433696/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:18:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> has been <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-by-jd-power/">recognized</a> as the best co-branded credit card for customer satisfaction with no annual fee for the fourth consecutive year by J.D. Power.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/apple-card-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-785924" /><br/>
As highlighted by Apple in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-by-jd-power/">press release</a> earlier today, this is the fourth year in a row that the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;, issued by Goldman Sachs, has earned the top spot in J.D. Power's 2024 U.S. Credit Card Satisfaction Study. The study measures overall customer satisfaction by assessing performance across several categories, including Account Management, Customer Service, and New Account Experience. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; was first introduced in 2019 and is deeply integrated into the Wallet app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, allowing users to track their spending in real time, categorize transactions, and set up payment plans. The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; also offers up to three percent Daily Cash on purchases, which can be used instantly or saved for future expenses. With &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; Family, users can share an &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; account with other members of their Family Sharing group. The &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; also features an integrated a Savings account option, providing users with the ability to automatically deposit their Daily Cash rewards into the account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction/">Apple Card Named Best in Customer Satisfaction for Fourth Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-named-best-in-customer-satisfaction-for-fourth-year.2433696/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats and Kim Kardashian Team Up for New Beats Studio Pro Colors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/kim-kardashian-beats-studio-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-and-kim-kardashian-team-up-for-new-beats-studio-pro-colors.2433693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/kim-kardashian-beats-studio-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Beats Studio Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/09/beats-fit-pro-kim-kardashian-colors/">successful 2022 collaboration with Kim Kardashian</a> for a set of three neutral color options for the Beats Fit Pro earphones, the <a href="http://apple.com/beatsxkim">"Beats x Kim" campaign is back</a> to bring the same colors to the Beats Studio Pro headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/kim-kardashian-beats-studio-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961587" /><br/>
As with the Beats Fit Pro, the new Beats Studio Pro color options from Kardashian's signature palette include Moon (light), Dune (medium), and Earth (deep).<blockquote>"I'm so excited we're bringing these three popular, chic colors to Beats' most iconic and advanced headphones," said Kim Kardashian. "Beats Studio have always been a fashion statement, so I can't wait to see how everyone styles them."</blockquote>Beats Studio Pro are the brand's latest over-ear headphones and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/beats-studio-pro-debut/">were originally released in July 2023</a>. They offer Active Noise Cancellation and Transparency modes, Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking, improved audio quality, and up to 40 hours of battery life. Connectivity options include Class 1 Bluetooth, USB-C, and 3.5mm analog.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Beats brand has been building up to today's launch with an ad campaign featuring Kardashian and Jimmy Fallon vying for the next Beats collaboration, with Kardashian's neutral Beats x Kim colors going up against a mustard-yellow "Beats x Jim" option that apparently did not make the cut.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/21029bAd4_w?si=sSiOeTyqiGJVwkdq" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The new Beats x Kim Beats Studio Pro headphones are priced at &#36;349.99 in the United States, and they are launching today through <a href="http://apple.com/beatsxkim">Apple's online stores</a> in the US, Canada, Mexico, UK, France, Germany, Japan, China, South Korea, Hong Kong, and Thailand, with limited availability at select Apple retail stores in those countries. They are also <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=http%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2Fbeatsxkim">available through Amazon</a> in the US, Canada, Mexico, and Japan, and at Argos in the UK, JB Hi-Fi in Australia, and Tmall and JD.com in China.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats-studio-pro/">Beats Studio Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/kim-kardashian-beats-studio-pro/">Beats and Kim Kardashian Team Up for New Beats Studio Pro Colors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-and-kim-kardashian-team-up-for-new-beats-studio-pro-colors.2433693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AltStore Pal Now Free Thanks to &#039;MegaGrant&#039; From Epic Games</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/altstore-pal-now-free-epic-games/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/altstore-pal-now-free-thanks-to-megagrant-from-epic-games.2433686/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:57:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/altstore-pal-now-free-epic-games/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://altstore.io/">AltStore PAL</a>, the open-source app that is designed to distribute apps in the EU from independent developers, is now free thanks to a grant provided by <em>Fortnite</em> developer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/altstore-pal-eu.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947008" /><br/>
The alternative iOS app store had charged a €1.50 plus tax annual subscription, in order to cover Apple's Core Technology Fee (CTF). Apple's terms for alternative app marketplaces requires developers to pay the CTF for each annual app installation.<br/>
<br/>
However, AltStore Pal will no longer pass on the cost of this fee after the third-party store received a "<a href="https://www.unrealengine.com/en-US/megagrants">MegaGrant</a>" from &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;. <a href="https://x.com/altstoreio/status/1823826482046886273">AltStore said</a> that existing subscribers won't be charged upon their renewal date, and that the AltStore team plans to "show our appreciation for our existing subscribers in a future update," but didn't go into details.<br/>
<br/>
Developer Riley Testut has been working on AltStore PAL since Apple announced plans to support alternative app marketplaces in iOS 17.4. It is open to all apps, but Testut says that it makes the most sense for "smaller, indie apps that otherwise couldn't exist due to ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>‌ rules."<br/>
<br/>
AltStore PAL is equipped with Patreon integration to allow developers to monetize their apps. Developers can offer their apps to just their patrons, and this method of distribution also allows for a sub-1 million cap on those who can subscribe to use an app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">GOOD NEWS EU &#x1f1ea;&#x1f1fa; For innovation in app distribution, Epic Games has granted us a MegaGrant grant that we plan to use to cover Apple’s Core Technology Fee going forward — and we won’t take it for granted!<br><br>What does this mean? AltStore PAL is now FREE — no subscription necessary &#x1f389; <a href="https://t.co/JSJo3FdhBx">pic.twitter.com/JSJo3FdhBx</a></p>&mdash; AltStore.io (@altstoreio) <a href="https://twitter.com/altstoreio/status/1823826343085433226?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 14, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in the European Union can download AltStore PAL from the AltStore website. Alternative app marketplaces are not available outside of the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
As for Epic, it has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/">submitted</a> the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store to Apple for notarization under Apple's alternative app marketplace policy in the European Union. The ‌&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;‌ Store will include <em>Fortnite</em>, which means ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ users in the EU will be able to install and play the title without having to use a cloud gaming service. An ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>‌ version of Fortnite is expected to follow this year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/altstore-pal-now-free-epic-games/">AltStore Pal Now Free Thanks to &#039;MegaGrant&#039; From Epic Games</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/altstore-pal-now-free-thanks-to-megagrant-from-epic-games.2433686/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Get macOS Sequoia 15.1 Beta With Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-macos-sequoia-15-1-beta-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-get-macos-sequoia-15-1-beta-with-apple-intelligence.2433683/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:05:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-macos-sequoia-15-1-beta-apple-intelligence&#038;post_date=1723734358/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has made available the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-2-to-developers/">second developer beta</a> of macOS Sequoia 15.1, which includes the ability to test Apple Intelligence features. If you have an Apple silicon Mac and don't live in China, you can try Apple Intelligence features for yourself, even if you're not a developer. Keep reading to learn how.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macOS-Sequoia-Night-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961501" /><br/>
Apple has split Apple Intelligence into a separate set of betas for Macs because these features will not be available in the initial launch version of ‌macOS Sequoia‌ 15. Apple Intelligence will be available to the public later in the fall with the release of macOS Sequoia 15.1. <br/>
<br/>
This point release will add several of the Apple Intelligence features, such as Writing Tools, an updated Siri design, Safari and Mail summaries, Reduce Interruptions Focus mode, and more. Other features, including Image Playground, Genmoji, and the Siri personal context and onscreen awareness will be coming later and are not in the macOS Sequoia 15.1 beta. You can learn more about what's available and when in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/#apple_intelligence">macOS 15 roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The good news is that Apple has already seeded the second developer beta of macOS 15.1, which means you can try some of the AI features out for yourself by signing up for macOS beta access. Signing up to get the macOS Sequoia beta is simple, and can be done by following the steps below. Be sure to back up your Mac using Time Machine before going on to follow the beta software installation steps, otherwise you won't be able to revert back to your previous version of macOS if you need to.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Things to Remember Before You Start</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Back up Your Mac.</li><br/>
<li>Apple Intelligence requires a Mac with an M1 Apple silicon processor or later.</li><br/>
<li>Apple Intelligence is only available in US English.</li><br/>
<li>Apple Intelligence for Mac is not available in China, but appears to be available in the EU and everywhere else when region and language settings are changed to United States (see below).</li><br/>
<li>Apple Intelligence is not available if macOS 15.1 is installed on an external drive.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Register for Developer Beta Access</h2><br/>
You can skip this first set of steps if you have previously joined the Apple Developer Program with your Apple ID. Note that registering in this way is free, and <strong>does not require paying for an Apple Developer Program membership</strong>.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Go to the Apple Developer website (<a href="https://developer.apple.com/account">developer.apple.com/account</a>) and sign in with your Apple ID.</li><br/>
  <li>Check the box to accept the terms and conditions, then tap the <strong>Submit</strong> button.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-developer-website.jpg" alt="apple developer" width="1361" height="872" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961716" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. You can now proceed to the next steps to download and install the macOS Sequoia 15.1 developer beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Download macOS 15.1 Beta</h2><br/>
To download and install the macOS Sequoia 15.1 Developer beta, follow these steps on your Mac.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Go to <strong>System Settings ➝ General ➝ Software Update</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Click the info button ⓘ next to "Beta updates."<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/1macos-15-beta-install.jpg" alt="settings" width="980" height="604" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961717" /><br/>
  <li>Choose the <strong>macOS Sequoia 15.1 Developer Beta</strong> option, then click <strong>Done</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/2macos-15-beta-install.jpg" alt="settings" width="1518" height="604" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961718" /><br/>
  <li>When the <strong>macOS 15 Sequoia 15.1 Beta</strong> update appears, click the <strong>Upgrade Now</strong> button to start downloading and installing it on your Mac.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/3macos-15-beta-install.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="972" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961719" /><br/>
</ol><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Activate Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
The following steps explain how to join the Apple Intelligence waitlist, which usually grants you access to the AI features in just a few minutes.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Go to <strong>System Settings ➝ Apple Intelligence & Siri</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Set Siri's language to <strong>English (United States)</strong>, and decline to restart your Mac at the prompt for now.</li><br/>
  <li>Set Voice to <strong>American</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/2macos-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="settings" width="1464" height="1141" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961720" /><br/>
  <li>Next, go to <strong>System Settings ➝ General ➝ Language & Region</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Click the "Region" selector and choose <strong>United States</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Under "Preferred Languages," click <strong>+</strong> and add <strong>English (US)</strong>, then set English (US) as the Primary language by dragging it above your other language(s).</li><br/>
  <li>Restart your Mac when prompted.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/1macos-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="settings" width="1472" height="901" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961721" /><br/>
  <li>After restarting, go to <strong>Settings ➝ Apple Intelligence & Siri</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Click the option to <strong>Join the Apple Intelligence waitlist</strong>. You will be notified when Apple Intelligence features are available for your Mac. In most cases this should take only a few minutes, but don't rule out waiting a couple of hours.</li><br/>
<li>When Apple Intelligence is available, toggle the switch to enable it.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/3macos-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="settings" width="1475" height="904" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961722" /><br/>
</ol>Note that Apple Intelligence will not be in the initial launch version of iOS 18 that comes out in September alongside new iPhones. It will instead be introduced in a separate iOS 18.1 update that is likely to come out a few weeks after ‌iOS 18‌ debuts. Have you had a chance to try out Apple Intelligence features on Mac? Let us know of your experience in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-macos-sequoia-15-1-beta-apple-intelligence/">How to Get macOS Sequoia 15.1 Beta With Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-get-macos-sequoia-15-1-beta-with-apple-intelligence.2433683/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Considering Bringing Back Its Old Mobile App Amid Ongoing Issues</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/sonos-bring-back-old-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-considering-bringing-back-its-old-mobile-app-amid-ongoing-issues.2433647/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:41:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/sonos-bring-back-old-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a few months after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">debuting an all-new mobile app</a> for controlling its audio products, Sonos is considering bringing back the previous version of the app following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/">numerous user complaints</a>, <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/14/24220421/sonos-s2-app-relaunch">reports <em>The Verge</em></a></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
While Sonos has been working to address a number of missing features and issues with the new app and has laid out a timeline to keep users updated on the company's progress, <em>The Verge</em> reports that "discussions high up within Sonos" have centered around potentially offering the old app as an interim solution.<blockquote>Letting customers fall back to the older software could ease their frustrations and reduce at least some of the pressure on Sonos to rectify every issue with the new app. At least for now, the redesigned version is all that’s available, which makes it impossible for some customers to avoid its flaws.</blockquote>Just last week, Sonos CEO Patrick Spence <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delays-product-launces-to-fix-app/">revealed on the company's earnings call</a> that it will be delaying two upcoming product launches due to "challenges with our new app." While Spence did not identify the products in question, one of them is likely to be the successor to the company's flagship Arc soundbar.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/sonos-bring-back-old-app/">Sonos Considering Bringing Back Its Old Mobile App Amid Ongoing Issues</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-considering-bringing-back-its-old-mobile-app-amid-ongoing-issues.2433647/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Aiming to Launch Tabletop Robotic Home Device as Soon as 2026 With Pricing Around &#36;1,000</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/apple-tabletop-robotic-home-device-2026/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-aiming-to-launch-tabletop-robotic-home-device-as-soon-as-2026-with-pricing-around-1-000.2433643/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:30:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/apple-tabletop-robotic-home-device-2026/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is moving forward with its project to develop a tabletop robotic device, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-14/apple-pushes-ahead-with-tabletop-home-device-in-shift-to-robotics">according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/G-vEDI_dr-Y" title="Apple is Making a Tabletop Robotic Home Device &#x1f914;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The device would feature a large iPad-like display mounted on a "thin robotic arm" that would allow the display to tilt and up and down and rotate a full 360º, and it would serve as a "smart home command center," a videoconferencing machine such as for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls, and a home security monitoring tool.<br/>
<br/>
The tabletop robot would leverage <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and Apple Intelligence, allowing it to respond to an array of verbal commands, recognize different voices, and automatically orient the display to face users in the room. <br/>
<br/>
While Apple has been toying with the idea for some time, Gurman says Apple has recently prioritized development of the device, putting it under the purview of Kevin Lynch, Apple's vice president of technology who has overseen such projects as the Apple Watch and Apple's defunct self-driving car venture.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is now looking to launch the device as soon as 2026 or 2027 and is aiming to get the price down to around &#36;1,000, though plans may change as development proceeds.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/apple-tabletop-robotic-home-device-2026/">Apple Aiming to Launch Tabletop Robotic Home Device as Soon as 2026 With Pricing Around &#36;1,000</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-aiming-to-launch-tabletop-robotic-home-device-as-soon-as-2026-with-pricing-around-1-000.2433643/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
