<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:00:58 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;100 Off 9th and 10th Gen iPads, Starting at &#36;229</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/amazon-9th-10th-gen-ipads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-100-off-9th-and-10th-gen-ipads-starting-at-229.2433123/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:02:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/amazon-9th-10th-gen-ipads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today is offering up to &#36;100 off the 9th generation and 10th generation iPads, starting as low as <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;229.00</strong></a> for the former model. Most of the iPads in this sale can be delivered as soon as the end of this week for Prime members, and by early next week for everyone else.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ipad-best-buy-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946064" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 2021 9th generation iPad, Amazon has introduced a new all-time low price on this tablet. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;229.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00, and the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;379.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;479.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;229.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This is the iPad generation from before the design overhaul of the 10th generation, so it features a Home Button with Touch ID, A13 Bionic chip, and a 10.2-inch Retina display. Anyone looking for a simple and cheap iPad model to have for daily Internet browsing should be satisfied with this one.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-ipad-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940260" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the more recent 10th generation iPad from 2022, Amazon also has a few solid low prices on these models. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;299.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;349.00, and the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDDCGS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;499.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDDCGS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple released these iPads in October 2022 with a complete redesign, introducing a larger display, USB-C port, A14 Bionic chip, and slim bezel design similar to the iPad Pro lineup. Although we're expecting an update to these iPads later this year, anyone looking for an iPad now who doesn't want to wait should definitely take advantage of Amazon's low prices.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/amazon-9th-10th-gen-ipads/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;100 Off 9th and 10th Gen iPads, Starting at &#36;229</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-100-off-9th-and-10th-gen-ipads-starting-at-229.2433123/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Hide App Names on Your iPhone Home Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/hide-app-icon-labels-iphone-home-screen/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-hide-app-names-on-your-iphone-home-screen.2433122/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:00:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/hide-app-icon-labels-iphone-home-screen&#038;post_date=1723050017/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, currently in beta, Apple has broadened the customization options for the Home Screen on iPhone, and thanks to a new setting it is now possible to make app icons and widgets bigger by hiding their labels. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/big-icons-home-screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960988" /><br/>
With the setting enabled in iOS 18, the names of apps are removed from the grid, which increases the size of the icons and widgets on your Home Screen with the space saved. With larger icons, you still get a maximum of six icon rows with four icons each, the same that you're limited to when icon names are turned on.<br/>
<br/>
If you're familiar enough with your favorite apps that you don't feel the need to see the names underneath the icons, then it's worth giving it a try. With the labels removed, the design of your app icons takes center stage, resulting in a cleaner look for your Home Screen. Note that this setting is universal, so you cannot have small icons on one app page and large icons on a different app page.<br/>
<br/>
The following steps show you how it's done.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Press on an empty space on your Home Screen to enter jiggle mode.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the <strong>Edit</strong> button in the top-left corner, then choose <strong>Customize</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the <strong>Large</strong> option in the customization panel.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap on an empty space to hide the customization panel.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/large-home-screen-app-icons.jpg" alt="Home Screen" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960989" /><br/>
That's all there is to it. If you decide you want to see app labels again, simply repeat the steps, but choose the <strong>Small</strong> option in the customization panel instead. iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">currently in public beta</a> and will be officially released to iPhone users in the fall.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/hide-app-icon-labels-iphone-home-screen/">iOS 18: Hide App Names on Your iPhone Home Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-hide-app-names-on-your-iphone-home-screen.2433122/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google TV Streamer Announced as Chromecast Replacement and Rival to Apple TV 4K</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/google-tv-streamer-announced/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-tv-streamer-announced-as-chromecast-replacement-and-rival-to-apple-tv-4k.2433121/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 06:40:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/google-tv-streamer-announced/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Chromecast</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google has <a href="https://blog.google/products/google-nest/google-tv-streamer/">announced</a> the Google TV Streamer, a new device that replaces the Chromecast and directly rivals the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/google-tv.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="563" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960978" /><br/>
The discontinuation of the Chromecast marks the end of an era for Google's original streaming dongle, which has been a staple in the market since its launch in 2013. Over 100 million Chromecast devices were sold during its 11-year run. The Google TV Streamer is positioned as a high-end replacement for the Chromecast, promising to deliver a next-generation, AI-powered streaming experience while also functioning as a central hub for smart home devices.<br/>
<br/>
The Google TV Streamer provides access to over 700,000 movies and shows through popular streaming apps like YouTube TV, Netflix, Disney+, and &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, as well as live TV with over 800 free channels. One of the standout features is the AI-powered content recommendation system, which uses Google's Gemini technology to curate personalized watchlists and provide detailed summaries, reviews, and season-by-season breakdowns of content.<br/>
<br/>
The Google TV Streamer features a faster processor, double the memory, and 32GB of storage. It supports 4K HDR with Dolby Vision and Dolby Atmos. <br/>
<br/>
The Google TV Streamer is available in two colors: Porcelain and Hazel, with the latter being exclusive to the U.S. Google Store. The device is intended to sit in front of the TV, rather than behind it, to improve connectivity with smart home devices. The Google TV Streamer supports Matter and includes a built-in Thread border router, which enhances the connectivity and response times of smart home devices like locks and motion sensors.<br/>
<br/>
The redesigned voice remote features improved ergonomics with a textured back for better grip and an optimized button layout. It includes a customizable button that can be programmed to open a favorite app, switch inputs, or launch the Google Home panel. The remote also has a built-in "find my remote" feature, allowing users to locate it by voice command or by pressing a button on the back of the device.<br/>
<br/>
The Google TV Streamer is positioned to rival high-end streaming devices such as the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K. While the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K offers similar features like 4K HDR and Dolby Vision support, the Google TV Streamer is priced more competitively at &#36;99.99 compared to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K's starting price of &#36;129. The Google TV Streamer includes Ethernet connectivity as standard, but it lacks the additional storage options that the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K provides, with Apple offering both 64GB and 128GB models.<br/>
<br/>
The Google TV Streamer is <a href="https://store.google.com/product/google_tv_streamer">now available for pre-order</a>, with shipping set to begin on September 24, 2024.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chromecast/">Chromecast</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/google-tv-streamer-announced/">Google TV Streamer Announced as Chromecast Replacement and Rival to Apple TV 4K</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-tv-streamer-announced-as-chromecast-replacement-and-rival-to-apple-tv-4k.2433121/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Lineup Could Launch Earlier Than Usual in Korea</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/iphone-16-lineup-could-launch-earlier-in-korea/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-could-launch-earlier-than-usual-in-korea.2433119/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 06:08:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/iphone-16-lineup-could-launch-earlier-in-korea/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Korea Times</category>
		<category>South Korea</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is considering launching the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup in Korea earlier than usual due to weakening demand in China, the <a href="https://koreatimes.co.kr/www/tech/2024/08/133_380047.html"><em>Korea Times</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Perspective.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-935161" /><br/>
If correct, this would mark a significant shift for Apple, as Korea has not been part of the initial release countries since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 3GS in 2009. Apple is expected to launch the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup in mid-September, with an announcement on the 10th being the most probable date based on the company's historical patterns. Sources speaking to the <em>Korea Times</em> claim that preparations appear to be underway for an early release in the country.<br/>
<br/>
Historically, despite the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s strong market share in Korea, new models have been released in the country weeks after their debut in other markets. This is partly due to Apple's rigorous confidentiality policies and Korea's stringent certification system. All electronic devices in Korea must be certified by the National Radio Research Agency, and details about these devices are disclosed on the agency's website, which could lead to premature leaks of new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; specifications.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these challenges, Apple appears to be reconsidering its strategy for the Korean market, driven by the country's steady demand and the potential for positive early sales. Data from Canalys claims that Apple's market share in China dropped to 14% in the second quarter of this year, down from 16% a year earlier. This decline <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-drops-to-sixth-place-in-china/">pushed Apple out of the top five smartphone vendors</a> in China, potentially providing an opportunity to reallocate inventory to other markets, such as Korea.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/koreatimes-co-kr/">Korea Times</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/south-korea/">South Korea</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/iphone-16-lineup-could-launch-earlier-in-korea/">iPhone 16 Lineup Could Launch Earlier Than Usual in Korea</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-could-launch-earlier-than-usual-in-korea.2433119/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Adds Camera Setting to Allow iPhone Audio Playback When Shooting Video</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/ios-18-shoot-video-during-audio-playback/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-adds-camera-setting-to-allow-iphone-audio-playback-when-shooting-video.2433116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:11:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/ios-18-shoot-video-during-audio-playback/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, Apple has added a control in the Camera app's Settings menu that lets you choose whether audio playing on your iPhone should pause or continue when you start recording in Video mode.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/allow-audio-playback-camera-setting.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960959" /><br/>
In previous versions of iOS, shooting in Video mode in the Camera app automatically pauses any playing audio including music and podcasts. This behavior is based on the assumption that you don't want any sound coming out of your iPhone's speakers to be picked up on the video recording, but it's no good if you want to play a soundtrack to accompany whatever you're shooting.<br/>
<br/>
One way to get around this is to use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-quicktake-iphone-11/">QuickTake method of recording video</a> in Photo mode, introduced in iOS 13, which allows any audio playback to continue during shooting. The only issue is that QuickTake records in lower quality than Video mode is capable of. <br/>
<br/>
But that won't matter soon, because iOS 18 lets you control what happens to audio playback in dedicated Video mode, thanks to a new Allow Audio Playback toggle. "Audio playback will not pause automatically when recording video," notes Apple under the setting. "When playing audio using the iPhone speaker, audio will be recorded in mono."<br/>
<br/>
iPhone users can look forward to several new features when iOS 18 arrives in the fall, around mid-September, with new customization options, generative AI features, Siri improvements, and more. For details on everything that's new, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">dedicated iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/ios-18-shoot-video-during-audio-playback/">iOS 18 Adds Camera Setting to Allow iPhone Audio Playback When Shooting Video</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-adds-camera-setting-to-allow-iphone-audio-playback-when-shooting-video.2433116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Logitech Says It Has No Plans for a Subscription-Based &#039;Forever Mouse&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/logitech-no-plans-subscription-mouse/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-says-it-has-no-plans-for-a-subscription-based-forever-mouse.2433112/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:26:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/logitech-no-plans-subscription-mouse/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Logitech</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Logitech on Wednesday denied reports that the company is working on a "forever mouse" that could come with a subscription fee for regular software updates, after comments by its CEO suggesting it could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/logitech-forever-mouse/">introduce such a product</a> in the future received immediate backlash.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/logitech-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="1187" height="668" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960435" /><br/>
"There are no plans for a subscription mouse," said Logitech communications head Nicole Kenyon in a statement given to several media publications. Kenyon was responding to reports based on comments made by Logitech chief Hanneke Faber on <a href="https://www.theverge.com/24206847/logitech-ceo-hanneke-faber-mouse-keyboard-gaming-decoder-podcast-interview"><em>The Verge</em>'s Decoder podcast</a> with Nilay Patel. <br/>
<br/>
During the podcast, Faber said that the Logitech innovation center team in Ireland showed her a "forever mouse" that is designed to be used for many years. It's a "little heavier" than a standard mouse, and it has "great software and services" that get constantly updated.<br/>
<br/>
Patel asked Faber if she could "envision a subscription mouse," to which she responded "possibly." Faber went on to explain that customers would "never have to worry about [their mice] again," which is similar to Logitech's video conferencing services.<br/>
<br/>
When asked whether Logitech had some other model for monetization than subscription fees or advertising, Faber said no, and that she was "intrigued" by a forever mouse that has an accompanying business model around software updates.<br/>
<br/>
Kenyon sought to downplay the comments, saying: "The mouse mentioned is not an actual or planned product but a peek into provocative internal thinking on future possibilities for more sustainable consumer electronics."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/logitech/">Logitech</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/logitech-no-plans-subscription-mouse/">Logitech Says It Has No Plans for a Subscription-Based &#039;Forever Mouse&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-says-it-has-no-plans-for-a-subscription-based-forever-mouse.2433112/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Blackmagic Camera App 2.0 Adds Multi-iPhone Control and iPad Version</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/blackmagic-camera-app-2-ipad-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/blackmagic-camera-app-2-0-adds-multi-iphone-control-and-ipad-version.2433108/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:40:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/blackmagic-camera-app-2-ipad-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>DaVinci Resolve</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Blackmagic Design has released version 2.0 of its <a href="https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/blackmagiccamera">Blackmagic Camera app</a>, bringing several new additional features along with official iPad support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/blackmagic-camera-app-ipad.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960948" /><br/>
For readers unfamiliar with the app, Blackmagic Camera features the same digital film camera controls and image processing functions that are available with Blackmagic Design's cameras. The company says that this allows users to create YouTube, TikTok, and Instagram content with a "Hollywood" cinematic look and feel.<br/>
<br/>
In a significant update, version 2.0 of the app adds support for controlling multiple iPhones remotely. With the feature enabled, one iPhone acts as a controller, and other iPhones can be connected using the app via a wired or Wi-Fi network. Users can then control app features like zoom, focus, white balance, frame rate, shutter angle, and lens selection, and synchronize the cameras to record simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
This update also brings support for recording up to 100fps in HD on iPhone 15 Pro models, as well as the ability to select multiple clips in the media tab to share them easily or batch copy/edit them. There are also general performance and stability improvements across the app.<br/>
<br/>
And in a notable new addition, Blackmagic Camera 2.0 introduces iPad support for the first time, allowing users to make the most of the iPad's bigger screen, particularly when monitoring multiple iPhone captures remotely. <br/>
<br/>
Blackmagic Camera integrates with Blackmagic Cloud and uploads content directly to the DaVinci Resolve video editing app. Like DaVinci Resolve for Mac, Blackmagic Camera is free to use, and the app can be <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/blackmagic-camera/id6449580241">downloaded from the App Store</a>. More information on the Blackmagic Camera app for iOS can be found on the <a href="https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/blackmagiccamera">Blackmagic website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/davinci-resolve/">DaVinci Resolve</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/blackmagic-camera-app-2-ipad-support/">Blackmagic Camera App 2.0 Adds Multi-iPhone Control and iPad Version</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/blackmagic-camera-app-2-0-adds-multi-iphone-control-and-ipad-version.2433108/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps Real-Time Transit Information Now Available in Tokyo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/apple-maps-real-time-transit-info-tokyo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-real-time-transit-information-now-available-in-tokyo.2433107/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:35:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/apple-maps-real-time-transit-info-tokyo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		<category>Japan</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Real-time transit information in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> has been expanded to Tokyo, Japan, enabling users to get live details of more than 20 railway, bus, and tram lines throughout the metropolitan area, Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/newsroom/2024/08/apple-maps-introduces-real-time-transit-information-in-tokyo/">announced</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/real-time-transit-maps-tokyo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960942" /><br/>
With real-time updates on &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj;, users in Tokyo can view detailed schedules, real-time departure and arrival times, and transfers to help plan their journeys. Apple adds that important real-time transit information such as service suspensions and delays will also be provided.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the transit information in its Maps app covers services provided by JR East, Tokyo Metro, and other agencies through the ODPT (Open Data Public Transportation Council).<br/>
<br/>
No update is required to get the real-time transit data. Additionally, with the release of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> this fall, users across Japan will also be able to explore detailed topographic maps on their iPhones, complete with contour lines, shaded relief, and hiking trails.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/japan/">Japan</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/apple-maps-real-time-transit-info-tokyo/">Apple Maps Real-Time Transit Information Now Available in Tokyo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-real-time-transit-information-now-available-in-tokyo.2433107/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade to Gain NFL Retro Bowl &#039;25, Monster Train+, and Puzzle Sculpt</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-arcade-september-games/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-to-gain-nfl-retro-bowl-25-monster-train-and-puzzle-sculpt.2433087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:13:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-arcade-september-games/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> gaming service is <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-arcade-launches-three-new-games-in-september-including-nfl-retro-bowl-25/">set to gain three new games</a> in September, including NFL Retro Bowl '25, an NFL and NFLPA-licensed relaunch of the popular Retro Bowl game that initially came out in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-arcade-retro-bowl.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960904" /><br/>
NFL Retro Bowl '25 lets NFL fans create their own football dynasty by selecting their favorite NFL teams and players to manage. The game focuses on roster management and game strategies, with the &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; version offering authentic rosters and NFL players in the original game's retro style.<br/>
<br/>
Monster Train+ is another &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; revamp of a popular original. It is a roguelite deck builder with more than 250 cards to unlock and six monster clans to discover. The &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; version of the game includes a new strategic layer with three vertical playing fields to defend, along with support for The Last Divinity DLC with an additional clan and more gameplay challenges.<br/>
<br/>
For the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is gaining Puzzle Sculpt, a game where players decipher increasingly challenging clues to solve puzzles. Gameplay consists of removing unnecessary cubes to uncover Deco Objects that can then be placed anywhere in the virtual space around the player.<br/>
<br/>
Several &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games are set to get new content updates, including new Shrek-themed hoops for Stitch, a Smithsonian-inspired area in Crayola Create and Play, and Tiana from The Princess and the Frog for Disney Dreamlight Valley.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is priced at &#36;6.99 per month, a fee that allows up to six family members to play games. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; titles have no in-app purchases or ads. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is also part of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a>, Family, and Premier plans.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-arcade-september-games/">Apple Arcade to Gain NFL Retro Bowl &#039;25, Monster Train+, and Puzzle Sculpt</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-to-gain-nfl-retro-bowl-25-monster-train-and-puzzle-sculpt.2433087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Aqara Launches New HomeKit-Compatible Presence Sensor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/aqara-homekit-presence-sensor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/aqara-launches-new-homekit-compatible-presence-sensor.2433083/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:03:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/aqara-homekit-presence-sensor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		<category>Aqara</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Aqara today introduced <a href="https://www.aqara.com/us/product/presence-sensor-fp1e/">a new Presence Sensor</a> that is designed to keep smart home products like lights turned on when someone is in the room. The Presence Sensor FP1E uses Zigbee, but it is able to connect to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> and other smart home platforms through an Aqara Matter bridge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/aqara-presence-sensor.jpg" alt="" width="1785" height="1004" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960901" /><br/>
The Presence Sensor FP1E uses millimeter wave technology to detect even minute human movements for prompt presence detection that can be used to trigger &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; automations. If you want to have a light come on in the laundry room when you go inside, for example, you need a HomeKit-compatible sensor.<br/>
<br/>
A Presence Sensor differs from a motion detection sensor by continuing to recognize when someone is in the room, keeping the automation active. A standard motion sensor might turn on the lights, but will turn off on a timer rather than the continued presence of a person. The FP1E is able to determine that a person is in the room even when the person is sitting or lying still, plus it can recognize when a person leaves the room to trigger an automation to turn off the lights or other home product.<br/>
<br/>
Aqara says that the new Presence Sensor is able to detect presence within a distance of up to 20 feet, and it can monitor a room that is up to 538 square feet in size if it is mounted on the ceiling. The sensor is able to distinguish human movement from pets and inanimate objects like curtains that might shift from the air conditioner.<br/>
<br/>
The FP1E Presence Sensor joins Aqara's previous Presence Sensor FP2, which offers multi-person detection and zone-based automation triggers. The FP1E Presence Sensor is more affordable at &#36;50, and it can be <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D5QPH3T6">purchased from Amazon starting today</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aqara/">Aqara</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/aqara-homekit-presence-sensor/">Aqara Launches New HomeKit-Compatible Presence Sensor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/aqara-launches-new-homekit-compatible-presence-sensor.2433083/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Flighty Now Able to Provide Early Warnings About Flight Delays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/flighty-update-flight-delays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/flighty-now-able-to-provide-early-warnings-about-flight-delays.2433075/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:40:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/flighty-update-flight-delays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Flight tracking app <a href="https://www.flightyapp.com">Flighty</a> was today updated with a new feature that is designed to provide users with additional information on the reason behind delayed flights.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/flighty-app-update.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960897" /><br/>
Flighty is using aviation authority data and machine learning to provide early warnings of delays, and when a delay is official, the reason for the delay. Most delays are due to airspace issues and late aircraft, both of which Flighty will monitor.<br/>
<br/>
The app is able to predict delays "hours in advance," and give information to Flighty users that airlines often decline to share. The result is more control over travel plans.<blockquote>For example, the airline might delay your flight by 30 minutes ... and then another hour. But with these updates, Flighty 4 can tell you that's likely to be at least a five-hour delay due to an official ground stop at your airport. That gives users more insight to adjust their travel plans on the fly rather than being stuck for hours at the airport.</blockquote>Flighty tracks late arriving airplanes, Air Traffic Control notices, airport operational issues, weather problems, and even major events that can impact air traffic, such as the Super Bowl.<br/>
<br/>
Information on air space delays is limited to the United States, Canada, and the European Union, though late aircraft, airport issues, and live delay trends are available worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features in today's update include live airport performance trends, aircraft internal names, fixes for missing tail numbers, and clear in-app updates when flight schedules change.<br/>
<br/>
Flighty is available on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac. The app is free to download, but the delay features are part of Flighty Pro, which is priced at &#36;4 for one week or &#36;48 for a year. More information on the app can be <a href="https://www.flightyapp.com">found on the Flighty website</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/flighty-update-flight-delays/">Flighty Now Able to Provide Early Warnings About Flight Delays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/flighty-now-able-to-provide-early-warnings-about-flight-delays.2433075/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: WaterField Designs&#039; Shield Case Offers More Sensible Vision Pro Protection Than Apple&#039;s Travel Case</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/waterfield-designs-vision-pro-shield-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-waterfield-designs-shield-case-offers-more-sensible-vision-pro-protection-than-apples-travel-case.2433073/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:28:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/waterfield-designs-vision-pro-shield-case&#038;post_date=1722983296/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>WaterField Designs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For users looking to transport their Vision Pro units and various accessories, Apple offers the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW2F3LL/A/apple-vision-pro-travel-case">Apple Vision Pro Travel Case</a> as an optional &#36;199 accessory. But if you're looking for a third-party alternative, WaterField Designs offers a <a href="https://www.sfbags.com/products/vision-pro-shield-case">Shield Case starting at &#36;159</a> that might be worth considering, and I've spent the past few months using one for occasional travel to see how it fares.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/waterfield-vision-pro-shield-case.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960878" /><br/>
First things first though, and that's the question of why you might want to consider something other than Apple's first-party case. Apple's case is a hardshell polycarbonate covered with a white ripstop outer shell to provide protection for the relatively fragile headset, with a microfiber inner lining protecting the Vision Pro from scratches or other superficial damage.<br/>
<br/>
While that all sounds good and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> Travel Case seems to do a reasonably good job of protecting the expensive headset, it has been widely mocked for its overall size, the loose-fitting outer cover, and the white color that suggests it could become a dirt and stain magnet. Some have likened the overall appearance of Apple's case to an astronaut suit or some other item of space gear, and that's not wholly inaccurate.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/waterfield-vision-pro-shield-case-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960877" /><br/>
Put simply, Apple's case is massive, with copious amounts of empty space inside as Apple has prioritized allowing users to keep their Vision Pro's head strap attached to the body of the device. The result is an oblong case measuring nearly a foot long by almost 9 inches wide and 6.5 inches thick. It's unwieldy on its own despite a carry handle, and there's little chance of it fitting well in a backpack, and even a modest carry-on suitcase will see a considerable amount of its interior space taken up by the case.<br/>
<br/>
And that's where WaterField's Shield Case for &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; really shines. At under 8 inches square and a little over 5 inches thick, the Shield Case takes up less than half the volume of Apple's case, making it a much more sensible travel companion.<br/>
<br/>
So how does WaterField manage to fit a Vision Pro and all of its parts into a significantly smaller space than Apple's case? It starts with requiring the user to remove the head strap, whether it be the Solo Knit Band or the Dual Loop Band. This reduces the required volume from something that would need to fit around an entire head to a much more compact package.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/watefield-vision-pro-shield-case-assembled.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="961" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960885" /><br/>
The main body of the Vision Pro and the integrated Audio Straps remain all in one piece, but the head bands fold up into fairly small and flexible pieces, making it easy to tuck them into the Shield Case. And given it's trivial to remove and reattach the head bands, this is an easy sacrifice to make.<br/>
<br/>
WaterField's Shield Case has a plush inner lining with a good amount of closed-cell foam padding in the outer covering, so it protects the Vision Pro very well in my experience. You should of course keep the front cover that comes with Vision Pro in place at all times while transporting the device, as it provides additional protection from impacts and scratches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/waterfield-vision-pro-shield-case-open.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960879" /><br/>
Aside from the main compartment of the Shield Case that holds the Vision Pro body, WaterField has included an accessory pouch that fits within the void created by the Vision Pro, the Light Seal and the Audio Straps.<br/>
<br/>
All of your various accessories can fit neatly inside that pouch, including both head straps, the cleaning cloth, the power adapter, and the USB-C charging cable. There are even two slots sewn into the lid of the pouch for storing Zeiss lens inserts if you use those with the Vision Pro, although you can also just keep them installed in the Vision Pro itself during transport since they are held firmly in place with magnets.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/waterfield-vision-pro-shield-case-small.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960882" /><br/>
Inside the lid of the Shield Case is a plush slot where you can store the Vision Pro battery with its cable wound around it during transport. The case then closes up tight with waterproof zippers to keep everything secure, and there's even an additional zippered slot pocket on the outside of the Shield Case if you prefer to keep the charging adapter and cable or other small items there. In another nice touch, there is a small slot deep in the outside pocket where an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> can be tucked away to help you keep tabs on your Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/waterfield-vision-pro-shield-case-contents.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960883" /><br/>
An integrated nylon grab handle makes it easy to carry the Shield Case, though the case can also be easily gripped in one hand by most users. Two small D rings on the top rear edge of the Shield Case let you attach an optional &#36;20 Simple Strap that uses small carabiner-style clips and an adjustable slide buckle to allow for easier carrying over a shoulder.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/waterfield-vision-pro-shield-case-top.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960880" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.sfbags.com/products/vision-pro-shield-case">Shield Case for Apple Vision Pro</a> is available in several different material combinations, with the cheapest being constructed entirely of ballistic nylon on the exterior in either black or blue for &#36;159. For &#36;179, you can get the Shield Case in that same black ballistic nylon but with the front panel serving as an accent in either white, black, or chocolate leather. And finally, there's a configuration with the body of the case made of waxed canvas with a chocolate leather front panel, also priced at &#36;179.<br/>
<br/>
It's impossible to overstate how much of a difference the size of the Shield Case makes compared to Apple's Vision Pro Travel Case. With the Travel Case as my only option, I never really considered taking my Vision Pro on any trips, simply due to its overwhelming size.<br/>
<br/>
When traveling by plane, I'm certainly not going to put my Vision Pro into checked baggage, no matter how well it's protected in a case, and there simply isn't room to reasonably pack that oversized case in a backpack or carry-on. But with WaterField's Shield Case, I still feel like I have adequate protection for my expensive and fragile Vision Pro, yet I can slide it into the bottom of my travel backpack and still have plenty of room for other items.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: WaterField Designs provided MacRumors with the Vision Pro Shield Case for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/waterfield-designs/">WaterField Designs</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/waterfield-designs-vision-pro-shield-case/">Review: WaterField Designs&#039; Shield Case Offers More Sensible Vision Pro Protection Than Apple&#039;s Travel Case</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-waterfield-designs-shield-case-offers-more-sensible-vision-pro-protection-than-apples-travel-case.2433073/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Disney Raising Prices for Hulu, ESPN+, and Disney+ This Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/disney-raising-streaming-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-raising-prices-for-hulu-espn-and-disney-this-fall.2433071/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:43:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/disney-raising-streaming-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ESPN</category>
		<category>Disney</category>
		<category>Hulu</category>
		<category>Disney Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Disney will soon increase the cost of its suite of streaming services, including Hulu, ESPN+, and Disney+. <a href="https://thewaltdisneycompany.com/disney-streaming-playlists/">Prices will go up</a> for both ad-supported and ad-free plans, and some of Disney's bundles will also be more expensive. Most plans are increasing by &#36;1 to &#36;2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/07/hulu-logo-2019.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-701546" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Disney+ With Ads</strong> - &#36;9.99, up from &#36;7.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Disney+ Ad-Free</strong> - &#36;15.99, up from &#36;13.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Hulu With Ads</strong> - &#36;9.99, up from &#36;7.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Hulu Ad-Free</strong> - &#36;18.99, up from &#36;17.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>ESPN+</strong> - &#36;11.99, up from &#36;10.99</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The Disney Duo Basic plan with ad-supported versions of Hulu and Disney+ is going from &#36;9.99 to &#36;10.99, but pricing for the premium version is not changing and will remain at &#36;19.99.<br/>
<br/>
The ad-supported trio bundle with Disney+, Hulu, and ESPN+ is increasing from &#36;14.99 to &#36;16.99, and the premium trio bundle is increasing from &#36;24.99 to &#36;26.99. Hulu's Live TV plan with VoD ads will be priced at &#36;82.99, up from &#36;76.99, and the ad-free version will be priced at &#36;95.99, up from &#36;89.99.<br/>
<br/>
Disney is giving Disney+ subscribers access to ABC News Live and new continuous playlists starting on September 4, with the first playlist offering preschool content. Four additional curated playlists are set to come out later this year with seasonal content, "Epic Stories" from franchises like Marvel and Star Wars, "Throwbacks" with nostalgic pop culture content, and "Real Life" with documentaries and biopics.<br/>
<br/>
Disney plans to implement the pricing increases on Thursday, October 17. Disney said in its blog post that its subscription plans "remain among the best values in streaming today."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/espn/">ESPN</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney/">Disney</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/hulu/">Hulu</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney-plus/">Disney Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/disney-raising-streaming-prices/">Disney Raising Prices for Hulu, ESPN+, and Disney+ This Fall</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-raising-prices-for-hulu-espn-and-disney-this-fall.2433071/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Makes It Harder to Override Gatekeeper Security</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/macos-sequoia-gatekeeper-security-change/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-makes-it-harder-to-override-gatekeeper-security.2433066/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:29:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/macos-sequoia-gatekeeper-security-change/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, Apple is making it more difficult for users to override the built-in Gatekeeper security function to install Mac software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-security-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1145" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796484" /><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=saqachfa">eliminating the option</a> to Control-click to open Mac software that is not correctly signed or notarized in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;. To install apps that Gatekeeper blocks, users will need to open up System Settings and go to the Privacy and Security section to "review security information" before being able to run the software.<br/>
<br/>
Some &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; users <a href="https://mjtsai.com/blog/2024/07/05/sequoia-removes-gatekeeper-contextual-menu-override/">have already noticed</a> that the function was removed, but Apple today confirmed that it is no longer available in the update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recommends that software distributed outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a> be submitted for notarization, a process that scans Developer ID-signed software and performs security checks. Notarized software does not trigger Gatekeeper.<br/>
<br/>
Gatekeeper ensures that Macs only run "trusted" software in order to protect users from malware, viruses, and other security risks. Gatekeeper checks to make sure that software comes from an identified developer and is free from malicious content.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/macos-sequoia-gatekeeper-security-change/">macOS Sequoia Makes It Harder to Override Gatekeeper Security</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-makes-it-harder-to-override-gatekeeper-security.2433066/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third macOS Sequoia Public Beta With iPhone Mirroring and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-macos-sequoia-public-beta-with-iphone-mirroring-and-more.2433061/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:08:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> update to its public beta testing group, giving the general public a chance to try out the new operating system's features ahead of its fall launch. The third public beta comes two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-2/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; from the Software Update section of the System Settings app after <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">signing up on Apple's beta testing website</a> and opting into the public beta under the Beta Updates section.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;'s biggest feature is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which is designed to let you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac using your keyboard and mouse. You can see notifications and use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps even when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is tucked away and locked, and later this year, you'll be able to use the feature to drag and drop apps from your Mac to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
Window tiling has been improved to make it easier to get multiple windows on your Mac in a way that works for you, Safari can summarize websites and show you highlights, and the Messages app supports scheduling messages and using the Tapback feature with any emoji.<br/>
<br/>
There's a new Passwords app for managing your passwords, logins, and passkeys, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app has a new design, the Notes app supports audio transcription and summarization, and you can also type in any equation and get it solved automatically.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; supports all of the new Apple Intelligence features that are also coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, offering all kinds of quality of life improvements. Writing tools help you proofread and polish your writing across apps, you can create unique images with Image Playground, and make up your own emoji with Genmoji. &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; includes a Clean Up tool for removing unwanted images, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> will use AI for better language understanding and contextual relevance. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will even be able to consult ChatGPT for complicated queries.<br/>
<br/>
There are a long list of additional features coming to &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">more information available in our dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-3/">Apple Releases Third macOS Sequoia Public Beta With iPhone Mirroring and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-macos-sequoia-public-beta-with-iphone-mirroring-and-more.2433061/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 Public Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-ios-18-public-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-ios-18-and-ipados-18-public-betas.2433060/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:07:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-ios-18-public-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided the third betas of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> to public beta testers, bringing the new software to the general public. The third public beta comes a week after Apple released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-2/">the second public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957836" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Public-Beta-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers who have <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">signed up for Apple's beta testing program</a> can download the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; updates by opening up the Settings app, going to General, tapping into the Software Update section and selecting the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; Public Beta option.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; introduces Apple Intelligence, which are AI features deeply integrated into the operating system. Not all functionality is available at this time, but it brings Writing Tools for rewriting, polishing, proofreading, and summarizing text across apps, and you can generate custom images with Image Playground. There are custom emoji available through the Genmoji feature, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting entirely overhauled. Note that Apple Intelligence isn't live in the public betas.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957173" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ipaos-18-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2150" height="1210" /><br/>
Along with the AI features (which will be limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and M-series iPads), &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; brings a redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> with the option to rearrange app icons and widgets with open spaces, plus there's a tint option and new darker colors for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957459" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Home-Screen-Feature-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Control Center has been revamped and you can pick and choose what you want to have front and center from the new Controls Gallery. There are multiple pages so you can group related controls, and you can customize sizes. As part of this update, the Flashlight and Camera icons on the Lock Screen can be swapped out, and you can also choose Control Center options for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954460" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/control-center-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The Messages app supports scheduling texts, you can use any emoji for the Tapback feature, and you can send messages via satellite. There are text effects you can use for any word, phrase, or emoji, plus formatting like bold and italic is an option. For texts with Android users, Apple now supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>, which basically means you won't run into issues with sending images and files, plus you can see typing indicators and read receipts and send texts over Wi-Fi.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955789" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-Send-Later-iOS-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Safari is able to summarize webpages and show you important info at a glance, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app has been overhauled to focus more on surfacing your best photos. A dedicated Passwords app makes it easier to get to your saved passwords and logins, and you can now lock any app with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957055" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-safari-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
With today's beta specifically, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/safari-distraction-control-hands-on/">adding support Distraction Control</a>, a feature that is designed to let you hide distracting elements like popups on webpages. <br/>
<br/>
There are a ton of new features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; that aren't mentioned here, so for a more in-depth look make sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a> and our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-ios-18-public-beta-3/">Apple Releases Third iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 Public Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-ios-18-and-ipados-18-public-betas.2433060/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-watchos-11-public-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2433064/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-watchos-11-public-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to give the new features a try ahead of when the software launches this fall. The third beta comes two weeks <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-2/">after the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957264" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-vitals.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; can be downloaded after signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's beta software website</a> and upgrading your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to the public beta version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. You'll need to open up the Watch app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, go to General, select Software Update, and choose the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Public Beta option under Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, Apple added a new Vitals app that can be used to give you a daily overview of your health metrics, letting you know if anything is out of the ordinary. It compares information collected at night like heart rate, sleep, respiratory rate, and oxygen level to your levels over the previous weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Smart Stack has new widgets like Translate and Shazam, plus it's smarter because it is able to suggest widgets based on time, date, location, and daily routine. Interactive widgets let you access app features from the Smart Stack, and it also supports Live Activities.<br/>
<br/>
Training Load is a new way of measuring how the intensity and duration of workouts impact the body over time, with Apple providing an effort level for cardio-based workouts to help you know when to rest and when to push harder.<br/>
<br/>
You can now customize your Activity Ring requirements for different days of the week, and Apple added support for rest days. Taking a break from activity will no longer ruin a streak because you can pause for a day, a week, a month, or more.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include more workout types, Check In for Messages, a revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face, improvements to Double Tap, and more, with additional information <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">available in our watchOS 11 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-watchos-11-public-beta-3/">Apple Releases Third watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2433064/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third tvOS 18 Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-public-beta.2433065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third public beta of tvOS 18, giving the general public a chance to try out the new features ahead of the software's fall launch. The third beta comes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-seeds-second-tvos-18-public-beta/">a week after the second beta</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796083" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-tv-4k-design-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download the tvOS 18 beta by opening up the Settings app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, choosing the Software Updates section under System, and then toggling on the Get Public Beta Updates option. Signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's public beta website</a> is required to get the option to show up.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 isn't as feature rich as some of Apple's other updates, but it brings a new InSight feature to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app. InSight is similar to Amazon X-Ray, providing real-time information about actors, music, and more in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> shows and movies.<br/>
<br/>
The Enhanced Dialogue feature uses computational audio and machine learning to better boost vocal clarity over background noise and music, plus it works with built-in TV speakers, AirPods, and other Bluetooth devices. Subtitles have been tweaked to show up automatically when relevant, such as when the TV is muted.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added new screen savers and made it easier to swap between them, plus there's 21:9 aspect ratio support for projectors and an option for Live Captions during <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-public-beta/">Apple Seeds Third tvOS 18 Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-public-beta.2433065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>SpongeBob SquarePants Environment Now Available in Paramount+ App on Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/spongebob-environment-available-on-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spongebob-squarepants-environment-now-available-in-paramount-app-on-apple-vision-pro.2433055/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 08:56:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/spongebob-environment-available-on-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> users can now explore an immersive SpongeBob SquarePants-themed environment with the Paramount+ app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Final_SB-Bikini-Bottom-Environment.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960869" /><br/>
The new experience debuts to celebrate the 25th anniversary of the iconic animated series. Upon launching the Paramount+ app on the device, users can select the new environment, which takes them to the familiar setting of Bikini Bottom featuring locations such as SpongeBob's pineapple house, Patrick Star's rock, and Squidward Tentacles' house.<br/>
<br/>
When users start streaming content on Paramount+, the environment adapts. The sun sets in Bikini Bottom, and the screen moves to a position near SpongeBob's house. The character himself appears, sitting down with popcorn.<br/>
<br/>
The update to the Paramount+ app also introduces an interactive game where users can catch jellyfish. By looking at jellyfish and tapping their fingers together, users can catch them with a net that appears on the screen. <br/>
<br/>
Yesterday, Disney+ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/disney-plus-immersive-environment-iceland/">introduced a new Iceland environment</a> in collaboration with National Geographic, and Apple itself recently added a Lake Vrangla environment, with a Bora Bora option slated for release later in 2024 as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/spongebob-environment-available-on-vision-pro/">SpongeBob SquarePants Environment Now Available in Paramount+ App on Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spongebob-squarepants-environment-now-available-in-paramount-app-on-apple-vision-pro.2433055/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing iOS 17.6.1 Update Alongside iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-preparing-ios-17-6-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-ios-17-6-1-update-alongside-ios-18-and-ios-18-1-betas.2433054/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 08:46:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-preparing-ios-17-6-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing to release a minor iOS 17.6.1 update for the iPhone, according to a post shared today by an anonymous leaker on X, formerly known as Twitter. The leaker has a private account, so we are not identifying it or linking to it, but they have proven to be a consistently accurate source for upcoming iOS updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/General-iOS-17-Feature-Orange-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898582" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> can independently confirm that Apple is internally testing an iOS 17.6.1 update, which is present in our analytics logs. <br/>
<br/>
Nothing is known about iOS 17.6.1, beyond the leaker claiming that the update will have a build number of 21G93. However, the update will almost certainly be a minor one, especially given that Apple is focused on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/ios-18-beta-5-features/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">iOS 18.1 beta testing</a>. iPhone users still running iOS 17 can expect the update to include bug fixes and/or security patches.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear when iOS 17.6.1 will be released to the public, but updates revealed by this leaker typically become available within a few weeks after they post on social media. The update will likely be released in the first half of August.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-preparing-ios-17-6-1/">Apple Preparing iOS 17.6.1 Update Alongside iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-ios-17-6-1-update-alongside-ios-18-and-ios-18-1-betas.2433054/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
