<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:04:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1: How to Shuffle a Photo Album on Your Lock Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-lock-screen-shuffle-between-photos-album/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-how-to-shuffle-a-photo-album-on-your-lock-screen.2408507/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:11:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-lock-screen-shuffle-between-photos-album&#038;post_date=1698156665/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to release iOS 17.1 later today, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-1-beta-features/">amongst other features</a> the update includes a new Lock Screen personalization option for iPhones. Here's how to make your Lock Screen wallpaper shuffle through photos from a specific album in your photo library.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/shuffle-photos-lock-screen.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848808" /><br/>
In recent versions of iOS, Apple has made it possible for users to customize the Lock Screen in ways that were simply not possible in earlier versions of its mobile software, and one feature in particular that has proven popular is the ability to shuffle photos on your Lock Screen wallpaper at specific intervals or whenever you wake or tap the screen. <br/>
<br/>
In iOS 17.1, Apple has extended this feature so that you can now shuffle pictures from a specific album from your photo library, rather than having to manually select individual photos or rely on Apple's preset options of People, Pets, Nature, and Cities. The following steps show you how it's done on iPhones running iOS 17.1.<br/>
<ol><li>Wake your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> to unlock it, but don't swipe up on the Lock Screen.</li><br/>
<li>Press and hold on the Lock Screen until the wallpaper gallery appears, then tap the blue <strong>+</strong> button in the bottom-right corner of the screen.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Photo Shuffle</strong> from the wallpaper menu.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/lock-screen-photo-shuffle.jpg" alt="Lock Screen" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918216" /><br/>
<li>Tap the new <strong>Album</strong> option, then choose the album of photos from your library that you'd like to shuffle between.</li><br/>
<li>Next, choose a <strong>Shuffle Frequency</strong>: <strong>Daily</strong>, <strong>Hourly</strong>, <strong>On Lock</strong>, or <strong>On Tap</strong>.<br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Use Album</strong> to move on.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/choose-shuffle-album.jpg" alt="shuffle" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918217" /><br/>
<li>Tap the screen to preview the photos in your chosen album as they will appear on your Lock Screen, and tap the clock to adjust the font style and color so that the time, date, and any widgets remain legible against all of your pictures.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Done</strong> in the top-right corner to finish, then choose either <strong>Set as Wallpaper Pair</strong> to finish or <strong>Customize Home Screen</strong> to tweak its look separately, then tap <strong>Done</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/photo-shuffle-preview.jpg" alt="photo shuffle" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918219" /></ol>Tap your new album-specific photo shuffle wallpaper in the gallery to make it live. Then you can tap or wake your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s screen to change the photo, or wait for it to change automatically, depending on your chosen option.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-lock-screen-shuffle-between-photos-album/">iOS 17.1: How to Shuffle a Photo Album on Your Lock Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-how-to-shuffle-a-photo-album-on-your-lock-screen.2408507/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Adds Support for Passkeys, Allowing for More Secure Logins</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/amazon-adds-support-for-passkeys/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-adds-support-for-passkeys-allowing-for-more-secure-logins.2408484/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 19:00:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/amazon-adds-support-for-passkeys/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		<category>Passkeys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon <a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/retail/amazon-passwordless-sign-in-passkey">today announced</a> that it has added passkey support to its desktop sites and mobile apps, allowing customers to sign in to their accounts without the need for a password.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/amazon-app-passkey.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1127" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918179" /><br/>
Passkeys are a more secure alternative to passwords because a passkey cannot be shared with another person through a phishing attempt or leaked online through a database hack. Passkeys do not require customers to remember a password or add a two-factor authentication code, but they do require a verified device.<br/>
<br/>
Passkeys can be set up in the Amazon settings, and on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac, logging in to an Amazon account can be done with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> scan once the feature is turned on. To enable it, go to Your Account &gt; Login and Security, and choose the Set up option next to Passkeys.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/08/apple-passkeys-next-generation-passwords/">implemented support for passkeys</a> with iOS 16 and macOS Ventura. Passkeys work through a public key that's stored on a website server and paired with a private key that's kept on a specific device. On Apple's devices, passkeys are authenticated with &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;, and two keys must match to allow for a user to log in.<br/>
<br/>
Passkeys rely on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, which in turn requires two-factor authentication for further protection. Passkeys sync across all of a user's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and Mac devices, but they can also be used on non-Apple devices through a QR code system.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon says that passkey support is available today for all Amazon customers using browsers, and that it will be rolling out to the Amazon app for iOS devices in the near future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/passkeys/">Passkeys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/amazon-adds-support-for-passkeys/">Amazon Adds Support for Passkeys, Allowing for More Secure Logins</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-adds-support-for-passkeys-allowing-for-more-secure-logins.2408484/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Updated Matter 1.2 Specification Supports New Device Types and Brings Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/matter-1-2-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/updated-matter-1-2-specification-supports-new-device-types-and-brings-performance-improvements.2408469/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:35:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/matter-1-2-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Matter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA) that Apple is a member of <a href="https://csa-iot.org/newsroom/matter-1-2-arrives-with-nine-new-device-types-improvements-across-the-board/">today announced</a> that an updated Matter 1.2 specification is available for device makers and platforms. Matter 1.2 adds support for additional device types and brings improvements to Matter. Matter is a smart home protocol that allows devices to work across multiple platforms, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/matter-update.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918175" /><br/>
With Matter 1.2, Matter support can be added to refrigerators, standalone room air conditioners, dishwashers, laundry machines, robotic vacuums, smoke and carbon monoxide alarms, air quality sensors, air purifiers, and fans.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; supports some of these device types such as air quality monitors, air purifiers, and smoke alarms, but Apple may need to implement &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; updates to add Matter 1.2 support.<br/>
<br/>
Matter 1.2 also adds improvements for multi-unit switches and multi-light fixtures, along with semantic tags and improvements for device operational states, which should give device makers more options for more complex smart home products.<br/>
<br/>
According to the CSA, Matter 1.2 includes enhancements to testing and certification, which will allow companies to bring products to market faster.<br/>
<br/>
Matter 1.2 certification is open as of now, and the Matter 1.2 devices and improvements are expected to be available on the market later this year. More information on the changes can be found <a href="https://csa-iot.org/newsroom/matter-1-2-arrives-with-nine-new-device-types-improvements-across-the-board/">on the CSA website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/matter/">Matter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/matter-1-2-update/">Updated Matter 1.2 Specification Supports New Device Types and Brings Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/updated-matter-1-2-specification-supports-new-device-types-and-brings-performance-improvements.2408469/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Could Spend &#36;4.75 Billion on AI Servers in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-ai-server-spending-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-could-spend-4-75-billion-on-ai-servers-in-2024.2408458/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:56:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-ai-server-spending-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to spend several billion on hardware to support its artificial intelligence development in 2024, according to speculation from <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/how-much-does-apple-need-to-invest-annually-in-generative-ai-to-catch-up-with-the-competition-56e237ea3feb">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. Kuo expects Apple to spend "at least" &#36;620 million on servers in 2023 and &#36;4.75 billion on servers in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" /><br/>
Apple could purchase between 2,000 and 3,000 servers this year, and up to 20,000 next year. Kuo thinks that Apple is purchasing servers equipped with Nvidia's HGX H100 8-GPU for generative AI training, with the company planning to upgrade to B100 next year. Nvidia calls its H100 an AI supercomputing platform, and each one is priced at around &#36;250,000.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo appears to be guessing at Apple's purchasing plans here, and he says that he expects Apple will use AI servers it is purchasing and installing itself to train large language models rather than virtual hosting from other cloud service providers for improved security and privacy. He does say that Apple could develop its own server chips to save on server costs, but he has seen no evidence that Apple is doing that at this time.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple appears to be making a major investment into AI, Apple's server purchasing will fall behind other companies like Meta and Microsoft. Apple will also need to invest in labor costs, infrastructure, and more, and Kuo suggests that Apple will need to spend several billion dollars annually to have a chance of catching up with competitors. Kuo claims that he is "genuinely concerned" about the future of Apple's generative AI business if Apple spends just a billion dollars a year as suggested by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Over the weekend, Gurman said that Apple is on track to spend &#36;1 billion per year on its AI efforts. Gurman says that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">Apple is working on</a> a new, smarter version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and is aiming to integrate AI into many Apple apps.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kuo/">Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-ai-server-spending-2024/">Kuo: Apple Could Spend &#36;4.75 Billion on AI Servers in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-could-spend-4-75-billion-on-ai-servers-in-2024.2408458/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air Drops to All-Time Low Price of &#36;899 (&#36;200 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/deals-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-drops-to-all-time-low-price-of-899-200-off.2408444/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:34:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/deals-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air has dropped to <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPZTZF5dZ"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> today on Best Buy, down from &#36;1,099.00. Best Buy offers free next-day shipping as well as in-store pick-up for most locations, and has all four colors of Space Gray, Silver, Midnight, and Starlight at this price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/macbook-air-spacegray-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1428" height="802" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-887878" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is an all-time low price on the 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air, and Best Buy has been one of the few retailers to offer this sale over the past few months. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPZTZF5dZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy also has the 512GB model of the 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air on sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckQP5k7JDAC"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;,1399.00. Compared to past sales, this is a second-best price and still a solid discount on the 2022 notebook.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckQP5k7JDAC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/deals-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-2/">Deals: Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air Drops to All-Time Low Price of &#36;899 (&#36;200 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-drops-to-all-time-low-price-of-899-200-off.2408444/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Likely to Launch Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/ios-17-1-likely-to-launch-tomorrow/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-likely-to-launch-tomorrow.2408441/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:24:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/ios-17-1-likely-to-launch-tomorrow/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iOS 17.1, iPadOS 17.1, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.1, tvOS 17.1, watchOS 10.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> Software 17.1 updates are expected to be released to the public tomorrow following several weeks of beta testing. We are expecting the software to go live at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time, which is when Apple typically releases updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.1-Update-Available-Next-Week-With-New-Features-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917893" /><br/>
Last week, Apple seeded release candidates (RCs) for all of the upcoming software refreshes. Apple usually tests RCs for about a week to make sure there are no device-breaking bugs, and this time around, we're also clued in on a specific launch date because of an update in France.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 in France includes a feature to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/">reduce the radiation level</a> of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 models when they are stationary on a table or another surface, and French regulatory group ANFR two weeks ago confirmed that the iOS 17.1 update is expected to come out "by October 24."<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 isn't going to bring us the Journal app, but it does have some useful new features. It includes the option to continue large AirDrop transfers over the internet once initiated, so if you're sending someone files, you can walk away while the transfer is in progress.<br/>
<br/>
It includes new options for favoriting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> songs, there are new options for leaving the display on in StandBy mode, and Screen Time should work better across devices. There are also several bug fixes, so if you've been having issues with search in the Messages app or persistent images on the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, you're going to want to download the update right away.<br/>
<br/>
If you have an Apple Watch, it's actually watchOS 10.1 that's going to bring some of the best features. The update includes support for NameDrop for quickly sharing contact info with another person, and it adds Double Tap on the latest models. Double Tap lets you tap your index finger and thumb together to do things like answer phone calls and bring up the Smart Stack.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1 has a few bug fixes, and if you have an original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, you'll be pleased to hear that &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.1 adds the Enhance Dialogue feature to these devices. When a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; is used as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> speaker, Enhance Dialogue cuts down on background noise and music when there's speaking so you can better hear what's being said.<br/>
<br/>
We have a full rundown on all of the new features coming in iOS 17.1 in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-1-beta-features/">iOS 17.1 beta features guide</a>. Apple is already working on iOS 17.2, so we could be seeing new beta features as soon as later this week after iOS 17.1 and its sister updates come out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/ios-17-1-likely-to-launch-tomorrow/">iOS 17.1 Likely to Launch Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-likely-to-launch-tomorrow.2408441/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Samsung&#039;s New Weeklong Event Has Low Prices on ViewFinity S9 5K Display and Smart Monitor M8</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/deals-samsungs-weeklong-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-samsungs-new-weeklong-event-has-low-prices-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-display-and-smart-monitor-m8.2408412/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 06:19:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/deals-samsungs-weeklong-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung is back this week with new discounts on a wide variety of categories, and in this article we're focusing on <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPbMCoHS6">monitors</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPcQwr1xo">TVs</a>. The highlights of the sale include the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display at &#36;300 off and the Smart Monitor M8 at &#36;200 off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/samsung-viewfinity-s9-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903409" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the newer 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display, this monitor is available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. This is a match of the all-time low price on the device, which we last tracked around Prime Day, and you'll find the same price <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-ViewFinity-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87">on Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>ViewFinity S9 Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The ViewFinity S9 is a 27-inch display with a Thunderbolt 4 port, three USB-C ports, and a Mini DisplayPort, and it includes 90 watts of power for machines connected through the Thunderbolt 4 port. A removable 4K SlimFit webcam supports tilt adjustments, as well as Auto Framing of subjects in the shot, similar to Apple's Center Stage feature. Built-in speakers with an Adaptive Sound+ option to automatically adjust noise levels are also included.<br/>
<br/>
The new model of the 32-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also on sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;699.99. This is a second-best price on the M80C model, and Samsung has every color at this price. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Streaming-Slim-fit-Experience-Speakers%2Fdp%2FB0C3WMX69W">On Amazon</a>, it's only available in Warm White.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>Smart Monitor M80C for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've gathered a few more monitors and TVs on sale below, but be sure to head to Samsung to see the full extent of the sale. This event is set to run the rest of the month, and end on November 1. The prices on Amazon are not directly part of the Samsung website event, so they could expire sooner.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPfgT45F4">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Monitor</a> - &#36;279.99 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPgKIod0i">34-inch OLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPrWHb9fr">49-inch Odyssey OLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,399.99 (&#36;400 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPiqMBwhC">55-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPjtEBtoT">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,799.99 (&#36;500 off)</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/deals-samsungs-weeklong-event/">Deals: Samsung&#039;s New Weeklong Event Has Low Prices on ViewFinity S9 5K Display and Smart Monitor M8</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-samsungs-new-weeklong-event-has-low-prices-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-display-and-smart-monitor-m8.2408412/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Bloomberg: Apple Likely to Hold Mac Launch Event on October 30 or 31</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-mac-launch-event-coming-october-30-or-31/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bloomberg-apple-likely-to-hold-mac-launch-event-on-october-30-or-31.2408392/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-mac-launch-event-coming-october-30-or-31/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 13&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is likely planning a Mac-related launch event this month that will take place on either Monday, October 30 or Tuesday, October 31, according to <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1716065994995900691?s=20"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7PthWRt_GU0" title="Apple October Mac Event Happening Next Week!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The well-connected reporter's <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">prediction</a> is based on information obtained from sources with apparent knowledge of Apple's plans, as well as the fact that some existing Mac models are in short supply online and at Apple retail stores.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman notes that several configurations of Apple's 24-inch iMac, 13-inch MacBook Pro, and 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro are facing shipping delays running into mid-November. This several-week delay alone is "a clear sign that <em>something</em> is about to happen," says Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
Another reason leads the reporter to believe a Mac announcement will happen next week: Apple's earnings call is due to take place on Thursday, November 2. The last time the company posted its quarterly results in the month of November was in 2018, and that followed an October 30 launch event that saw new iPads and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman reckons that the most likely Mac to be announced this month is a new 24-inch iMac. The current iMac has not been updated for more than 900 days, and it is the only remaining model in Apple's Mac lineup still using the M1 chip. <br/>
<br/>
He also believes there is a chance we will see new 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models. This would be somewhat of a surprise, given that Apple only updated its premium MacBook Pros in January 2023. However, as Gurman notes, "an additional update the same year would be unusual, but not inconceivable."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman's latest report reveals little about what improvements the new iMac will bring, but he has previously said that Apple's next iMac will leapfrog the M2 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/06/no-m2-imac-on-the-horizon-for-2022/">instead adopt the rumored new M3 chip</a>, bringing performance and efficiency improvements. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">NEW: Appleâ€™s iMacs and MacBook Pros are in extremely short supply online and at retail stores. And new models may be coming soon: the company is likely planning a Mac related launch event at the end of this month. <a href="https://t.co/3xwhck5JBs">https://t.co/3xwhck5JBs</a></p>&mdash; Mark Gurman (@markgurman) <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1716065994995900691?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 22, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
As for the 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro, Gurman said he does not expect any major changes other than new processors, but his latest report stops short on offering specifics. Gurman earlier this month <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024/">claimed</a> that new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models featuring M3 Pro and M3 Max chips would likely launch between early 2024 and the spring. Gurman may be hedging in his latest predictions, which is likely to lead to speculation that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/04/13/a12z-gpu-identical-to-a12x/">iterative update</a> to the M2 Pro and M2 Max is coming this year instead.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman says the new MacBook Pro models could include "minor improvements to displays." Notably, <em>DigiTimes</em> recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/05/new-14-16-inch-macbook-pro-models-2023/">claimed</a> that Apple will release new 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with more efficient mini-LED displays before the end of the year. <em>DigiTimes</em>' report was originally met with skepticism because of the alleged launch timing, but couched in terms of Gurman's latest predictions, there could well be more substance to it after all.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, <em>MacRumors</em> received information in early October indicating that Apple was preparing to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/trade-in-changes-may-indicate-new-mac-this-month/">accept some of its latest Mac models for trade-in</a>, suggesting it may be proceeding with plans to release new Mac models. Whether this correlates with the launch of at least one new machine in late October remains to be seen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro-13/">MacBook Pro 13"</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_13">13" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-mac-launch-event-coming-october-30-or-31/">Bloomberg: Apple Likely to Hold Mac Launch Event on October 30 or 31</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bloomberg-apple-likely-to-hold-mac-launch-event-on-october-30-or-31.2408392/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Host &#039;Secretive&#039; Vision Pro Training Event for Retail Staff</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-to-host-secretive-vision-pro-training-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-host-secretive-vision-pro-training-event-for-retail-staff.2408357/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 12:17:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-to-host-secretive-vision-pro-training-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to bring select retail store employees to Cupertino, California in early 2024 to learn about the Vision Pro headset ahead of the device's launch, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">Mark Gurman reports</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/Vision-Pro-lab.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-907266" /><br/>
Gurman revealed details about the "product training event" in the latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">"Power On" newsletter</a>. Apple apparently recent sent a memo to retail employees asking them to apply for the "secretive" event. Acceptance is dependent on an application and interview process. An extract from the memo reads:<blockquote>Selected team members will travel and participate in an event in Cupertino, California, at some point in the first months of 2024. Upon returning to their home store, they'll deliver training and ongoing support to store team members. This is a group opportunity for those who have a deep passion for demonstrating Apple products and teaching others.</blockquote>Gurman explained that the event seeks to teach employees about the Vision Pro and train them on the complex procedure involved when selling the device to customers. Apple hopes that a couple of members of staff from each retail store in the United States will attend before returning to their local store to teach their colleagues about the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The rollout of the Vision Pro headset is expected to be the most complicated in Apple's history. Apple is planning to assemble customers' Vision Pro headsets in-store, compiling the appropriate headband, light seal, and optional prescription lenses. Flagship retail stores are set to gain dedicated Vision Pro hands-on areas, while other stores will only receive one or two units.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman believes that the memo's wording indicates that the device will not be ready at the very beginning of the new year. Apple simply says that Vision Pro will launch in "early" 2024.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-to-host-secretive-vision-pro-training-event/">Apple to Host &#039;Secretive&#039; Vision Pro Training Event for Retail Staff</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-host-secretive-vision-pro-training-event-for-retail-staff.2408357/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15&#039;s Record High Production Costs Could Push Up iPhone 16 Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/record-high-iphone-15-costs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15s-record-high-production-costs-could-push-up-iphone-16-prices.2408344/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 10:03:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/record-high-iphone-15-costs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Nikkei</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>'s production costs are appreciably higher than those of last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models, marking record high component prices that Apple could pass onto customers in 2024, <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/iPhone-15-teardown-reveals-10-costlier-parts-than-2022-flagship"><em>Nikkei Asia</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max is calculated to cost &#36;558, a 12% increase over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max model released in 2022. This is a record high for the total cost of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s components. From 2018 to 2021, the total cost of parts for Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; "Pro Max" models ranged from &#36;400 to &#36;450. Component costs rose around 20% in 2022 before reaching today's record high of &#36;558.<br/>
<br/>
The cost of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max's telephoto camera now stands at &#36;30, a 380% increase over the previous model. Likewise, the titanium frame costs &#36;50, a 43% increase over the stainless steel frame of previous devices. The A17 Pro chip comes in at &#36;130, a 27% increase over the A16 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
The other models in the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup are also not immune to cost increases. The standard &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s components come in at &#36;423, a 16% increase compared to the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus is calculated at &#36;442, a 10% increase over its predecessor, while the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; grew by 8% to &#36;523.<br/>
<br/>
Despite increased costs, Apple did not increase the retail prices of any of its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models this year and chose to absorb the impact of increased expenses. The only notable change was the discontinuation of the 128GB Pro Max model, meaning that users who normally purchased the 128GB model now have to pay &#36;100 more to obtain the device.<br/>
<br/>
In collaboration with <em>Nikkei</em>, Tokyo-based research company Fomalhaut Techno Solutions believes that if Apple continues to absorb the impact of increased production costs, its bottom line will soon take a hit. As a result, Apple may finally choose to hike &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; retail prices upon the launch of next year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nikkei-com/">Nikkei</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/record-high-iphone-15-costs/">iPhone 15&#039;s Record High Production Costs Could Push Up iPhone 16 Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15s-record-high-production-costs-could-push-up-iphone-16-prices.2408344/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: New iPads Scheduled for Launch in March 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-march-2024-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-launch-in-march-2024.2408341/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 09:38:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-march-2024-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is not planning to launch new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> models until around March 2024, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">Mark Gurman claims</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/ipad-air-5-colors.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-839734" /><br/>
In the most recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">new Apple Pencil with USB-C</a> comes ahead of an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; refresh in the spring. He added that Apple has been working on the 11th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, and sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> for some time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is apparently planning to release new iPads in March, which will likely "at least" include these three refreshed devices. The next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> is also a possibility, but only the "more minor" &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; updates appear to be locked down for the spring at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman added that he anticipates that the first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> will be discontinued alongside the ninth-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, since there will no longer be any new iPads on sale from Apple with a Lightning connector at that point. This change is not expected to happen "anytime soon."<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-march-2024-launch/">Gurman: New iPads Scheduled for Launch in March 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-launch-in-march-2024.2408341/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Generative AI Features and Smarter Siri Could Launch Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri-could-launch-next-year.2408328/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 05:53:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is developing a large array of features that use generative AI, including a new version <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, that could launch next year, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
In his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that despite Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>'s claim that Apple has been working on generative AI technology for years, Apple's executives were "caught off guard" by the industry's sudden interest in AI and have been anxiously "scrambling since late last year to make up for lost time."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's senior vice president of machine learning and AI strategy, John Giannandrea, and senior vice president of software engineering Craig Federighi are apparently leading the company's AI efforts. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a>, Apple's senior vice president of services, is also involved in the push.<br/>
<br/>
Giannandrea is said to be overseeing development of the underlying technologies for a new AI system. Most notably, his team is working on a new, "smarter version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;" that is deeply integrated with AI. Gurman says it could be ready as soon as next year.<br/>
<br/>
On the other hand, Federighi is supervising the integration of AI into to the next major version of iOS by introducing features running on Apple's large language model (LLM). Among the new features is a revamped interaction between &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and the Messages app, enabling users to field complex questions and auto-complete sentences more effectively. Federighi's team is also looking at integrating AI into Xcode to help developers write code more quickly, bringing it in line with services like Microsoft's GitHub Copilot.<br/>
<br/>
Cue is reportedly attempting to add AI to as many Apple apps as possible, including features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, such as auto-generated playlists, and productivity apps like Pages and Keynote, where AI could assist with writing or creating slide decks. Apple is also apparently testing the use of generative AI for internal customer service apps within <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is purportedly on course to spend &#36;1 billion per year on AI research. Whether Apple should deploy generative AI as a completely on-device experience, a cloud-based setup, or a hybrid approach, is currently a source of debate internally.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously reported that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/15/apple-engineers-working-on-chatgpt-like-ai/">working on</a> a chatbot tool that some engineers have dubbed "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/apple-experimenting-with-chatgpt-tool/">Apple GPT</a>" to rival OpenAI's ChatGPT.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">Apple Generative AI Features and Smarter Siri Could Launch Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri-could-launch-next-year.2408328/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple to Announce New Macs This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month.2408323/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 05:21:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning a Mac-focused product launch, likely including the announcement of a refreshed 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, for the end of this month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">Mark Gurman reports</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7PthWRt_GU0" title="Apple October Mac Event Happening Next Week!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
In the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that Apple is "planning a Mac-centered product launch around the end of this month" that could see the the release of a refreshed 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; model, which is long overdue a hardware update. The current model launched in April 2021 and it is the only current-generation Mac left with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip. Gurman has repeatedly said that Apple's next <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/06/no-m2-imac-on-the-horizon-for-2022/">iMac will skip the M2</a> and feature the M3 chip instead, but he declined to mention which chip the new machine will feature in this newsletter.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman noted that Apple retail stores are now in short supply of the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, 13-inch MacBook Pro, and 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro, and many configurations now will not arrive until mid-November, in what he believes is "a clear sign that something is about to happen" regarding these three machines. He added that Apple has "made headway" on new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pros. While the current, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models launched in January, he thinks that an "additional update the same year would be unusual, but not inconceivable."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman believes that the upcoming Mac announcement will take place on Monday, October 30 or Tuesday, October 31, followed by Apple's earnings call on Thursday, November 2. He does not expect any of the new Macs to feature major changes other than new processors, but mused that there could be minor improvements to their displays.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also reiterated rumors that next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models with M3 chips will not launch until early 2024 and that a larger "pro" version of the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with a 32-inch display and a new design is tabled for late 2024 or 2025. Mac redesigns are apparently likely to occur when Apple begins adding touchscreens to the lineup further in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/">Gurman: Apple to Announce New Macs This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month.2408323/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube Music Integration Comes to HomePod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/youtube-music-integration-comes-to-homepod/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-music-integration-comes-to-homepod.2408314/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 02:12:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/youtube-music-integration-comes-to-homepod/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>YouTube Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube Music is <a href="https://support.google.com/youtubemusic/answer/9231765?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform%3DiOS&oco=1#zippy=%2Capple-homepod">now available</a> directly on Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, thanks to new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> integration support in the YouTube Music app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/youtube-music-logo.png" alt="" width="1200" height="626" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910085" /><br/>
The change means subscribers to the streaming service can now choose to use voice commands to start YouTube Music on a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, without having to append "on YouTube Music" to every request. From Google's <a href="https://support.google.com/youtubemusic/answer/9231765?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform%3DiOS&oco=1#zippy=%2Capple-homepod">support document</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>YouTube Music is supported on the following Apple HomePod models: Apple HomePod 1st Generation, Apple HomePod 2nd Generation, Apple HomePod Mini.<br/>
<br/>
With YouTube Music on Apple HomePod, you can:<br/>
â€“ Use Siri voice commands or physical touch controls on Apple HomePod to play music <br/>
â€“ Handoff playback between your Apple HomePod and iPhone, and vice versa<br/>
â€“ Control playback in the Apple Home app.</blockquote> Support for the option was announced by YouTube Music in a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/YoutubeMusic/comments/17cht03/you_can_now_use_youtube_music_on_your_apple/">Reddit post</a> spotted by <em><a href="https://9to5google.com/2023/10/20/youtube-music-homepod/">9to5Google</a></em>. The update has been expected since September, when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/youtube-music-homepod-integration/">hidden code was revealed in the app</a>.<br/>
<br/>
To set up &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; integration for YouTube Music, make sure you have updated the app, then follow these steps.<ol><li>Open the YouTube Music app.</li><br/>
<li>Tap your profile image in the top-right corner.</li><br/>
<li>Go to Settings âž Connected Apps.</li><br/>
<li>Select Connect with &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;.</li><br/>
<li>Tap Use in Home.</li></ol>If you don't see the option in YouTube Music, try force-closing the app and re-opening it.<br/>
<br/>
After you have done that, you will need to select YouTube as the "Default Service" for your &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;(s).<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Home app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the More button (three encircled dots) in the top-right corner.</li><br/>
<li>Tap Home Settings.</li><br/>
<li>Tap your username under the "People" section.</li><br/>
<li>Tap Default Service and choose YouTube Music.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/youtube-music-homepod.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918044" /><br/>
<br/>
Note that to connect YouTube Music to &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, you will need to have either a YouTube Music or YouTube Premium account.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has supported a handful of third-party music services on â€Œ&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;â€Œ for the last couple of years, and the functionality is already available with Pandora, iHeartRadio, Deezer, and TuneIn Radio.<br/>
<br/>
Other music services including Spotify have not supported this option even though Apple made the SiriKit Media feature available in iOS 14, so it remains limited in scope. With the direct play function, users can set a third-party service as a default music option, and when â€Œ&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;â€Œ on â€Œ&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;â€Œ is asked to play content, â€Œ&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;â€Œ will play music from the selected service.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube-music/">YouTube Music</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/youtube-music-integration-comes-to-homepod/">YouTube Music Integration Comes to HomePod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-music-integration-comes-to-homepod.2408314/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Unreleased HomePod With LCD Display Allegedly Shown in Images [Update]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/images-show-new-homepod-with-screen/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unreleased-homepod-with-lcd-display-allegedly-shown-in-images-update.2408299/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 19:24:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/images-show-new-homepod-with-screen/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update:</strong>Kosutami has since revealed that the LcdUTest app shown on the HomePod's display has been superimposed and doesn't exist in the original picture, but the <a href="https://x.com/KosutamiSan/status/1716312059569467839?s=20">LCD display panel shown on the HomePod is real</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to be developing a new HomePod with a screen, and new images shared online allegedly give us a first glimpse of the new smart speaker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/lcd-screen-homepod-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918030" /><br/>
The above image appears to show a HomePod similar in size to the second-generation HomePod that was launched earlier this year, but with what appears to be a functioning LCD display on the top.<br/>
<br/>
The image was <a href="https://twitter.com/KosutamiSan/status/1715673352986403091">shared</a> by device collector and leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>," who has previously shared accurate pre-release information about Apple's FineWoven accessories, various prototypes such as the MagSafe chargers and AirPods in different color options, and more. <br/>
<br/>
Earlier in the day, Kosutami also shared <a href="https://twitter.com/KosutamiSan/status/1715670862773514358">images of component parts</a> allegedly belonging to a prototype HomePod that features a large touch screen sensor at the top, with a much larger area than the current HomePod panel. <br/>
<br/>
Separately, <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/10/21/new-homepod-lcd-display/">9to5Mac</a></em> claims to have verified the legitimacy of these images with its own sources, and says that the prototype, codenamed B720, is a new product being actively worked on by Apple, rather than something that the company has experimented with in the past.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em>9to5Mac</em>, the LcdUTest app shown on the assembled HomePod's display panel is an internal app used by engineers to test the new display. The outlet says that code in tvOS 17 suggests that Apple Music and Apple Podcasts are the first apps being rewritten to be compatible with the new display, which will show a blurred animation based on the colors of the album art when a song or podcast is playing. The screen could also potentially show important notifications. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">An Engineering build HomePod frameshell with a completely different glass on top- itâ€™s set for touchscreen, with black bezel<br>The design of shell is similar to HomePod 2nd gen&#39;s, not the 1st genâ€”it stands ï£¿ might decided add &#x1f5a5;&#xfe0f; for 2&#39;s but not at last, OR itâ€™s next generation <a href="https://t.co/W5zRIVGPiK">pic.twitter.com/W5zRIVGPiK</a></p>&mdash; Kosutami (@KosutamiSan) <a href="https://twitter.com/KosutamiSan/status/1715670862773514358?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 21, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </div><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman was first to suggest in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/22/apple-speakers-with-screens-and-cameras-report/">2021</a> that Apple is working on new HomePods with displays and cameras. Earlier this year, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo claimed Apple plans to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">redesigned HomePod with a 7-inch display</a> in the first half of 2024. <br/>
<br/>
In the long term, Apple is believed to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/08/apple-engineers-pessimistic-apple-tv-strategy/">rethinking its smart home strategy</a>, and is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/28/gurman-combined-homepod-apple-tv-in-development/">combined Apple TV and HomePod device</a>, as well as a HomePod with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/12/homepod-ipad-with-robotic-arm/">screen mounted on a robotic arm</a>, according to a Gurman.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/images-show-new-homepod-with-screen/">Unreleased HomePod With LCD Display Allegedly Shown in Images [Update]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unreleased-homepod-with-lcd-display-allegedly-shown-in-images-update.2408299/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: New USB-C Apple Pencil, iPad and iMac Rumors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/top-stories-usb-c-apple-pencil/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-new-usb-c-apple-pencil-ipad-and-imac-rumors-and-more.2408251/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/top-stories-usb-c-apple-pencil/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After a flurry of rumors suggesting we might see some new iPad models this week, a new Apple Pencil turned out to actually be what was in the cards. The new Apple Pencil charges via USB-C, launches early next month, and is the cheapest model in a lineup that now includes three different Apple Pencils.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/top-stories-21oct2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917959" /><br/>
This week saw some additional rumors about future iPad and iMac models, while we're continuing to hear more about next year's iPhone 16 lineup, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Apple Pencil Announced With Hidden USB-C Port and More</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">announced a new lower-cost Apple Pencil</a> that will be sold alongside the original Apple Pencil and the Apple Pencil 2. It will be available in early November, with U.S. pricing set at &#36;79.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917176" /><br/>
The new Apple Pencil has a similar design as the Apple Pencil 2, but with a USB-C port hidden under a sliding cap for charging and pairing over a USB-C cable. It is compatible with all iPad models equipped with a USB-C port, including the lower-end iPad 10.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/8-things-to-know-about-new-apple-pencil/">8 Things to Know About the New Apple Pencil</a></li></ul><br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">coverage of the new Apple Pencil announcement</a>, our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">overview of the updated Apple Pencil lineup</a>, and our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil-buyers-guide/">Apple Pencil buyer's guide</a> for more details.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Possibly Working on Larger iPad Air With 12.9-Inch Display</h2><br/>
A confusing new report from supply chain publication <em>DigiTimes</em> suggests Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-working-on-larger-ipad-air/">may be planning to release a larger iPad Air with a 12.9-inch display</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
A preview of the report earlier this week indicated that a larger 12.9-inch iPad Air would be coming in the next update to the lineup, presumably alongside an updated 10.9-inch model, but the full article is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/2024-ipad-pro-lcd-panel-not-oled-or-mini-led/">less clear about the prospects for a 12.9-inch consumer model</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The report confusingly also claims that the next 12.9-inch iPad Pro will revert to traditional LCD backlighting rather than using the more advanced mini-LED backlighting found on the current model, while also mentioning upcoming iPad Pro models with OLED displays. Stay tuned for additional rumors that will hopefully clear things up.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New 24-Inch iMac Rumored to Launch in 2024</h2><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/24-inch-imac-2024-launch/">plans to release a new 24-inch iMac in 2024</a>, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. The current model with the M1 chip was announced in April 2021 and is now quite old.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iMac-M3-Blue-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917291" /><br/>
If Kuo is accurate, there will not be a new iMac this year. The all-in-one desktop computer is expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m3/">updated with a faster M3 chip</a> eventually, but no design changes have been rumored for the next model.<br/>
<br/>
Those hoping for a larger iMac may have to wait a bit longer, as Kuo also claims that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">32-inch model with a higher-end mini-LED display</a> won't be coming until 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Pro Rumor Recap: Larger Displays, Capture Button, 5G Advanced, and More</h2><br/>
While the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</a> are still around 11 months away from launching, there are already several rumors about the devices. We recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/iphone-16-pro-rumor-recap-october/">recapped new features and changes expected for the devices</a> so far, so check out the list to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
Key new features rumored for the iPhone 16 Pro models include larger displays, an all-new Capture Button, support for 5G Advanced, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Rumored to Follow ChatGPT With Generative AI Features on iPhone as Soon as iOS 18</h2><br/>
Apple plans to start <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-generative-ai-late-2024-jeff-pu/">implementing generative AI technology on the iPhone and iPad in late 2024</a> at the earliest, according to analyst Jeff Pu. This timeframe suggests that generative AI features could be introduced with iOS 18 and iPadOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
Generative AI surged in popularity last year when the company OpenAI released ChatGPT, a chatbot that can respond to questions and other prompts, and Apple has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">ramping up its work</a> on similar technology.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/oct-19-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/top-stories-usb-c-apple-pencil/">Top Stories: New USB-C Apple Pencil, iPad and iMac Rumors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-new-usb-c-apple-pencil-ipad-and-imac-rumors-and-more.2408251/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the &#36;1,700 &#039;OnePlus Open&#039; Foldable Smartphone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/oneplus-open-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-1-700-oneplus-open-foldable-smartphone.2408215/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 13:35:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/oneplus-open-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>OnePlus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Chinese smartphone company OnePlus this week introduced its first foldable smartphone, the OnePlus Open. OnePlus joins several other manufacturers that have come out with foldable smartphones, including Samsung, Google, and Xiaomi. We picked up the OnePlus Open to see how it compares to Apple's latest flagship, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hE172rh7BDo" title="OnePlus Open: Best Foldable in 2023?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The OnePlus Open is similar to the Galaxy Fold in that it opens up like a book. When folded, the cover screen has a 6.31-inch display that's about in the middle of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max in terms of size. Unfolded, the display measures in at 7.82 inches, so a bit smaller than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>. The displays are OLED and support a 120Hz refresh rate, with OnePlus advertising a "Ceramic Guard" cover glass, which sounds almost identical to the Ceramic Shield that Apple uses.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/oneplus-open.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917966" /><br/>
When it comes to form factor, the OnePlus Open is nothing like the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max from Apple since Apple hasn't delved into foldable smartphones as of yet, but there are similar components inside. The OnePlus Open has a premium feel, and size wise, it's between the Z Fold5 and the Pixel Fold. It is able to fold down flat with a crease that's almost unnoticeable, plus it's thin and lightweight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/oneplus-open-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917967" /><br/>
The Open is 11.7mm thick when it's folded in half, but when you open it up, it's 5.8mm. For comparison, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max is 8.25mm thick. As for weight, it is 239 grams, or 18 grams heavier than the 15 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
OnePlus has a partnership with camera company Hasselblad, and it is using a 48-megapixel wide-angle camera, a 64-megapixel telephoto camera with 6x in-sensor lossless zoom, and a 48-megapixel ultra wide-angle camera. There's also a 20-megapixel front-facing selfie camera accessible when the OnePlus Open is unfolded, and a 32-megapixel selfie camera that can be used when it's closed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/oneplus-open-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917968" /><br/>
Design wise, the lenses are in a large circular housing at the back of the device, which OnePlus likens to a the face of a luxury watch. The lens housing is super massive, and it can be hard to get photos from some of the lenses without your fingers getting in the way.<br/>
<br/>
Other features include the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 mobile platform, 16GB RAM, a fingerprint sensor power button, a 4,805mAh battery, and support for Wi-Fi 7.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/oneplus-open-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917969" /><br/>
The OnePlus Open is <a href="https://www.oneplus.com/us/open">available for pre-order</a> as of now, and it is set to launch on October 26. It is priced starting at &#36;1,700.<br/>
<br/>
What do you think of the OnePlus Open? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oneplus/">OnePlus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/oneplus-open-hands-on/">Hands-On With the &#36;1,700 &#039;OnePlus Open&#039; Foldable Smartphone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-1-700-oneplus-open-foldable-smartphone.2408215/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: No New Macs or iPads Expected to Launch for Remainder of 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/no-new-macs-or-ipads-expected-rest-of-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-no-new-macs-or-ipads-expected-to-launch-for-remainder-of-2023.2408214/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 13:10:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/no-new-macs-or-ipads-expected-rest-of-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is unlikely to release any new Macs or iPads for the remainder of 2023, according to a series of predictions shared in recent weeks by analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-wwdc-2022-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878408" /><br/>
<h2>Macs</h2><br/>
<br/>
Last month, Kuo said Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/kuo-first-m3-macbooks-unlikely-2023/">unlikely to release any new MacBooks with the M3 chip</a> this year. All existing MacBook Air and MacBook Pro models are equipped with M2 series chips, so any new models would presumably be equipped with M3 chips, which effectively means that Kuo does not expect any new MacBooks at all for the rest of 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Kuo added that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/24-inch-imac-2024-launch/">24-inch iMac would be updated next in 2024</a>, ruling out an update to the all-in-one desktop computer this year. All other desktop Macs, including the Mac mini, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro, were already updated in 2023 and are highly unlikely to be updated again until 2024 or later.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Macs by Date Last Updated</h3><br/>
<ul><li><strong>15-inch MacBook Air:</strong> June 2023</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac Studio:</strong> June 2023</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac Pro:</strong> June 2023</li><br/>
<li><strong>14-inch MacBook Pro:</strong> January 2023</li><br/>
<li><strong>16-inch MacBook Pro:</strong> January 2023</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac mini:</strong> January 2023</li><br/>
<li><strong>13-inch MacBook Air:</strong> June 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>13-inch MacBook Pro:</strong> June 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iMac:</strong> April 2021</li></ul><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
<h2>iPads</h2><br/>
<br/>
Last month, Kuo said Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/kuo-new-ipads-unlikely-to-launch-this-year/">unlikely to release any new iPad models</a> before the end of 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to release any new iPad Pro, iPad Air, iPad mini, or entry-level iPad models this year. If that trend continues for the remainder of 2023 as expected, it would be the first calendar year with no new iPads released in the device's 13-year history.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPads by Date Last Updated</h3><br/>
<ul><li><strong>iPad Pro:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPad:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPad Air:</strong> March 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPad mini:</strong> September 2021</li></ul><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/no-new-macs-or-ipads-expected-rest-of-2023/">Kuo: No New Macs or iPads Expected to Launch for Remainder of 2023</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-no-new-macs-or-ipads-expected-to-launch-for-remainder-of-2023.2408214/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second iOS 17.1 Release Candidate for iPhone 15 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/apple-seeds-second-ios-17-1-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-ios-17-1-release-candidate-for-iphone-15-models.2408209/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:20:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/apple-seeds-second-ios-17-1-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded a second release candidate (RC) version of iOS 17.1 to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a few days after Apple seeded the first RC. The second release candidate is limited to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, and it won't be available for download on other devices. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912331" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the iOS 17.1 beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the â€Œ<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>â€Œ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta. <br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 adds the option to favorite songs, albums, playlists, artists, and more, with favorited content added to the Library and used for suggestions. Favoriting can be done from the Lock Screen using the Now Playing widget, plus when starting a playlist, you'll now see Song Suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
AirDrop transfers can be finished over the internet so close proximity does not need to be maintained, and an Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 can now use NameDrop with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running iOS 17.1. On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, iOS 17.1 ensures you won't activate the Camera or Flashlight in your pocket.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include a flashlight indicator in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> for non &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, and a Wallet feature that lets U.S. Discover card users and those in the UK connect their banks to see balances and transactions. Apple's release notes for the update are below:<br/>
<blockquote><strong>AirDrop</strong><br/>
- Content continues to transfer over the internet when you step out of AirDrop range<br/>
<br/>
<strong>StandBy</strong><br/>
- New options to control when the display turns off (iPhone 14 Pro, iPhone 14 Pro Max, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Music</strong><br/>
- Favorites expanded to include songs, albums, and playlists, and you can filter to display your favorites in the library<br/>
- New cover art collection offers designs that change colors to reflect the music in your playlist<br/>
- Song suggestions appear at the bottom of every playlist, making it easy to add music that matches the vibe of your playlist<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update also includes the following improvements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Option to choose a specific album to use with Photo Shuffle on the Lock Screen<br/>
- Home key support for Matter locks<br/>
- Improved reliability of Screen Time settings syncing across devices<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may cause the Significant Location privacy setting to reset when transferring an Apple Watch or pairing it for the first time<br/>
- Resolves an issue where the names of incoming callers may not appear when you are on another call<br/>
- Addresses an issue where custom and purchased ringtones may not appear as options for your text tone<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may cause the keyboard to be less responsive<br/>
- Crash detection optimizations (all iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 models)<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may cause display image persistence<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, the update also adds support for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">new USB-C Apple Pencil</a>. <br/>
<br/>
More information on some of the unmentioned features in iOS 17.1 can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">available in our iOS 17.1 features article</a>. iOS 17.1 is expected to launch next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/apple-seeds-second-ios-17-1-rc/">Apple Seeds Second iOS 17.1 Release Candidate for iPhone 15 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-ios-17-1-release-candidate-for-iphone-15-models.2408209/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Sonos Takes &#36;100 Off Move Speaker and Anker&#039;s Pre-Black Friday Sale Has Big USB-C Accessory Discounts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-20-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-sonos-takes-100-off-move-speaker-and-ankers-pre-black-friday-sale-has-big-usb-c-accessory-discounts.2408204/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:13:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-20-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Highlights of this week's deals include a rare sale on the Sonos Move speaker at &#36;100 off and a huge collection of Anker USB-C accessory discounts. You'll also find solid sales on the AirPods 3 at Verizon and the 10th generation iPad at Amazon<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0000.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847990" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917913" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to 50% off Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/ckNTaeRyl5Y">Anker</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ankers-pre-black-friday-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTaeRyl5Y"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 50% OFF</div>Anker's Pre-Black Friday Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker kicked off its pre-Black Friday sale this week, with up to 50 percent off select charging accessories. This includes low prices on USB-C chargers and portable batteries, some of which we've collected below. You'll also find some of the accessories are being matched on Amazon, and note that many of these deals will expire this Sunday.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTihynVor">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTdoG6VVS">67W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;59.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469063005">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTeKlQeKI">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.50, down from &#36;29.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK77HJ">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTo2cHQpF">PowerCore 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;36.52, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTnSeYEIs">PowerCore 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTlSZyqr4">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTmKHIliZ">PowerCore 26,000 mAh</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTckazLPK">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469007512">Amazon</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sonos</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/sonos-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917912" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;100 off Sonos Move (gen 1)</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/move">Sonos</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/deals-sonos-move-speaker/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/move"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Sonos Move (Gen 1) for &#36;299</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Sonos introduced a rare discount on its first generation Move speaker this week, available for &#36;299.00, down from &#36;399.00. This version of the Sonos Move supports AirPlay 2, Wi-Fi and Bluetooth, an 11 hour battery life, voice and touch controls, and has IP56 water resistance. It's available in Lunar White and Shadow Black at this 25 percent discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 3</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airpods-3-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917911" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;20 off AirPods 3</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation-lightning-charging-case%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5600049">Verizon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/deals-airpods-3-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation-lightning-charging-case%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5600049"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirPods 3 (Lightning) for &#36;149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku4820001"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirPods 3 (MagSafe) for &#36;159.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Verizon has discounts on both models of the AirPods 3, priced at &#36;149.99 for the Lightning model and &#36;159.00 for the MagSafe model. These discounts are overall second-best prices on the AirPods 3, but we haven't tracked all-time low deals in months, so they're still good deals for anyone looking to purchase the AirPods 3 soon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917910" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off 10th gen iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/deals-apples-10th-gen-ipad-2/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 10th generation iPad hit &#36;399.00 this week on Amazon in every color, and they're all still on sale today. This is &#36;50 in savings and a solid second-best discount on the tablet.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-20-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Sonos Takes &#36;100 Off Move Speaker and Anker&#039;s Pre-Black Friday Sale Has Big USB-C Accessory Discounts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-sonos-takes-100-off-move-speaker-and-ankers-pre-black-friday-sale-has-big-usb-c-accessory-discounts.2408204/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
