<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 02:03:46 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Planning &#039;Ten Year Celebration&#039; Activity Achievement for Apple Watch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-watch-anniversary-activity-achievement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-planning-ten-year-celebration-activity-achievement-for-apple-watch.2442103/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 15:42:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-watch-anniversary-activity-achievement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple appears to be planning an activity challenge to celebrate the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch, which was released in 2015. In the latest iOS 18.2 beta, there's a mention of a "Ten Year Celebration" with references to an activity achievement, so it sounds like something is in the works.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-watch-series-10-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972560" /><br/>
While the Apple Watch was introduced at Apple's September 2014 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> event, it was not released until April 2015. The delay between the device's introduction and its launch have raised questions about whether the Apple Watch 10th anniversary is in 2024 or 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Apple celebrated the 10th anniversary of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with the launch of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X in 2017, and this year, the company highlighted the 10th anniversary of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>. Apple does see 10th anniversaries as notable, so we can expect something for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Back in 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> claimed that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">planning a complete revamp</a> of the Apple Watch for its 10th anniversary, complete with a magnetic band attachment system and a slimmer design. In September 2024, the Apple Watch did get a design update with larger displays and a thinner chassis, but the device was not branded the "Apple Watch X" as Gurman said it would be, nor did it have a new band attachment system.<br/>
<br/>
It is possible that those updates that Gurman talked about in 2023 will actually come in 2025 as part of an anniversary celebration for the device, but it is unclear because the slimmed down look that Gurman mentioned has already been implemented.<br/>
<br/>
Next year will also mark the 10th anniversary of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> streaming service, which came out in June 2015. Apple could also have something planned for that anniversary.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-watch-anniversary-activity-achievement/">Apple Planning &#039;Ten Year Celebration&#039; Activity Achievement for Apple Watch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-planning-ten-year-celebration-activity-achievement-for-apple-watch.2442103/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Continues Working to Get Blood Oxygen Sensing Back in U.S. Apple Watches as Next Masimo Trial Begins</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/masimo-apple-california-trade-secret-trial/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-continues-working-to-get-blood-oxygen-sensing-back-in-u-s-apple-watches-as-next-masimo-trial-begins.2442095/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 13:56:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/masimo-apple-california-trade-secret-trial/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Masimo are back in a California court this week for a bench trial that will see Masimo arguing that Apple illegally poached its employees and stole trade secrets when developing the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/masimo-watch-freedom.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-973055" /><br/>
Masimo first filed the trade secret lawsuit against Apple in 2020, and there was a jury trial in April 2023. During that trial, the court threw out more than half of Masimo's trade secret claims, but the judge ultimately declared a mistrial because the jury was not able to come to a final decision. Six of seven jurors sided with Apple, while one Masimo holdout would not change her opinion.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Masimo were slated to retry the case with another jury, but Masimo abandoned all claims asking for monetary compensation in order to get a bench trial instead. Masimo originally requested &#36;1.85 billion in damages, along with reasonable royalties, lost profits, and a penalty for willful trade secret appropriation.<br/>
<br/>
With the bench trial, Masimo is no longer claiming any monetary damages, but it wants an injunction against the Apple Watch. The bench trial will first determine if there were any trade secret violations, and then the court will consider Masimo's argument for an injunction. It is unclear what injunctive relief Masimo could ask for in this situation, especially as many of the claims in this case have now been thrown out.<br/>
<br/>
During the case, Masimo accused Apple of infringing on 17 patents. After an ITC review, 15 of the 17 patents were invalidated, with two remaining. The patent portion of the trade secret case is on hold.<br/>
<br/>
Note that the Masimo trade secret lawsuit against Apple is separate from both an ITC injunction preventing the sale of Apple Watch models with a blood oxygen sensor and a patent infringement case that Apple filed against Masimo.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is appealing the ITC's Apple Watch injunction, but it has been able to continue selling the Apple Watch by disabling the blood oxygen sensor that allegedly infringes on Masimo's technology. To get the sales ban in the first place, Masimo had to prove that it was using the patents that Apple was infringing, so Masimo rushed to create its own smart watch in 2022, deliberately copying several of Apple's patents.<br/>
<br/>
Masimo's W1 Freedom smart watch was the subject of the patent lawsuit that Apple filed against Masimo, and just last week, a jury <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/27/apple-wins-250-masimo-watch-patent-trial/">decided that Masimo's devices</a> had infringed on Apple Watch patents. Apple says that it only asked for &#36;250 in damages, as the goal of the lawsuit wasn't profit, it was to get Masimo to stop copying the design of the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
The ITC order is the most damaging to Apple because Apple is prevented from selling Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing in the United States. Apple believes the appeals court will overturn the ITC's ruling, and the company said this week that it is exploring all possible methods to get blood oxygen sensing back in U.S. Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
Over the last five years, Masimo has been fighting three separate cases with Apple. Masimo did win the ITC ban of the blood oxygen sensing feature, but it ultimately had no material impact on Apple's business because Apple was able to simply disable the feature and continue selling the device. So far, Masimo has not gained much in its legal battle with Apple, and it isn't looking like the trade secret case will go in Masimo's favor.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/masimo-apple-california-trade-secret-trial/">Apple Continues Working to Get Blood Oxygen Sensing Back in U.S. Apple Watches as Next Masimo Trial Begins</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-continues-working-to-get-blood-oxygen-sensing-back-in-u-s-apple-watches-as-next-masimo-trial-begins.2442095/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OWC&#039;s Thunderbolt 5 External SSD for Latest Macs is Impressively Fast</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/owc-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-for-macs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-for-latest-macs-is-impressively-fast.2442093/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 13:51:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/owc-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-for-macs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>OWC</category>
		<category>Thunderbolt 5</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new Mac mini with the M4 Pro chip and MacBook Pro models with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/30/apple-announces-macbook-pro-models/">support for the faster Thunderbolt 5 specification</a>, and reputable accessory maker OWC is ready with a new external SSD.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/MacBook-Pro-OWC-Envoy-Ultra.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975784" /><br/>
Announced in September, OWC's <a href="https://eshop.macsales.com/shop/owc-envoy-ultra">Envoy Ultra external SSD</a> is <a href="https://www.owc.com/news/other-world-computing-owc-helps-power-the-future-for-apple-users-with-thunderbolt-5-solutions-for-new-mac-mini-and-macbook-pro-with-m4">compatible</a> with Apple's latest Macs, and it has Thunderbolt 5 support for advertised data transfer speeds of more than 6GB per second. That is up to double the speeds that OWC's previous high-end external SSDs with Thunderbolt 3/Thunderbolt 4 support can achieve. <br/>
<br/>
The external SSD has a built-in Thunderbolt 5 cable, and it is powered by the Mac that it is connected to, rather than an external power supply.<br/>
<br/>
Unsurprisingly, these impressive speeds come at a steeper price compared to the average external SSD. OWC is now <a href="https://eshop.macsales.com/shop/owc-envoy-ultra">accepting pre-orders</a> for the Envoy Ultra through its online store in the U.S., with 2TB and 4TB storage capacities available for &#36;399.99 and &#36;599.99, respectively. Orders are estimated to begin shipping in early November.<br/>
<br/>
OWC plans to announce a Thunderbolt 5 dock with an array of ports later in November.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's new Macs launch on Friday.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/owc/">OWC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/thunderbolt-5/">Thunderbolt 5</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/owc-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-for-macs/">OWC&#039;s Thunderbolt 5 External SSD for Latest Macs is Impressively Fast</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-thunderbolt-5-external-ssd-for-latest-macs-is-impressively-fast.2442093/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Plans to Fine Apple for Anticompetitive App Store Practices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/eu-apple-fine-anticompetitive-app-store-practices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-plans-to-fine-apple-for-anticompetitive-app-store-practices.2442092/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 13:23:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/eu-apple-fine-anticompetitive-app-store-practices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The European Commission plans to fine Apple for not adequately complying with Digital Markets Act (DMA) requirements for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-11-05/apple-to-face-first-eu-fine-under-bloc-s-digital-markets-act">Bloomberg</a></em>. Regulators apparently believe that Apple did not implement changes that allowed developers to steer users to cheaper prices outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Back in June, the EU said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">Apple was in breach</a> of the DMA due to its anti-steering rules. The European Commission said that developers should be able to inform their customers of alternative purchasing options, steer them to offers, and allow them to make purchases outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
In August, Apple again <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/app-store-external-links-european-union/">changed its App Store rules</a> in Europe to satisfy regulators. Apple began allowing EU developers to communicate and promote offers that would direct customers outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and it marked a significant loosening of Apple's prior rules. Developers are able to communicate discounts and deals without opting into Apple's new developer terms or paying the Core Technology Fee, but Apple is requiring developers to report external purchase transactions and pay an initial acquisition fee and a store services fee.<br/>
<br/>
It is not clear when the European Commission will announce the fine, but it could happen before current competition commissioner Margrethe Vestager leaves the position later this month. It could also be pushed back to later in the year, though.<br/>
<br/>
Exactly how much Apple will have to pay is unknown at this time, but earlier this year, the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/eu-fines-apple-2-billion/">fined Apple &#36;2 billion</a> for anticompetitive behavior against third-party music services. Under the DMA, the European Union can fine Apple up to 10 percent of its global annual sales.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/eu-apple-fine-anticompetitive-app-store-practices/">EU Plans to Fine Apple for Anticompetitive App Store Practices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-plans-to-fine-apple-for-anticompetitive-app-store-practices.2442092/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stores Moving This Weekend in Three U.S. Cities, Including Tucson</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/three-apple-stores-moving-this-weekend/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-moving-this-weekend-in-three-u-s-cities-including-tucson.2442088/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 12:16:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/three-apple-stores-moving-this-weekend/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/laencantada/">announced</a> that its retail store at La Encantada in Tucson, Arizona will be moving to a temporary location that opens Saturday, November 9 at 10 a.m. local time. Apple says the temporary store will be located on the second level of the outdoor shopping center, just in front of the stairs and escalator leading to that level.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Apple-Store-La-Encantada-Tucson-AZ.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1612" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975758" /><br/>
Apple will likely renovate its original store at La Encantada while operating out of the temporary location, but the company did not share details or a timeframe. Apple first opened a store there in 2004, and its interior design is now dated.<br/>
<br/>
Last week, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/31/apple-store-revamps-long-island-and-fairfax/">we reported</a> that Apple would be opening a relocated store in Fairfax, Virginia, and a temporary store at Roosevelt Field on Long Island in New York. Apple has since announced that both of these stores will open on November 9 as well. Overall, it will be an eventful weekend for Apple retail in the U.S., with three stores on the move.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/three-apple-stores-moving-this-weekend/">Apple Stores Moving This Weekend in Three U.S. Cities, Including Tucson</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-moving-this-weekend-in-three-u-s-cities-including-tucson.2442088/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Veterans Day Apple Watch Activity Challenge Set for November 11</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-watch-veterans-day-activity-challenge-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/veterans-day-apple-watch-activity-challenge-set-for-november-11.2442087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 11:45:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-watch-veterans-day-activity-challenge-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning an Apple Watch Activity Challenge to honor Veterans Day, which takes place next Monday in the United States. Apple Watch owners are tasked with doing any workout for 11 minutes or more on November 11.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/apple-watch-activity-challenge-veterans-day.jpg" alt="" width="809" height="455" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975728" /><br/>
Apple Watch owners who complete the challenge will win an Apple Watch activity award in the Fitness app. <br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Earn this award on November 11 by doing any workout for 11 minutes or more. Record your time with the Workout app or any app that adds workouts to Health.</blockquote>Like all of Apple's Activity Challenges, the Veterans Day event will come with animated stickers that can be found in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/veterans_day_2024_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975723" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/veterans_day_2024_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975724" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/veterans_day_2024_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975725" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/VeteransDay_Sticker_animated.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975726" /><br/>
Apple's Veterans Day Activity Challenge is offered on an annual basis, and the company often includes other Veterans Day-themed content in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, Books app, and more. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-watch-veterans-day-activity-challenge-2/">Veterans Day Apple Watch Activity Challenge Set for November 11</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/veterans-day-apple-watch-activity-challenge-set-for-november-11.2442087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing the Vision Pro With New Ultrawide Display Option in visionOS 2.2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/vision-pro-ultrawide-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-the-vision-pro-with-new-ultrawide-display-option-in-visionos-2-2.2442082/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 11:00:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/vision-pro-ultrawide-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first developer beta of visionOS 2.2 came out yesterday, and it includes a much anticipated new feature for Vision Pro users. When using the Vision Pro as a display for a Mac, there are now options to use wide and ultrawide layouts in addition to the standard virtual display.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Wide &amp; Ultrawide Displays with Mac &amp; Apple Vision Pro is CRAZY!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x3_0kNLr3Ew" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
We thought we'd check out the new display settings for those who might be interested in seeing how this changes the Vision Pro Mac workflow.<br/>
<br/>
With the wide display option, there's enough screen real estate to use four apps at once without compromising on window size. Ultrawide bumps up the available space even more, and it's almost too much display space.<br/>
<br/>
Using the ultrawide setting is like having multiple curved Mac displays in front of you to handle your Mac apps, and then you can also add in visionOS apps to better utilize the virtual space around you. The larger screen sizes for the Mac do improve productivity because there's so much more space to work with.<br/>
<br/>
Note that you still can't use multiple Mac windows when mirroring your Mac display to your Vision Pro, but the wide and ultrawide provide so much space that it's essentially the same function. Apple says that the ultrawide mode is equivalent to using two 4K monitors side by side.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to adding these display modes, Apple improved the quality of the virtual displays so they're crisper and higher resolution, plus audio plays from the Vision Pro rather than the Mac so it sounds better.<br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.2 is in beta right now, but it will see a launch alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.2 and iOS 18.2 in early December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/vision-pro-ultrawide-display/">Testing the Vision Pro With New Ultrawide Display Option in visionOS 2.2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-the-vision-pro-with-new-ultrawide-display-option-in-visionos-2-2.2442082/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker&#039;s Early Black Friday Sale Includes Exclusive 20% Off for MacRumors Readers, Mystery Boxes, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/anker-black-friday-exclusive-macrumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-early-black-friday-sale-includes-exclusive-20-off-for-macrumors-readers-mystery-boxes-and-more.2442080/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 10:56:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/anker-black-friday-exclusive-macrumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[MacRumors readers can get <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">20 percent off a collection of Anker's best chargers</a>, power banks, cables, hubs, and docks this month, just in time for holiday shopping. In order to get this deal, head to Anker's website and add an accessory to your cart, then enter the code <strong>akmacrumors20ch</strong> at checkout to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/anker-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975712" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Our exclusive 20 percent off code works on most accessories sitewide, including Anker's new line of MagSafe-compatible products. Our code does not stack with any existing offers, including any early access Black Friday deals. We've collected some of the best accessories to use our code on in the list below. In some cases Anker's own on-page coupons are better, so we have marked them as such.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE 20% OFF</div>Anker Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker is also currently hosting a <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fblack-friday-sale%3Fref%3Dhomepage_masterBanner_1">new Black Friday event</a> where you can buy two accessories to get 20 percent off, or buy three for 25 percent off, so if you plan on buying in bulk this may be a better offer. There are also mystery boxes where you can spend up to &#36;79.99 in order to win a piece of gear worth as much as &#36;799.00.<br/>
<br/>
Don't forget that our exclusive code works with even more devices sitewide. All prices listed below will appear after you enter the code <strong>akmacrumors20ch</strong> at the checkout screen on Anker's website.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Prime Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa88e2-anker-prime-usb-c-cable-3-ft-240w-upcycled-braided%3FranEAID%3DJ2shFQg6J%252FU%26ranMID%3D43469%26ranSiteID%3DJ2shFQg6J_U-1xC0ZLVCf6fRYJ1o_5yn2g%26variant%3D43931966537878">Prime USB-C to USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;28.00, down from &#36;34.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2683-anker-prime-charger-200w-6-ports-gan%3Fvariant%3D43856909074582">Prime Charger (200W, 6 Ports)</a> - &#36;68.40, down from &#36;84.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2688-anker-prime-charger-100w-3-ports-gan%3Fvariant%3D43931966079126">Prime Charger (100W, 3 Ports)</a> - &#36;64.00, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1339-anker-prime-power-bank-9600mah-65w-fusion%3Fvariant%3D43931966210198">Prime Power Bank</a> - &#36;72.00, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa91b2-anker-prime-charging-station-240w-8-in-1%3Fvariant%3D43931967651990">Prime Charging Station (8-in-1)</a> - &#36;132.00, down from &#36;164.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1340-250w-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D43739694465174">Prime Power Bank 27,650 mAh</a> - &#36;144.00, down from &#36;179.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa83b6-anker-prime-charging-docking-station-14-in-1-dual-display-160w%3Fvariant%3D43931966734486">Prime Charging Docking Station (14-in-1)</a> - &#36;200.00, down from &#36;249.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wireless Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa25m8-maggo-qi2-wireless-charging-station-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D44057193316502%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo 3-in-1 Foldable Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;72.00, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa25x1-maggo-qi2-wireless-charging-stand-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D44058196639894%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo Wireless Charger Stand</a> - &#36;28.80, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2544-maggo-qi2-wireless-charger-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D43823744516246%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo 2-in-1 Wireless Charger Stand</a> - &#36;40.00, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa25m7-maggo-qi2-wireless-charger-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D44058260177046%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo 2-in-1 Wireless Charger Dock Stand</a> - &#36;40.00, down from &#36;49.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Power Banks</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1664-maggo-10000mah-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D44058070548630%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo Power Bank 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;60.00, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1657-maggo-10000mah-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D44058151452822%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo Power Bank for Apple Watch</a> - &#36;59.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;79.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa90h1-maggo-iphone-magnetic-case%3Fvariant%3D44058277413014%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo Magnetic Case with Stand</a> - &#36;24.00, down from &#36;32.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa83d1-maggo-usb-c-adapter%3Fvariant%3D44058148241558%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo USB-C Adapter</a> - &#36;23.10 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;34.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa720c-iphone-16-screen-protector%3Fvariant%3D44058257588374%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">Easy Fit Screen Protector</a> - &#36;19.20 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;31.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/anker-black-friday-exclusive-macrumors/">Anker&#039;s Early Black Friday Sale Includes Exclusive 20% Off for MacRumors Readers, Mystery Boxes, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-early-black-friday-sale-includes-exclusive-20-off-for-macrumors-readers-mystery-boxes-and-more.2442080/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Employee Count Grew This Year Despite Smaller-Scale Layoffs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-employee-count-grew-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-employee-count-grew-this-year-despite-smaller-scale-layoffs.2442077/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 10:38:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-employee-count-grew-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's employee count grew in 2024, despite reports that the company had at least four incidents of smaller-scale layoffs this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/imac-video-apple-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2302" height="1296" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-973310" /><br/>
As of late September, Apple had approximately 164,000 full-time employees worldwide, the company disclosed <a href="https://d18rn0p25nwr6d.cloudfront.net/CIK-0000320193/c87043b9-5d89-4717-9f49-c4f9663d0061.pdf">in a filing</a> last week. That's up from the 161,000 full-time employees that Apple reported a year ago. These figures include corporate employees, such as software engineers, and retail employees at its stores.<br/>
<br/>
Apple now has as many employees as it did in 2022, following a slight decrease last year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's full-time employee counts by year, per the company's filings:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>2024:</strong> 164,000</li><br/>
<li><strong>2023:</strong> 161,000</li><br/>
<li><strong>2022:</strong> 164,000</li><br/>
<li><strong>2021:</strong> 154,000</li><br/>
<li><strong>2020:</strong> 147,000</li><br/>
<li><strong>2019:</strong> 137,000</li><br/>
<li><strong>2018:</strong> 132,000</li></ul>Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/apple-employee-layoffs-car-project/">laid off more than 600 employees</a> this year after canceling its long-running electric vehicle project, according to a notice the company filed in California. The company also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-moving-san-diego-siri-team-to-austin/">relocated a Siri evaluation team from San Diego, California to Austin, Texas</a>, and some on the 120-person team who were not willing to make the long-distance move were laid off.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-lays-off-services-staff-apple-books/">cut around 100 jobs across its Apple Books and Apple News teams</a> this year, and laid off some employees after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">abandoning its plan to develop in-house Apple Watch displays with micro-LED technology</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
While some other tech companies like Google and Microsoft have laid off tens of thousands of employees over the past two years, Apple has managed to avoid larger-scale layoffs in that time. With its employee count once again at an all-time high, and its quarterly revenues <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/31/apple-4q-2024-earnings/">in record territory again</a>, Apple is heading into 2025 on a good note.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-employee-count-grew-this-year/">Apple&#039;s Employee Count Grew This Year Despite Smaller-Scale Layoffs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-employee-count-grew-this-year-despite-smaller-scale-layoffs.2442077/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Silicon Unified Memory: How Much Mac RAM Do You Need?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-much-mac-ram/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-silicon-unified-memory-how-much-mac-ram-do-you-need.2442072/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 08:42:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-much-mac-ram&#038;post_date=1730835753/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		<category>RAM</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When choosing a new Mac, one of the most important decisions you'll make is how much memory to configure. This guide helps you to work out how much RAM you need.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-silicon-feature-joeblue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945652" /><br/>
With the advent of Apple silicon and its unified memory architecture in 2020, the traditional understanding of RAM has evolved, leading to new considerations for users when selecting a memory option. Unlike traditional PC RAM, where separate components like the CPU and GPU each have their own dedicated memory pools, Apple's unified memory architecture allows all processing units to access a single, shared pool of high-bandwidth, low-latency memory. <br/>
<br/>
As a result, in Apple silicon systems, data doesn't need to be copied between multiple memory areas, significantly improving speed and power efficiency. By uniting memory, Apple devices with this technology theoretically deliver superior performance across multitasking, creative workflows, and demanding applications while minimizing the latency typically associated with data transfer between separate memory types. With the optimizations of macOS, this means that less memory can go further than before, for most Mac users.<br/>
<br/>
All Mac models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/30/entire-mac-lineup-now-at-least-16gb-ram/">now start with 16GB of memory</a>, up from 8GB, with the option to upgrade to higher configurations with build-to-order models. However, choosing to do so can add considerable cost to the base price of a new Mac. <br/>
<br/>
To help you make the best choice for your workflow and budget, here's a breakdown of who should choose each memory tier currently available in the entire Mac lineup and why it may be the right fit for you:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>16GB</strong>: General users, students, and professionals with standard workloads should opt for 16GB. This configuration is perfect for those who primarily browse the web, stream content, use productivity apps, and perform multitasking. Thanks to the performance of Apple silicon and the efficiency of macOS, 16GB is more than sufficient for a smooth experience with everyday tasks.</li><br/>
<li><strong>24GB</strong>: Users who need slightly more headroom for multitasking and moderate creative work should consider 24GB. This tier is ideal for those who work with slightly heavier applications such as video editing, gaming, graphic design, or coding but do not push these tasks to the absolute extreme. It provides an additional buffer for users who run multiple intensive apps simultaneously and perform more multitasking than what 16GB can handle comfortably.</li><br/>
<li><strong>32GB or 36GB</strong>: Professionals engaging in intensive creative workflows, such as video editing in 4K, music production with multiple tracks, or large-scale coding projects, should opt for 32GB or 36GB. These configurations suit users who frequently use memory-heavy applications like Adobe Creative Cloud apps, Xcode, or virtual machines. It provides sufficient power for consistent performance without frequent reliance on disk swapping, even under substantial workloads.</li><br/>
<li><strong>64GB</strong>: Power users and creative professionals who manage high-resolution media and extensive multitasking should choose 64GB. It is ideal for those working on large 3D modeling projects, editing 8K video, or handling complex simulations and data analysis. This memory quantity should support running multiple virtual machines or advanced software development environments without any slowdown.</li><br/>
<li><strong>96GB</strong>: High-end creative professionals and developers handling intensive projects involving large datasets or media should consider 96GB. This tier offers significant overhead for those who need more than 64GB, ensuring seamless performance when editing multiple streams of high-resolution video, detailed 3D rendering, or working with substantial datasets that need to be kept in active memory.</li><br/>
<li><strong>128GB</strong>: Professionals in specialized fields like film editing, data science, or engineering should look at 128GB. This memory configuration is designed for workflows that involve extremely large projects and require vast amounts of data to be kept in active memory. It is perfect for those working on high-resolution visual effects in cinema, simulation-based software, or advanced scientific computations, providing robust multitasking and peak performance across demanding tasks.</li><br/>
<li><strong>192GB</strong>: Enterprise-level users, researchers, and industry professionals dealing with mission-critical, memory-intensive applications should opt for 192GB. This option is suitable for large-scale data processing, machine learning, or AI development, ensuring maximum efficiency and reducing the need for data swapping between RAM and storage. It is also ideal for developers working on complex server-side projects requiring powerful single-machine testing.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
With Apple silicon's Unified Memory Architecture and macOS's efficient memory management, the base 16GB configuration now meets the needs of most users, providing a good balance of cost and performance for everyday computing tasks and moderate creative work. <br/>
<br/>
The increasing importance of demanding artificial intelligence features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> and the potential for more intensive applications over time mean that those with more demanding workflows or plans for longevity should consider upgrading the memory. Opting for 24GB or 32GB can provide an added buffer for the future, supporting heavier multitasking, creative software, and emerging AI features. Higher configurations, such as 64GB or more, are better for professionals in fields that require significant data handling, including video production, 3D rendering, and machine learning.<br/>
<br/>
For users who already own an Apple silicon Mac, it will be worthwhile to evaluate your current system's performance to determine whether you'll need more memory next time around. Consider whether your current memory configuration handles your typical workload efficiently or if you experience slowdowns during multitasking or when using resource-intensive applications. Ultimately, your decision should balance your current workload, any anticipated future requirements, and cost—especially since adding memory can be expensive and it cannot be changed after purchase. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ram/">RAM</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-much-mac-ram/">Apple Silicon Unified Memory: How Much Mac RAM Do You Need?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-silicon-unified-memory-how-much-mac-ram-do-you-need.2442072/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>GM Again Attempts to Explain Its Decision to Drop CarPlay in New EVs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/gm-further-explains-phasing-out-carplay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gm-again-attempts-to-explain-its-decision-to-drop-carplay-in-new-evs.2442066/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 08:17:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/gm-further-explains-phasing-out-carplay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[American automaker General Motors (GM) last year announced it would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/31/general-motors-to-phase-out-apple-carplay/">phasing out support for CarPlay</a> and Android Auto in its new electric vehicles, in favor of its own software platform called Ultifi. The decision has been very controversial, as many drivers consider CarPlay to be a must-have feature in a new vehicle. In 2022, for example, Apple said 79% of U.S. buyers would only consider a vehicle that works with CarPlay.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2015/02/carplay-widescreen-dashboard.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969132" /><br/>
To make matters worse, GM's rollout of Ultifi went rather poorly, with some early reviewers of the Chevrolet Blazer EV last year experiencing technical issues with the platform. Some of those problems have since been resolved, but it is clear that the automaker might not be as effective at developing software as a tech company like Apple.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/gm-carplay-removal-safer-drivers/">statement shared with <em>MacRumors</em></a> last year, GM said its software strategy is "driven by the benefits of having a system that allows for greater integration with the larger GM ecosystem and vehicles." In other words, the automaker wants to control the entire in-vehicle experience, which is both a reasonable and a risky decision.<br/>
<br/>
In a recent interview <a href="https://www.theverge.com/24285581/gm-software-baris-cetinok-apple-carplay-android-auto-google-cars-evs-decoder-podcast">with <em>The Verge</em>'s Nilay Patel</a>, GM's senior vice president of software Baris Cetinok further attempted to defend the automaker's decision to phase out CarPlay. Cetinok worked at Apple between 2012 and 2021, helping to spearhead the launch of Apple Pay, Find My, iCloud Drive, and more, according to his LinkedIn profile.<br/>
<br/>
Cetinok joined GM months after it announced its decision to phase out CarPlay and Android Auto, but unsurprisingly he stands by the automaker's decision. He told Patel that GM believes with "strong conviction" that creating its entire in-vehicle experience provides "a better customer experience" with "end-to-end magic."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/2024-Chevrolet-Blazer-EV-Ultifi.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975643" /><em>2024 Chevrolet Blazer EV with GM's Ultifi software platform</em></div><br/>
"But we have a strong conviction that effort pays off in a better customer experience," said Cetinok, speaking <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/why-gm-ditched-carplay-with-software-boss-baris-cetinok/id1011668648?i=1000675593119">on the <em>Decoder</em> podcast</a>. "You get the most out of your vehicle because now we're the company that builds the vehicle and is also creating the infotainment experience, the cluster experience, the app, and everything. We're going to build that one day and maybe a voice assistant on top of it. The only way you can create that end-to-end magic is to have a strong conviction that you want to own all of these."<br/>
<br/>
He said GM wants to offer a seamless experience that does not require having to switch in and out of phone mirroring systems like CarPlay and Android Auto.<br/>
<br/>
"When you want to create something so seamless, it's hard to think about getting into a car and going, 'Okay, so I'm doing highway trailering, but let me flip to a totally different user interface to pick my podcast,'" said Cetinok. "By the way, it's a single app-obsessed interface — it's still hard to believe. So I pick my podcast, flip back to trailering. Oh, now I can also do Super Cruise trailering. Let me manage that. Then, wait, we're now getting into potentially Level 3, Level 4 autonomy levels that should be deeply integrated with talking to the map where the lanes lie. But wait a minute, the map that I'm using doesn't really talk to my car."<br/>
<br/>
The full transcript of the interview with more CarPlay commentary is available <a href="https://www.theverge.com/24285581/gm-software-baris-cetinok-apple-carplay-android-auto-google-cars-evs-decoder-podcast">on <em>The Verge</em></a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/gm-further-explains-phasing-out-carplay/">GM Again Attempts to Explain Its Decision to Drop CarPlay in New EVs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gm-again-attempts-to-explain-its-decision-to-drop-carplay-in-new-evs.2442066/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Black Friday iPad Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals.2442060/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 07:02:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday is still a few weeks away, but you can already find great prices on numerous iPads, including the 9th generation iPad, 10th generation iPad, iPad Air, and iPad mini.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipads-early-bf-deals.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975363" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there is a chance that we could see better deals on these iPads arrive as Black Friday gets closer. This is a risk anyone has to take while shopping during the holidays, so with that in mind, many of the deals shared below are currently their best prices ever seen. More information on these sales can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
Unless otherwise noted, all the deals in this guide will be found on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_ipad_deals">Best iPad Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi)</strong></a> for &#36;199.99 (&#36;129 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%2Fref%3Dtwister_B0CMXMNNCH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26_encoding%3DUTF8%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi)</strong></a> for &#36;296.00 (&#36;53 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>Magic Keyboard for 11-inch iPad Pro</strong></a> for &#36;249.99 (&#36;49 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>Apple Pencil Pro</strong></a> for &#36;91.99 (&#36;37 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_black_friday_deals">Best Early Black Friday Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals-2024/">The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/02/early-black-friday-airpods-deals-2024/">The Best Early Black Friday AirPods Deals</a></li></ul><br/>
<h2 id="9th_gen_ipad">9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/new-ipad.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975366" /><br/>
<br/>
We've been tracking a great all-time low discount on the ninth generation iPad since Prime Day, and that discount is still around in November. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;329.00. At this price, the iPad is a perfect entry-level tablet for a kid or family member who doesn't need the tablet for work-intensive projects.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;129 OFF</div>10.2-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><h2 id="10th_gen_ipad">10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipad-10th-gen-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975369" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 64GB Wi-Fi iPad from 2022 is being discounted to the all-time low price of &#36;297.00 right now on Amazon, from &#36;349.00. This upgraded model comes with a larger 10.9-inch Liquid Retina display, A14 Bionic chip for a performance boost, Wi-Fi 6, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%2Fref%3Dtwister_B0CMXMNNCH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26_encoding%3DUTF8%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;53 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;296.00</div></a></div><h2 id="6th_gen_ipad_mini">7th Gen iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipad-mini-7-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975370" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's new 8.3-inch iPad mini 7 is down to &#36;399.99 on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. You'll need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see this deal. This iPad mini has an 8.3-inch Liquid Retina display, A17 Pro chip, Wi-Fi 6E, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3YF38G%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad mini 7 (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><h2 id="m2_ipad_air">M2 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipad-air-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975372" /><br/>
<br/>
For the latest iPad Air models, Amazon has a few all-time low prices, including the 256GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air for &#36;596.00 (&#36;103 off) and the 128GB Wi-Fi 13-inch iPad Air for &#36;691.00 (&#36;108 off). There are a few cellular discounts as well on select M2 iPad Air tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5D33G%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;103 OFF</div>11-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;596.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7GPRX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;108 OFF</div>13-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;691.00</div></a></div><h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil (USB-C)</a> - &#36;69.00 (&#36;10 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil Pro</a> - &#36;91.99 (&#36;37 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Magic Keyboard for 11-inch iPad Pro</a> - &#36;249.99 (&#36;49 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5ZBFR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Magic Keyboard for 13-inch iPad Pro</a> - &#36;273.99 (&#36;75 off)</li></ul> We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals-2024/">The Best Early Black Friday iPad Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals.2442060/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing to Add New Screen Savers to tvOS 18.2, Including Snoopy and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/new-apple-tv-screen-savers-coming-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-to-add-new-screen-savers-to-tvos-18-2-including-snoopy-and-more.2442058/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 06:36:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/new-apple-tv-screen-savers-coming-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Monday seeded the first beta of tvOS 18.2 to developers for testing, and the upcoming update includes hidden code-level references to new screen savers coming soon, according to <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Snoopy-Apple-TV-Screen-Saver.jpg" alt="" width="906" height="510" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975555" /><em>Snoopy</em></div><br/>
The code shows there will be four categories of screen savers added to the Apple TV, including Snoopy, TV and Movies, Music, and Soundscapes.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/TV-and-Movies-Apple-TV-Screen-Saver.jpg" alt="" width="906" height="510" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975557" /><em>TV and Movies</em></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Music-Apple-TV-Screen-Saver.jpg" alt="" width="906" height="510" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975561" /><em>Music</em></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Soundscapes-Apple-TV-Screen-Saver.jpg" alt="" width="906" height="510" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975560" /><em>Soundscapes</em></div><br/>
The new screen savers will likely become visible in a later tvOS 18.2 beta version. Apple's website <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-tv-4k/">indicates</a> that the Snoopy and TV and Movies options are "coming late 2024," and the Music and Soundscapes options will likely be available then too. We expect tvOS 18.2 to be released to the public in December, in line with the late 2024 timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
At least some of the new screen saver options, including Snoopy, will require a second-generation Apple TV 4K or newer, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Existing screen saver categories on the Apple TV include Aerials and Memories, along with a Portraits option with clocks added in tvOS 18.0.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/new-apple-tv-screen-savers-coming-soon/">Apple Preparing to Add New Screen Savers to tvOS 18.2, Including Snoopy and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-to-add-new-screen-savers-to-tvos-18-2-including-snoopy-and-more.2442058/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Track 2024 U.S. Election Results Live on Your iPhone Lock Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-news-us-election-results-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-2024-u-s-election-results-live-on-your-iphone-lock-screen.2442053/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 05:02:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-news-us-election-results-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple News is providing Live Activities support for the 2024 U.S. presidential election, allowing iPhone and iPad users to track electoral results in real time directly from their Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/election-results-2024-live-activities.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975519" /><br/>
The feature is rolling out for U.S. users over the course of Election Day, November 5, providing continuous updates of the electoral count. So if you're interested, you don't need to repeatedly check news websites or unlock your device. <br/>
<br/>
If you have an iPhone 14 Pro or later model running iOS 16.1 or newer, or an iPad running iPadOS 17 or later, you can activate the feature through the Apple News app. Setting it up in advance ensures you won't miss any updates when coverage begins. Open the Apple News app and tap the prominent "Follow Live" button when prompted. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/apple-news-election-updates.jpg" alt="Apple News" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975525" /><br/>
When active, the Live Activity will appear as an interactive widget on your Lock Screen – you can quickly access detailed coverage with a tap. For iPhone 14 Pro and newer models, updates will also be visible in the Dynamic Island at the top of the display, even if you're doing something else on your iPhone.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-news-us-election-results-iphone/">Track 2024 U.S. Election Results Live on Your iPhone Lock Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-2024-u-s-election-results-live-on-your-iphone-lock-screen.2442053/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Working on 90Hz Studio Display, iMac, iPad Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-working-on-90hz-studio-display-imac-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-working-on-90hz-studio-display-imac-ipad-air.2442047/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 03:11:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-working-on-90hz-studio-display-imac-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new rumor suggests Apple is developing 90Hz display technology that could make its way to future versions of the Studio Display, iPad Air, and 24-inch iMac, all of which currently feature 60Hz refresh rates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/studio-display-purple-february.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936777" /><br/>
The claim, spotted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/11/04/rumor-90hz-display-imac-studio-display-ipad-air/">9to5Mac</a></em>, comes from an anonymous source who contacted the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dkfMFNVnHVQ">Upgrade podcast</a>, hosted by Myke Hurley and Jason Snell. According to the source, Apple is working on "a higher refresh rate LCD display with a new liquid motion panel fixed at around 90Hz," with plans to implement the technology across multiple products.<br/>
<br/>
Such a development would be particularly noteworthy for the Studio Display, which hasn't received any hardware updates since its March 2022 launch. Many Apple users had hoped to see a refreshed model before the end of 2024, amid on-again, off-again rumors about a potential upgrade featuring mini-LED technology and ProMotion support. Apple's higher-end Pro Display XDR has also remained unchanged since its 2019 debut.<br/>
<br/>
Display analyst Ross Young, who is known for accurate predictions about Apple's display technology, reported in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/10/apple-27-inch-mini-led-display-cancelled/">April 2023</a> that Apple had abandoned plans for a 27-inch monitor with mini-LED backlighting. That canceled project, which could have been a next-generation Studio Display, was said to include the use of ProMotion technology with refresh rates up to 120Hz. Earlier, Young had anticipated such a display launching in 2022, but the release never materialized.<br/>
<br/>
According to the anonymous source, the 90Hz display technology will debut first in the next-generation M3 iPad Air, expected in early 2025, before expanding to other products. The 24-inch iMac, which just received an M4 update, likely wouldn't see this display improvement until late 2025 at the earliest.<br/>
<br/>
The current Studio Display features a 27-inch 5K LCD panel with 60Hz refresh rate, P3 wide color support, and up to 600 nits brightness, starting at &#36;1,599.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/apple-working-on-90hz-studio-display-imac-ipad-air/">Apple Reportedly Working on 90Hz Studio Display, iMac, iPad Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-working-on-90hz-studio-display-imac-ipad-air.2442047/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Indonesia iPhone Ban: Apple Proposes &#36;10M Manufacturing Investment</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-10m-investment/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-proposes-10m-manufacturing-investment.2442042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 02:25:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-10m-investment/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Indonesia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has proposed investing nearly &#36;10 million in Indonesian manufacturing operations in an effort to lift the country's recent ban on iPhone 16 sales, according to sources familiar with the matter (via <em><a href="https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/southeast-asia/article/3285194/apple-offers-indonesia-us10-million-sweetener-reverse-its-iphone-ban">South China Morning Post</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iPhone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964515" /><br/>
The investment would establish a factory in Bandung, near Jakarta, where Apple would partner with its suppliers to produce accessories and components for Apple devices. The proposal has been submitted to Indonesia's Ministry of Industry for review.<br/>
<br/>
The manufacturing investment comes in response to Indonesia <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/indonesia-bans-iphone-16-sales/">blocking iPhone 16 sales last month</a>, after it was determined that Apple's local unit failed to meet the country's requirement for 40% domestic content in smartphones. The ban is part of broader protectionist policies implemented under new President Prabowo Subianto's administration, which has also restricted sales of Google's Pixel phones for similar reasons.<br/>
<br/>
Indonesia represents a significant market for Apple, with the country's population of 280 million operating some 354 million active mobile phones. Apple has established four developer academies in Indonesia to train students and engineers, but the country's officials have pressed for more substantial manufacturing investments.<br/>
<br/>
The proposed &#36;10 million facility would mark Apple's first manufacturing presence in Indonesia, potentially helping the company comply with local content requirements. The Ministry of Industry is currently reviewing the proposal and is expected to make a decision soon.<br/>
<br/>
About 9,000 iPhone 16 units have entered Indonesia through personal imports, but these devices are restricted to personal use and cannot be sold commercially under the current ban.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/indonesia/">Indonesia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-10m-investment/">Indonesia iPhone Ban: Apple Proposes &#36;10M Manufacturing Investment</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-proposes-10m-manufacturing-investment.2442042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing for Upcoming Siri Onscreen Awareness Feature With New iOS 18.2 API for Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-onscreen-awareness-ios-18-2-api-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-for-upcoming-siri-onscreen-awareness-feature-with-new-ios-18-2-api-for-developers.2442015/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:32:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-onscreen-awareness-ios-18-2-api-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on more advanced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> functionality as part of its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> feature set, and to prepare, it has been providing developers with App Intent APIs so apps will be ready for the new capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963424" /><br/>
With the latest wave of betas, Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/appintents/making-onscreen-content-available-to-siri-and-apple-intelligence">has a new API</a> that lets developers make onscreen content in their apps available to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;. From Apple's documentation:<blockquote>When a user asks a question about onscreen content or wants to perform an action on it, Siri and Apple Intelligence can retrieve the content to respond to the question and perform the action. If the user explicitly requests it, Siri and Apple Intelligence can send content to supported third-party services. For example, someone could view a website and use Siri to provide a summary by saying or typing a phrase like "Hey Siri, what's this document about?"</blockquote>In the iOS 18.2 beta, ChatGPT integration with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; allows users to ask questions about photos and documents, such as PDFs and presentations, and get information about them. You can, for example, ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; "what's in this photo?" and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will take a screenshot and hand it over to ChatGPT. ChatGPT then relays what's in the image, and the same feature works for PDFs and other documents.<br/>
<br/>
It does not seem that the iOS 18.2 ChatGPT integration is the onscreen awareness functionality that Apple has planned for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, but it could be related. Apple describes onscreen awareness as the ability for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to understand and take action on things on the screen. If someone texts you an address, for example, you'll be able to say "Add this address to their contact card," and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will do it. This functionality is not available in iOS 18.2, and ChatGPT is limited to assessing screenshots, but it is somewhat confusing.<br/>
<br/>
Onscreen awareness, like personal context and in-app actions, is a feature that Apple has planned for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, but it's probably not something that we're getting this year. Many of the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features are coming in a future version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said we can expect to see them in iOS 18.4, an update set to be released in the spring of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
While there are multiple &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features that won't be coming until next year, Apple is providing developers with APIs in advance so that developers have several months to prepare and so the features are ready for the public when the updates actually come out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-onscreen-awareness-ios-18-2-api-developers/">Apple Preparing for Upcoming Siri Onscreen Awareness Feature With New iOS 18.2 API for Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-for-upcoming-siri-onscreen-awareness-feature-with-new-ios-18-2-api-for-developers.2442015/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 18.2 Beta Adds Support for 21:9 Projector Aspect Ratio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/tvos-18-2-projector-aspect-ratio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-2-beta-adds-support-for-21-9-projector-aspect-ratio.2442014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/tvos-18-2-projector-aspect-ratio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the first beta of tvOS 18.2, and the update adds support for the 21:9 aspect ratio that projectors use. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/tvOS-18-Thumb-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961868" /><br/>
As noted by Sigmund Judge, the update includes a new option that lets the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> automatically detect the best aspect ratio for a television or projector. Options include 16:9, 21:9, 2.37:1, 2.39:1, 2.40:1, DCI 4K, and 32:9. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">tvOS 18.2 Developer Beta 1 introduces the ability for Apple TV to automatically detect the best aspect ratio for your television or projector. <br><br>If you have an anamorphic lens or your television&#39;s aspect ratio is not detected, users will have the ability to manually choose from… <a href="https://t.co/QjAFvKME7d">pic.twitter.com/QjAFvKME7d</a></p>&mdash; Sigmund Judge (@sigjudge) <a href="https://twitter.com/sigjudge/status/1853538516803703066?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 4, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Support for the 21:9 aspect ratio was announced as a tvOS 18 feature, but it was not in the initial tvOS 18 release. tvOS 18.2 includes an option to show or hide volume feedback from external devices like sound bars in addition to the aspect ratio change. <br/>
<br/>
We are also waiting on new Snoopy screen savers, but those do not appear to be included in tvOS 18.2. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/tvos-18-2-projector-aspect-ratio/">tvOS 18.2 Beta Adds Support for 21:9 Projector Aspect Ratio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-2-beta-adds-support-for-21-9-projector-aspect-ratio.2442014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Internal Survey About Smart Glasses Hints at Future Product Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-smart-glasses-employee-survey/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-internal-survey-about-smart-glasses-hints-at-future-product-plans.2442007/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:30:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-smart-glasses-employee-survey/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is surveying its employees about smart glasses as it continues to consider releasing its own version of Meta's Ray-Ban glasses, reports <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/meta-ray-bans-ai-training/">Bloomberg</a></em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. Apple has launched an internal study of products that are on the market, and is currently gathering feedback from Apple employees.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-777635" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/Apple-Glasses-Triad-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
In an email sent out to employees, Apple's Product Systems Quality team called for participants for "an upcoming user study with current market smart glasses." According to Gurman, it is common for Apple to use focus groups when it is deciding on whether to enter a new market. Using employees for the focus groups allows Apple to keep its plans secret, something that wouldn't be possible with recruiting the public.<br/>
<br/>
While a product is several years away, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/11/will-apple-ever-make-ar-smart-glasses/">is mulling making smart glasses</a> that are similar to the Meta Ray-Bans. Meta's glasses have a camera and integrated AI so that users can ask questions about what's around them.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could potentially design a simple set of glasses with a camera, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> integration, and built-in speakers for listening to music, plus there could be included health capabilities. The glasses would essentially be an upgraded version of the AirPods with additional capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
Smart glasses that integrate just a camera, speakers, and AI would be easy for Apple to produce, and it could be a way to boost wearable profits while work continues on augmented reality glasses. Apple has not been able to make AR glasses due to high costs and technical limitations that the company has not yet been able to overcome.<br/>
<br/>
Gathering feedback from employees about Meta's glasses and other similar devices could provide Apple with valuable information on what features customers prefer.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-smart-glasses-employee-survey/">Apple&#039;s Internal Survey About Smart Glasses Hints at Future Product Plans</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-internal-survey-about-smart-glasses-hints-at-future-product-plans.2442007/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 18.0.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-0-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-0-1.2442006/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:15:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-0-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 18.0.1, preventing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users who have upgraded to iOS 18.1 from downgrading to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/apple-releases-ios-18-1/">released iOS 18.1</a> a week ago on October 28.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Generic-iOS-18.0.1-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968305" /><br/>
It is not unusual for Apple to stop signing older versions of iOS shortly after a new version of iOS is released. When Apple stops signing an update, it can no longer be installed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; due to a server-side software verification check that happens before new software is installed, so those who have upgraded to the latest version of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; cannot downgrade to iOS 18.0.1.<br/>
<br/>
Apple prevents downgrading to older versions of iOS to encourage &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to keep their operating systems up to date with the latest security fixes.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 18.1 update added the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features, including Writing Tools, a new look for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, summaries and smart replies, and more. Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/31/ios-18-1-adoption-exceeds-ios-17-1/">recently said</a> that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users are upgrading to iOS 18.1 twice as fast as iOS 17.1 during the same timeframe last year.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/04/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-0-1/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 18.0.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-0-1.2442006/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
