<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:03:37 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;New Driver&#039; iPhone 15 Ad Highlights Automatic Check In</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/new-driver-iphone-15-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-driver-iphone-15-ad-highlights-automatic-check-in.2416910/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:18:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/new-driver-iphone-15-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today premiered an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> ad entitled "New Driver" on its YouTube channel, using the stress of being a parent of a new teenage driver to highlight the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-check-in-feature-ios-messages/">Check In feature of the Messages app</a> in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/U-7ibjo1xHc?si=iXyVOrX8o_Sp0BFL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Check In allows you to automatically notify a friend or family member when you've arrived at your destination, reassuring them of your safety. In the new ad, an anxious father watches as his daughter awkwardly backs a car out the family's driveway, hitting a skateboard and a garbage cart on her way.<br/>
<br/>
The scene then transitions to the father nervously sitting at the family's dining room table until he receives a Check In alert letting him know his daughter has arrived at school. The father breathes a sigh of relief as the tagline "Relax, it's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>" appears onscreen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/new-driver-iphone-15-ad/">&#039;New Driver&#039; iPhone 15 Ad Highlights Automatic Check In</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-driver-iphone-15-ad-highlights-automatic-check-in.2416910/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next-Gen iPad Air With 12.9-Inch Display and Redesigned Camera Unit Revealed in CAD Renders</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders.2416895/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 06:56:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>91Mobiles</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The design of Apple's upcoming 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> model has today allegedly been revealed in new CAD renders shared by <em><a href="https://www.91mobiles.com/hub/exclusive-12-9-inch-ipad-air-design-revealed-fresh-renders/">91Mobiles</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/12-9-ipad-air-render-back.jpg" alt="" width="3625" height="1801" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-931871" /><br/>
As expected, the renders show an overall appearance that is very similar to the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; design used for the fourth- and fifth-generation models, but simply scaled up to accommodate a larger display.<br/>
<br/>
The most striking difference on the device is a redesigned rear camera unit, which now protrudes from the rear in a longer pill-shape, unlike the single, round protruding cutout on the current &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;. This new design seems to be somewhat reminiscent of the rear camera unit of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> X and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/12-9-ipad-air-render-front.jpg" alt="" width="3625" height="1801" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-931872" /><br/>
On the front of the tablet, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; looks very similar to the current 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, but with noticeably thicker bezels, just like how the 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has thicker borders around the display compared to the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The device is expected to be targeted at those who want a bigger tablet than the current, 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, but have no need for the high-end features of the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; such as ProMotion or a LiDAR scanner. This is similar to Apple's approach with the 13.6- and 15.3-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, as well as the 6.1-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and 6.7-inch &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus.<br/>
<br/>
<em>91Mobiles</em> also reiterated reports that the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will feature the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip. The device is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">rumored to enter production</a> in the first quarter of 2024, so it could already be underway. It is expected to launch "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ipad-air-ipad-pro-2024-refresh/">early</a>" this year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">likely in March</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/91mobiles-com/">91Mobiles</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/">Next-Gen iPad Air With 12.9-Inch Display and Redesigned Camera Unit Revealed in CAD Renders</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders.2416895/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Vision Pro Pre-Orders, iOS 17.3 Release Date, Apple Watch Blood Oxygen Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/top-stories-vision-pro-pre-orders/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-vision-pro-pre-orders-ios-17-3-release-date-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-ban.2416891/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/top-stories-vision-pro-pre-orders/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After years of rumors and months of waiting following its unveiling, Apple's headset is finally just about here, with pre-orders going live in the U.S. ahead of an early February launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/top-stories-20jan2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931799" /><br/>
While Vision Pro was the biggest news of the week, there were also big developments in the ongoing Apple Watch blood oxygen patent dispute, with Apple being forced to start selling Series 9 and Ultra 2 models with the sensor disabled for the time being.<br/>
<br/>
We also got a release time frame for upcoming iOS 17.3 and associated updates, while Apple is now begrudgingly allowing developers to offer non-Apple Store payment options for in-app purchases, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Now Available for Pre-Order</h2><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-now-available-for-pre-order/">now accepting pre-orders for the Apple Vision Pro</a>, the company's first spatial computing device. Orders are live in the U.S. online store ahead of the February 2 launch date with the Vision Pro limited to the United States for the time being, although shipping estimates for new orders <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-delivery-dates-slip/">quickly began slipping into March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Vision-Pro-Pre-Orders-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931603" /><br/>
Alongside the start of pre-orders, Apple shared some additional details about the Vision Pro, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-tech-specs/">full tech specs</a> such as storage options up to 1TB, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/applecare-plus-for-vision-pro/">AppleCare+ pricing</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-releases-vision-pro-accessories/">available accessories</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Begins Selling Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen Feature in U.S. Amid Dispute</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models sold in the U.S. no longer have a functional Blood Oxygen app</a> starting this week, allowing Apple to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">sidestep a sales ban</a> on these models. Previously-sold watches and models sold in other countries are not affected.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-watch-series-6-blood-oxygen-monitoring-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-759072" /><br/>
The U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered an import and sales ban</a> on Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents. Masimo has accused Apple of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/18/apple-masimo-legal-battle/">stealing trade secrets and poaching employees</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As a longer-term solution, Apple is reportedly working on changes to the Blood Oxygen app's algorithm in an attempt to avoid Masimo's patented technology, but it's unclear when these changes will be ready.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releasing iOS 17.3 Next Week With These New Features</h2><br/>
In its press release <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">unveiling a new Black Unity Sport Band</a> for the Apple Watch, Apple confirmed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-releasing-ios-17-3-next-week/">iOS 17.3 will be released next week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" /><br/>
The software update includes a few new features and additions for the iPhone, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-stolen-device-protection-feature/">Stolen Device Protection</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-17-3-collaborative-playlist-emoji/">collaborative Apple Music playlists</a>, the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">connect an iPhone to select hotel room TVs via AirPlay</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-black-unity-band-2024/">Unity Bloom wallpaper</a> for the Lock Screen, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>U.S. Developers Can Now Offer Non-App Store Purchasing Option, But Apple Will Still Collect Commissions</h2><br/>
In adherence with a U.S. court ruling, Apple is now allowing App Store apps to feature a single link to a developer website that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">leads to an alternative payment option for in-app purchases</a>, but Apple plans to continue to collect a 12 to 27 percent commission on content bought in this manner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
This change comes after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">U.S. Supreme Court declined to hear both Apple's and Epic Games' appeals</a> in their trial related to App Store rules, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-wants-epic-games-legal-expenses/">Apple now wants Epic to pay its legal fees</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Kuo: Apple Vision Pro to Launch Internationally Before WWDC</h2><br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo believes the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">will launch in additional countries beyond the U.S. by WWDC 2024 in June</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Teal-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929939" /><br/>
Apple previously announced that the Vision Pro would be released in additional countries later this year, but it did not list any specific countries. Canada, the UK, and other English-speaking nations are reportedly among the places where the headset is likely to launch next.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Virtual Keyboard Blasted As 'Complete Write-Off'</h2><br/>
Vision Pro's keyboard floats in mid-air, allowing you to input text in your spatial computing environment while wearing the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1278" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930653" /><br/>
However, anyone planning to ditch their physical keyboard may want to hold onto it for a little while longer. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard-criticism/">virtual keyboard experience in visionOS 1.0 is "a complete write-off,"</a> and most people will want to use a Bluetooth keyboard instead.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jan-18-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/top-stories-vision-pro-pre-orders/">Top Stories: Vision Pro Pre-Orders, iOS 17.3 Release Date, Apple Watch Blood Oxygen Ban</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-vision-pro-pre-orders-ios-17-3-release-date-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-ban.2416891/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Two Apple Stores in U.S. Permanently Closing Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/two-apple-stores-permanently-close-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/two-apple-stores-in-u-s-permanently-closing-today.2416887/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 05:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/two-apple-stores-permanently-close-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As previously announced, Apple will be permanently closing its <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/infiniteloop/">Infinite Loop</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/royalhawaiian/">Royal Hawaiian</a> retail stores in the U.S. later today. Apple said all employees at both stores would be given the opportunity to remain with the company.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-Infinite-Loop-Store.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1612" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927735" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple Infinite Loop</em></div><br/>
Infinite Loop served as Apple's headquarters in Cupertino, California from 1993 until 2017, when Apple Park opened nearby. The store on the campus is located at street level near the entrance to the main office building, and it has sold a mix of Apple products and Apple-branded merchandise, such as shirts, reusable bottles, mugs, and notebooks.<br/>
<br/>
After the <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/appleparkvisitorcenter/">Apple Park Visitor Center</a> opened in 2017, the Infinite Loop store became redundant. The newer and larger Visitor Center carries Apple-branded merchandise, and it features a café, a rooftop terrace, and an augmented reality model of Apple Park. Apple also has a store <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/valleyfair/">at the Valley Fair shopping mall</a> to serve customers in the area.<br/>
<br/>
"After many years of serving customers at our stores in the Bay Area, we plan to close our store at Infinite Loop," said Apple, in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apples-infinite-loop-store-closing-next-month/">statement shared last month</a>. The store will permanently close its doors at 6 p.m. local time today.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's store at Infinite Loop first opened in 1993 as The Company Store, and it mostly sold Apple-branded merchandise. The location became a more traditional Apple retail store in 2015 following renovations, but it still lacked a Genius Bar.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Royal-Hawaiian.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1612" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929600" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple Royal Hawaiian</em></div><br/>
Apple Royal Hawaiian in Honolulu will follow suit and permanently close its doors at 9 p.m. local time today, after over 15 years of operations.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple continuously evaluates its retail footprint to ensure it is in the best possible position to provide exceptional customer service and support for its customers," the company said in a letter to Hawaii's Department of Labor and Industrial Relations last year. Apple has two other stores in Honolulu at <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/alamoana/">Ala Moana</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/kahala/">Kahala</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple operates 271 other retail stores across the U.S., and it opened a new store in Seoul, South Korea earlier today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/two-apple-stores-permanently-close-today/">Two Apple Stores in U.S. Permanently Closing Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/two-apple-stores-in-u-s-permanently-closing-today.2416887/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Offers to Open NFC Payment Technology to Third-Party Developers in Europe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-in-europe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-payment-technology-to-third-party-developers-in-europe.2416882/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 04:11:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-in-europe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>NFC</category>
		<category>Europe</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has proposed opening its NFC payment technology to third-party developers in Europe, allowing direct rivals to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> to operate on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
Historically, the use of Apple's NFC chip in iPhones and Apple Watches for payments has been exclusively utilized by &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, limiting the ability of banks and other financial services to offer their own contactless payment solutions on Apple's platforms. In a statement to <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-commission-seeks-feedback-apple-offer-let-rivals-access-tap-and-go-tech-2024-01-19/">Reuters</a></em>, Apple said:<blockquote>We have offered commitments to provide third-party developers in the European Economic Area with an option that will enable their users to make NFC contactless payments from within their iOS apps, separate from Apple Pay and Apple Wallet.</blockquote>The concession comes as part of Apple's efforts to address antitrust charges levied by the European Commission, which accuse the company of stifling competition by restricting third-party access to NFC capabilities on iOS devices.<br/>
<br/>
Under the proposed commitments, developers of payment, banking, and digital wallet applications in the European Economic Area (EEA) will be able to integrate their own solutions with the NFC chip on Apple devices. This change means that consumers could have the option to use NFC-enabled apps from other providers, alongside or instead of &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;. The commitment reportedly includes additional functionalities such as defaulting to preferred payment apps and integrating with Apple's security features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While the focus of these changes is within the EEA, a region broader than the European Union, the implications of the shift could have a broader impact on the mobile payments market globally. The EEA covers the overwhelming majority of the European market, and Apple's decision could set a precedent for its operations in other areas of the world in the future as antitrust scrutiny increases.<br/>
<br/>
As part of the review process, the European Commission is currently seeking feedback from rival companies and customers on Apple's proposed concessions. The final decision will consider the responses from these stakeholders. If approved, the implementation of Apple's proposed commitments will be monitored by a trustee reporting to the Commission.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nfc/">NFC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/europe/">Europe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-in-europe/">Apple Offers to Open NFC Payment Technology to Third-Party Developers in Europe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-payment-technology-to-third-party-developers-in-europe.2416882/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Belkin and Spigen Debut Apple Vision Pro Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-accessories-spigen-belkin/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/belkin-and-spigen-debut-apple-vision-pro-accessories.2416841/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 15:22:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-accessories-spigen-belkin/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With pre-orders now available for the Vision Pro, the first accessories for the upcoming device are starting to come out. So far, both Belkin and Spigen have announced Vision Pro-related products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-battery-pack-holder.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1200" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931847" /><br/>
Belkin worked with Apple to <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRDR2ZM/A/belkin-battery-holder-for-apple-vision-pro">design a Battery Holder</a> for the Vision Pro Battery Pack. Priced at &#36;50, the Belkin Battery Holder for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> is the only non-Apple accessory that Apple is selling for Vision Pro at this time.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro battery fits inside the Battery Holder, which can be worn with a cross-body strap or a cable clip that clips on to a belt or pants. Apple is selling the accessory as an add-on for those that do not have a pocket to put the battery in while wearing the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Spigen has debuted <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSpigen-Klasden-Pouch-Designed-Vision%2Fdp%2FB0CNDX83NQ">a Vision Pro pouch</a> that offers protection for the device when it's not in use. Priced at &#36;90, Spigen's case is more than &#36;100 cheaper than the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW2F3LL/A/apple-vision-pro-travel-case">&#36;200 Vision Pro Travel Case</a> that Apple is selling.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-spigen-case.jpg" alt="" width="1836" height="1033" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931850" /><br/>
Spigen's case features a nylon exterior, leather carrying strap, and an EVA shell for protection. There's a padded interior that secures the Vision Pro in place, along with a secret <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> compartment for tracking the Vision Pro. It also appears to have space for the Vision Pro battery pack, cable, and ZEISS lens inserts. The case is set to deliver between February 21 and 23, so it won't be available right at launch day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/speck-vision-pro-accessories.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931849" /><br/>
Other accessory makers like Speck <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/apple-vision-pro">have started teasing</a> Vision Pro products ranging from carrying cases to battery holders, so it shouldn't be long before we see a whole range of Vision Pro accessory options.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-accessories-spigen-belkin/">Belkin and Spigen Debut Apple Vision Pro Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/belkin-and-spigen-debut-apple-vision-pro-accessories.2416841/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are All the Apps Pre-Installed on the Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-pre-installed-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-apps-pre-installed-on-the-apple-vision-pro.2416836/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 14:43:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-pre-installed-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Vision Pro comes with a number of Apple apps that are also available on the iPhone and the iPad. We've seen some of the apps over the past few months in tidbits of information that Apple has provided, but the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-vision-pro/specs/">Vision Pro technical specifications</a> that went live today alongside pre-orders list every app that the device comes with.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/visionos-home-screen-mt-hood.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900011" /><br/>
<br/>
Pre-installed apps optimized for Vision Pro:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>App Store</li><br/>
 	<li>Encounter Dinosaurs</li><br/>
 	<li>Files</li><br/>
 	<li>Freeform</li><br/>
 	<li>Keynote</li><br/>
 	<li>Mail</li><br/>
 	<li>Messages</li><br/>
 	<li>Mindfulness</li><br/>
 	<li>Music</li><br/>
 	<li>Notes</li><br/>
 	<li>Photos</li><br/>
 	<li>Safari</li><br/>
 	<li>Settings</li><br/>
 	<li>Tips</li><br/>
 	<li>TV</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Pre-installed apps not optimized for Vision Pro:<br/>
<br/>
 	<ul><li>Books</li><br/>
 	<li>Calendar</li><br/>
 	<li>Home</li><br/>
 	<li>Maps</li><br/>
 	<li>News</li><br/>
 	<li>Podcasts</li><br/>
 	<li>Reminders</li><br/>
 	<li>Shortcuts</li><br/>
 	<li>Stocks</li><br/>
 	<li>Voice Memos</li></ul><br/>
</ul><br/>
Curiously, while there is a Keynote app that's pre-installed, Apple does not list the other iWork apps like Pages and Numbers. Find My is not on Apple's list, nor are the Health, Clock, Contacts, and Weather apps. FaceTime is not on the list, but the fine print confirms that there is indeed a FaceTime app and also a Capture app for taking video and photos on the device.<br/>
<br/>
There may be some Apple apps that are not pre-installed but able to be downloaded from the App Store after launch, and there will be a number of third-party apps designed for the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
We'll be sharing a list of Vision Pro apps closer to when the headset debuts, and it is also worth noting that many iOS apps will run on the device automatically unless developers opt out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-pre-installed-apps/">Here Are All the Apps Pre-Installed on the Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-apps-pre-installed-on-the-apple-vision-pro.2416836/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Vision Pro Content Can Be Mirrored to Mac, iPhone, iPad, and Apple TV Using AirPlay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-airplay-content/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-content-can-be-mirrored-to-mac-iphone-ipad-and-apple-tv-using-airplay.2416831/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 13:54:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-airplay-content/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Content that is displayed on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> display can be mirrored to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, or AirPlay-compatible smart TV using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>, Apple confirmed today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-macbook.jpg" alt="" width="3022" height="1698" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930147" /><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-vision-pro/specs/">technical specifications page</a> for the Vision Pro says that what's on your Vision Pro can be mirrored to any AirPlay-enabled device at up to 720p, which will allow you to show people what you're seeing on your headset.<br/>
<br/>
iPhones and iPads were updated with the ability to receive content from the Vision Pro in iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2, and to use the feature, the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; Receiver toggle must be turned on under General > &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; & Handoff.<br/>
<br/>
While the Vision Pro's display can be mirrored to an &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; device, the headset can also serve as a display for a Mac. With the Mac Virtual Display feature, &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; 2 connects the Vision Pro wirelessly to a Mac, and a virtual representation of the Mac's display can be placed anywhere in space. Used this way, the Vision Pro essentially serves as an enormous, portable 4K display, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Note:</b> Apple's specifications page previously said that content could be AirPlayed at 1080p, but later updated it to say 720p.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-airplay-content/">Vision Pro Content Can Be Mirrored to Mac, iPhone, iPad, and Apple TV Using AirPlay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-content-can-be-mirrored-to-mac-iphone-ipad-and-apple-tv-using-airplay.2416831/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Re-Adds Access to iTunes TV Show and Movie Wishlists in iOS 17.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/itunes-movies-tv-show-wishlists-ios-17-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-re-adds-access-to-itunes-tv-show-and-movie-wishlists-in-ios-17-3.2416824/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 12:26:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/itunes-movies-tv-show-wishlists-ios-17-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today made a tweak to the iTunes Store app in iOS 17.3, giving users access to their TV show and movie wishlists. Apple with iOS 17.2, iPadOS 17.2, and tvOS 17.2 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/apple-removes-tv-show-movie-wishlists/">killed wishlists</a> without warning when it moved the option to purchase TV shows and movies from the iTunes Store app to the TV app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/itunes-movies-wishlist-ios-17-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931842" /><br/>
Wishlist access was actually re-added to tvOS 17.2 just a few days after the update went live, but there has been no way to access a wishlist on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> updated to iOS 17.2 or iPadOS 17.2.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple's over-the-air update, iPhones and iPads running the iOS 17.3 beta will now have a "Go to Your Wish List" button under the Movie and TV Show sections, which provides access to everything that's been added to the list in the past. The list was first noticed by <a href="https://twitter.com/il_fedetrevi/status/1748436509655511468">Twitter user Federico</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It may be a good idea to write down the TV shows and movies that are in the list because it might not be around forever. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app that Apple has transitioned to does not have a wishlist function and instead adds content to the "Up Next" interface.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 are set to be released to the public next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/itunes-movies-tv-show-wishlists-ios-17-3/">Apple Re-Adds Access to iTunes TV Show and Movie Wishlists in iOS 17.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-re-adds-access-to-itunes-tv-show-and-movie-wishlists-in-ios-17-3.2416824/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Details Using Vision Pro With Certain Medical Conditions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-medical-conditions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-details-using-vision-pro-with-certain-medical-conditions.2416823/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 11:55:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-medical-conditions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213935">support document</a> published online today, Apple detailed using its Vision Pro headset with certain medical conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
Apple says customers with pre-existing medical conditions should consult with a healthcare provider before using the Vision Pro, as using the headset could "aggravate symptoms or increase the risk of injury or discomfort."<br/>
<br/>
Apple says these medical conditions include:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Heart conditions</li><br/>
<li>Migraines or chronic headaches</li><br/>
<li>Dizziness or vertigo</li> <br/>
<li>Eye or vision conditions, such as binocular vision conditions</li><br/>
<li>Psychological conditions</li><br/>
<li>Inner ear conditions</li><br/>
<li>History of dry eyes, itchiness, or swelling of the eyelids </li><br/>
<li>Skin allergies or sensitivities</li><br/>
<li>Seizures</li><br/>
<li>Balance or gait conditions</li></ul>Apple adds that pregnant individuals should exercise additional caution when using the Vision Pro due to an increased risk of nausea or loss of balance.<br/>
<br/>
"If your medical provider confirmed that it's safe for you to use Apple Vision Pro, use the device seated and start with a less immersive experience," says Apple. "Use the device over short increments of time and take frequent breaks."<br/>
<br/>
Apple also warns that the Vision Pro and its battery pack could interfere with nearby electronics, including cardiac pacemakers, hearing aids, and defibrillators.<br/>
<br/>
"If you have a pacemaker or other implanted medical device, consult a medical provider or the manufacturer of your medical device before using Apple Vision Pro," says Apple. The headset and battery should be kept at a safe distance from these medical devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says customers should stop using the Vision Pro if they experience symptoms related to a medical condition or skin reactions.<br/>
<br/>
For more details, read <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213935">Apple's support document</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The information above is presented for reference only, and it does not substitute for medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-medical-conditions/">Apple Details Using Vision Pro With Certain Medical Conditions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-details-using-vision-pro-with-certain-medical-conditions.2416823/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Repairs Cost Up to &#36;2,400 Without AppleCare+</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-repair-cost/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-repairs-cost-up-to-2-400-without-applecare.2416819/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 11:09:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-repair-cost/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Vision Pro features an aluminum frame that houses a single piece of laminated glass for the front of the device, and as we've learned from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, glass is quite breakable. If the Vision Pro's glass cracks or the device is damaged in some other way, you could be facing an expensive repair without <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/vision-pro-headset-1.jpg" alt="" width="2698" height="1518" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898460" /><br/>
On <a href="https://support.apple.com/apple-vision-pro/repair">Apple's Vision Pro service page</a>, repair fees are listed. It will cost &#36;799 to fix cracked cover glass, but if you need any other component repaired, the cost shoots up to &#36;2,399. That's just &#36;1,100 less than the full cost of the Vision Pro to begin with.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/applecare-plus-for-vision-pro/">is priced at &#36;499</a> for two years of coverage, or customers can choose to pay &#36;24.99 per month for &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+, with the coverage lasting until payments are canceled, so it's not cheap.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ includes unlimited repairs for accidental damage, Apple-certified service and support, Express Replacement Service, and 24/7 priority access to "Apple experts." It is worth noting that there is a &#36;299 deductible for any &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ repair to the device itself (including a cracked display), and a &#36;29 service fee for any accessories such as the Light Seal that are in need of repair.<br/>
<br/>
Given the price of the Vision Pro headset, &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ might be worth purchasing. As repairs are expensive, it will be worth finding some kind of protective case to use at a minimum to keep it safe if you plan to bring it from one location to another. Apple sells a case for &#36;200, but there should soon be multiple third-party options available.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-repair-cost/">Apple Vision Pro Repairs Cost Up to &#36;2,400 Without AppleCare+</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-repairs-cost-up-to-2-400-without-applecare.2416819/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Apple Watch Discounts Hit Series 9, SE, and Ultra 2, Alongside AirPods and MacBook Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-19-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-apple-watch-discounts-hit-series-9-se-and-ultra-2-alongside-airpods-and-macbook-sales.2416812/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 10:10:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-19-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals include all-time low prices on AirPods Pro, MacBook Pro, and Apple Watch. You'll also find an ongoing sale at Samsung with big discounts on popular monitors like the ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and the Smart Monitor M8, as well as a few pre-order offers on the new Samsung Galaxy S24 Smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0005.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847995" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931786" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Samsung monitors and the new Galaxy S24 smartphones</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clsi2GYvJh3">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/samsung-introduces-new-sale-monitors/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;400 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;1,199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq2b1RAXhG"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;479.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsi2GYvJh3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">PRE-ORDER OFFERS</div>Galaxy S24 Smartphones</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Over at Samsung, you can find a few solid discounts on computer monitors, including the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor (&#36;400 off) and the 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 (&#36;170 off).<br/>
<br/>
For the new smartphones, customers can get up to &#36;750 off the <a href="https://howl.me/clsi09i1L1r">S24 Ultra</a> with a trade-in, along with an exclusive &#36;50 Samsung credit, a free storage upgrade (doubling storage at no cost), and a &#36;100 eCertificate, plus students can get a 15 percent discount.<br/>
<br/>
For the <a href="https://howl.me/clsi1u2tV5a">S24+</a>, up to a &#36;650 trade-in credit is available with a &#36;50 Samsung credit, storage upgrade, &#36;75 eCertificate, and a 7.5 percent student discount. For the <a href="https://howl.me/clsi1QchmkU">S24</a>, up to a &#36;550 trade-in credit is available, along with a &#36;50 Samsung credit, a storage upgrade, a &#36;25 eCertificate, and a five percent discount for students.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/airpods-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931789" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;60 off AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-airpods-pro-189/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple Vision Pro pre-orders went live today, and if you've got your order in and want to add lossless audio to the experience, be sure to pick up a pair of AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C. Amazon has the earbuds for &#36;189.00 right now, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-watch-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931788" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Apple Watch Series 9, SE, and Ultra 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clsfVkocNDP">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-buys-weekend-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsfUswIxJu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsfVkocNDP"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsfWaABiz9"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy is hosting a big sale on Apple Watch models this weekend, with the Apple Watch Series 9, SE, and Ultra 2 all available at a discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBooks</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/macbook-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931787" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;250 off MacBook Air and MacBook Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clsfKCmsThd">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-buys-weekend-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsfG4xs26m"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsfKCmsThd"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to Apple Watches, Best Buy's sale has big savings on MacBook Air and MacBook Pro notebooks. Some of these require you to have a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, which start at &#36;49.99/year.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfKCmsThd">256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfNvLGfyw">512GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfG4xs26m">512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfIhVcbIg">1TB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfMSroPVW">1TB M2 15-inch MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,649.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-1-19-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Apple Watch Discounts Hit Series 9, SE, and Ultra 2, Alongside AirPods and MacBook Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-apple-watch-discounts-hit-series-9-se-and-ultra-2-alongside-airpods-and-macbook-sales.2416812/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an 11-Inch iPad Pro, Dock and Stand From Plugable</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-ipad-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-11-inch-ipad-pro-dock-and-stand-from-plugable.2416807/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 10:01:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-ipad-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://plugable.com">Plugable</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an 11-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and two Plugable accessories to go along with it: the TBT4-UD5 Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station, and the magnetic AMS-STAND-11.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/plugable-dock-1.jpg" alt="" width="1333" height="750" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931772" /><br/>
<a href="https://plugable.com">Plugable</a> makes a range of docks, hubs, cables, stands, and other accessories for Apple's Mac and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup, and the TBT4-UD5 and AMS-STAND-11 are two of its newest devices.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNTTVVN6">Priced at &#36;180</a> with a limited-time &#36;20 discount, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNTTVVN6">TBT4-UD5 Thunderbolt 4 Dock</a> includes all of the ports that you might need for a Mac. It is equipped with dual-display HDMI support at 4K 60Hz (or a single 8K display), a downstream Thunderbolt 4 port, a 10Gb/s USB-C port, two 10Gb/s USB-A ports, two 5Gb/s USB-A ports, SD and microSD card readers, a gigabit ethernet port, and a 3.5mm headphone jack.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/plugable-dock-3.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="1302" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931773" /><br/>
The dock supports up to 100W power delivery, so it is able to provide power to even the 16-inch MacBook Pro. While it can drive dual 4K displays at 60Hz through the Thunderbolt 4 port, this requires an M-series Pro or Max chip. 15W of power is available for charging peripheral devices such as an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/plugable-dock-2.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931775" /><br/>
<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNTVH7CD">Plugable's AMS-STAND11 Magnetic iPad Stand</a> is compatible with the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and the 10.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>. It is made from an aluminum alloy that matches well with the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and it includes strong N52 magnets and anti-slip silicone padding to keep the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in place.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/magnetic-ipad-stand-1.jpg" alt="" width="1774" height="998" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931776" /><br/>
The stand has a 180-degree adjustable hinged arm that supports multiple viewing angles, along with a 360-degree rotatable panel for swapping between landscape and portrait orientations. With the adjustable arm, the stand can be folded down so far that it turns into a suitable surface for drawing and sketching.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/magnetic-ipad-stand-2.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="1465" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931777" /><br/>
When not in use, the stand is able to fold flat, which makes it easy to transport and take to school or work. Plugable is selling the stand for &#36;80, but there is a &#36;5 coupon available to celebrate the stand's launch. For those with the larger &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; model, there's <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNTW1RTW">also a 12.9-inch version</a>.<br/>
<br/>
We have an 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, Thunderbolt 4 dock, and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; stand for one lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/8Peb0/plugable-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Plugable Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (January 19) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on January 26. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after January 26 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-ipad-pro/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an 11-Inch iPad Pro, Dock and Stand From Plugable</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-11-inch-ipad-pro-dock-and-stand-from-plugable.2416807/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple Vision Pro Pre-Orders, CES 2024, and Samsung&#039;s New AI Phones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-pre-orders/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-pre-orders-ces-2024-and-samsungs-new-ai-phones.2416806/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:50:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-pre-orders/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/apple-vision-pro-pre-orders-ces-2024-samsungs-new-ai-phones/id1602394741?i=1000642237817">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a>, Samsung's S24 lineup, and the latest news surrounding Apple's Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yQhqnF3YzuI?si=IDQmNYEB_y1v2eNH" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We take a look at some of the latest advancements in TV technology, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-day-2-recap/">transparent models from LG</a>, and AI assistants like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-rabbit-r1/">Rabbit R1</a>. We also look at some of the tentpole features of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/samsung-launches-galaxy-s24-lineup/">Samsung's new Galaxy S24 lineup</a>, such as a 50-megapixel telephoto camera with 5x optical zoom and a wave of AI tools designed for enhancing photography and videography, editing text, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Following Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">announcement</a> of the impending launch of the Vision Pro headset on February 2, we discuss the device's potential to redefine the AR/VR space, especially in the context of productivity workflows. We also address potential concerns regarding comfort and design, storage configurations, and our sense of anticipation about the device's launch.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now <strong>exclusively</strong> on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/05/the-macrumors-show-everything-to-expect-2024/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our look forward at all of Apple's biggest rumored announcements for 2024. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-pre-orders/">The MacRumors Show: Apple Vision Pro Pre-Orders, CES 2024, and Samsung&#039;s New AI Phones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-pre-orders-ces-2024-and-samsungs-new-ai-phones.2416806/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Provides Behind-the-Scenes Look at How Vision Pro is Made</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-how-its-made-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-provides-behind-the-scenes-look-at-how-vision-pro-is-made.2416795/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 07:47:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-how-its-made-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided a behind-the-scenes look at how its upcoming Vision Pro headset is manufactured <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=luFGI13Mv8o">in a video</a> uploaded to its YouTube channel. The video was also <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook/status/1748337010191077462">shared by Apple CEO Tim Cook</a> on social media platform X.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/luFGI13Mv8o?si=LEYhXRopFFLlK1tE" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
"A peek behind the scenes to see how we make Apple Vision Pro, our first spatial computer," said Apple, in the video's description on YouTube.<br/>
<br/>
Apple began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-now-available-for-pre-order/">accepting pre-orders</a> for the Vision Pro in the U.S. today, with pricing starting at &#36;3,499. The headset launches February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-how-its-made-video/">Apple Provides Behind-the-Scenes Look at How Vision Pro is Made</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-provides-behind-the-scenes-look-at-how-vision-pro-is-made.2416795/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s Weekend Sale Introduces Steep Discounts on Apple Watches, AirPods, MacBooks, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-buys-weekend-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-weekend-sale-introduces-steep-discounts-on-apple-watches-airpods-macbooks-and-more.2416792/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 07:43:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-buys-weekend-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy has opened up a <a href="https://howl.me/clsf6sn6DIF">new 3-day weekend sale</a> today, offering sitewide discounts on laptops, TVs, video games, headphones, tablets, sound bars, and much more. In terms of <a href="https://howl.me/clsf2YBSlnu">Apple products</a>, this sale includes discounts on MacBooks, Apple Watches, AirPods, and iPads.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924133" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Some of these deals require a <a href="https://howl.me/clsfFR2NQAO">My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total membership</a>, which start at &#36;49.99/year. In addition to exclusive access to select discounts, you'll get free 2-day shipping, an extended 60-day return window, and more.<br/>
<br/>
For MacBooks, the highlight is Apple's 512GB 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/clsfG4xs26m"><strong>&#36;1,399.00</strong></a> for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, down from &#36;1,599.00. Best Buy also has the 1TB 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clsfIhVcbIg"><strong>&#36;1,599.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,799.00. Both of these are matches for the all-time low price on each computer.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clsf2YBSlnu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Best Buy Apple Discounts</div></a></div><h2>Apple Watches</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-watch-9-january.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931749" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfUswIxJu">Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS)</a> - &#36;199.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfYcJQiOO">Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS)</a> - &#36;229.00, down from &#36;279.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfVkocNDP">Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS)</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfXltxWin">Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfWaABiz9">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> - &#36;749.00, down from &#36;799.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>AirPods/Beats</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/airpods-january.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931748" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clsf1ertyOD">AirPods 2</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsf17QH30s">Beats Fit Pro</a> - &#36;159.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsf0Jjf7KS">AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C)</a> - &#36;189.99, down from &#36;249.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>MacBooks</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/macbook-pro-january.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931746" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfKCmsThd">256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfNvLGfyw">512GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfG4xs26m">512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfIhVcbIg">1TB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfMSroPVW">1TB M2 15-inch MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,649.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>iPads</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ipad-january.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931747" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfQkI36NK">64GB Wi-Fi 10th Gen iPad</a> - &#36;349.00, down from &#36;449.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfQUFWxvF">256GB Wi-Fi 10th Gen iPad</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfRtUFoXO">64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clsfR0jDk48">256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air</a> - &#36;649.99, down from &#36;749.99</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/best-buys-weekend-sale/">Best Buy&#039;s Weekend Sale Introduces Steep Discounts on Apple Watches, AirPods, MacBooks, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-weekend-sale-introduces-steep-discounts-on-apple-watches-airpods-macbooks-and-more.2416792/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shows What&#039;s in Vision Pro Box, Including Special Polishing Cloth</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-whats-in-box-visualized/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shows-whats-in-vision-pro-box-including-special-polishing-cloth.2416791/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 07:30:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-whats-in-box-visualized/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided a closer look at what comes in the box with the Vision Pro, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-now-available-for-pre-order/">now available to pre-order</a> in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Cloth-and-Cover-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2144" height="1206" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931739" /><br/>
Two notable accessories include a cover for the Vision Pro's front glass, and a polishing cloth with Vision Pro branding. Other accessories are more familiar by now, including the Solo Knit Band, Dual Loop Band, external battery pack, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside the Vision Pro, the following accessories are included in the box:<ul><li>Light Seal</li><br/>
<li>Light Seal Cushion (Two Sizes)</li><br/>
<li>Solo Knit Band</li><br/>
<li>Dual Loop Band</li><br/>
<li>Front Cover</li><br/>
<li>Battery Pack</li><br/>
<li>Polishing Cloth (Vision Pro Branding)</li><br/>
<li>30W USB-C Power Adapter</li><br/>
<li>USB‑C Charging Cable</li></ul>For more details about these accessories, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-everything-included-in-box/">previous coverage of what's in the box</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-whats-in-box-visualized/">Apple Shows What&#039;s in Vision Pro Box, Including Special Polishing Cloth</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shows-whats-in-vision-pro-box-including-special-polishing-cloth.2416791/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Weighs Almost as Much as a 12.9-Inch iPad Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-weighs-almost-as-much-as-ipad-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-weighs-almost-as-much-as-a-12-9-inch-ipad-pro.2416790/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 07:24:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-weighs-almost-as-much-as-ipad-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset can weigh almost 23 ounces (650 grams), depending on configuration, the company today confirmed.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tG9I7J4zfEU" title="Apple Vision Pro Available Now &amp; Full Walkthrough!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Apple says that the Vision Pro specifically weighs between 21.2 and 22.9 ounces (600 and 650 grams) depending on which Light Seal and head band is used on the device. The separate battery weighs 12.5 ounces (353 grams). For reference, this means that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, excluding the battery, weighs almost as much as a 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, which comes in at 24 ounces (682 grams).<br/>
<br/>
The weight of Apple's headset was unknown until today, but it was widely rumored to be heavy compared to competing devices. This is not necessarily the case, since while the Meta Quest 3 weighs 18.2 ounces (516 grams), the higher-end Meta Quest Pro weighs 25.5 ounces (722 grams) – substantially more than the Vision Pro. However, the Meta Quest Pro has a weighted battery pack at the back of the headset's headband to make it much less front-heavy and ostensibly improve comfort.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders of the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-now-available-for-pre-order/">opened earlier today</a> and the device launches in the United States on Friday, February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-weighs-almost-as-much-as-ipad-pro/">Apple Vision Pro Weighs Almost as Much as a 12.9-Inch iPad Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-weighs-almost-as-much-as-a-12-9-inch-ipad-pro.2416790/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Free Engraving Available With Apple Vision Pro ZEISS Lens Inserts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/free-engraving-available-with-vision-pro-inserts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/free-engraving-available-with-apple-vision-pro-zeiss-lens-inserts.2416786/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 06:47:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/free-engraving-available-with-vision-pro-inserts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99/">optional ZEISS lens inserts</a> designed for Apple's Vision Pro headset can be engraved at no additional cost. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-lens-inserts.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-931717" /><br/>
Custom wording of the customer's choice can be engraved into the black plastic sides of the optional ZEISS lens inserts designed for those who normally wear glasses or contact lenses. The option is probably intended to help multiple users identify which lens inserts belong to them, rather than be a novel way to personalize the device, since they are very small and there is no other engraving option for the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Apple offers two versions of the ZEISS Optical Inserts at different price points. "ZEISS Optical Inserts — Readers" are available for &#36;99, while "ZEISS Optical Inserts — Prescription" are available for &#36;149. The inserts attach to the Vision Pro lenses magnetically, allowing for precise viewing and eye tracking. Purchase requires a valid prescription from an optician.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders of the Vision Pro started earlier today and the device goes on sale in the United States on Friday, February 2.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/free-engraving-available-with-vision-pro-inserts/">Free Engraving Available With Apple Vision Pro ZEISS Lens Inserts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/free-engraving-available-with-apple-vision-pro-zeiss-lens-inserts.2416786/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro App Store, Apple Music, and TV App Require US Apple ID</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-apple-id-set-to-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-app-store-apple-music-and-tv-app-require-us-apple-id.2416783/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 06:01:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-apple-id-set-to-us/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For international customers who are thinking of purchasing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> in the United States and using it in their own country, Apple has cautioned that they will be faced with several limitations when attempting to use the device.  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Teal-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929682" /><br/>
According to a FAQ on Apple's Vision Pro <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-vision/apple-vision-pro">pre-order page</a> on its online store, the experience will differ from a U.S.-based customer in the following ways:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>&zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; only supports English (U.S.) for language and typing and English for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and Dictation.</li><br/>
    <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> requires an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> with region set to the U.S.</li><br/>
    <li>Purchases on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and TV app require an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; with region set to the U.S.</li><br/>
    <li>For customers with vision correction needs, ZEISS will only accept vision prescriptions written by U.S. eye care professionals, and will only ship to U.S. locations.</li><br/>
    <li>Customers may not be able to access certain apps, features, or content due to licensing or other restrictions in those countries or regions.</li><br/>
    <li>Apple Support is only available in the U.S.</li><br/>
</ul>Apple says that the spatial computing headset is designed for customers in the U.S. to use at home, at work, and while traveling. "We look forward to bringing &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; to more countries later this year," notes the company. <br/>
<br/>
While orders are limited to the United States for the time being, Apple is likely to launch the Vision Pro headset <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">outside the U.S. before WWDC 2024 in June</a>, with Canada and the United Kingdom tipped as the first two other countries in which the headset will be available.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro will launch on Friday, February 2, which is when pre-orders will be delivered to U.S. customers.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-apple-id-set-to-us/">Apple Vision Pro App Store, Apple Music, and TV App Require US Apple ID</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-app-store-apple-music-and-tv-app-require-us-apple-id.2416783/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
