<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:03:18 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Announces Plans to Enter Major New Product Category, Likely Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-announces-plans-to-enter-major-new-product-category-likely-headphones.2411202/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:59:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos</a> today <a href="https://investors.sonos.com/news-and-events/investor-news/latest-news/2023/Sonos-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Fiscal-2023-Results/default.aspx">announced plans</a> to expand into a new "multi-billion dollar" product category in 2024, which is widely believed to be headphones. Sonos CEO Patrick Spence declined to give specific details on the company's plans, but he said that the new product will "complement" current Sonos devices and will "delight customers and drive immediate revenue."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/airpods-max-spring-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-842859" /><br/>
Spence said that Sonos believes it will generate more than &#36;100 million from new products in 2024, and the new product will account for a "large portion" of this revenue in the second half of the year.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors for years now that Sonos intends to enter the headphone market with a pair of wireless headphones that could be similar in design to over-ear headphones like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>. Sonos has never confirmed its work on headphones, but a leaked internal memo that was obtained by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-16/sonos-plans-to-cut-jobs-as-it-prepares-push-into-headphones"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> earlier today confirmed that the company does indeed have a headphone division.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos develops</a> wireless speakers, soundbars, and other home theater devices, so headphones seem to be a logical next step for the company. As Sonos manufactures higher-end devices, the first headphones could perhaps be designed to compete with over-ear headphones from companies like Bose, Sony, Sennheiser, Shure, and Bowers &amp; Wilkins, but Sonos could also target the AirPods market.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-24/sonos-is-said-to-plan-headphones-in-move-outside-the-home">in 2019</a> said that Sonos was targeting a &#36;300 price point and was focusing on features like audio quality and multi-service interoperability, but it has been several years since new details emerged.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos speakers already compete with Apple's speakers, so a set of heaadphones that serve as an alternative to &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; and Beats would not be a surprise. At this point, little is known about Sonos' plans for the headphones, and there is no specific launch date that has been shared.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/">Sonos Announces Plans to Enter Major New Product Category, Likely Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-announces-plans-to-enter-major-new-product-category-likely-headphones.2411202/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Series 9 Model at All-Time Low Prices for Black Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-series-9-model-at-all-time-low-prices-for-black-friday.2411189/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:53:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last week, Amazon introduced the first major discounts on the Apple Watch Series 9. Today, these deals have returned and offer some of the best Black Friday deals around with &#36;50 off nearly every Series 9 device, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a> for the 41mm GPS model, down from &#36;399.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-series-9-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921790" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple launched the Series 9 models back in September, and early on the steepest discounts were about &#36;10-15. Amazon's Black Friday deals are blowing those early markdowns out of the water, and they include both GPS and cellular models. This time around, the 41mm GPS device is available in two Aluminum models, as well as in both S/M and M/L fits.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the 45mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;379.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;429.00. It's available in four Aluminum color options, both S/M and M/L fits, and this is another record low price on the smartwatch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Cellular Apple Watch Series 9 deals are just as abundant on Amazon right now. You can get the 41mm Cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.00</strong></a> and the 45mm Cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;479.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;50 discounts and all-time low prices. You'll find all five Aluminum options on sale at these prices, as well as multiple size options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;479.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anyone shopping for Apple Watch deals should head to our dedicated guide for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-apple-watch-deals/">Best Early Black Friday Apple Watch Deals</a>. Right now, this also includes a record low price on the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE (2022), priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3GRK2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;279.00.<br/>
<br/>
If you're starting your holiday shopping this week, we've got you covered with even more guides for the best early Black Friday deals for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">HomePod</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">iPad</a>. We've also been keeping an eye on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">best overall Apple deals</a> in the lead-up to November 24. All of these guides will be updated as the month continues, so be sure to bookmark and revisit to stay up-to-date on the best prices for the products you have an eye on.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, we're tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories, so it's another good resource for your online holiday shopping.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices/">Amazon Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Series 9 Model at All-Time Low Prices for Black Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-series-9-model-at-all-time-low-prices-for-black-friday.2411189/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s In-House 5G Modem Work Faces Further Delays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-in-house-5g-modem-delays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-in-house-5g-modem-work-faces-further-delays.2411187/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:24:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-in-house-5g-modem-delays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing to run into troubles in its attempt to develop a 5G modem to replace Qualcomm's 5G modems in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and other products, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-16/apple-project-to-replace-modems-made-by-qualcomm-falls-further-behind-to-2026">reports <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/5G-Modem-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886940" /><br/>
Apple in 2019 acquired the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/25/apple-intel-acquisition/">majority of Intel's smartphone business</a> and started in on a serious effort to develop its own modem hardware, but the project has suffered multiple setbacks. Apple is still "years away" from creating a chip that is able to perform as well as or better than chips from rival Qualcomm.<br/>
<br/>
The Cupertino company initially wanted to have an in-house modem chip ready to go by 2024, a goal that could not be met, and now Gurman says that Apple is also going to miss an extended spring 2025 launch timeline. As of now, the modem chip launch has been postponed until the end of 2025 or early 2026, and Apple is still planning to introduce the technology in a version of the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Development on a modem chip is said to be in the early stages, and it "may lag behind the competition by years." One version in development does not support faster mmWave technology, and Apple has also run into issues with the Intel code that it has been working with. Rewrites have been required, and adding new features has been causing existing features to break, plus Apple has to be careful not to infringe on Qualcomm patents while developing the chip.<br/>
<br/>
"Why we thought we could take a failed project from Intel and somehow succeed is a mystery," an Apple employee allegedly told Gurman. Apple's hardware technologies group is also said to be "stretched thin" across numerous projects, leading to difficulty resolving bugs. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's dissatisfaction with Qualcomm surfaced in 2017, which is when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/16/apple-qualcomm-settlement/">Apple sued Qualcomm</a> for unfairly collecting royalties for technologies it had nothing to do with. Apple was of the opinion that Qualcomm was charging too much for its modem chip technology.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 lineup, Apple was able to opt out of using Qualcomm chips, instead equipping iPhones with chips from Intel, but the relationship between Intel and Apple was short lived. After the launch of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, Apple wanted to continue to use Intel chips for its first 5G iPhones, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models, but Intel could not manufacture 5G chips that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/03/intel-delays-5g-iphone-2020/">were up to Apple's standards</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was instead forced to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/16/apple-qualcomm-settlement/">settle its legal dispute</a> with Qualcomm, and all litigation was dropped. The two companies signed a new contract, which was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/">extended in September 2023</a>. The latest deal with Qualcomm covers smartphone launches in 2024, 2025, and 2026, and will last through Apple's delayed modem chip development.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple's in-house modem chip has been delayed, the company is continuing development because it is eager to end its expensive deal with Qualcomm. Apple's first modem chip will be a standalone chip, but the company hopes to eventually develop a system-on-a-chip that will also cut out suppliers like Broadcom and give it more control over component development.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-in-house-5g-modem-delays/">Apple&#039;s In-House 5G Modem Work Faces Further Delays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-in-house-5g-modem-work-faces-further-delays.2411187/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Digital Car Key and Ultra Wideband Groups Team Up for Future Apple Car Keys Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/digital-car-key-ultra-wideband-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/digital-car-key-and-ultra-wideband-groups-team-up-for-future-apple-car-keys-improvements.2411182/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:37:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/digital-car-key-ultra-wideband-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The way vehicles take advantage of new connectivity standards could be improving in the near future, leading to updates on how smartphones like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> control cars.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/bmw-car-key-photo.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-778616" /><br/>
This month, the Car Connectivity Consortium (CCC) and the FiRa Consortium that oversees the development of the Ultra-wideband (UWB) standard, <a href="https://carconnectivity.org/car-connectivity-consortium-and-fira-consortium-partner-on-uwb-technology-used-in-the-ccc-digital-key/">announced a partnership</a> for the future development of UWB features used for the CCC Digital Key function.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is a member of both the CCC and FiRa. The CCC's Digital Key specification has been adopted by Apple for its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/carkey/">Car Keys</a> feature that allows the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and the Apple Watch to unlock compatible vehicles over NFC. Select BMW, Kia, Hyundai, Mercedes, and Genesis vehicles <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/carplay/available-models/">work with Car Keys</a>, but Apple undoubtedly wants to expand adoption.<br/>
<br/>
The CCC and FiRa Consortiums will work together to "develop and maintain" the UWB technology specifications used for the Digital Key standard that serves as the basis for &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; on Apple devices. Apple engineer Jinjing Jiang will oversee the joint effort.<br/>
<br/>
The partnership is expected to encourage broader adoption of UWB technology use in vehicles. As of now, UWB is used for the Digital Key standard to relay how close a user is to their vehicle, allowing a smartphone or wearable to be used for vehicle access or to start the car when at the appropriate range.<br/>
<br/>
Apple uses UWB for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple Watch, and AirTag. UWB enables more precise location awareness and it powers features like Precision Finding for the AirTag.<br/>
<br/>
Along with Apple, CCC members include most vehicle manufacturers like Ford, BMW, GM, Honda, Volkswagen, Mercedes-Benz, and more, while FiRa members include Apple, Google, Qualcomm, Cisco, Samsung, NXP, and more.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/digital-car-key-ultra-wideband-improvements/">Digital Car Key and Ultra Wideband Groups Team Up for Future Apple Car Keys Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/digital-car-key-and-ultra-wideband-groups-team-up-for-future-apple-car-keys-improvements.2411182/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Adopt RCS Messaging Standard for Better Interoperability With Android Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard-for-better-interoperability-with-android-devices.2411170/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:08:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>RCS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After years of persuading from Google, Apple plans to adopt the Rich Communication Services (RCS) standard. An Apple spokesperson told <em><a href="https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/breaking-apple-will-support-rcs-in-2024">TechRadar</a></em> and <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/16/apple-rcs-coming-to-iphone/">9to5Mac</a></em> that support for RCS will be coming next year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Mz_44PZ-0Js" title="No More Green Bubbles? Apple Officially Announces RCS Support!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<blockquote>Later next year, we will be adding support for RCS Universal Profile, the standard as currently published by the GSM Association. We believe the RCS Universal Profile will offer a better interoperability experience when compared to SMS or MMS. This will work alongside iMessage, which will continue to be the best and most secure messaging experience for Apple users.</blockquote><br/>
According to Apple, RCS will "work alongside iMessage" and will improve communication between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Android users. iMessage will continue to be the default for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; communication, with RCS serving as a replacement for the existing SMS and MMS standards. SMS and MMS will remain available as a fallback when necessary, though.<br/>
<br/>
Rich Communication Services is a communication protocol adopted by Google. Smartphone makers and carriers worldwide have adopted RCS, but Apple has been resisting its adoption. Google has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/google-ipager-ad-rcs-apple/">pushing Apple to accept RCS</a> through a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/02/google-again-pushes-apple-to-adopt-rcs/">long-running ad campaign</a> involving billboards, a website, social media pressure, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Google has had a "Get the Message" website <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/09/android-website-rcs-apple/">since August 2022</a>, with the site calling on Apple to "fix what's broken" in texts between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users. Earlier this year, even Samsung got into the PR campaign, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/samsung-pushes-apple-to-adopt-rcs/">publishing a bizarre ad</a> where "Romeo" with his green bubbles and "Juliet" with her blue bubbles were unable to be together because of Apple's hesitation to adopt RCS.<br/>
<br/>
"Green bubbles and blue bubbles want to be together," read Samsung's ad, which also included the #GetTheMessage hashtag Google used for its social media push.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to MMS and SMS, the standards that Apple uses for text messages, RCS supports higher resolution photos and videos, audio messages, and bigger file sizes. It also adds improved encryption for chats between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users, cross-platform emoji reactions, and more reliability for group chats across different devices.<br/>
<br/>
With RCS, real-time typing indicators, read receipts, better photos and videos, and much improved group chats will be standard on iPhones and Android phones, putting an end to the frustration that some &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users experience when attempting to communicate with Android smartphone owners. Apple claims that while RCS improves security for cross-device messaging, it is not as secure as iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, RCS will provide users with the option to share their location with others inside text threads over text messages, and like iMessage, RCS will work over Wi-Fi in addition to cellular.<br/>
<br/>
Back in September 2022, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that adopting RCS was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/08/tim-cook-on-ios-rcs-buy-your-mom-an-iphone/">not a priority for Apple</a>. "I don't hear our users asking that we put a lot of energy into that at this point," he said. It is not clear why Apple has changed its stance, but the company is facing regulatory scrutiny over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, iMessage, and other proprietary technologies in multiple countries, so adopting RCS could be seen as a willingness to work with other companies to improve device interoperability.<br/>
<br/>
The European Union, for example, has been working on legislation that would have required Apple to make changes to iMessage to make it available on other platforms. With RCS, iMessage will no longer have as many benefits that are unavailable cross-platform.<br/>
<br/>
Going forward, Apple plans to work with Google and other Global System for Mobile Communications Association (GSMA) members on further improving RCS. RCS support will be introduced in a software update next year, and carriers will need to implement support for full functionality. In the United States, Verizon, T-Mobile, and AT&amp;T already support RCS.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">Apple to Adopt RCS Messaging Standard for Better Interoperability With Android Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard-for-better-interoperability-with-android-devices.2411170/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung&#039;s Smart Monitor M8 Gets Massive &#36;300 Black Friday Discount, Now Just &#36;399.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-black-friday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-gets-massive-300-black-friday-discount-now-just-399-99.2411173/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-black-friday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung's 32-inch Smart Monitor M8 has hit a new all-time low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;699.99. This is the newest M80C model of the Smart Monitor, and the only color Amazon has at this price is Warm White.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-monitor-xmas.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922865" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You will need to clip an on-page coupon worth &#36;100 in order to see this discounted price applied at the checkout screen. You'll also need to be sure that you're purchasing the monitor from Amazon and not any other seller, as Amazon is the only one with the &#36;100 on-page coupon code. If you follow the link below and don't see the code, navigate to "other sellers" tab on the right side of the page on Amazon and find the direct Amazon listing.<br/>
<br/>
Once you do, you'll be able to buy the iMac-like Smart Monitor M8 with this massive &#36;300 discount, which is a new all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>Samsung Smart Monitor M80C for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung launched this refreshed version of the Smart Monitor M8 back in June, including updates like HDR10+ support and a portrait orientation option.<br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This deal has expired, but you can still get the monitor for &#36;499.99 on Amazon.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-black-friday/">Samsung&#039;s Smart Monitor M8 Gets Massive &#36;300 Black Friday Discount, Now Just &#36;399.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-gets-massive-300-black-friday-discount-now-just-399-99.2411173/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some iPhone 15 Owners With GM Cars Experiencing Wireless Charging Issues</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-15-gm-charging-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-15-owners-with-gm-cars-experiencing-wireless-charging-issues.2411168/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:59:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-15-gm-charging-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest flagship iPhones are not charging as expected in some GM vehicles, according to a number of consumer complaints highlighted by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/16/23963780/iphone-15-wireless-charging-gm-chevy-buick-cadillac">The Verge</a></em>. On <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BoltEV/comments/178mqp9/iphone_15_max_pro_wireless_charging_doesnt_work/">Reddit</a>, <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255233412">Apple's site</a>, and other forums, there are reports from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> users who own Chevrolet, Cadillac, and Buick vehicles with wireless chargers that are not able to charge their new iPhones. Some people see the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> charge for a few seconds, but then it seems to stop, while others can't get their devices to charge at all.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/pacifica-2021-wireless-charging.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1005" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-788160" /><br/>
On Reddit, there are several complaints from Chevy owners who can't get their wireless chargers to work properly. Placing the device in the wireless charging cubby does not result in a charge, regardless of whether the device is in a case.<blockquote>Happy to know that it isn't just me. My iPhone 12 Pro Max worked perfectly (every time) in my '23 Chevy Traverse. I went to the iPhone 15 Pro Max about 6 weeks ago and the feature broke just as described in other comments: Charge for a few seconds and then stops - case on or off yields same results. I am currently on iOS 17.1.1 and have taken every update since the phone was purchased on 10/8/23.</blockquote>Many of the complaints are from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max users, and the problem may be linked to the iOS 17.1 update.<br/>
<br/>
Some in-car wireless chargers are notoriously unreliable because of they are designed for a range of smartphone sizes and sometimes cannot accommodate larger devices. Alignment issues are common, resulting in a lot of frustration when it comes to wireless car charging.<br/>
<br/>
General Motors told <em>The Verge</em> that it is "aware of the concern" and "is investigating," with nothing to confirm on the issue at this time.<br/>
<br/>
This is the second charging-related issue that is plaguing the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models. Following the release of the new devices, some BMW owners quickly found that wireless chargers in their vehicles were temporarily disabling the NFC chip in their iPhones. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-to-fix-iphone-15-bmw-charging-issue/">confirmed the issue in October</a> and introduced a fix <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/">in the iOS 17.1.1 update</a> that came out in early November.<br/>
<br/>
The launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/first-qi2-wireless-chargers-coming-soon/">Qi2 wireless charging standard</a> may cut down on future problems with in-car charging because Qi2 chargers include magnetic alignment, but it often takes car manufacturers many months or even years to introduce new technology, and it won't be helpful to vehicle owners with existing Qi chargers.<br/>
<br/>
Given that the charging issues that GM owners are experiencing seem to have popped up with iOS 17.1, Apple may be able to address the problem with a subsequent update, and there is also a chance that GM can issue a firmware update to restore charging capabilities. As of now, the iOS 17.2 update does not fix the problem.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-15-gm-charging-issue/">Some iPhone 15 Owners With GM Cars Experiencing Wireless Charging Issues</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-15-owners-with-gm-cars-experiencing-wireless-charging-issues.2411168/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Deadlines for Ordering Holiday Gifts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-holiday-shipping-deadlines-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-deadlines-for-ordering-holiday-gifts.2411158/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:07:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-holiday-shipping-deadlines-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-black-friday-shopping-event-gift-cards/">Black Friday bonus gift card announcement</a>, Apple has also released its <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/gifts/holiday-shipping">holiday shipping guide</a> in the United States and other countries that outlines deadlines for customers looking to order gifts online for arrival by December 24.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-holiday-deadlines-2023.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922847" /><br/>
Unlike in some recent years, Apple appears to have ample stock of all of its main products as we head into the holiday season, with Apple currently saying that most products can be ordered up until December 21 while still receiving delivery in time for Christmas.<br/>
<br/>
For items that can be engraved through Apple, two additional days are generally required, meaning orders must be placed by December 19. The lone exception to that is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a>, which must be ordered by December 12 if you wish to have them engraved. Finally, physical gift cards must be ordered by December 19.<br/>
<br/>
While these deadlines are for shipments of orders placed through Apple's online store, the company says customers may still be able to get orders in time after the deadline if items are in stock and customers choose Apple Pickup or 2-hour delivery from a local <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Deadlines in other countries vary somewhat, such as a flat December 21 deadline for all products (including engraved ones) in <a href="https://www.apple.com/de/shop/gifts/holiday-shipping">Germany</a> and a flat December 22 deadline in the <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/shop/gifts/holiday-shipping">United Kingdom</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may update the deadlines on these pages in the coming weeks as it assesses product availability, so it pays to keep an eye on it and ensure you order in plenty of time to receive your items in time for the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/apple-2023-holiday-return-policy/">extended return policy</a> is also now in effect, allowing items purchased in most countries between November 3 and December 25 to be returned through January 8, 2024. Select countries have a longer window with items purchased between November 4 and January 6 able to be returned through January 20, 2024.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-holiday-shipping-deadlines-2023/">Apple Shares Deadlines for Ordering Holiday Gifts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-deadlines-for-ordering-holiday-gifts.2411158/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Black Friday Shopping Event to Offer Free Gift Cards on Select Products</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-black-friday-shopping-event-gift-cards/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-black-friday-shopping-event-to-offer-free-gift-cards-on-select-products.2411151/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 07:15:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-black-friday-shopping-event-gift-cards/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Cyber Monday</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared details about its upcoming "<a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/gifts/shopping-event">Apple Store Shopping Event</a>" between Black Friday on November 24 and Cyber Monday on November 27 where customers will be able to get a gift card with the purchase of select products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-black-friday-2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922825" /><br/>
From November 24 to November 27, customers will receive Apple Gift Cards with the purchase of eligible items from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>:<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Mac: Up to a &#36;200 Gift Card</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>iPad: Up to a &#36;100 Gift Card</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> (10th generation)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>iPhone and AirPods: Up to a &#36;75 Gift Card</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> (2nd generation)</li><br/>
<li>AirPods (3rd generation)</li><br/>
<li>AirPods (2nd generation)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Apple Watch, Apple TV, HomePod, Beats, and Accessories: Up to a &#36;50 Gift Card</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></li><br/>
<li>Magic Keyboard</li><br/>
<li>Magic Keyboard Folio</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> (2nd generation)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-keyboard/">Smart Keyboard</a> Folio.</li><br/>
<li>Beats Studio Pro</li><br/>
<li>Beats Solo3 Wireless</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/powerbeats-pro/">Powerbeats Pro</a></li><br/>
<li>Beats Fit Pro</li><br/>
<li>Beats Studio Buds +</li><br/>
<li>Beats Studio Buds</li><br/>
<li>Beats Flex</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Customers who plan to trade their current device in for a new product are still eligible for a gift card. The <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/gifts/shopping-event">Apple Store Shopping Event</a> is set to run for four days and will be available through Apple's online store in the United States, the United Kingdom, and various other countries.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/cyber-monday/">Cyber Monday</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-black-friday-shopping-event-gift-cards/">Apple&#039;s Black Friday Shopping Event to Offer Free Gift Cards on Select Products</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-black-friday-shopping-event-to-offer-free-gift-cards-on-select-products.2411151/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Rumored to Feature New Thermal Design</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-rumored-to-feature-new-thermal-design.2411142/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:06:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to introduce a new thermal system on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> to reduce overheating, according to the leaker known as "Kosutami."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-Updated-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922680" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/KosutamiSan/status/1724948467473408101?s=20">recent post</a> on X (formerly Twitter), Kosutami explained that Apple is working on a graphene thermal system for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, while the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro models could add metal battery casings to reduce overheating. The move appears to come in response to widely encountered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/">overheating issues</a> experienced with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, which Apple addressed through a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/04/apple-releases-ios-17-0-3/">software update</a> earlier this year. <br/>
<br/>
Graphene has high thermal conductivity, surpassing that of copper, which is currently used in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> heat-sinks. Apple has been interested in graphene for thermal management for some time, filing patents related to its exploration of the material for heat dissipation in portable devices. Apple previously transitioned the Apple Watch's battery from black foil casings to ones made of metal with the Series 7, so an equivalent change on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; seems plausible.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/">iPhone 16 Rumored to Feature New Thermal Design</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-rumored-to-feature-new-thermal-design.2411142/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft &#039;Windows App&#039; Offers Access to Windows PCs From Any Device</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/microsoft-windows-app-access-any-device/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-windows-app-offers-access-to-windows-pcs-from-any-device.2411141/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:01:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/microsoft-windows-app-access-any-device/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Windows 365</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft is launching a "<a href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-gb/windows-app/overview">Windows App</a>" that can remotely connect to a Windows PC and provide access to it from any platform. Available for macOS, iOS, iPadOS, PCs, and web browsers, the app also provides a gateway to Windows 365, Azure Virtual Desktop, Microsoft Dev Box, and the company's Remote Desktop Services.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/windows-app-overview.jpg" alt="" width="1782" height="1101" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922802" /><br/>
The Windows app includes a customizable Home Screen from which users can access multiple different cloud services and remote PCs. The app features multiple monitor support, custom display resolutions, dynamic display resolutions and scaling, peripheral redirection, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft has offered the Remote Desktop Connection app in Windows for years now, but the Windows app signals a broader shift to cloud computing for Windows more generally.<br/>
<br/>
For now the app is only available as a preview for enterprise accounts, but it is likely to support regular customers in time, although the option to sign in using a personal Microsoft account doesn't currently work, according to <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/16/23963568/microsoft-windows-app-ios-ipados-macos-web">The Verge</a></em>. The Mac version requires macOS 12 or later, while the iOS/iPadOS app needs a device running iOS or iPadOS 16 or later. The web version of the app can be accessed by going to <a href="http://windows.cloud.microsoft">windows.cloud.microsoft</a>. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/windows-365/">Windows 365</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/microsoft-windows-app-access-any-device/">Microsoft &#039;Windows App&#039; Offers Access to Windows PCs From Any Device</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-windows-app-offers-access-to-windows-pcs-from-any-device.2411141/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Promotes New Apple Pay UK Bank Account Balance Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-pay-uk-bank-account-balance/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-new-apple-pay-uk-bank-account-balance-feature.2411136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:50:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-pay-uk-bank-account-balance/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/newsroom/2023/11/new-apple-pay-feature-helps-users-access-account-information-more-conveniently/">highlighted</a> the ability in iOS 17.1 for UK users to connect their credit and debit cards in Apple Wallet and easily access information like account balance, spending history, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-Wallet-connected-accounts-hero.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922788" /><br/>
Users can view their up-to-date bank card balance, payments, deposits, and withdrawals in Wallet and when they're checking out with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> online or in-apps. Apple says the new feature "empowers users to make more informed purchases, increases their confidence when making a transaction, and allows them to simply view frequent information so that they have more control when it comes to their finances."<br/>
<br/>
From Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/newsroom/2023/11/new-apple-pay-feature-helps-users-access-account-information-more-conveniently/">press release</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>"By enabling users to conveniently access their most useful account information within Wallet and at the time of their purchase, they can make informed financial decisions and better understand and manage their spend," said Jennifer Bailey, Apple's vice president of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet. "We look forward to working with U.K. partners under the Open Banking initiative to help users better their financial health, and provide more ways in which banks can deepen their relationships with customers."</blockquote>Apple added the transaction and card balance functionality to the Wallet app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">October's iOS 17.1 update</a> as part of its Connected Cards feature, and several banks have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/more-uk-banks-show-account-balance-apple-wallet/">since come on board</a>, including Barclays, Barclaycard, First Direct, Halifax, HSBC, Lloyds, M&S Bank, Monzo Bank, NatWest Bank, and Royal Bank of Scotland.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">How to View UK Bank Account Balance in Apple Wallet</a></li></ul><br/>
UK banks support the Open Banking API to integrate with the Wallet app, which has made the feature widely available to UK users, while the Connected Cards rollout in the United States has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/">lagged behind</a>. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-pay-uk-bank-account-balance/">Apple Promotes New Apple Pay UK Bank Account Balance Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-new-apple-pay-uk-bank-account-balance-feature.2411136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Classical Comes to iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-music-classical-comes-to-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-classical-comes-to-ipad.2411131/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 01:39:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-music-classical-comes-to-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Music Classical</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Music Classical was updated on the App Store today and extends the service's availability beyond iPhone and Android to bring it to iPads for the first time (via <em><a href="https://x.com/9to5mac/status/1725083398941622603?s=20">9to5Mac</a></em>). Apple released Apple Music Classical on the Google Play Store in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/apple-music-classical-now-available-for-android/">March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-music-classical-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="2973" height="2288" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922782" /><br/>
Version 1.1 of Apple's app includes an interface designed specifically for the larger iPad display, with a navigation sidebar and media playback controls along the bottom of the screen.<br/>
<br/>
In 2021, Apple announced that it had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/30/apple-acquires-primephonic-classical-music-service/">purchased</a> the classical music streaming service Primephonic and would be folding it into Apple Music via a new app dedicated to the genre. Apple launched Apple Music Classical in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/28/apple-music-classical-now-available/">March</a>, offering a standalone experience for discovering and listening to classical music.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Music Classical app offers Apple Music subscribers access to over five million classical music tracks, including new high-quality releases, in addition to hundreds of curated playlists, thousands of exclusive albums, and other features like composer bios and deep dives on key works.<br/>
<br/>
The app offers a simpler interface for interacting with classical music specifically. Unlike the existing Apple Music app, Apple Music Classical allows users to search by composer, work, conductor, catalog number, and more. Users can get more detailed information from editorial notes and descriptions.<br/>
<br/>
Apple commissioned high-resolution digital portraits of famous composers like Ludwig van Beethoven, Frdric Chopin, and Johann Sebastian Bach for the app, using color palettes and artistic references from the relevant classical period, with more unique artwork to be added over time. Apple works with classical music artists and institutions to offer exclusive content and recordings.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-classical/">Apple Music Classical</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-music-classical-comes-to-ipad/">Apple Music Classical Comes to iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-classical-comes-to-ipad.2411131/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 10.2 Beta Reintroduces Option to Change Apple Watch Faces With a Swipe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/watchos-10-2-watch-face-swipe-change/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-10-2-beta-reintroduces-option-to-change-apple-watch-faces-with-a-swipe.2411103/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:46:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/watchos-10-2-watch-face-swipe-change/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The third watchOS 10.2 beta that Apple released this week reintroduces an Apple Watch feature for swapping watch faces that was initially removed with the upgrade to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-ultra-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907490" /><br/>
Users can now choose to use a swipe gesture to switch the active Apple Watch face by enabling the option in the Apple Watch Settings app. With the feature turned on, swiping left or right on the watch face scrolls through the available watch faces that have been set up.<br/>
<br/>
Switching watch faces with a swipe gesture was the default in watchOS 9, but Apple updated the interaction because of complaints that it was too easy to accidentally change watch faces. The current gesture requires long pressing before swiping to change the active watch face. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">watchOS 10.2 beta 3 adds back the feature that allows you to swipe between watch faces!<br><br>This feature was removed in watchOS 10.0 <a href="https://t.co/7OWgdMkp72">pic.twitter.com/7OWgdMkp72</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1724952001681789227?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 16, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
With watchOS 10.2, Apple Watch owners who preferred the prior method of changing their watch faces can choose to enable the setting if desired. The option is under Settings > Clock in the third beta. <br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.2 is available to both developers and public beta testers at this time, and it is expected to see a public launch in December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/watchos-10-2-watch-face-swipe-change/">watchOS 10.2 Beta Reintroduces Option to Change Apple Watch Faces With a Swipe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-10-2-beta-reintroduces-option-to-change-apple-watch-faces-with-a-swipe.2411103/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Models Have Up to 54% Better 5G Download Speeds Than iPhone 14 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-15-5g-download-speeds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-have-up-to-54-better-5g-download-speeds-than-iphone-14-models.2411097/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:09:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-15-5g-download-speeds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>5G</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models are equipped with Qualcomm's X70 modem chip that promises faster 5G speeds than the X65 in the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models, and testing <a href="https://www.ookla.com/articles/iphone-15-samsung-fold5-performance-q3-2023">shared by Ookla</a> confirms that download speeds have notably improved.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ookla-5g-iphone-15-speed.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="826" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922751" /><br/>
Using data collected from its online Speedtest for measuring connection speeds, Ookla has been able to determine that the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models support download speeds that are up to 54 percent faster than the download speeds available on the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to their equivalent &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus saw 54 percent faster download speeds, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; had 45 percent better download speeds, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max was 27 percent faster, and the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; had a 25 percent better download speed.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models had the fastest download speeds out of all the Apple and Samsung devices included on Ookla's results list. Median download speeds on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max were at 285Mb/s, and the other iPhones weren't far behind.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; had the slowest median download speed out of Apple's lineup at 249Mb/s, but it still came out ahead of Samsung's latest smartphones, including the Galaxy Z Fold5 and the Galaxy Z Flip5.<br/>
<br/>
Note that Ookla's data covers median download speeds across the entire United States, and connectivity could vary depending on location, proximity to a major city, location of the closest cellular tower, carrier, and more. Data shared for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> was collected from September 22 to October 30.<br/>
<br/>
5G download speeds also improved in multiple other countries, including Australia, Brazil, Canada, France, India, South Korea, Spain, the UK, and the UAE, with full results <a href="https://www.ookla.com/articles/iphone-15-samsung-fold5-performance-q3-2023">available on the Ookla website</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/5g/">5G</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-15-5g-download-speeds/">iPhone 15 Models Have Up to 54% Better 5G Download Speeds Than iPhone 14 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-have-up-to-54-better-5g-download-speeds-than-iphone-14-models.2411097/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Six Months of Free Apple Music Available to PlayStation 5 Owners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-music-ps5-trial/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-months-of-free-apple-music-available-to-playstation-5-owners.2411092/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:15:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-music-ps5-trial/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of an effort to promote <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> on the PlayStation, Apple is <a href="https://www.playstation.com/en-us/deals/apple-music-playstation-offers">offering PlayStation 5 owners</a> up to six months of free access to the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; streaming service.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-music-playstation-5.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="878" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922759" /><br/>
PlayStation 5 owners will need to sign into the PlayStation Network, download the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app, and follow the on-screen instructions to accept the offer. Users will need to sign in with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> or create one.<br/>
<br/>
The PlayStation website suggests that gamers use &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; to create a personalized gaming playlist to listen to before, during, and after gameplay sessions.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; promotion is only available on the PlayStation 5, and it has to be redeemed on a PlayStation 5 console. Only new and qualified returning subscribers to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; can get free access, so this is not a deal that is available to current subscribers. New subscribers will receive six months of &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, while returning subscribers will get five months.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will be <a href="https://www.playstation.com/en-us/deals/apple-music-playstation-offers">offering the deal</a> until 11/15/24. After the six-month period expires, a subscription can be continued for &#36;10.99 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-music-ps5-trial/">Six Months of Free Apple Music Available to PlayStation 5 Owners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-months-of-free-apple-music-available-to-playstation-5-owners.2411092/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 183 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2411091/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:55:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 183 includes fixes and updates for Accessibility, AutoFill, CSS, Forms, HTML, JavaScript, Media, Rendering, Scrolling, SVG, URLs, Web API, Web Inspector, and WebGL.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Ventura and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, the latest version of macOS that Apple released in September 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 183 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2411091/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTuber Explains How to Watch Spatial Videos From iPhone 15 Pro on VR Headsets</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/spatial-video-iphone-15-vr-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtuber-explains-how-to-watch-spatial-videos-from-iphone-15-pro-on-vr-headsets.2411087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 13:53:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/spatial-video-iphone-15-vr-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the iOS 17.2 beta, Apple added a feature that allows the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max to record Spatial Video that's designed for the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset. As the Vision Pro is not yet available, there's no way to watch Spatial Video in its 3D form on an Apple device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Vision-Pro-Spatial-Video.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922277" /><br/>
Spatial Video content can, however, be watched on the Meta Quest 3 and other 3D devices thanks to a workaround shared by YouTuber Hugh Hou. Earlier this week, Hou described <a href="https://www.threads.net/@hugh.hou">how to manipulate Spatial Video</a> to get it to run on Meta's VR headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Spatial Video in 3D! Shot on iPhone 15 Pro for Vision Pro &amp; Meta Quest 3" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x3v-0XbWI2s" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
An &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; running the iOS 17.2 beta is required, of course, in order to record Spatial Video in the first place. The beta is available to both developers and public beta testers, and downloading it is as simple as going to the Software Update section in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Settings app and toggling on beta updates.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial Video recording needs to be enabled in the Camera settings after the iOS 17.2 update, and from there, Hou instructs users to <a href="https://testflight.apple.com/join/EEFFsOzJ">get the "Spatialify" app</a> on TestFlight.<br/>
<br/>
The app has instructions on decoding and exporting Spatial Video in a format that the Meta Quest 3 or other 3D headsets and TVs can view, and there is an extra step involving encoding 3D metadata.<br/>
<br/>
It is not the most straightforward process, but it may be of interest to &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; users who have a VR headset or 3D TV and want to try viewing Spatial Video ahead of when the Vision Pro headset comes out.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial Video is designed to allow Vision Pro headset wearers to view video in a more immersive 3D format. Along with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, the headset will also be able to be used to record Spatial Video content.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/spatial-video-iphone-15-vr-headset/">YouTuber Explains How to Watch Spatial Videos From iPhone 15 Pro on VR Headsets</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtuber-explains-how-to-watch-spatial-videos-from-iphone-15-pro-on-vr-headsets.2411087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Adds New Filters, Support for Custom Stickers From Photos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/instagram-new-filters-stickers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-adds-new-filters-support-for-custom-stickers-from-photos.2411078/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:32:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/instagram-new-filters-stickers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular social network Instagram <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2023/11/new-ways-to-create-content-on-instagram/">was today updated</a> with a number of improvements that are designed to give users more ways to edit their content before sharing it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Instagram-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786418" /><br/>
Instagram has added more than 20 new filters that can be used to tweak the look of images, and this is the first time in several years that filters have been updated. Some of the filters add subtle color changes, while others change the look entirely by adding blur and other effects. All of the filters have an intensity slider to tweak the final look.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside the new filters, the posting interface has been simplified. It's easier to find specific images from the camera roll thanks to improved previews and the ability to zoom and search by keyword.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram is using its Segment Anything AI model to give users the ability to create custom stickers from their own photos and videos, or from eligible photos and videos shared on Instagram. These features are being tested, and may not be accessible to everyone.<br/>
<br/>
For Reels, Instagram is testing options for scaling, cropping, and rotating individual clips, plus there are options to add from the clip hub for creating "more memeable content." The Reels interface is being updated to make it easier to locate tools like Voiceover, and undo and redo functionality is being added.<br/>
<br/>
There are 10 new English text-to-speech voices to choose from to have Instagram read text content, and there are six new text fonts and styles to work with. Note that these features are rolling out and are not available to all users at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram is a free app, and more information on the changes can be <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2023/11/new-ways-to-create-content-on-instagram/">found on the Instagram blog</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/instagram-new-filters-stickers/">Instagram Adds New Filters, Support for Custom Stickers From Photos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-adds-new-filters-support-for-custom-stickers-from-photos.2411078/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker Black Friday Early Access Sale Includes Mystery Boxes With Hundreds in Savings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-black-friday-early-access-sale-includes-mystery-boxes-with-hundreds-in-savings.2411077/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:59:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anker's <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu">Black Friday Early Access</a> sale is winding down this week, so we're again highlighting all of the best deals from the event before it ends on November 16. With this sale, when you buy two or more Anker products sitewide you can get 25 percent off your entire order. There are also a few "mystery boxes" that can include hundreds of dollars in savings, if you're willing to risk not knowing what you're buying ahead of time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/anker-new-gold.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922736" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In terms of the base sale, there are plenty of great accessories that you can buy to take advantage of the bundle savings, including the new MagSafe-compatible <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/y1811?ref=black-friday-sale">Anker 3-in-1 Charging Cube</a> (&#36;149.95). This device has space to simultaneously charge an iPhone, Apple Watch, and AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
There's also the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1336-20000mah-power-bank?ref=black-friday-sale&amp;variant=42691854925974">Anker Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> (&#36;129.99). Although this one is on sale at &#36;110.49 without the bundle deal, if you buy this and the 3-in-1 Cube together, you'll net a bigger discount. The Power Bank will be knocked down to &#36;97.50 and the 3-in-1 Cube will go down to &#36;112.46 thanks to the 25 percent savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">25% OFF</div>Anker Black Friday Early Access</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
At the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu">bottom of the Black Friday Early Access sale page</a>, Anker also has a few blind boxes on sale, priced at &#36;19.99 (up to &#36;219.99 in value) and at &#36;59.99 (up to &#36;799.99 in value). These mystery boxes include one Anker accessory, but you won't know what you're getting until they arrive. All items in the &#36;19.99 box are worth more than &#36;19.99, and all items in the &#36;59.99 box are worth more than &#36;59.99, so no matter what you'll be getting a deal.<br/>
<br/>
All mystery box items are non-returnable (with the exception of quality issues). They are also excluded from the 25 percent off promotion when purchasing two or more items. These could net you a huge discount with a collection of solid stocking stuffers for the holidays, if you're willing to take the blind box risk.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Wall Chargers</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2668?variant=41974350315670">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;37.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2669-3-port-wall-charger">67W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;59.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469063005">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2340?variant=41974288777366">150W 4-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;87.99, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6CZDXZV%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.SVW72ULYCRBB%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.SVW72ULYCRBB_1700146470555">Prime 240W 4-Port Desktop Charger</a> - &#36;109.99 at Amazon with on-page coupon, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Portable Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1653-usb-c-portable-charger-5000mah">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.50, down from &#36;29.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK77HJ">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1268">PowerCore 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;36.52, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1651">PowerCore 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1289">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/b1291">PowerCore 26,000 mAh</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<strong>Portable Power Stations</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1751">PowerHouse 535</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1761">SOLIX C1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;749.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1770111">PowerHouse 757</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1780">PowerHouse 767</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul> You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/">Anker Black Friday Early Access Sale Includes Mystery Boxes With Hundreds in Savings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-black-friday-early-access-sale-includes-mystery-boxes-with-hundreds-in-savings.2411077/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
