<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:01:09 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Drops to Sixth Place in China&#039;s Smartphone Market</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-drops-to-sixth-place-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-drops-to-sixth-place-in-chinas-smartphone-market.2432269/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 05:06:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-drops-to-sixth-place-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Canalys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For the first time in years, Apple has fallen out of the top five smartphone vendors in China, ranking sixth in the second quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-lineup-store.jpg" alt="" width="2976" height="1538" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911377" /><br/>
Data from <a href="https://www.canalys.com/newsroom/china-smartphone-market-Q2-2024">Canalys</a>, a market research firm, shows that Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> shipments in China declined by 6.7% year-on-year. This drop has been attributed to fierce competition from domestic brands such as Huawei, Vivo, Oppo, Honor, and Xiaomi. Huawei, in particular, has seen a resurgence in the high-end smartphone market, fueled by advanced chips produced entirely in China.<br/>
<br/>
Canalys reported that the overall Chinese smartphone market experienced a 10% year-on-year growth in the second quarter of 2024, with shipments exceeding 70 million units. Vivo reclaimed the number one spot by shipping 13.1 million units, capturing a 19% market share. Oppo followed with 11.3 million units, Honor with 10.7 million units, and Huawei with 10.6 million units. Xiaomi re-entered the top five with a 17% year-on-year increase, shipping 10 million units. In contrast, Apple's shipments dropped to 9.7 million units, representing a 14% market share.<br/>
<br/>
The increased competition and market dynamics in China have posed significant challenges for Apple. The company's market share decreased from 16% in the previous year to 14%, pushing it from third to sixth place. Despite promotional efforts, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">significant discounts</a> of up to 23%, Apple has struggled to maintain its market position. The competitive landscape has been further complicated by the overall growth of local vendors, which have benefited from their localized supply chains and strong brand loyalty among Chinese consumers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Chief Operating Officer Jeff Williams <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/new-apple-lab-in-china-to-test-products/">recently visited China</a>, meeting with officials in Beijing and Shenzhen to reinforce Apple's commitment to the Chinese market. Canalys analyst Lucas Zhong emphasized the importance of the company localizing Apple Intelligence for China within the next year to regain market share. The anticipated release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup later this year is also expected to drive demand and potentially improve Apple's market position.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/canalys/">Canalys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-drops-to-sixth-place-in-china/">Apple Drops to Sixth Place in China&#039;s Smartphone Market</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-drops-to-sixth-place-in-chinas-smartphone-market.2432269/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Lowers iPhone Prices and Eyes iPad Assembly in India</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-cuts-iphone-prices-in-india/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-lowers-iphone-prices-and-eyes-ipad-assembly-in-india.2432267/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 04:45:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-cuts-iphone-prices-in-india/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>India</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has reduced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> prices in India for the first time following a cut in import duties and is considering assembling iPads in the country for the first time. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/Apple-BKC-Mumbai-India-media-preview-hero.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-892713" /><br/>
As noted by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/apple-cuts-iphone-price-in-india-amid-china-slowdown/"><em>TechCrunch</em></a>, Apple has lowered the prices of its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models in India by 3-4% after the Indian government <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-expansion-in-india-to-accelerate/">reduced import duties on smartphones</a> from 20% to 15% in its annual budget on July 23. This price reduction marks the first time Apple has decreased prices on its Pro models in India, with the cuts ranging from 300 rupees (&#36;3.60) for models like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>, 14, and 15, to up to 6,000 rupees (&#36;71.70) for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
In parallel with these price adjustments, Foxconn, Apple's main contract manufacturer, is reportedly exploring the possibility of assembling iPads at its facility in Tamil Nadu, India, according to <a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/technology/foxconn-eyes-major-expansion-in-india-plans-to-assemble-apple-ipads-at-tamil-nadu-facility/articleshow/112024233.cms"><em>The Economic Times</em></a>. This would mark a significant expansion from Foxconn's current focus on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; production in India and reflects confidence in India's growing supply chain capabilities, aligning with Apple's broader strategy to diversify its manufacturing base away from China. Discussions between Foxconn and the Indian government have apparently already taken place.<br/>
<br/>
The reduction in import duties is part of India's broader economic strategy to boost local manufacturing and integrate more deeply into the global electronics supply chain. By lowering the cost of high-end smartphones like the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, the Indian government aims to make these devices more accessible to a larger segment of the population. This also supports Apple's ongoing efforts to expand its footprint in the Indian market, which has become increasingly important as growth in more established markets like China has slowed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's assembly operations in India have seen significant growth in recent years. Currently, about 14% of all iPhones are produced in India, a number that is expected to increase as Foxconn and other partners expand their facilities in the country. Foxconn has already invested heavily in new manufacturing plants in Karnataka and Tamil Nadu, and the prospect of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> assembly in India could see Apple's presence in the country increase even further.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/india/">India</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-cuts-iphone-prices-in-india/">Apple Lowers iPhone Prices and Eyes iPad Assembly in India</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-lowers-iphone-prices-and-eyes-ipad-assembly-in-india.2432267/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Agrees to Follow President Biden&#039;s AI Safety Guidelines</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-agrees-to-ai-safety-guidelines/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-agrees-to-follow-president-bidens-ai-safety-guidelines.2432265/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 04:13:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-agrees-to-ai-safety-guidelines/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>United States</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has committed to a set of voluntary AI safeguards established by President Joe Biden's administration, joining other tech giants in a move to ensure responsible AI development (via <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-07-26/apple-to-adopt-voluntary-ai-safeguards-established-by-biden">Bloomberg</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
Apple is now part of the a group of influential technology companies agreeing to the Biden administration's voluntary safeguards for artificial intelligence. The safeguards, <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/30/fact-sheet-president-biden-issues-executive-order-on-safe-secure-and-trustworthy-artificial-intelligence/">announced by the White House</a> last year as part of an Executive Order, aim to guide the development of AI systems, ensuring they are tested for discriminatory tendencies, security vulnerabilities, and potential national security risks.<br/>
<br/>
The principles outlined in the guidelines call for companies to share the results of AI system tests with governments, civil society, and academia. This level of transparency is intended to foster an environment of accountability and peer review, promoting the development of safer and more reliable AI technologies. The safeguards Apple and other tech companies have agreed to also include commitments to test their AI systems for biases and security concerns. <br/>
<br/>
Although these guidelines are not legally binding, they signify a collective effort by the tech industry to self-regulate and mitigate the potential risks associated with AI technologies. The executive order signed by President Biden last year also requires AI systems to undergo testing before being eligible for federal procurement.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's participation in the initiative coincides with its plans to introduce its own cohesive AI system and deep integration with OpenAI's ChatGPT. Apple Intelligence will be supported by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, as well as all upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. For the Mac and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, all devices equipped with M-series Apple silicon chips will support Apple Intelligence. <br/>
<br/>
While Apple Intelligence is not yet available in beta for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, the company has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-intelligence-coming-in-later-ios-18-dev-beta/">pledged to release some features in beta soon</a>, with a public release expected by the end of the year. Further enhancements, including an overhaul to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> that leverages in-app actions and personal context, are anticipated to roll out in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-powered-siri/">spring of 2025</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-states/">United States</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/apple-agrees-to-ai-safety-guidelines/">Apple Agrees to Follow President Biden&#039;s AI Safety Guidelines</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-agrees-to-follow-president-bidens-ai-safety-guidelines.2432265/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: What&#039;s New With the Calculator App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-calculator-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-whats-new-with-the-calculator-app.2432238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:22:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-calculator-app&#038;post_date=1721960537/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple doesn't typically focus much on the Calculator app, but with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it's getting a notable overhaul and some surprising integration with the Notes app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Calculator-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960038" /><br/>
This guide walks through everything that's new with the Calculator in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; (and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>).<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="math_notes">Math Notes</h2><br/>
The biggest change to the Calculator app is the addition of Math Notes, a feature that's basically an integration between the Calculator and the Notes app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-math-notes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960057" /><br/>
Math Notes lets you type equations in the Notes app and have them solved automatically when you put in an equals sign. So you can do things like calculate how much everyone owes for a group trip, or split up a dinner bill.<br/>
<br/>
You can do more complex equations too, defining variables and then using those definitions for your calculations. If you write dinner = &#36;57 and movies = &#36;24 in a note, for example, you can then type in "dinner + movies" and add an equals sign and get the total, with the Math Notes feature understanding what you're referencing.<br/>
<br/>
In Math Notes, your equations are solved automatically wherever you put in an equals sign, as that signals to Apple that you want to solve what you've typed.<br/>
<br/>
Math Notes is technically a Notes app feature, but you can in fact start a Math Note in the Calculator app, and use it right there without having to swap over to Notes.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Calculator app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the calculator symbol at the bottom left of the app.</li><br/>
 <li>Select Math Notes.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the new note symbol at the bottom right of the display.</li><br/>
 <li>Start your calculations.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
You can do this same thing directly in the Notes app with any existing or new note. It's all the same feature, just accessed from different places.<br/>
<br/>
If you're in a Math Note in the Calculator app and you want to get back to the standard calculator interface, just tap again on the calculator icon and choose the Basic or Scientific option.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that Math Notes is available for math written using Western Arabic numerals and common mathematical symbols, or typed using Arabic (Eastern &amp; Western) and Devanagari numerals and common mathematical symbols.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="math_notes_on_ipad">Math Notes on iPad</h2><br/>
With &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, Math Notes works in the same way, but there is an added bonus - you can use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>. Once you start a Math Note from the Calculator app or the Notes app, you can write your equations by hand and have them solved in the exact same way.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ipados-18-math-notes.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954476" /><br/>
<h2 id="math_notes_everywhere">Math Notes Everywhere</h2><br/>
You can in fact get Math Notes results almost anywhere in the operating system. If you type an equation into search, for example, you'll get a result, and the same goes for apps like Messages.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-math-notes-anywhere.jpg" alt="" width="2526" height="1421" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960058" /><br/>
<h2 id="unit_conversion">Unit Conversion</h2><br/>
When using Math Notes, you can do unit conversions. Just type in what you want to convert, and you'll get the result automatically. For example, if you type in 10 kilograms to pounds in the Math Notes interface in the Calculator app, the result is automatically generated.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-conversions.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960059" /><br/>
Unit conversions work in search, Messages, Notes, the Calculator app, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="calculation_history">Calculation History</h2><br/>
If you open up the Calculator app and tap on the three lines at the upper left of the interface, you can see a history of all of the calculations you have entered into the app. Apple only saves calculations done with the Basic or Scientific calculators here, and Math Notes are saved in the Notes app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-history.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960060" /><br/>
You can long press on any of the calculations to copy either the expression or the result, and if you swipe, you can delete them from the list. You can also tap on the Edit button to select several expressions to delete, or use the Delete All option from this menu to clear out the app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="portrait_orientation">Portrait Orientation</h2><br/>
There is now an option to use the scientific calculator in portrait orientation, so you don't need to turn your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to landscape orientation to get to it anymore.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-scientific-calculator.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960061" /><br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
Additional information on new features that Apple has added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-calculator-app/">iOS 18: What&#039;s New With the Calculator App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-whats-new-with-the-calculator-app.2432238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fortnite Coming to AltStore on iOS in European Union</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/fortnite-altstore-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-coming-to-altstore-on-ios-in-european-union.2432235/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:26:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/fortnite-altstore-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple rival <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/site/en-US/news/epic-s-new-game-strategy-for-mobile-stores">today announced plans</a> to bring Fortnite to alternative app store AltStore in the European Union, which will mean the popular game will soon be available to download on iPhones and iPads.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite_apple_featured.jpg" alt="" width="2140" height="1204" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-754674" /><br/>
Created by developer Riley Testut, AltStore PAL was one of the first alternative app stores on iOS when it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/altstore-eu-alternative-app-marketplace/">launched back in April</a>. AltStore PAL is available in the European Union, where Apple supports sideloading to comply with Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
AltStore is an open-source app that distributes Testut's popular Delta game emulator as well as apps from other independent developers. Distributing apps through AltStore is free of charge, so &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; will not need to pay a fee to Testut, but Apple will collect an 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee (CTF) from &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; after Fortnite receives more than one million annual first installs.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who install AltStore must also pay 1.50 euros per year, a fee that is required because of Apple's CTF. Apple charges Testut 0.50 euros each time AltStore is installed.<br/>
<br/>
Along with bringing Fortnite to AltStore, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; said that it will bring Fortnite to other mobile stores that "give all developers a great deal," while also "ending distribution partnerships with mobile stores that serve as rent collectors." &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; said that it will be removing Fortnite and other Epic titles from the Samsung Galaxy Store to protest Samsung's "anticompetitive decision to block side-loading by default" on Samsung devices.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; also reiterated plans to bring its &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store to iOS in the European Union. Epic will charge a store fee of 12 percent for payments that it processes, and 0 percent on third-party payments.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/fortnite-altstore-eu/">Fortnite Coming to AltStore on iOS in European Union</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-coming-to-altstore-on-ios-in-european-union.2432235/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iCloud Private Relay Experiencing Outage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/icloud-private-relay-experiencing-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-private-relay-experiencing-outage.2432234/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:18:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/icloud-private-relay-experiencing-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple’s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Private Relay service is down for some users, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple’s System Status page</a>. Apple says that the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay service may be slow or unavailable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/icloud-private-relay-outage.jpg" alt="" width="1339" height="753" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960053" /><br/>
The outage started at 2:34 p.m. Eastern Time, but it does not appear to be affecting all &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; users. Some impacted users are unable to browse the web without turning &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay off, while others are seeing slow loading times. <br/>
<br/>
We'll update this article when the outage has been resolved. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/icloud-private-relay-experiencing-outage/">iCloud Private Relay Experiencing Outage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-private-relay-experiencing-outage.2432234/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Debuts SearchGPT AI Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/openai-debuts-searchgpt-ai-search-engine/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-debuts-searchgpt-ai-search-engine.2432230/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:25:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/openai-debuts-searchgpt-ai-search-engine/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI <a href="https://openai.com/index/searchgpt-prototype/">today introduced SearchGPT</a>, a prototype of AI search features that are designed to provide "fast and timely answers" combined with "clear and relevant sources."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
<a href="https://chatgpt.com/search">SearchGPT</a> is available to a small group of users and publishers at the current time, with OpenAI seeking feedback on the product. The prototype is temporary at the current time, but "best" of the features will be integrated into ChatGPT in the future.<br/>
<br/>
OpenAI designed SearchGPT to pair conversational capabilities with real-time information with the web, which the company says can make it faster and easier to find what you're looking for. SearchGPT is able to respond to questions with up-to-date information from the web. SearchGPT is able to answer follow-up questions in a conversational manner, with shared context included with each additional query.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">We’re testing SearchGPT, a temporary prototype of new AI search features that give you fast and timely answers with clear and relevant sources. <br><br>We’re launching with a small group of users for feedback and plan to integrate the experience into ChatGPT. <a href="https://t.co/dRRnxXVlGh">https://t.co/dRRnxXVlGh</a> <a href="https://t.co/iQpADXmllH">pic.twitter.com/iQpADXmllH</a></p>&mdash; OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1816536290822881780?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
OpenAI says that it is committed to a "thriving ecosystem of publishers and creators" and that it wants to help users discover publisher sites. Responses that SearchGPT provides have in-line, named attribution and links so users are aware where information is coming from, plus there's a sidebar with additional source links.<br/>
<br/>
Publishers are able to manage how they appear in SearchGPT, but OpenAI says that SearchGPT is "about search" and separate from training generative AI models. Sites can be surfaced in search results even if they've opted out of generative AI training.<br/>
<br/>
Those interested in testing out SearchGPT can <a href="http://chatgpt.com/search">join OpenAI's waitlist</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/openai-debuts-searchgpt-ai-search-engine/">OpenAI Debuts SearchGPT AI Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-debuts-searchgpt-ai-search-engine.2432230/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Apologizes for Widely Criticized App Redesign, Provides Progress Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-apologizes-for-widely-criticized-app-redesign-provides-progress-update.2432227/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 10:42:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos CEO Patrick Spence <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/blog/update-on-the-sonos-app">today penned a blog post</a> on the Sonos website apologizing for the controversial Sonos app redesign and promising ongoing updates throughout the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
Spence said that improving the app for customers is the company's number one priority, and he explained that addressing bugs that came up in the new app delayed the introduction of additional features.<blockquote>We know that too many of you have experienced significant problems with our new app which rolled out on May 7, and I want to begin by personally apologizing for disappointing you. There isn't an employee at Sonos who isn't pained by having let you down, and I assure you that fixing the app for all of our customers and partners has been and continues to be our number one priority.</blockquote>Spence shared an outline of future feature plans, with Sonos planning to push updates on a bi-weekly basis. Alarms are set to be addressed in September, with edit mode for playlists and the queue coming in September or October.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>July and August:</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Improving the stability when adding new products</li><br/>
 	<li>Implementing Music Library configuration, browse, search, and play</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<strong>August and September:</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Improving Volume responsiveness</li><br/>
 	<li>User interface improvements based on customer feedback</li><br/>
 	<li>Improving overall system stability and error handling</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<strong>September:</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Improving Alarm consistency and reliability</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<strong>September and October:</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Restoring edit mode for Playlists and the Queue</li><br/>
 	<li>Improving functionality in settings</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Spence says that Sonos is working hard to earn back customer trust through the continual app improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos in May <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">released its redesigned app</a> with customizable home screen and a more personalized listening service. Sonos customers quickly found that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/sonos-said-rolling-out-widely-criticized-app-redesign-took-courage/">app lacked several key features</a>, and suffered from multiple bugs. Complaints across social media called the app a "step back" for removing playlist management, alarms, and other features.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/">Sonos Apologizes for Widely Criticized App Redesign, Provides Progress Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-apologizes-for-widely-criticized-app-redesign-provides-progress-update.2432227/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Big Savings on Popular Accessories From Anker, Eufy, and Jackery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/amazon-savings-anker-eufy-jackery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-savings-on-popular-accessories-from-anker-eufy-and-jackery.2432226/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 10:32:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/amazon-savings-anker-eufy-jackery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a large collection of discounts from <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Anker</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1721927168527">Eufy</a>, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM_1721927194783">Jackery</a>, including a wide array of wall chargers, Bluetooth trackers, and other USB-C accessories. Some of these deals will require you to clip an on-page coupon then head to the checkout screen before you see the final sale price, and some require a Prime membership.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/new-anker-jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946517" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Eufy's main discount is on the SmartTrack Link 4 Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1721927231278"><strong>&#36;48.99</strong></a> with a Prime membership, down from &#36;69.99. This tracking accessory is compatible with Apple's Find My app, so you can get left behind notifications and many other Find My features when you add it to the app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1721927231278"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;21 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Link 4 Pack for &#36;48.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Switching to the Anker deals, you can get the 24,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09VPHVT2Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3Y9TDY9TTSHK%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3Y9TDY9TTSHK_1719241374306"><strong>&#36;109.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.99. If you need a bigger battery, you can get the Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324"><strong>&#36;104.99</strong></a> with a Prime membership, down from &#36;149.99. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;45 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;104.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, for the Jackery deals you'll find an array of portable power stations on sale this week, including the Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM_1721927194783"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a> with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.99. This is a miniature-sized portable power station that can fit in the palm of your hand and weighs just 2.13 lbs, while featuring a 31,000 mAh capacity and 128W output.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1721927434960">SmartTrack Link 2 Pack</a> - &#36;29.88, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1721927483999">SmartTrack Link 4 Pack</a> - &#36;48.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;69.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM_1720797135027">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;199.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.RBRZCEOCA88O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.RBRZCEOCA88O_1720797474320">Solar Generator 240 with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB083KBKJ8Q%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_title">Explorer 1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;549.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3N2AT8FS2RCU5%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3N2AT8FS2RCU5_1720797246445">Explorer 1000 Power Station V2</a> - &#36;599.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NIEM436WQUAO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NIEM436WQUAO_1720797439732">Explorer 2000 PRO Power Station</a> - &#36;999.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1717512037932">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;35.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;149.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;79.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1717513024737">MagGo 3-in-1 Folding Charging Station</a> - &#36;87.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;104.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 for Prime members, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;49.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;45.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/amazon-savings-anker-eufy-jackery/">Amazon Introduces Big Savings on Popular Accessories From Anker, Eufy, and Jackery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-savings-on-popular-accessories-from-anker-eufy-and-jackery.2432226/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Apple Lab in China to Test Products Under Extreme Conditions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/new-apple-lab-in-china-to-test-products/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-lab-in-china-to-test-products-under-extreme-conditions.2432215/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:22:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/new-apple-lab-in-china-to-test-products/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Jeff Williams</category>
		<category>Apple Research</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is set to open a new applied research lab in Shenzhen, China, focusing on enhancing the quality and reliability of its flagship products (via <a href="https://x.com/szdaily1/status/1816308232463474990"><em>Shenzhen Daily</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/apple-china-iphone-factory.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-844992" /><br/>
<br/>
The new lab in Shenzhen is expected to boost Apple's research capabilities, focusing on reliability and quality testing for key products. The new facility will focus on testing new materials and production techniques, ensuring that products such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> can withstand extreme conditions, from intense physical activity to harsh temperatures. The lab's readiness comes at a crucial time as Apple ramps up production for its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, which is widely expected to launch in the fall.<br/>
<br/>
The choice of Shenzhen is significant due to its proximity to many of Apple's suppliers. Apple first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-to-expand-research-facilities-in-china/">announced plans</a> for the new lab in March. Despite diversifying its production capacity to other countries like Vietnam and India, China remains a key manufacturing hub for Apple. The new Shenzhen facility is part of a broader expansion, which includes research and development centers in Beijing, Shanghai, and Suzhou. Apple has invested over 1 billion yuan (approximately &#36;138 million) in these facilities. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-07-23/apple-and-micron-leaders-visit-china-as-us-ramps-up-chip-curbs"><em>Bloomberg</em> reports</a> that Apple's Chief Operating Officer, Jeff Williams, recently visited Shenzhen to discuss investment and collaboration plans. He <a href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3271741/apple-coo-meets-shenzhen-official-discuss-supply-chain-ahead-iphone-16-launch">reportedly</a> emphasized the critical role Shenzhen plays in Apple's market strategy. Williams' visit to China also included meetings with senior Chinese officials in Beijing, a visit to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> in the Wangfujing shopping district, watching a film <a href="https://www.szdaily.com/content/2024-07/25/content_31105020.htm">shot on the iPhone 15 Pro Max</a>, and a meeting with entertainment company Migu, which showcased its app developed for the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-williams/">Jeff Williams</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-research/">Apple Research</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/new-apple-lab-in-china-to-test-products/">New Apple Lab in China to Test Products Under Extreme Conditions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-lab-in-china-to-test-products-under-extreme-conditions.2432215/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads App Gets TweetDeck-Like Ability to Create Dedicated Feeds</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/threads-app-gets-tweetdeck-dedicated-feeds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-app-gets-tweetdeck-like-ability-to-create-dedicated-feeds.2432205/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 03:44:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/threads-app-gets-tweetdeck-dedicated-feeds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Threads is currently rolling out a new way for users of its iOS app to create dedicated feeds based on search results, similar to how it works for Threads on the web.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
When a search is performed, the new option in the app lets users bookmark the search, after which it lives on in the Home tab, alongside the For You and Following feeds.<br/>
<br/>
The feature has been available for a while on the Threads web view for desktop, where users could pin multiple customized columns, similar to the TweetDeck feature that used to be available on Twitter. The new addition for the iOS app is rolling out now, so you will probably want the latest app update installed so that you don't miss out when it arrives in your region.<br/>
<br/>
Threads has been around for over a year now. When it launched back in July 2023, the experience was very barebones, but Meta has worked to add new functionality on a regular basis to put the social network on a more level pegging with X (Twitter). <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="text-post-media" data-text-post-permalink="https://www.threads.net/@mahmoudzitani/post/C90CjFHqy1Z" data-text-post-version="0" id="ig-tp-C90CjFHqy1Z" style=" background:#FFF; border-width: 1px; border-style: solid; border-color: #00000026; border-radius: 16px; max-width:540px; margin: 1px; min-width:270px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"> <a href="https://www.threads.net/@mahmoudzitani/post/C90CjFHqy1Z" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%; font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, sans-serif;" target="_blank"> <div style=" padding: 40px; display: flex; flex-direction: column; align-items: center;"><div style=" display:block; height:32px; width:32px; padding-bottom:20px;"> <svg aria-label="Threads" height="32px" role="img" viewBox="0 0 192 192" width="32px" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"> <path d="M141.537 88.9883C140.71 88.5919 139.87 88.2104 139.019 87.8451C137.537 60.5382 122.616 44.905 97.5619 44.745C97.4484 44.7443 97.3355 44.7443 97.222 44.7443C82.2364 44.7443 69.7731 51.1409 62.102 62.7807L75.881 72.2328C81.6116 63.5383 90.6052 61.6848 97.2286 61.6848C97.3051 61.6848 97.3819 61.6848 97.4576 61.6855C105.707 61.7381 111.932 64.1366 115.961 68.814C118.893 72.2193 120.854 76.925 121.825 82.8638C114.511 81.6207 106.601 81.2385 98.145 81.7233C74.3247 83.0954 59.0111 96.9879 60.0396 116.292C60.5615 126.084 65.4397 134.508 73.775 140.011C80.8224 144.663 89.899 146.938 99.3323 146.423C111.79 145.74 121.563 140.987 128.381 132.296C133.559 125.696 136.834 117.143 138.28 106.366C144.217 109.949 148.617 114.664 151.047 120.332C155.179 129.967 155.42 145.8 142.501 158.708C131.182 170.016 117.576 174.908 97.0135 175.059C74.2042 174.89 56.9538 167.575 45.7381 153.317C35.2355 139.966 29.8077 120.682 29.6052 96C29.8077 71.3178 35.2355 52.0336 45.7381 38.6827C56.9538 24.4249 74.2039 17.11 97.0132 16.9405C119.988 17.1113 137.539 24.4614 149.184 38.788C154.894 45.8136 159.199 54.6488 162.037 64.9503L178.184 60.6422C174.744 47.9622 169.331 37.0357 161.965 27.974C147.036 9.60668 125.202 0.195148 97.0695 0H96.9569C68.8816 0.19447 47.2921 9.6418 32.7883 28.0793C19.8819 44.4864 13.2244 67.3157 13.0007 95.9325L13 96L13.0007 96.0675C13.2244 124.684 19.8819 147.514 32.7883 163.921C47.2921 182.358 68.8816 191.806 96.9569 192H97.0695C122.03 191.827 139.624 185.292 154.118 170.811C173.081 151.866 172.51 128.119 166.26 113.541C161.776 103.087 153.227 94.5962 141.537 88.9883ZM98.4405 129.507C88.0005 130.095 77.1544 125.409 76.6196 115.372C76.2232 107.93 81.9158 99.626 99.0812 98.6368C101.047 98.5234 102.976 98.468 104.871 98.468C111.106 98.468 116.939 99.0737 122.242 100.233C120.264 124.935 108.662 128.946 98.4405 129.507Z" /></svg></div> <div style=" font-size: 15px; line-height: 21px; color: #999999; font-weight: 400; padding-bottom: 4px; "> Post by @mahmoudzitani</div> <div style=" font-size: 15px; line-height: 21px; color: #000000; font-weight: 600; "> View on Threads</div></div></a></blockquote><br/>
<script async src="https://www.threads.net/embed.js"></script></div><br/>
It has since gained a web app, the ability to search for posts chronologically, a post editing feature, built-in translation, fediverse integration, fast account switching, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The gradual trickle of new features appears to be paying off: The app now has more than <a href="https://www.threads.net/@zuck/post/C89oeSORn81">175 million active monthly users</a>, according to Meta chief Mark Zuckerberg.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/threads-app-gets-tweetdeck-dedicated-feeds/">Threads App Gets TweetDeck-Like Ability to Create Dedicated Feeds</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-app-gets-tweetdeck-like-ability-to-create-dedicated-feeds.2432205/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Auto-Populate iPhone Home Screen With Your Most Used Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/siri-suggested-apps-widget-home-screen/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/auto-populate-iphone-home-screen-with-your-most-used-apps.2432201/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 02:51:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/siri-suggested-apps-widget-home-screen&#038;post_date=1721911890/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Do you find yourself frequently scrolling through multiple Home Screen pages on your iPhone to get to the apps you access most often? If so, chances are you've already filled up the first page with some of your favorite apps. But what if you could automatically make all of your most-used apps appear on page one? With the Siri Suggestions widget, you can.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/siri-suggested-apps-iphone-home-screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959800" /><br/>
The Siri Suggestions widget intelligently recommends apps based on your usage patterns. By populating your Home Screen with multiple instances of this widget, you can ensure that the apps you need most are always just a tap away. Read on to learn how it's done.<br/>
<ol><br/>
    <li>With your iPhone unlocked, swipe to a Home Screen page with at least two free rows available.</li><br/>
    <li>Press and hold the empty space on the Home Screen until the apps start to jiggle.</li><br/>
    <li>Tap the "<strong>+</strong>" button in the top-left corner of the screen to access the widget gallery.</li><br/>
    <li>Search for "Siri Suggestions" in the widget gallery or scroll through the list to find it.</li><br/>
    <li>Tap the Siri Suggestions widget option, then choose the first option showing two rows of apps by tapping <strong>Add Widget</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/1siri-suggested-apps-home-screen.jpg" alt="siri suggestions" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959818" /><br/>
    <li>Drag the widget to a fresh new page containing no other apps.</li><br/>
    <li>Add another instance of the Siri Suggestions widget by tapping the "+" button in the top-left corner of the screen again, then selecting it in the widget gallery, just like you did for the first one.</li><br/>
   <li>Add a third Siri Suggestions widget in the same way.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/siri-suggestions-home-screen-apps.jpg" alt="siri suggestions" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959829" /><br/>
    <li>Next, tap the row of dots representing your ‌Home Screen‌ pages.</li><br/>
    <li>In the ‌Home Screen‌ grid that appears, touch and drag the page of widgets you just made and move it so that it's the first Home Screen page (the one you see when you unlock your iPhone). The others will move to make way in response to your drag action.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Done</strong> in the top-right corner of the screen when you're happy with the new arrangement, then tap <strong>Done</strong> again to exit jiggle mode.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/move-home-screen-pages.jpg" alt="Home Screen pages" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959822" /></ol>Don't worry if the widgets first show the same suggested apps as each other – this will correct itself when you swipe away from the page and return to it. That's all there is to it. By following the above steps, you will have quick access to your most-used apps, even if your habits change, ensuring your Home Screen is both dynamic and tailored to your needs.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/siri-suggested-apps-widget-home-screen/">Auto-Populate iPhone Home Screen With Your Most Used Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/auto-populate-iphone-home-screen-with-your-most-used-apps.2432201/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Privacy Team Does Deep Dive Into iOS 18 Privacy Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-privacy-team-interview-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-privacy-team-does-deep-dive-into-ios-18-privacy-features.2432174/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-privacy-team-interview-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's User Privacy Engineering Manager Katie Skinner and Privacy Product Marketing Lead Sandy Parakilas recently sat down with YouTuber Andru Edwards for a wide-ranging discussion on Apple's privacy policies.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Talking Privacy with Apple - Are Your Secrets Safe?" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1YOi0r3vptQ" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Topics covered include Apple's approach to privacy, the ways Apple contends with privacy laws in different countries, and how Apple deals with government requests, plus there's a good deal of information on the new features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Some of what's discussed covers privacy information that Apple has reiterated over and over again, but there are some interesting tidbits on Apple's adoption of ChatGPT, Maps privacy, the Passwords app, and accessory pairing in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
It's a long discussion at almost 45 minutes, but worth it for those who want a bit more insight into Apple's philosophy on privacy.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-privacy-team-interview-ios-18/">Apple&#039;s Privacy Team Does Deep Dive Into iOS 18 Privacy Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-privacy-team-does-deep-dive-into-ios-18-privacy-features.2432174/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>NCAA College Football Teams to Start Using iPads for Video Replay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/ncaa-college-football-ipads-on-sidelines/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ncaa-college-football-teams-to-start-using-ipads-for-video-replay.2432168/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/ncaa-college-football-ipads-on-sidelines/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A trio of NCAA college football conferences, including the <a href="https://espnpressroom.com/us/press-releases/2024/07/the-southeastern-conference-will-bring-ipad-technology-to-sec-football-sidelines-in-2024/">SEC</a>, <a href="https://theacc.com/news/2024/7/15/general-the-atlantic-coast-conference-will-bring-ipad-technology-to-acc-football-sidelines-and-coaches-booths-in-2024.aspx">ACC</a>, and <a href="https://x.com/bigten/status/1815776492523065572">Big Ten</a>, recently announced that coaches and players will use iPads on the sidelines of games for video replay purposes starting in the upcoming 2024 season.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iPad-College-Football.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959975" /><br/>
"We're thrilled the SEC, ACC, and Big Ten are utilizing iPad, as its unique capabilities and versatility make it the ideal solution to support coaches and student-athletes," said Scott Brodrick, an iPad product marketing employee at Apple. "With an unrivaled combination of advanced displays, powerful performance, portability, fast connectivity, all-day battery life and versatile accessories, iPad will let coaches and players make in-game adjustments and empower athletes to compete at the highest level."<br/>
<br/>
The introduction of iPads is a result of upcoming NCAA rule changes that allow for video replay technology to be used on the sidelines of college football games, for the first time. The 2024 season begins on Saturday, August 24.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/ncaa-college-football-ipads-on-sidelines/">NCAA College Football Teams to Start Using iPads for Video Replay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ncaa-college-football-teams-to-start-using-ipads-for-video-replay.2432168/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone SE 4 and Ultra-Thin iPhone 17 to Use Apple&#039;s Own 5G Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-iphone-se-4-thin-iphone-17-apple-5g-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-se-4-and-ultra-thin-iphone-17-to-use-apples-own-5g-chip.2432157/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:19:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-iphone-se-4-thin-iphone-17-apple-5g-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is rumored to have been working on its own 5G modem for iPhones since 2018, but the project has reportedly faced numerous <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/28/apple-5g-modem-failed-qualcomm-remains-supplier/">challenges and delays</a>. At last, however, the project may be finally getting closer to completion.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/5G-Modem-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886940" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1816132182039232624">short article</a> posted on social media platform X today, well-known Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said two iPhone models with an Apple-designed 5G modem will be released in 2025, including a fourth-generation iPhone SE in the first quarter of the year and an all-new, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">ultra-thin iPhone 17 model</a> in the third quarter.<br/>
<br/>
All existing iPhones that are currently sold by Apple are equipped with Qualcomm modems for cellular connectivity. Earlier this year, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/31/apple-extends-qualcomm-modem-licensing-deal/">extended its 5G modem supply agreement with Qualcomm</a> for iPhone launches through 2026, so Apple's transition to its own in-house 5G chips will likely be gradual over multiple years.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/25/apple-intel-acquisition/">acquired the majority of Intel's smartphone modem business</a> in 2019, as part of its efforts to design its own 5G chip. It is unclear if Apple's chip would have any consumer benefits over Qualcomm's modems, but it would reduce Apple's reliance on Qualcomm. In 2017, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/01/20/apple-qualcomm-1-billion-lawsuit/">Apple sued Qualcomm</a> over alleged anticompetitive practices and &#36;1 billion in unpaid royalty rebates. The two companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/16/apple-qualcomm-settlement/">settled the lawsuit</a> in 2019.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-iphone-se-4-thin-iphone-17-apple-5g-chip/">Kuo: iPhone SE 4 and Ultra-Thin iPhone 17 to Use Apple&#039;s Own 5G Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-se-4-and-ultra-thin-iphone-17-to-use-apples-own-5g-chip.2432157/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps Now Available on the Web</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-maps-now-available-on-the-web/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-now-available-on-the-web.2432149/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:08:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-maps-now-available-on-the-web/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/apple-maps-on-the-web-launches-in-beta/">today announced</a> that it has launched <a href="http://beta.maps.apple.com/">an Apple Maps on the web feature</a>, which is available in a public beta capacity. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> for the web works in Safari and other web browsers, allowing users to get directions without having to open up the Maps app. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-maps-on-web.jpg" alt="" width="2496" height="1404" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959915" /><br/>
&zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; on the web works like the &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; app, so users can get driving and walking directions, find places to visit, view ratings and hours, and browse curated Guides. There are also features for ordering food directly from the Maps place card and discovering places to eat, shop, and explore in cities around the world. Apple says that additional options like Look Around will be introduced in the coming months. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; on the web will serve as an alternative to Google Maps, which has long been the most popular web-based mapping option. You can check out &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; on the web <a href="http://beta.maps.apple.com/">on Apple's Maps.Apple.com website</a>. Developers are able to link out to Maps on the web in their apps, so users can get driving directions and see location information.<br/>
<br/>
Maps on the web is available in English at the current time, and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120585">it works with</a> Safari and Chrome on Mac and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Chrome and Edge on Windows PCs. Apple plans to add support for additional languages, browsers, and platforms over time. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-maps-now-available-on-the-web/">Apple Maps Now Available on the Web</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-now-available-on-the-web.2432149/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Features Still Coming in Later iOS 18 Developer Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-intelligence-coming-in-later-ios-18-dev-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-features-still-coming-in-later-ios-18-developer-beta.2432148/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:02:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-intelligence-coming-in-later-ios-18-dev-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/#apple_intelligence">Apple Intelligence</a> is still not available as of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/23/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-4/">fourth developer beta of iOS 18</a> this week, leading some to wonder if the features have been delayed. However, we have confirmed that Apple still plans to add some of the new Apple Intelligence features to an upcoming beta this summer. In other words, developers will be able to test the first Apple Intelligence features at some point before iOS 18 is widely released to the public.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
Given that public betas of iOS are based on developer betas, Apple Intelligence will likely be added in an upcoming iOS 18 public beta version as well.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in mid-June removed the "this summer" timeframe that initially appeared at the bottom of its <a href="https://developer.apple.com/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence page for developers</a>, but as we stated above, there is no change in plans from what Apple announced at WWDC. The features will likely be added before the end of August, ahead of iOS 18 being widely released in September.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features will be available in U.S. English only at launch, and they will require an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max. The features will also be available on Mac and iPad models equipped with an M1 chip or newer.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence will be able to summarize text, prioritize notifications and emails, and generate custom emoji and images, while the technology will also power a smarter version of Siri with richer language understanding, deeper per-app controls, on-screen awareness, and more. Apple said some of the features, along with support for additional languages and software platforms, will be added "over the course of the next year."<br/>
<br/>
Even when iOS 18 is widely released in September, Apple said some of the Apple Intelligence features will still be considered a "preview" for all users. The full rollout of Apple Intelligence on the iPhone is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-powered-siri/">expected to be completed in 2025</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-intelligence-coming-in-later-ios-18-dev-beta/">Apple Intelligence Features Still Coming in Later iOS 18 Developer Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-features-still-coming-in-later-ios-18-developer-beta.2432148/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second macOS Sequoia Public Beta With iPhone Mirroring and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-macos-sequoia-public-beta-with-iphone-mirroring-and-more.2432139/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:06:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> update to its public beta testing group, giving the general public a chance to try out the new operating system's features ahead of its fall launch. The second public beta comes a bit over a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; from the Software Update section of the System Settings app after <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">signing up on Apple's beta testing website</a> and opting into the public beta under the Beta Updates section.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;'s biggest feature is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which is designed to let you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac using your keyboard and mouse. You can see notifications and use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps even when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is tucked away and locked, and later this year, you'll be able to use the feature to drag and drop apps from your Mac to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
Window tiling has been improved to make it easier to get multiple windows on your Mac in a way that works for you, Safari can summarize websites and show you highlights, and the Messages app supports scheduling messages and using the Tapback feature with any emoji.<br/>
<br/>
There's a new Passwords app for managing your passwords, logins, and passkeys, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app has a new design, the Notes app supports audio transcription and summarization, and you can also type in any equation and get it solved automatically.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; supports all of the new Apple Intelligence features that are also coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, offering all kinds of quality of life improvements. Writing tools help you proofread and polish your writing across apps, you can create unique images with Image Playground, and make up your own emoji with Genmoji. &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; includes a Clean Up tool for removing unwanted images, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> will use AI for better language understanding and contextual relevance. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will even be able to consult ChatGPT for complicated queries.<br/>
<br/>
There are a long list of additional features coming to &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">more information available in our dedicated roundup</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta-2/">Apple Releases Second macOS Sequoia Public Beta With iPhone Mirroring and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-macos-sequoia-public-beta-with-iphone-mirroring-and-more.2432139/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2432141/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to give the new features a try ahead of when the software launches this fall. The second beta comes a week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/watchos-11-public-beta/">after the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957264" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-vitals.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; can be downloaded after signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's beta software website</a> and upgrading your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to the public beta version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. You'll need to open up the Watch app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, go to General, select Software Update, and choose the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Public Beta option under Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, Apple added a new Vitals app that can be used to give you a daily overview of your health metrics, letting you know if anything is out of the ordinary. It compares information collected at night like heart rate, sleep, respiratory rate, and oxygen level to your levels over the previous weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Smart Stack has new widgets like Translate and Shazam, plus it's smarter because it is able to suggest widgets based on time, date, location, and daily routine. Interactive widgets let you access app features from the Smart Stack, and it also supports Live Activities.<br/>
<br/>
Training Load is a new way of measuring how the intensity and duration of workouts impact the body over time, with Apple providing an effort level for cardio-based workouts to help you know when to rest and when to push harder.<br/>
<br/>
You can now customize your Activity Ring requirements for different days of the week, and Apple added support for rest days. Taking a break from activity will no longer ruin a streak because you can pause for a day, a week, a month, or more.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include more workout types, Check In for Messages, a revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face, improvements to Double Tap, and more, with additional information <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">available in our watchOS 11 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-releases-watchos-11-public-beta-2/">Apple Releases Second watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2432141/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second tvOS 18 Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-seeds-second-tvos-18-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-tvos-18-public-beta.2432140/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-seeds-second-tvos-18-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second public beta of tvOS 18, giving the general public a chance to try out the new features ahead of the software's fall launch. The second beta comes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-seeds-first-tvos-18-public-beta/">a week after the first</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796083" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-tv-4k-design-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download the tvOS 18 beta by opening up the Settings app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, choosing the Software Updates section under System, and then toggling on the Get Public Beta Updates option. Signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's public beta website</a> is required to get the option to show up.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 isn't as feature rich as some of Apple's other updates, but it brings a new InSight feature to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app. InSight is similar to Amazon X-Ray, providing real-time information about actors, music, and more in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> shows and movies.<br/>
<br/>
The Enhanced Dialogue feature uses computational audio and machine learning to better boost vocal clarity over background noise and music, plus it works with built-in TV speakers, AirPods, and other Bluetooth devices. Subtitles have been tweaked to show up automatically when relevant, such as when the TV is muted.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added new screen savers and made it easier to swap between them, plus there's 21:9 aspect ratio support for projectors and an option for Live Captions during <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 is limited to public beta testers and developers right now, but it will see a public launch this fall.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/apple-seeds-second-tvos-18-public-beta/">Apple Seeds Second tvOS 18 Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-tvos-18-public-beta.2432140/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
