<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 09:02:50 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next Apple Watch Said to Use Material Allowing for Thinner Logic Board</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/next-apple-watch-thinner-logic-board-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-apple-watch-said-to-use-material-allowing-for-thinner-logic-board.2424824/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 09:01:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/next-apple-watch-thinner-logic-board-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At least one next-generation Apple Watch model will start using resin-coated copper, according to supply chain sources cited by <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240422PD225/nanya-pcb-apple-supply-chain-ic-substrate.html">Taiwanese website <em>DigiTimes</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/s9-chip-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1501" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913379" /><br/>
As the name implies, resin-coated copper is a thin layer of copper foil coated with a resin, such as an epoxy. While adoption of this material would offer many benefits for a future Apple Watch's logic board, such as improved durability and water resistance, a key advantage is that it would <a href="https://na.industrial.panasonic.com/products/electronic-materials/lineup/circuit-board-materials/series/133871">allow for a thinner logic board</a>, which in turn would provide additional internal space for other components and sensors in the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Any extra space that can be freed up in the Apple Watch is extremely valuable, as Apple continues to add health features to the device. The next Apple Watch models due later this year are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/apple-watch-2024-health-features/">rumored to feature blood pressure sensing</a>, for example, and Apple is reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/26/apple-watch-blood-glucose-up-to-seven-years-away/">working on non-invasive blood glucose monitoring</a> as a long-term project.<br/>
<br/>
There is still uncertainty surrounding the next Apple Watch lineup, as it is unclear if the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">redesigned "Apple Watch X"</a> will be launching this year or next year. In addition, it was rumored that there <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-3-in-2024-odds-decreasing/">might not be an Apple Watch Ultra 3 this year</a>. A new Apple Watch SE is likely this year if Apple sticks to a two-year refresh cycle for that model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo last year said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/rcc-thinner-circuit-boards-2025/">iPhone 17 Pro models also might adopt resin-coated copper</a> for the logic board next year, so this is a change that might extend to multiple devices in Apple's lineup over the next few years.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/next-apple-watch-thinner-logic-board-rumor/">Next Apple Watch Said to Use Material Allowing for Thinner Logic Board</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-apple-watch-said-to-use-material-allowing-for-thinner-logic-board.2424824/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>12.9-Inch iPad Air No Longer Expected to Feature Mini-LED Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/12-9-inch-ipad-air-will-not-feature-mini-led/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/12-9-inch-ipad-air-no-longer-expected-to-feature-mini-led-display.2424821/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:37:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/12-9-inch-ipad-air-will-not-feature-mini-led/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Mini-LED</category>
		<category>2024 iPad Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> will feature an LCD display like its smaller sibling, according to <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/">Display Supply Chain Consultants</a> CEO and analyst Ross Young.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, Young said that the larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/12-9-inch-ipad-air-mini-led-display-rumor/">would feature a mini-LED display</a> like the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> of the same size. The existing 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is equipped with a standard LCD panel, and the move to mini-LED technology for the 12.9-inch model would have provided increased brightness for HDR content, deeper blacks, lower power consumption, and more. He said the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; would use leftover mini-LED display panels from the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, with the 10.9-inch model sticking with LCDs.<br/>
<br/>
Now, in a <a href="https://x.com/dsccross/status/1783153530678944154?s=46&t=7hGG_t1VNNuDJze42Vj_-w">post to subscribers</a> on X (formerly Twitter), he said that this is no longer expected to be the case due to the panel's high cost, despite confirmation from multiple supply chain sources. As a result, both &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models will feature LCD displays, clearly delineating them from the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, which is expected to move to OLED.<br/>
<br/>
However, Young added that there may be a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> model with a 12.9-inch mini-LED display introduced in the fourth quarter of 2024. Speculatively, the device could be a high-end &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, a low-end &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, or something else entirely. Next-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are expected to be announced at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">Apple's "Let loose" event</a> on May 7.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mini-led/">Mini-LED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/">2024 iPad Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/12-9-inch-ipad-air-will-not-feature-mini-led/">12.9-Inch iPad Air No Longer Expected to Feature Mini-LED Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/12-9-inch-ipad-air-no-longer-expected-to-feature-mini-led-display.2424821/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;100 Off M1 iPad Air, Starting at &#36;499.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/best-buy-100-off-m1-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-100-off-m1-ipad-air-starting-at-499-99.2424817/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:42:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/best-buy-100-off-m1-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy this week has steep &#36;100 discounts on every M1 iPad Air model, with prices starting at <a href="https://howl.me/cl612g8HSNh"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet. These deals follow in the wake of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">announcement</a> of an event coming in May, which is expected to include refreshed iPad Air models with M2 chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ipad-air-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942250" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
As is typical when new product generations are set to launch, we're now seeing prices consistently dip on the outgoing generation of iPad Air. In addition to the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet, Best Buy also has the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cl613joJjPc"><strong>&#36;649.99</strong></a>, as well as both cellular models on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl612g8HSNh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl613joJjPc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;649.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl614WMA722"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (64GB Cellular) for &#36;649.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl615su1AVd"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (256GB Cellular) for &#36;799.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has every color available on sale for every configuration of the fifth generation iPad Air. Across the board, these prices are all solid second-best prices on the iPad Air. If you're a My Best Buy Plus/Total member, you can also save 25 percent on the Logitech Crayon stylus when purchasing an iPad.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/best-buy-100-off-m1-ipad-air/">Best Buy Takes &#36;100 Off M1 iPad Air, Starting at &#36;499.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-100-off-m1-ipad-air-starting-at-499-99.2424817/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Facing Potential US Ban as Congress Passes Bill Requiring Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/tiktok-facing-us-ban-congress-passes-bill/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-facing-potential-us-ban-as-congress-passes-bill-requiring-sale.2424807/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 04:18:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/tiktok-facing-us-ban-congress-passes-bill/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Senate voted on Tuesday to pass a bill that will either ban TikTok from app stores operating in the country or force Chinese company ByteDance to sell the short-form video app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/tiktok-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-752609" /><br/>
The landmark bill has now passed both chambers of Congress, having already been approved by the House of Representatives. President Biden says he will sign the bill into law on Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
Once that happens, TikTok will be banned in the United States if ByteDance does not divest ownership within nine months, with a possible three-month extension to that deadline if a deal is in progress.  China would need to approve any sale, but the Chinese government has already made it clear that it will "<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/23/technology/tiktok-congress-hearing.html">firmly oppose</a>" such a move.<br/>
<br/>
ByteDance is also expected to launch a legal challenge against the bill by arguing that it will deprive the app's 170 million U.S. users of their First Amendment rights protecting freedom of speech.<br/>
<br/>
U.S. lawmakers want TikTok to be sold to a company outside of China over concerns that the Chinese government could force ByteDance to hand over data from users located in the United States. If Beijing made the request, ByteDance would not be able to refuse. There have also been suggestions that Chinese authorities could use TikTok to spread political propaganda.<br/>
<br/>
ByteDance has attempted to alleviate these fears by storing data from U.S. users on servers owned by Oracle, but the White House and lawmakers do not believe that is enough. There are a limited number of companies that would be able to afford TikTok, while most tech giants would likely be prevented from acquiring it due to antitrust concerns.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/tiktok-facing-us-ban-congress-passes-bill/">TikTok Facing Potential US Ban as Congress Passes Bill Requiring Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-facing-potential-us-ban-as-congress-passes-bill-requiring-sale.2424807/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Right to Repair Rules Force Companies to Fix Out-of-Warranty Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/new-eu-right-to-repair-law-devices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-right-to-repair-rules-force-companies-to-fix-out-of-warranty-devices.2424805/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 03:04:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/new-eu-right-to-repair-law-devices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Right to Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The European Commission has waved through <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_24_608">new 'right to repair' legislation</a> that aims to make it easier for consumers to get their broken devices fixed, even if products are out of warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
The EU already requires companies to offer a two-year minimum warranty on common household appliances and electronics, such as smartphones, TVs, washing machines, and vacuum cleaners, but the new rules impose additional requirements.<br/>
<br/>
According to the legislation, if a consumer chooses to have their device repaired under warranty, the warranty must be extended by a year. Consumers may also borrow a device while theirs is being repaired, and if it cannot be fixed, they have the right to opt for a refurbished unit as an alternative.<br/>
<br/>
When a product's warranty expires, companies are still required to repair devices at a "reasonable price," so as not to intentionally discourage consumers from repairing them. Manufacturers will also be prohibited from using "hardware or software related barriers to repair," including preventing the use of second-hand, compatible, and 3D-printed spare parts by independent repairers as long as they conform to EU laws. <br/>
<br/>
Additionally, manufacturers will be unable to refuse to repair a product solely for economic reasons or because it was previously repaired by someone else. Companies will be required to publish information about their repair services, including indicative prices of the most common repairs.<br/>
<blockquote>"Consumers' right to repair products will now become a reality," said <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/press-room/20240419IPR20590/right-to-repair-making-repair-easier-and-more-appealing-to-consumers">European Parliament rapporteur René Repasi</a>. "It will be easier and cheaper to repair instead of purchase new, expensive items. This is a significant achievement for Parliament and its commitment to empower consumers in the fight against climate change. The new legislation extends legal guarantees by 12 months when opting for repair, gives better access to spare parts and ensures easier, cheaper and faster repair."</blockquote>The legislation will come into effect after formal approval by the Council, with the directive set to activate 20 days after its publication. <br/>
<br/>
Europe's <a href="https://repair.eu/news/analysis-of-the-adopted-directive-on-common-rules-promoting-the-repair-of-goods/">Right to Repair group</a> welcomed the legislation, calling it "a step in the right direction," but said "the scope of products covered remains very narrow," and would introduce loopholes. The coalition noted that the rules only cover consumer products, and not anything purchased by businesses or industrial goods. It also criticized the lack of guidance on what constituted a "reasonable price" for spare parts. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is likely to be impacted by the legislation, especially with regard to its controversial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/apple-responds-to-parts-pairing-criticism/">"parts pairing" requirement</a> that prevents third-party replacements of certain device components. Currently, if an iPhone part is replaced with a like-for-like replacement by an unofficial third party, it may not be recognised by the iPhone's system software. The wording of the new EU rules suggests this will no longer be allowed.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile in the U.S., more than two-dozen states are working on individual right-to-repair legislation. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/california-right-to-repair-law/">California's Right to Repair Act</a> will become law this July, requiring manufacturers to make repair materials available for all electronics and appliances that cost &#36;50 or more.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/right-to-repair/">Right to Repair</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/new-eu-right-to-repair-law-devices/">EU Right to Repair Rules Force Companies to Fix Out-of-Warranty Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-right-to-repair-rules-force-companies-to-fix-out-of-warranty-devices.2424805/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M4 Mac Studio: What We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-studio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-mac-studio-what-we-know-so-far.2424785/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:31:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-studio&#038;post_date=1713922303/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac Studio</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>M4 Mac Studio</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to refresh the entire Mac lineup with updated M4 chips starting in late 2024 and continuing into 2025, and that will include a new M4 chip for Apple's mid-tier desktop machine, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Studio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2672" height="1503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946114" /><br/>
<h2 id="m4_chip_rumors">M4 Chip Rumors</h2><br/>
Apple has a lineup of M4 chips in development, including the standard M4, the M4 Pro and M4 Max, and a higher-end version that's codenamed "Hidra." This higher-end chip could be an "Ultra" version that's equivalent to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Ultra, or it might even be something even more powerful.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; lineup, the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra is a chip that is in fact two &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips linked together. There is no M3 Ultra at this time, but the architecture of the M3 Max chip <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/m3-max-chip-hidden-change/">has led to speculation</a> that future Ultra chips might be standalone chips rather than constructed from two Max dies.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 Max seems to lack the UltraFusion interconnect that allowed the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips to function as an Ultra. Because that's missing, it's likely the Ultra chip would have dedicated development with customizations for heavy workloads. Apple could tweak the number of performance and efficiency cores to focus on power, and add more GPU cores.<br/>
<br/>
Current &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; machines use &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chips, so we can expect the M4 models to be equipped with M4 Max and M4 Ultra (or its equivalent) chips. Aside from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>, the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; is the only Apple machine that uses "Ultra" chips.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; is designed for Mac users who have system intensive workflows that require advanced compute and graphics capabilities. There isn't a lot of differentiation between the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; and &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; as of right now, so Apple may be planning for a more powerful M4 Ultra variant for the &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is going all-in on artificial intelligence across its product lineup in the coming months, so the M4 is expected to have a focus on boosting AI and machine learning performance. Rumors suggest there will be an updated Neural Engine with a greater number of cores to handle AI tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="memory_updates">Memory Updates</h3><br/>
The next &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; and &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; could support as much as 500GB of Unified Memory, up from the current 192GB maximum.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_about_the_m3">What About the M3?</h2><br/>
With Apple planning to refresh the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; with M4 chips in 2025, it's not entirely clear as of yet if there will be an M3 refresh this year.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, MacBook Pro, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> lines have been updated with M3 chips, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;, and &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; are still using &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chips. With the M4 refresh already planned, Apple could skip the M3 update for its desktop machines, but it's also possible we'll get an M3 refresh around the middle of the year and a second M4 refresh next year, which would put a year between each update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is testing a version of the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; with an M3 processor, so an update this year and then a second update next year is plausible.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design_changes">Design Changes</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; hasn't had a design update since it was first launched in March 2022, but it hasn't really existed long enough to need a refresh. Apple tends to wait several years before making major changes to Mac hardware, and we are not expecting the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; to get a refreshed look in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
It will likely be closer to 2026 or 2027 before Apple considers updating the design, though it could be even longer. The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; has not seen notable design changes since 2010.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
According <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, the &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; with M4 chip is expected to be released in mid-2025, which would suggest a possible introduction at the 2025 Worldwide Developers Conference.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac-Studio">Mac Studio (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-studio.237">Mac Studio</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-studio/">Apple&#039;s M4 Mac Studio: What We Know So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-mac-studio-what-we-know-so-far.2424785/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;105 Off Apple&#039;s M3 iMacs on Amazon, Starting at &#36;1,199</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/m3-imacs-amazon-105-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-105-off-apples-m3-imacs-on-amazon-starting-at-1-199.2424760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:17:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/m3-imacs-amazon-105-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is back with a big sale on the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JGD9X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">newest 24-inch M3 iMac</a>, including both 256GB and 512GB models. This time around, the deals do not require any sort of coupon in order to see the final discounted price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/iMac-Deals-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-837855" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 8-core GPU/256GB M3 iMac, this model is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JGD9X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> in two colors, down from &#36;1,299.00. Amazon also has the 10-core GPU/256GB M3 iMac on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,409.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. This one is available in four colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JGD9X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-core/256GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/256GB) for &#36;1,409.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KBG3M%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;105 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/512GB) for &#36;1,594.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the 10-core GPU/512GB M3 iMac has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KBG3M%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,594.00</strong></a> in three colors, down from &#36;1,699.00. All of Amazon's deals today are solid second-best prices on the M3 iMac, and right now many of the computers can be delivered as soon as this Friday, April 26 if you have a Prime membership.<br/>
<br/>
Apple launched the M3 iMac back in October 2023, bringing significant speed and efficiency improvements with the upgrade from the M1 to the M3 chip. Otherwise, there are no major design changes to the newest iMac model. Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/m3-imacs-amazon-105-off/">Get Up to &#36;105 Off Apple&#039;s M3 iMacs on Amazon, Starting at &#36;1,199</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-105-off-apples-m3-imacs-on-amazon-starting-at-1-199.2424760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-5-to-developers.2424756/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:06:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.5 update to developers, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-2/">released the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what might be included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.5, and no new features were found in the first two developer betas.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-5-to-developers.2424756/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-5-and-ipados-17-5-to-developers.2424754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:04:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/">released the second betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943813" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
Most of the features that Apple promised would be coming in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have now been released, but iOS 17.5 adds additional app ecosystem changes in the European Union. App developers can offer apps for download on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">directly from their websites</a>, in addition to through app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
There are also code changes that hint at new Apple Pencils and a Battery Health feature for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, with more information on what's new available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-5-beta-features/">iOS 17.5 beta features post</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-5-and-ipados-17-5-to-developers.2424754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of visionOS 1.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-visionos-1-2-to-developers.2424758/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:04:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.2 update to developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The third &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2 beta comes one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-2-to-developers/">release the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may make further improvements to Personas, EyeSight, and other features with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2, but no major new additions were found in the first two betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of visionOS 1.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-visionos-1-2-to-developers.2424758/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-watchos-10-5-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-5-to-developers.2424759/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-watchos-10-5-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.5 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-watchos-10-5-beta-2-to-developers/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.5 update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.5 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what's included in watchOS 10.5, and there were no new features found in the first two beta updates.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-watchos-10-5-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-5-to-developers.2424759/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-tvos-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-5-to-developers.2424757/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-tvos-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.5 to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-tvos-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.5 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.5.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-tvos-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-5-to-developers.2424757/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Cuts Vision Pro Shipments as Demand Falls &#039;Sharply Beyond Expectations&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-cuts-vision-pro-shipments/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cuts-vision-pro-shipments-as-demand-falls-sharply-beyond-expectations.2424752/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:44:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-cuts-vision-pro-shipments/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has dropped the number of Vision Pro units that it plans to ship in 2024, going from an expected 700 to 800k units to just 400k to 450k units, <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple-cuts-2024-2025-vision-pro-shipment-forecasts-unfavorable-to-mr-headset-pancake-and-micro-38796834f930">according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Orange-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929937" /><br/>
Orders have been scaled back before the Vision Pro has launched in markets outside of the United States, which Kuo says is a sign that demand in the U.S. has "fallen sharply beyond expectations." As a result, Apple is expected to take a "conservative view" of headset demand when the Vision Pro launches in additional countries. <br/>
<br/>
Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">previously said</a> that Apple will introduce the Vision Pro in new markets before the June Worldwide Developers Conference, which suggests that we could see it available in additional areas in the next month or so.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expecting Vision Pro shipments to decline year-over-year in 2025 compared to 2024, and the company is said to be "reviewing and adjusting" its headset product roadmap. Kuo does not believe there will be a new Vision Pro model in 2025, an adjustment to a prior report suggesting a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-vision-pro-major-upgrades-unlikely-until-2027/">modified version of the Vision Pro</a> would enter mass production late next year.<br/>
<br/>
In a February report, Kuo said that Apple was working to improve the efficiency of production and supply change management, with little change to the product specifications and user experience. At the time, Kuo estimated that we would not see a Vision Pro with significant updates until 2027.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes that Apple needs to work to address the lack of key applications, price, and comfort without impacting user experience. Poor Vision Pro sales is expected to impact the growth of pancake lenses and the adoption of microOLED display technology in small-sized consumer electronics. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-cuts-vision-pro-shipments/">Apple Cuts Vision Pro Shipments as Demand Falls &#039;Sharply Beyond Expectations&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cuts-vision-pro-shipments-as-demand-falls-sharply-beyond-expectations.2424752/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Finally Plans to Release a Calculator App for iPad Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-finally-plans-to-release-a-calculator-app-for-ipad-later-this-year.2424750/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:08:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is finally planning a Calculator app for the iPad, over 14 years after launching the device, according to a source familiar with the matter. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iPad-And-Calculator-App-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947832" /><br/>
iPadOS 18 will include a built-in Calculator app for all iPad models that are compatible with the software update, which is expected to be unveiled during the opening keynote of Apple's annual developers conference WWDC <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">on June 10</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>AppleInsider</em> last week reported that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macos-15-revamped-calculator-app/">macOS 15 will feature a revamped Calculator app</a> with a resizable window, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">integration with the Notes app</a>, a sidebar that lists recent calculations, and more. While we have not independently confirmed those details, it is possible that the updated Mac app will be based on the new iPad app.<br/>
<br/>
The lack of an official Calculator app on the iPad has been a long-running meme on social media, given it is such a basic tool. In the meantime, iPad users must rely on third-party calculator apps in the App Store, such as PCalc and Calcbot.<br/>
<br/>
In June 2020, Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q2aaCDNjWEg">told tech reviewer Marques Brownlee</a> that the company simply "hadn't gotten around" to releasing a "great" calculator app for the iPad. "That day may come," he added.<br/>
<br/>
The first beta of iPadOS 18 is expected to be released immediately following the WWDC keynote, and the update should be widely released in September.<br/>
<br/>
Now, if only we could get Instagram and WhatsApp for the iPad…<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">Apple Finally Plans to Release a Calculator App for iPad Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-finally-plans-to-release-a-calculator-app-for-ipad-later-this-year.2424750/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Launches Glow 2.0 Apple Watch Sport Band and iPhone Case</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/nomad-glow-watch-band-iphone-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-glow-2-0-apple-watch-sport-band-and-iphone-case.2424749/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/nomad-glow-watch-band-iphone-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nomad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular accessory maker Nomad today announced the launch a second-generation glow in the dark band designed for the Apple Watch, with the new version featuring a much more pronounced glow than before.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nomad-glow-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947538" /><br/>
Nomad says that its <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/sport-band-glow-2">Glow 2.0 Sport Band</a> is three times brighter than the prior-generation version, and it did indeed have a strong and long lasting glow in our testing. In the light, the band is a soft green color, but in the dark, it shifts to a bright, neon green color. Nomad said that it experimented with more than two dozen variations to get the color and glow of the band correct.<br/>
<br/>
To go along with the Glow 2.0 Sport Band, Nomad is also introducing a <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/sport-case-glow-iphone-15-pro-max">Glow Sport Case</a>, which is its first glow in the dark <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> case option. It has the same light green color in the light, and it too turns a neon green to match the band. It is worth noting that glow in the dark products need light exposure, so the intensity and length of the glow depend on the light exposure the watch and case receive during the day.<br/>
<br/>
The Glow 2.0 Sport Band is made from the same FKM fluoroelastomer rubber as Nomad's other Sport Bands, so if you've tried one of those, this is the same general feel. It's thicker and more rigid than Apple's sport band, and the lack of flex makes it a little less comfortable, but it is still overall easy to wear. It is waterproof and sweatproof, so it is ideal for swimming and other activities that involve water. There are holes in the band to keep it from getting too sweaty underneath during heavy activity.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/nomad-glow-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947539" /><br/>
The case is a variation of Nomad's Sport Case, and it is available for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models. The case itself is glossy, but there is adequate grip that keeps it from being easily dropped, and there is a rubber bumper around the sides and the camera. Buttons are made from aluminum and are easy to press, and it does include support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> so it works with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessories.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad says that its Sport Cases are designed to provide 8-foot drop protection, and the rubber bumper does provide quite a bit of extra cushioning to the area around the display. The case is not as thin as Apple's silicone case, but it does seem to offer good protection, and the glow in the dark feature is fun at night. During the day, the case is a pleasant light green.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/sport-band-glow-2">Glow 2.0 Sport Band</a> is priced at &#36;60, while the <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/sport-case-glow-iphone-15-pro-max">Glow Sport Case</a> is priced at &#36;50. Both products can be purchased from the Nomad website starting today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nomad/">Nomad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/nomad-glow-watch-band-iphone-case/">Nomad Launches Glow 2.0 Apple Watch Sport Band and iPhone Case</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-glow-2-0-apple-watch-sport-band-and-iphone-case.2424749/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Event on May 7 Has Six Artistic Logos as Tim Cook Hints at New Apple Pencil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-has-six-artistic-logos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-on-may-7-has-six-artistic-logos-as-tim-cook-hints-at-new-apple-pencil.2424743/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:05:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-has-six-artistic-logos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>May 2024 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is promoting its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">upcoming "Let loose" event</a> using six artistic logos amid the expectation that a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> is to be announced.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/5.7.24-Logos-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2925" height="1646" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-947814" /><br/>
The six different logos cycle through randomly upon refreshing <a href="https://www.apple.com">Apple's homepage</a>. In 2018, Apple promoted its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2018-event/">"There's more in the making" event</a> that saw the introduction of the radically <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/10/30/apple-new-ipad-pro-models/">redesigned iPad Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/10/30/apple-announces-new-apple-pencil/">second-generation Apple Pencil</a> using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/10/24/all-the-apple-logos/">more than 350 one-of-a-kind Apple logos</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The artistic logos likely allude to the illustration and graphic design capabilities of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, both of which are expected to receive a substantial hardware refresh at the event. The main artwork being used to promote the event features the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; and Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> today hinted at the importance of the accessory to the event in a new post on X (formerly Twitter):<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Pencil us in for May 7! &#x270f;&#xfe0f; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AppleEvent?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AppleEvent</a> <a href="https://t.co/1tvyB7h450">pic.twitter.com/1tvyB7h450</a></p>&mdash; Tim Cook (@tim_cook) <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook/status/1782785458881302714?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 23, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
Two new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models and a redesigned Magic Keyboard accessory are also expected to be unveiled at the event.<br/>
<br/>
The May 7 Apple event will take place at 7 a.m. Pacific Time (10 a.m. Eastern Time), with a live stream to be available on apple.com and on YouTube. The event invitation did not mention an in-person component, with Apple inviting the media to watch online alongside the general public.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/may-2024-apple-event/">May 2024 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-has-six-artistic-logos/">Apple Event on May 7 Has Six Artistic Logos as Tim Cook Hints at New Apple Pencil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-on-may-7-has-six-artistic-logos-as-tim-cook-hints-at-new-apple-pencil.2424743/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces &#039;Let Loose&#039; Event on May 7 Amid Rumors of New iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-let-loose-event-on-may-7-amid-rumors-of-new-ipads.2424737/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:11:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has announced it will be holding a <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">special event on Tuesday, May 7</a> at 7 a.m. Pacific Time (10 a.m. Eastern Time), with a live stream to be available on Apple.com and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f1J38FlDKxo">on YouTube</a> as usual. The <a href="https://twitter.com/JoannaStern/status/1782772951365894419">event invitation</a> has a tagline of "Let Loose" and shows an artistic render of an Apple Pencil, suggesting that iPads will be a focus of the event.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2O7X1Lkphuo" title="Apple Announces May 7th &#39;Let Loose&#39; iPad Event | New iPads &amp; Accessories!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The event invitation does not mention an in-person component, with Apple inviting the media to watch online alongside the general public.<br/>
<br/>
During the event, Apple is expected to announce new iPad Pro and iPad Air models, along with updated Apple Pencil and Magic Keyboard accessories.<br/>
<br/>
Here is everything that has been rumored:<ul><li>Two new iPad Pro models with the M3 chip, OLED displays, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/">thinner enclosure</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-models-thinner-bezels-rumor/">thinner bezels</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-to-gain-matte-option/">matte screen option</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape-oriented front camera</a>, other design changes, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">possibly MagSafe wireless charging</a>.</li><br/>
<li>Two new iPad Air models with the M2 chip and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape-oriented front camera</a>, including a first-ever 12.9-inch iPad Air <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/12-9-inch-ipad-air-mini-led-display-rumor/">with a mini-LED display</a>.</li><br/>
<li>A new Magic Keyboard for the iPad Pro with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">aluminum enclosure</a>, larger trackpad, and other design tweaks.</li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ios-17-5-apple-pencil-4-rumor/">new Apple Pencil</a>, which may have a new "squeeze" gesture for certain actions and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-pencil-visionon-support-in-testing/">support visionOS eventually</a>.</li></ul>Apple has not released any new iPads since late 2022, so this event has been a long time coming. The event will take place just over a month before Apple's annual developers conference WWDC, which runs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">from June 10 through June 14</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-event/">Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">Apple Announces &#039;Let Loose&#039; Event on May 7 Amid Rumors of New iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-let-loose-event-on-may-7-amid-rumors-of-new-ipads.2424737/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mophie Launches Juice Pack Battery Cases for iPhone 15 Lineup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/mophie-juice-pack-iphone-15/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mophie-launches-juice-pack-battery-cases-for-iphone-15-lineup.2424736/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/mophie-juice-pack-iphone-15/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Mophie</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mophie today announced the launch of <a href="https://www.zagg.com/mophie/juice-pack/">Juice Pack battery cases</a> that are designed to work with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup. Like Mophie's prior Juice Pack cases, the latest version attaches to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to provide a little extra battery life during daily use.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/mophie-juice-pack.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947521" /><br/>
The case comes apart in two pieces so that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can fit inside, and as the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models have USB-C ports, there is a USB-C charger inside that fits right in to the port. The case also has a USB-C port that can be used for charging the case and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; inside.<br/>
<br/>
Priority goes to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; when charging, so if it's plugged in, it'll charge up first, and then the case itself will also charge. It's a super simple solution for adding extra battery life to your phone on a long day.<br/>
<br/>
The Juice Pack for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max that we tested ahead of launch has a 3,000mAh battery, so it's not able to charge an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to full, but it is about an extra half charge. The 15 and 15 Pro Juice Pack models have a 2,400mAh battery inside because they're smaller, but that also delivers about the same 50 percent battery charge. In my testing, I was able to get about an additional 45 percent battery out of the case once I had drained my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery, so Mophie's estimate seems about right.<br/>
<br/>
Mophie's Juice Pack case is made from a soft-touch material that's pleasant in the hand and it only comes in black. It offers a protective lip around the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s display and camera, and covers all of the buttons and ports for additional protection. There's a bump at the back for the battery, and while the case remains on the slimmer side is not too bulky, it does add some extra weight. <br/>
<br/>
The case is meant to provide protection from a drop of up to six feet, and it feels rugged enough to be able to handle that kind of impact without damage to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Mophie says that the extra battery life provides up to 44 hours of talk time and music playback, or up to 11 hours of video playback.<br/>
<br/>
There's a button on the back to turn the Juice Pack on and off and to check charge level with the four LEDs. It's handy to be able to turn it off to control when you want to use up the extra battery life rather than having it charge automatically, but note that you do need to hold it down for a few seconds to get charging to initiate. Mophie has Juice Pack cases for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, but there is not a model for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus.<br/>
<br/>
The Mophie Juice Pack can be <a href="https://www.zagg.com/mophie/juice-pack/">purchased for &#36;99.95</a> starting today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mophie/">Mophie</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/mophie-juice-pack-iphone-15/">Mophie Launches Juice Pack Battery Cases for iPhone 15 Lineup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mophie-launches-juice-pack-battery-cases-for-iphone-15-lineup.2424736/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Developing Its Own Custom Silicon for AI Servers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-developing-its-own-ai-server-processor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-developing-its-own-custom-silicon-for-ai-servers.2424735/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:55:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-developing-its-own-ai-server-processor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is said to be developing its own AI server processor using TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process, targeting mass production by the second half of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Silicon-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-947754" /><br/>
According to a post by the Weibo user known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a>," Apple has ambitious plans to design its own artificial intelligence server processor. The user, who claims to have 25 years of experience in the integrated circuit industry, including work on Intel's Pentium processors, suggests this processor will be manufactured using TSMC's &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; node.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC is a vital partner for Apple, manufacturing all of its custom silicon chips. The chipmaker's &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; technology is one of the most advanced semiconductor processes available, offering significant improvements in performance and energy efficiency over the previous 5nm and 7nm nodes.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's purported move toward developing a specialist AI server processor is reflective of the company's ongoing strategy to vertically integrate its supply chain. By designing its own server chips, Apple can tailor hardware specifically to its software needs, potentially leading to more powerful and efficient technologies.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could use its own AI processors to enhance the performance of its data centers and future AI tools that rely on the cloud. While Apple is rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/">prioritizing on-device processing</a> for many of its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/">upcoming AI tools</a>, it is inevitable that some operations will have to occur in the cloud. By the time the custom processor could be integrated into operational servers in late 2025, Apple's new AI strategy should be well underway. <br/>
<br/>
The Weibo user has a number of accurate previous claims, including that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 7 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/28/iphone-7-already-rumored-to-be-waterproof/">would be water-resistant</a> and that the standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models would continue using the A15 Bionic chip, with the more advanced A16 chip being exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro models. These predictions were later corroborated by multiple credible sources and proved correct upon the products' release. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-developing-its-own-ai-server-processor/">Apple Reportedly Developing Its Own Custom Silicon for AI Servers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-developing-its-own-custom-silicon-for-ai-servers.2424735/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Launches Redesigned App With Customizable Home Screen For More Personalized Listening</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-launches-redesigned-app-with-customizable-home-screen-for-more-personalized-listening.2424733/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos</a> today unveiled a redesigned Sonos app that is meant to unify an increasingly fragmented streaming market. The app is focused around a customizable home screen that supports more than 100 streaming services, so each user can set up a personalized listening experience.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
The home screen layout can be customized, and it displays the services that each user has set up along with controls for accessing content. There are quick access options for recently played songs, podcasts, and books, along with options to browse libraries and see recommendations from preferred services.<br/>
<br/>
Favorite content and services can be pinned in rows to the home screen, and the rows are rearrangeable and customizable. A built-in always-visible search feature allows users to search for artists, songs, podcasts, audiobooks, and more across all of their preferred streaming apps.<br/>
<br/>
Swiping up from the bottom of the home screen allows for a quick visual overview of everything that's playing on connected devices, and there are tools for groping speakers and adjusting volume across the home.<br/>
<br/>
The new Sonos app will be available globally on mobile and through the web on May 7.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">Sonos Launches Redesigned App With Customizable Home Screen For More Personalized Listening</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-launches-redesigned-app-with-customizable-home-screen-for-more-personalized-listening.2424733/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
