<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 21:03:39 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some iPhone Models Mysteriously Shutting Off at Night</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/iphone-models-turning-off-at-night/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-models-mysteriously-shutting-off-at-night.2407266/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:32:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/iphone-models-turning-off-at-night/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There appears to be a curious phenomenon that is causing some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models to turn off temporarily at night, which can interrupt alarms and other &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/iphone-passcode-green.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886806" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/175dic1/2_different_iphones_alarms_didnt_go_off_this/">thread on Reddit</a>, a user complains that two separate &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; alarms in his home failed to go off. Several other users also chimed in with similar issues, and it turns out that some of the issues could be linked to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; turning off at night. From Reddit:<blockquote>Hijacking top comment. Check your battery settings and see if there is a gap during the night. Yesterday a lot of iPhones turned off for a few hours during the night. In my case the phone turned back on 1 minute before the alarm</blockquote>Some other people noted having to put in their passcodes in the morning, an indication that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; restarted or shut off during the night. <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/10/10/iphone-restart-overnight/">9to5Mac</a></em> highlighted these issues earlier this week, and we've also experienced the problem here at <em>MacRumors</em>, as have <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphones-spontaneously-rebooted-last-night.2407082/">multiple users on the <em>MacRumors</em> forums</a>. From <em>MacRumors</em>:<blockquote>So my iPhone 15 Pro Max with iOS 17.0.3 spontaneously rebooted last night (10. October around 01:00 AM CET). The same happened to 3 of my friends with the same iPhone and same iOS, and to someone else with an iPhone 13 Mini, also on the same iOS.</blockquote>You can tell if your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; turned off at night by opening up the Settings app, navigating to Battery, and checking the charging status over the past 24 hours. If there's a gap, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was turned off for a period of time.<br/>
<br/>
The problem affects <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, but it is also impacting other devices, suggesting that it's something in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>. Not all users are experiencing the shutdown issues, nor does it appear to be happening every night.<br/>
<br/>
It is not yet clear what is going on, and Apple has not commented.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/iphone-models-turning-off-at-night/">Some iPhone Models Mysteriously Shutting Off at Night</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-models-mysteriously-shutting-off-at-night.2407266/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple-Backed Right to Repair Bill Signed Into Law in California</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/california-right-to-repair-law/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-backed-right-to-repair-bill-signed-into-law-in-california.2407256/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 15:12:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/california-right-to-repair-law/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>California</category>
		<category>Right to Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[California this week officially adopted new right to repair legislation, with California Governor Gavin Newsom this week <a href="https://www.gov.ca.gov/2023/10/10/governor-newsom-signs-legislation-10-10-23/">signing SB 244 into law</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895789" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Apple-Self-Service-Repair-Program-iPhone.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The Right to Repair law requires companies to provide customers with the tools to diagnose and repair consumer electronics and appliances. Apple in August sent a letter urging California to adopt the bill, despite the fact that Apple has lobbied against other Right to Repair legislation.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has already launched a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair program</a> for iPhones and Macs, with the repair program providing customers with repair kits, repair manuals, and components for repairs. Apple also has repair programs for independent repair shops, such as the Apple Authorized Service Provider option and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/29/apple-independent-repair-program/">Independent Repair Provider program</a>.<br/>
<br/>
California's law requires service and repair facilities that are not authorized repair providers to disclose whether they're using replacement parts that are not from the device manufacturer, which would prevent Apple repair stores from using non-Apple parts without making that explicitly clear. As legitimate repair parts must come from Apple, the repair law in California is to Apple's benefit.<br/>
<br/>
Manufacturers are also not required to make tools, parts, and documentation available for any component that would disable or override antitheft security measures, which encompasses Apple features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Independent repair shops have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/02/06/apple-independent-repair-shops-contracts/">in the past complained</a> that Apple forces them to sign invasive contracts, and the kits that Apple sells for self-service repair are not much more affordable than simply getting a repair direct from Apple, but California's law does ensure that customers have options other than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
SB 244 requires that Apple and other companies provide components, repair manuals, and other repair information to be available for seven years after the sale of any product that costs more than &#36;99.99. It is applicable to products sold after July 1, 2021.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/california/">California</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/right-to-repair/">Right to Repair</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/california-right-to-repair-law/">Apple-Backed Right to Repair Bill Signed Into Law in California</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-backed-right-to-repair-bill-signed-into-law-in-california.2407256/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>T-Mobile Automatically Upgrading Users to More Expensive Plans, But There&#039;s an Opt-Out Option</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/t-mobile-plan-migration/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-automatically-upgrading-users-to-more-expensive-plans-but-theres-an-opt-out-option.2407252/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 14:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/t-mobile-plan-migration/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile will be forcing customers on older smartphone plans to move to newer, more expensive plans, according to information that has been <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tmobile/comments/174uelk/megathread_forced_plan_migration_for_older_plans/">shared on Reddit</a>. The migration will be automatic, but customers can contact support to ask to opt out of the migration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/t-mobile-logo-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893072" /><br/>
Those who had the prior Magenta and One plans will be upgraded to Go5G, while those on the Magenta 55+ plan will be upgraded to Go5G+. Simple Choice and Select Choice users will be moved to Magenta or Essentials Select.<br/>
<br/>
With these migrations to new plans, customers will see price increases of &#36;5 to &#36;10 per line depending on current plan. Those on the Simple/Select Choice plans, for example, will see a &#36;10 per line price increase.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who miss the notification about the upcoming plan changes can still ask to revert back for a short period, though customer service will attempt to push customers to new plans with one-time credits.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://tmo.report/2023/10/breaking-t-mobile-will-force-customers-onto-newer-plans-unless-you-opt-out/">The Mobile Report</a></em>, customer support representatives will attempt to convince users about the benefits of the new plan. "We are not raising the price of any of your plans; we are moving you to a newer plan with more benefits at a different cost," T-Mobile instructs employees to say.<br/>
<br/>
Customers will begin receiving notifications about the upcoming plan changes on October 17, both through text messages and emails. Migration timing will vary based on bill cycle.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/t-mobile-plan-migration/">T-Mobile Automatically Upgrading Users to More Expensive Plans, But There&#039;s an Opt-Out Option</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-automatically-upgrading-users-to-more-expensive-plans-but-theres-an-opt-out-option.2407252/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Camera Comparison: iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Pixel 8 Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-8-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-8-pro.2407238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:59:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-8-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Google Pixel</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Both Apple and Google came out with new high-end flagship smartphones this autumn, debuting the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max and the Pixel 8 Pro, respectively. As with any expensive smartphone, the cameras in both produce amazing images, but there are some notable differences that can be seen in our comparison video and article.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RdKdQ_bMW4c" title="Camera Comparison: Google Pixel 8 Pro vs iPhone 15 Pro Max" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max has a triple-lens camera system with 48-megapixel Main (wide) camera that can be set to three focal lengths, a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera, and a 12-megapixel Telephoto lens that supports up to 5x optical zoom. The Pixel 8 Pro also has a triple-lens camera system with 50-megapixel Wide camera, a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera, and a 48-megapixel Telephoto camera also with 5x optical zoom.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-3.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916454" /><br/>
The Google and Apple camera systems have similarities in available lenses and technologies like portrait mode, night mode, HDR, and more, but there are different software algorithms that are at work under the hood, and that's what brings in some of the biggest differences that we're seeing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-9.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916455" /><br/>
When it comes to landscape images that show a lot of sky, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max looks more natural. The colors are more accurate and the differences between sky and cloud are more pronounced for an overall better looking image. The Pixel 8 Pro trends toward a more blue tint for sky images, and it also has a tendency to overexpose in some shots. You'll also notice that the Pixel photos tend to be brighter, while the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> photos are downright moody.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-10.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916456" /><br/>
There are definite themes to color temperature, saturation, exposure, and other factors. Several of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max images feel oversaturated compared to the Pixel 8 Pro, with Apple giving deeper blacks and more vibrant colors, while Google's images have a brighter feel with contrast bumped down. In the taxi image, for example, the cars were not that shade of yellow that Apple produced, but both images look good and choosing a favorite will depend on whether you prefer images that are more saturated or brighter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-11.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916457" /><br/>
Apple's 5x Telephoto lens is limited to 12 megapixels and it does not have the wide aperture of the Main lens, so it should not be a surprise that the images that come out of it look different in terms of sharpness and saturation. 5x images from the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max and the Pixel 8 Pro look similar in most instances, but the Pixel 8 Pro seems to have more pronounced textures because the images are brighter with the contrast bumped up a bit more than what we're getting with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-15.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916458" /><br/>
Apple's 5x zoom lens has an edge when it comes to portrait mode because it can capture 5x portraits, while the Pixel is limited to 2x portraits. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; really wins out in terms of background blur, and even in portraits with other lenses, Apple is doing better with color, skin tone, and blur. The Pixel's portrait images sometimes come out better in situations with lower light.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-18.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916459" /><br/>
As for night shots, iPhones have always been a bit ahead in terms of a natural look, and that hasn't changed. The nighttime images from the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are more true to life, while the Pixel 8 Pro is much brighter and doesn't have the same nighttime mood.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-16.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916460" /><br/>
Apple's video stabilization has always been tough to beat, and the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max produces better video than you get with the Pixel 8 Pro. Google has caught up somewhat with its latest smartphones, but Apple remains a step ahead. For pros, Apple also has an option for ProRes Log recording, so you can record a flat image that can be used with custom LUTs in post-processing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-22.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916461" /><br/>
Google has added some fun AI features to its camera that Apple can't compete with. Best Take, for example, sorts through multiple group photos that have been captured and finds the best shot. You can go change each person's face, swapping in from another in the series so that each person is smiling and looking at the camera. Magic Editor lets you erase objects in an image and uses generative AI to fill in the blank spot, and the Audio Magic Eraser can pull out unwanted sounds.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/phone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-27.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916462" /><br/>
Which images do you prefer? &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max or Pixel 8 Pro? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-pixel/">Google Pixel</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-8-pro/">Camera Comparison: iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Pixel 8 Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-8-pro.2407238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Pro With OLED Display Likely Still at Least Three Years Away</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/macbook-pro-oled-three-years-away/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-with-oled-display-likely-still-at-least-three-years-away.2407237/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:43:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/macbook-pro-oled-three-years-away/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's first MacBook Pro models with OLED displays are still at least three years away from launching, according to information shared today by Ross Young, CEO of research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-MacBook-Pro-M2-Feature-Blue-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-881249" /><br/>
On a <a href="https://bloomberg.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_lWrE5XzyQkSCqFzJhqor1w#/registration">display-related webinar</a> with Bloomberg Intelligence's Woo Jin Ho, Young said it will take a few years for Apple's supply chain partners to build out manufacturing lines for mass production of laptop-sized OLED panels, so he does not expect MacBook Pro models with OLED displays to launch until 2026 or 2027. He has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/04/macbook-pro-not-getting-oled-until-2026/">shared this timeframe previously</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to current MacBook Pro models with LCD screens, benefits of OLED technology would include increased brightness, higher contrast ratio with deeper blacks, improved power efficiency for longer battery life, and more.<br/>
<br/>
As widely rumored, Young reiterated that the next-generation iPad Pro models launching in 2024 will also be equipped with OLED displays. The first iPad Air and iPad mini models with OLED displays are not expected to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/oled-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air-2026/">until 2026</a>; accordingly, Young confirmed that these devices will remain equipped with LCD screens next year.<br/>
<br/>
Young has been a dependable source of display-related information for future Apple products for several years, with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">highly-accurate track record</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/macbook-pro-oled-three-years-away/">MacBook Pro With OLED Display Likely Still at Least Three Years Away</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-with-oled-display-likely-still-at-least-three-years-away.2407237/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.1 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-1-to-developers.2407232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:18:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.1 to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-beta-2-to-developers/">second tvOS 17.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can download the tvOS 17.1 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes. tvOS 17.1 adds a new favoriting option to the Music app on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, along with some other minor Music changes.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't often know much about what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release. Apple has also seeded a new beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 17.1 software for developers. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.1 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-1-to-developers.2407232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The 30 Best Apple Deals From Amazon&#039;s October Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/30-best-apple-deals-prime-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-30-best-apple-deals-from-amazons-october-prime-day.2407228/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:52:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/30-best-apple-deals-prime-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2F">Prime Big Deal Days</a> event is coming to a close later today, so we're quickly recapping all of the best Apple-related deals that are still live right now. Shipping on some may be slightly delayed, but all of the products listed below remain at some of the lowest prices we've ever seen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Prime-Big-Deal-Days-Feature-Best-Apple-Discounts.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916310" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You will need an active Amazon Prime subscription to see these deals. You can get <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>one month of Amazon Prime for free</strong></a> when signing up this week, and afterwards the service will renew at &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;139 per year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best Overall Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods 2</a> for &#36;89.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C</a> for &#36;189.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PR4W22%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us0">Beats Studio Pro</a> for &#36;179.00, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch SE</a> for &#36;199.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX4JGWL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> for &#36;749.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">9th Gen iPad</a> for &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">15-inch MacBook Air</a> for &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF_1696870847309">Anker MagSafe 3-in-1 Charger Stand</a> for &#36;112.46, down from &#36;149.95</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The standout deal this season is Apple's new AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case at its new all-time low price of &#36;189.00. Apple Watch shoppers are in luck as well, with the best prices we've ever seen on the Apple Watch SE (2nd gen) and new Apple Watch Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best AirPods and Headphones Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airpods-new-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916420" /><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods 2</a> for &#36;89.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C</a> for &#36;189.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods Max</a> for &#36;479.99, down from &#36;549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Cancelling-Earbuds-Built-Bluetooth-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB096SV8SJG%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Beats Studio Buds</a> for &#36;89.95, down from &#36;149.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09JL41N9C%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us2">Beats Fit Pro</a> for &#36;159.99, down from &#36;199.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PR4W22%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us0">Beats Studio Pro</a> for &#36;179.00, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Along with the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C deal, you'll find sales on AirPods 2 and AirPods Max during Prime Day. We're also tracking a few Beats deals with all-time low prices on Beats Studio Buds, Beats Fit Pro, and Beats Studio Pro. <br/>
<br/>
For the Beats Studio Pro, you can get these brand new headphones for &#36;179.00, which is &#36;170 off their regular price and the best price we've ever seen. They're available in all four colors at this price tag.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><h2>Best Apple Watch Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-watch-se-new-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916419" /><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS)</a> for &#36;199.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS)</a> for &#36;229.00, down from &#36;279.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX4JGWL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> for &#36;749.00, down from &#36;799.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The best Apple Watch deals this season focus on the Apple Watch SE and the Apple Watch Ultra 2, both of which have hit record low prices during Prime Day. For the Apple Watch SE, you'll find discounts on both Wi-Fi and cellular models, so be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-se/">full article on Apple Watch SE deals</a> for even more details.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><h2>Best MacBook Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/macbook-air-new-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916418" /><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">13-inch MacBook Air (M1, 256GB)</a> for &#36;749.99, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5HNXJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">13-inch MacBook Pro (M2, 256GB)</a> for &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">15-inch MacBook Air (M2, 256GB)</a> for &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">15-inch MacBook Air (M2, 512GB)</a> for &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
MacBook Pro and MacBook Air deals are abundant this Prime Day, with the standout sale focused on the new 15-inch MacBook Air. You can get both the 256GB and 512GB models for &#36;250 off and all-time low prices on Amazon. If you're buying for someone who doesn't need the latest and greatest computer, the 13-inch M1 MacBook Air at &#36;749.99 remains one of the best deals in 2023 on an Apple notebook.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><h2>Best iPad Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-new-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916417" /><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">9th Gen iPad</a> for &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">10th Gen iPad</a> for &#36;399.00, down from &#36;449.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">iPad mini 6</a> for &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3JJT5D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">iPad Air</a> for &#36;499.99, down from &#36;599.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
In terms of the best iPad deals, you'll find record low prices on Apple's 9th and 10th generation iPads, priced at &#36;249.00 and &#36;399.00, respectively. The 9th generation device is a great entry-level tablet for anyone looking for a simple internet browsing device who doesn't need the faster A14 Bionic chip and redesigned format of the 10th generation iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><h2>Best Tech Accessory Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-new-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916416" /><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK6DDL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1696871001262">Anker Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;22.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1696871510134">Anker 67W USB-C 3-Port Wall Charger</a> for &#36;37.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C5QY4BL2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1696871892175">Anker USB-C 6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> for &#36;52.79, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09SG31NPT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1696871339620">Anker 100W Compact Power Strip (2x Outlets, 2x USB-A, 2x USB-C)</a> for &#36;63.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSGH355C%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1696870924260">Anker USB-C 6-in-1 Compact Power Strip</a> for &#36;76.99, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1696871558769">Anker 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> for &#36;89.99, down form &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF_1696870847309">Anker MagSafe 3-in-1 Charger Stand</a> for &#36;112.46, down from &#36;149.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVBGWBT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.35NYJJ20QKEV8%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.35NYJJ20QKEV8_1696430004527">Jackery Explorer 1000</a> for &#36;899.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TKZ7KS4%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1WO8T7NJKVON3%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1WO8T7NJKVON3_1696429932221">Jackery Solar Generator 1000</a> - &#36;889.00, down from &#36;1,289.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
There are many Apple-related tech accessory discounts happening during Prime Day in October. We've highlighted the best above, including the Anker MagSafe 3-in-1 Charger Stand for &#36;112.46, which is &#36;38 off of this brand new accessory that can simultaneously charge your iPhone, Apple Watch, and AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
Otherwise, you'll find great USB-C accessories for your new iPhone 15 and portable power stations from Jackery. If you want an extensive look at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-tech-accessories/">tech accessory deals during Prime Day</a>, be sure to check out our full article.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1HY9ZNVDCHPZF_1696870847309"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;38 OFF</div>Anker MagSafe 3-in-1 Charger Stand for &#36;112.46</div></a></div><h2>Best Apple Accessory Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airtag-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916415" /><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirTag 4-Pack</a> for &#36;88.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">MagSafe Charger</a> - &#36;33.00, down from &#36;39.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB099BWY7WT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">MagSafe Battery Pack</a> - &#36;83.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08MWR2NXZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">MagSafe Duo Charger</a> - &#36;108.99, down from &#36;129.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple's MagSafe accessories and AirTags haven't seen as steep discounts as previous sale events earlier in 2023, but you can still find decent deals during Prime Day. The AirTag 4-Pack at &#36;88.99 is a good second-best price for the tracking accessory, and the MagSafe Charger at &#36;33.00 is just about &#36;3 higher than its most common sale price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;88.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We will continue to track Prime Day deals as the event continues, so be sure to keep an eye on our front page for more news. We'll also be regularly updating this article as prices have been fluctuating and several products have gone in and out of stock throughout the event. Remember that you can <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>sign up for Amazon Prime for free for one month</strong></a> to take advantage of the deals.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/30-best-apple-deals-prime-day/">The 30 Best Apple Deals From Amazon&#039;s October Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-30-best-apple-deals-from-amazons-october-prime-day.2407228/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares 1.5-Hour &#039;Study With Me&#039; Guided Session</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-study-with-me-session/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-1-5-hour-study-with-me-guided-session.2407221/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:13:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-study-with-me-session/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a new "Study With Me" Mac-focused video on its YouTube channel, providing a 1.5-hour guided study session for Apple device users.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Study With Me feat. Storm Reid x Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ti6r17_TWf4" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Hosted by Storm Reid, Euphoria actress and University of Southern California student, the video uses the Pomodoro technique for three 25-minute study sessions with three five minute breaks.<blockquote>90-minute Study With Me video featuring Storm Reid that's designed to keep you focused on studying and away from distractions. Storm uses the Pomodoro technique, with three 25-minute study sessions followed by fun 5-minute breaks that you can follow along with or use as inspiration for your own break time. She studies using the MacBook Air 15", chill lo-fi music to stay focused, and some of her favorite relaxation techniques.</blockquote>The video has a series of lo-fi songs provided by Platoon Beats, which users can listen to while they work. The video is meant to highlight the 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, which is the machine that Storm is using in the video. Apple promotes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, multitasking capabilities, and 18-hour battery life.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-study-with-me-session/">Apple Shares 1.5-Hour &#039;Study With Me&#039; Guided Session</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-1-5-hour-study-with-me-guided-session.2407221/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Planning to Bring OLED to iPad Mini and iPad Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air.2407197/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:56:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Naver</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to bring OLED displays to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, according to a post on the Korean social media site Naver from a user with a track record for posting Apple rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/OLED-iPad-Air.jpg" alt="" width="2363" height="1329" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-806474" /><br/>
The <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223232907661&navType=by">post</a> cites supply chain sources and claims that Apple has now begun negotiations with Chinese suppliers, as well as Samsung and LG, related to OLED displays for future &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models. Apple reportedly seeks for the components to be mass produced from the end of 2025, suggesting that launch could follow in early 2026.<br/>
<br/>
The information lines up with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/oled-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air-2026/">report</a> from technology research firm Omdia that was published earlier this week, which forecasted Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> display panel purchase plans. The potential transition to OLED on Apple's two mid-range tablets is said to be part of its OLED strategy from 2026 onwards.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has apparently not yet fully committed to bringing the more advanced display technology to its mid-range tablets, and may be planning to review how the market responds to the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models that feature OLED displays, which are expected to launch next year, before locking in new panels for the 2026 &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The report also corroborated details about the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">iPad Pro models with OLED displays</a> that are widely anticipated to launch next year, with the panels due to be supplied by LG and Samsung. Apple was said to be seeking more suppliers for OLED displays designed for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, which aligns with the Naver post's mention of additional Chinese suppliers.<br/>
<br/>
Reports suggest that the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and sixth-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which are expected to launch relatively soon, will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/new-ipad-air-reportedly-in-development/">minor specification upgrades</a> that focus on newer processors, rather than major updates <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ipad-mini-7-no-promotion-display/">like more advanced display technology</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/naver/">Naver</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/">Apple Reportedly Planning to Bring OLED to iPad Mini and iPad Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air.2407197/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Pays Apple &#36;18B to &#36;20B a Year to Be Default iOS Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-pays-apple-18b-to-20b-a-year-to-be-default-ios-search-engine.2407183/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 03:10:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's widely known that Apple and Google have a considerable monetary agreement that ensures Google's position as the default search engine on Apple's iOS devices, but neither company reveals the amounts involved. In 2021, financial advisor Bernstein <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/27/google-could-pay-apple-15-billion-default-search/">suggested</a> Google was paying Apple as much as &#36;10 billion a year to maintain the status quo. However, in a new investor note, the analyst claims Google's payment to Apple is now between &#36;18 billion and &#36;20 billion. <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/safari-google-search.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916340" /><br/>
First reported by <em><a href="https://www.theregister.com/2023/10/10/google_pays_apple_18_20_claims_bernstein/">The Register</a></em>, Bernstein published a report assessing the potential implications for Apple of the US government's ongoing antitrust trial against Google, with the Department of Justice considering Google's Information Services Agreement (ISA) with Apple as evidence that it has a search engine monopoly.<br/>
<blockquote>"We believe there is a possibility that federal courts rule against Google and force it to terminate its search deal with Apple," said Bernstein in the report seen by The Register. "We estimate that the ISA is worth &#36;18B-20B in annual payments from Google to Apple, accounting for 14-16 percent of Apple's annual operating profits."</blockquote>Bernstein says Google pays out 22 percent of total ad revenue under its traffic acquisition costs (TAC) and estimates Apple likely receives around 40 percent of this. Bernstein bases its numbers on Apple's public filings as well as a bottom-up analysis of Google's traffic acquisition costs. The DoJ has said in the trial that it thinks Apple receives around &#36;10 billion from the ISA with Google, although its information comes from external sources.<br/>
<blockquote>"Importantly, Google is on trial, not Apple, and Apple could (in theory) partner with another search engine to be the default (and/or retain the agreement with Google outside the US)," the report states. "One more likely scenario is that Apple offers a choice screen. We note that Apple controls access to its installed base, which generates ~&#36;60B + in advertising revenues, and accordingly, we believe that Apple would continue to command a commission (in the 25-30 percent range) for providing access to those search advertising revenues.<br/>
<br/>
"Moreover, introduction of a choice screen could offer Apple the opportunity to potentially launch its own search engine as an option  something it could likely not do today without raising the eyebrows of regulators," the Bernstein report adds.</blockquote>Last month, the trial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/microsoft-bing-acquisition-talks/">revealed</a> that Microsoft considered selling its Bing search engine to Apple. Had the acquisition happened, Bing would have replaced Google as the default search engine on Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
Experts say there is a chance Google could lose the case, which would put Apple's lucrative agreement, which has been in place for a decade, in significant jeopardy. However, a ruling in the case isn't expected before next year, and the likelihood is that proceedings will be extended by the lengthy appeals process.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/">Google Pays Apple &#36;18B to &#36;20B a Year to Be Default iOS Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-pays-apple-18b-to-20b-a-year-to-be-default-ios-search-engine.2407183/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Bringing Online Store to Chile on October 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-bringing-online-store-to-chile-on-october-16.2407177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 02:28:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Chile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/">announced</a> that it plans to open an online store in Chile on Monday, October 16, providing customers located in the country with a way to purchase iPhones, Macs, iPads, and more directly from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/chile-online-store-opening-announcement.jpg" alt="" width="1291" height="760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916336" /><br/>
As in other countries, Apple's Chilean online store will offer a full range of Apple products and accessories, with shopping assistance from Apple Specialists, a trade-in program for iPhone sales, free one-on-one online training sessions with certain product purchases, build-to-order Mac options, and multiple payment options including financing.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, customers in Chile can only purchase Apple products through third-party Apple Authorized Distributors. The Apple online store will allow customers from all regions of Chile to purchase from Apple directly and have their orders shipped for free to all regions in the country. <br/>
<br/>
To celebrate the opening, Apple has made special Chile flyer wallpapers for the <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/i/banner-download/iPhone_Wallpaper.png">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/i/banner-download/iPad_Wallpaper.png">iPad</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/i/banner-download/Mac_Wallpaper.png">Mac</a> available to download on its website.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chile/">Chile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/">Apple Bringing Online Store to Chile on October 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-bringing-online-store-to-chile-on-october-16.2407177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Qualcomm to Take on Apple Silicon Chips With Snapdragon X Series for PCs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/qualcomm-to-take-on-apple-silicon-chips-with-snapdragon-x-series-for-pcs.2407143/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 16:49:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Qualcomm <a href="https://www.qualcomm.com/news/onq/2023/10/introducing-our-next-gen-intelligent-pc-platforms-the-snapdragon-x-series">today outlined</a> its plans for its next-generation chips designed for PCs. The Snapdragon X series is set to come out in 2024, and Qualcomm claims that it will mark an "inflection point for the PC industry" thanks to the "next-level performance" brought by the new chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x.jpg" alt="" width="1790" height="1007" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916314" /><br/>
Snapdragon X chips will use the Qualcomm Oryon CPU, which is built on the chip technology that it got <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/13/qualcomm-to-acquire-chip-startup-nuvia/">when it purchased Nuvia</a>. Founded by ex-Apple chip designers, Nuvia designed custom Arm-based chips that are expected to bring Apple silicon-like performance to PCs with improved power and efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to improved efficiency, Qualcomm's upcoming PC chips include on-device AI processing and 5G connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/10/23911431/qualcomm-snapdragon-x-platform-oryon-cpu-windows-pc-apple-silicon">The Verge</a></em>, Arm has sued Qualcomm and Nuvia for violating the licensing agreements for Arm processor designs and architecture. Arm claims that licenses provided to Nuvia are not valid now that the company has been sold to Qualcomm.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x/">Qualcomm to Take on Apple Silicon Chips With Snapdragon X Series for PCs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/qualcomm-to-take-on-apple-silicon-chips-with-snapdragon-x-series-for-pcs.2407143/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Continues to Be Most Popular Smartphone Among Teens, Apple Watch Ownership Growing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/iphone-teen-survey-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-continues-to-be-most-popular-smartphone-among-teens-apple-watch-ownership-growing.2407139/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 16:20:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/iphone-teen-survey-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Teen Survey</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> continues to be the most popular smartphone among teens, according to data shared today by investment firm Piper Sandler in its <a href="https://www.pipersandler.com/teens">biannual teen survey</a>. 87 percent of teens surveyed own an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, while 88 percent expect the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to be their next phone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915641" /><br/>
Teen &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; ownership numbers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/11/teen-survey-iphone-ownership/">have not shifted</a> since last year, but over the last decade, interest in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; among teenagers has soared. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2013/10/08/ipad-and-iphone-usage-remains-strong-among-u-s-teenagers/">Back in October 2013</a>, 55 percent of teenagers reported owning an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, while 24 percent had an Android device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/teen-iphone-ownership-2023.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1037" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916329" /><br/>
Apple Watch ownership is also growing, albeit more slowly. 34 percent of teens surveyed own an Apple Watch, up from 31 percent last year. 10 percent of teens said they plan to buy an Apple Watch in the next six months, down from 16 percent in fall 2022. Apple was the favorite watch brand, beating out Rolex, Casio, Garmin, and Cartier.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> was the top payment app for teens, with 42 percent reporting using the service in the last month. &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; beat out Cash App (27 percent), Venmo (20 percent), and PayPal (10 percent).<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not dominate in the streaming music category, coming second to Spotify. 70 percent of teens surveyed said they use Spotify as their music service, while just over 30 percent use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>. 46 percent of teens that pay for a service pay for Spotify, while just 30 percent pay for &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Piper Sandler has also been asking teens about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Private Relay, and usage has jumped in the second half of 2023. 37 percent of teens said they use &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay, while another 17 percent said they're interested in using it in the next six months. Earlier this year, just 24 percent of teens were using &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay, which does require an &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; subscription fee.<br/>
<br/>
Teen surveys are conducted twice per year, with Piper Sandler putting out these reports for over 10 years. For this fall's report, 9,193 teens with an average age of 15.7 were surveyed across 49 states.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teen-survey/">Teen Survey</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/iphone-teen-survey-2023/">iPhone Continues to Be Most Popular Smartphone Among Teens, Apple Watch Ownership Growing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-continues-to-be-most-popular-smartphone-among-teens-apple-watch-ownership-growing.2407139/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Adobe Highlights New Generative AI Features for Photoshop and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/adobe-generative-ai-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-highlights-new-generative-ai-features-for-photoshop-and-more.2407137/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 15:31:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/adobe-generative-ai-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Adobe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At its annual MAX conference, Adobe today provided <a href="https://news.adobe.com/news/news-details/2023/Adobe-Releases-Next-Generation-of-Firefly-Models/default.aspx">insight into its plans</a> for generative AI technology in Photoshop, Illustrator, and other popular design apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/adobe-generative-fill-photoshop.jpg" alt="" width="1300" height="713" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916320" /><br/>
Adobe has iterated on Firefly, its AI image generation model, with the Firefly Image 2 Model. Improved Text to Image capabilities can be used on the <a href="https://www.adobe.com/sensei/generative-ai/firefly.html">Firefly web app</a>, and a Generative Match option lets users generate content in user-specified styles. Photo Settings allows for photography-style image adjustments, and Prompt Guidance helps users refine their suggestions for better end results.<br/>
<br/>
As for quality, Firefly Image renders better skin, hair, eyes, hands, and body structure, plus it offers better colors and improved dynamic range. The generative AI model is used for generative fill in Adobe Photoshop, allowing users to add, expand, and remove content with text prompts.<br/>
<br/>
There's now a Firefly Vector Model, which Adobe says is the world's first generative AI model for creating vector graphics. Integrated into Adobe Illustrator, Firefly Vector Model can be used to create all manner of vector graphics, including logos, website designs, and product packaging.<br/>
<br/>
According to Adobe, the Firefly Vector Model can create "human quality" vector and pattern outputs with a Text to Vector graphic feature. Generated graphics are organized into groups and fully editable, with options to match an artboard's existing style.<br/>
<br/>
Adobe Express also has a new Firefly Design model for generating templates for social media posts and marketing assets. Firefly Design Model can generate templates in popular aspect ratios that are editable in Express.<br/>
<br/>
More information about Adobe's new AI features can be <a href="https://www.adobe.com/">found on the Adobe website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/adobe/">Adobe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/adobe-generative-ai-features/">Adobe Highlights New Generative AI Features for Photoshop and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-highlights-new-generative-ai-features-for-photoshop-and-more.2407137/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Beta 3 Prevents Action Button From Activating the Camera or Flashlight in a Pocket</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-beta-3-prevents-action-button-from-activating-the-camera-or-flashlight-in-a-pocket.2407118/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:32:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the third beta of iOS 17.1 tweaked the functionality of the Action Button to prevent certain actions from being triggered while the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is in a pocket or a bag. The Camera, Flashlight, Voice Memo, Focus, and Magnifier functions will no longer activate when the Action Button is pressed if the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is tucked away in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-action-button-settings.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1624" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910653" /><br/>
Actions that make sense to trigger in a pocket like the mute function and a shortcut can still be activated while the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is inside of a pocket by long pressing on the Action Button, but other features are disabled.<br/>
<br/>
In earlier versions of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and iOS 17.1, all of the Action Button functions can be accidentally activated in a pocket, draining &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery and causing unwanted recordings and images.<br/>
<br/>
Though the Action Button requires a long press to activate, there have still been complaints about it triggering unintentionally while in a pocket, which this change will prevent for functions that cannot be used when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
Note that these changes apply only to the Action Button, so it is still possible to accidentally trigger the Camera or the Flashlight from the Lock Screen while the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in a pocket.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/">iOS 17.1 Beta 3 Prevents Action Button From Activating the Camera or Flashlight in a Pocket</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-beta-3-prevents-action-button-from-activating-the-camera-or-flashlight-in-a-pocket.2407118/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wallet App Now Shows Balances for Discover Credit Cards</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-now-shows-balances-for-discover-credit-cards.2407117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:25:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[U.S. Discover users who add their credit cards to Apple Wallet can now see their total card balance and transaction history right on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with iOS 17.1 beta 3, which came out today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/uk-bank-account-apple-wallet-2-discover-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916302" /><br/>
Apple added the transaction and card balance functionality to the Wallet app as part of its Connected Cards feature, according to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-integrates-balances-discover-us-credit-cards/">9to5Mac</a></em>. Tapping on one of the listed transactions in the Wallet app will take users to the Discover app or website for more information. As of right now, this feature is only available for Discover card holders as Apple must work with each U.S. credit card provider or bank to implement support.<br/>
<br/>
A limited number of credit cards have previously supported full transaction history, such as American Express but total credit card balance has not been available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in the initial iOS 17.1 beta began allowing &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users in the UK to view the account balances of their bank cards and credit cards <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">in the Wallet app</a>. UK banks support Apple's Open Banking API to integrate with the Wallet app, and the feature is much more widely available to UK users. Barclays, Monzo, Starling, HSBC, Lloyds, and RBS all support card balances in the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
Following the release of the UK banking feature, <em>MacRumors</em> discovered that code in iOS 17.1 and references on Apple's website suggested that the feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-wallet-connected-cards-feature-in-us/">would expand to the United States</a>, which turned out to be accurate.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely partner with additional U.S. banks and credit institutions as the launch of iOS 17.1 approaches.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/">Apple Wallet App Now Shows Balances for Discover Credit Cards</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-now-shows-balances-for-discover-credit-cards.2407117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warning for iOS 17.1 Beta Testers: Update to Beta 3 or Your Wallet App May Crash</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-wallet-crash/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-for-ios-17-1-beta-testers-update-to-beta-3-or-your-wallet-app-may-crash.2407113/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:04:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-wallet-crash/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/">third developer beta of iOS 17.1</a>, an update that is set to come out in October. With this beta, Apple has a warning about the Wallet app, which may not function as intended for those running an earlier iOS 17.1 beta.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Wallet-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899453" /><br/>
According to the release notes for the update, now that beta 3 has been released, the Wallet app might crash on launch for those who have not yet updated and are still on iOS 17.1 beta 1 or iOS 17.1 beta 2. Note that this impacts those who have used Apple's "Connected Cards" feature, which is the function that allows UK users to see their debit and credit card balance info directly in the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on an earlier beta and wondering why the Wallet app isn't working, the answer is Apple changed something in the backend. You can fix the Wallet app by upgrading to beta 3. Right now, the update is only available to developers, so public beta testers could potentially run into issues. Apple will likely release the third public beta of iOS 17.1 tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also says that the connection between a card and a bank account could unexpectedly revoke, and that users who encounter this issue will need to follow an "Update Your Connection" repair flow that includes going to Settings, navigating to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> &amp; Wallet &gt; Connections, and re-connecting a card.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-wallet-crash/">Warning for iOS 17.1 Beta Testers: Update to Beta 3 or Your Wallet App May Crash</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-for-ios-17-1-beta-testers-update-to-beta-3-or-your-wallet-app-may-crash.2407113/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: 2024 Apple Watch &#039;Unlikely&#039; to Have &#039;Significant&#039; Innovation</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-2024-apple-watch-unlikely-to-have-significant-innovation.2407108/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:33:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Apple Watch X</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 2024 Apple Watch is "unlikely" to offer "significant innovative experiences," according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
For instance, in a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple-watch-estimates-and-predictions-apple-watch%E4%BC%B0%E7%AE%97%E8%88%87%E9%A0%90%E6%B8%AC-71aaeea2ffd4">post on Medium</a> today, Kuo said the Apple Watch will not be equipped with a micro-LED display or blood glucose monitoring in 2024. He believes these features are at least two years away from being added to the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear if Kuo's prediction rules out the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">rumored "Apple Watch X"</a> next year. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said a significantly overhauled "Apple Watch X" would launch in either 2024 or 2025, to mark the tenth anniversary of the device. The original Apple Watch was announced in September 2014 and released in April 2015.<br/>
<br/>
The information shared today by Kuo is quite vague, so there are a lot of possibilities and unanswered questions for now. For example, perhaps Kuo is referring to the model that will succeed the Apple Watch Series 9, and the "Apple Watch X" will be an additional high-end model that does offer more innovative changes. This would be similar to the iPhone X launching shortly after the iPhone 8 and iPhone 8 Plus in 2017.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the "Apple Watch X" would be equipped with a thinner case, and potentially a magnetic band attachment system. And if the device doesn't launch until 2025, perhaps the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/microled-apple-watch-still-on-track-for-2025/">rumored micro-LED display will also be ready</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo added that Apple Watch shipments are expected to decline to 36-38 million units in 2023, a decline of approximately 15% on a year-over-year basis. However, he said that Apple Watch integration with Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro</a> headset could "create an unparalleled and innovative health management experience" that boosts shipments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/">Kuo: 2024 Apple Watch &#039;Unlikely&#039; to Have &#039;Significant&#039; Innovation</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-2024-apple-watch-unlikely-to-have-significant-innovation.2407108/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2407106/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:26:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced new firmware for both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 with Lightning port and the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 with USB-C port. The new firmware is 6A303, up from the 6A301 update that was released in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not provide details on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware, so it is unclear what's new. Apple added multiple new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> such as Adaptive Audio, Conversation Awareness, and Personalized Volume, so there could be refinements to those updates.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not offer instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the AirPods are connected to an iOS device. Putting the AirPods in the case, connecting the AirPods to a power source, and then pairing the AirPods to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap AirPods.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in these firmware releases, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-2/">Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2407106/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Big Deal Days: Get Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749 (&#36;50 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-ultra/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-get-apple-watch-ultra-2-for-749-50-off.2407104/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:47:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-ultra/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's Prime Big Deal Days event is in full swing today, and you can get the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.99 in multiple styles, down from &#36;799.00. This is a new all-time low price on the wearable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-watch-ultra-2-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916105" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has nearly every model of the new Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00 during Prime Day, down from &#36;799.00. This version of the wearable just launched in September and this sale beats the previous low price by about &#36;20.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9N594%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We will continue to track Prime Day deals as the event continues, so be sure to keep an eye on our front page for more news. We'll also be regularly updating this article as prices have been fluctuating and several products have gone in and out of stock throughout the event. Remember that you can <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>sign up for Amazon Prime for free for one month</strong></a> to take advantage of the deals.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-ultra/">Amazon Prime Big Deal Days: Get Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749 (&#36;50 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-get-apple-watch-ultra-2-for-749-50-off.2407104/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
