<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:02:59 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps vs. Google Maps: Which Is Better?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-maps-vs-google-maps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-vs-google-maps-which-is-better.2420799/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 07:10:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-maps-vs-google-maps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Google Maps</category>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> has been providing navigational guidance to Apple users for almost 13 and a half years now, and much has changed about the app in that time. However, according to data from Canalys, the overwhelming majority of iPhones in the U.S. still have Google Maps downloaded as an alternative to &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj;, which comes preinstalled on all iPhones. We want to hear from <em>MacRumors</em> readers. Which do you prefer to get you from A to B?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Maps-vs-Google-Maps-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939046" /><br/>
Launched in September 2012, &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; was quickly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2012/09/20/apples-new-ios-6-maps-app-drawing-significant-criticism/">criticized</a> for having incomplete and inaccurate mapping data, which led some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users on dangerous routes. Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> offered a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2012/09/28/tim-cook-publishes-open-letter-on-maps-for-ios-6/">rare public apology</a> for the frustration it caused customers, and iOS chief Scott Forstall was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2012/10/29/scott-forstall-reportedly-forced-out-of-apple/">ousted</a> just one month later.<br/>
<br/>
Since then, Apple has made significant improvements to &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj;, building in new features and correcting lingering errors. Real-time traffic information and navigation options for pedestrians were added to Maps in 2013, which is also the same year Maps was extended to OS X. In 2015, Maps was updated with "Nearby," a feature that offers up local points of interest and transit directions in a handful of cities.<br/>
<br/>
In early 2020, Apple completed an overhaul of its maps in the United States, adding significantly greater detail including updated buildings, parks, sports fields, pools, and more. A Look Around feature in select cities is similar to Google's Street View, and the updated maps have been rolling out to more countries in the time since. In iOS 15, Apple introduced immersive walking directions shown in augmented reality, curated guides for select cities, real-time transit updates, and more road details for enhanced driving navigation. In iOS 16 it gained multi-stop routing. And in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, Apple made it possible to download maps for offline use – something Google Maps users have been able to do for quite some time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple_Apple-Maps_New-Ways_09272021_big.jpg.large_2x.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1290" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939053" /><br/>
Have Apple's incremental improvements been enough for it to be considered an equal to Google Maps in users' eyes? Of course, Google developers have not stood idly by watching &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj;' gradual evolution. Google has introduced several enhancements aimed at enriching the user experience through advanced AI technology and more immersive visualization tools, and has even taken a leaf or two out of Apple's book.<br/>
<br/>
One notable recent update in this regard is the Immersive View for Routes, which provides a comprehensive preview of a user's journey, whether they are driving, walking, or cycling. Launched last year, the tool combines billions of Street View and aerial images to create an intricate digital representation of the world, allowing users to visually navigate through bike lanes, sidewalks, intersections, and parking spaces along their route. It also includes a dynamic time slider indicating how conditions such as air quality and weather change throughout the day, helping users plan their trips with more precision.<br/>
<br/>
Another significant improvement is the integration of Lens in Maps, an evolution of the Search with Live View feature. Leveraging AI and augmented reality, Lens in Maps helps users get their bearings in a new location by providing information about nearby amenities like ATMs, transit stations, and dining options. The feature has since been expanded to over 50 cities.<br/>
<br/>
Google Maps has also rolled out updates to make navigation maps more reflective of real-world conditions. These include more detailed and realistic representations of buildings and improved lane guidance on highways. For electric vehicle owners, Google Maps also offers information on charging stations, including compatibility details, charger speed, and the last usage time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/google-maps-immersive-view.jpg" alt="" width="1060" height="666" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939059" /><br/>
Despite these concurrent improvements to Google Maps, their combined effect hasn't stopped users coming away impressed by how far Apple's navigational guidance has come. Based on anecdotal reports, the app is increasingly recommended by users for its cleaner view versus the more cluttered design of Google Maps.<br/>
<br/>
Likely thanks to its disastrous launch, &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; still gets a bad rap among some users, but Apple's continued efforts to improve the app appear to have helped reverse some of those opinions. "Maps has come a long way, and people have noticed," Craig Federighi, Apple's head of software, said at WWDC 2023. Are you more or less likely to use &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; these days? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-maps/">Google Maps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-maps-vs-google-maps/">Apple Maps vs. Google Maps: Which Is Better?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-vs-google-maps-which-is-better.2420799/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Return to Best-Ever &#36;189 Price on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-189-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-return-to-best-ever-189-price-on-amazon.2420798/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 06:54:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-189-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today is back with an all-time low price on the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C Charging Case, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. These are available for free delivery on Amazon as soon as Monday, March 4, and you won't need any coupon code to see this deal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Warm-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895411" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The last time we tracked this discount was about two weeks ago, and right now it's the only AirPods model with an all-time low price on Amazon. There are still some solid second-best options on AirPods 2 (<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a>), AirPods 3 (<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;149.99</strong></a>), and AirPods Max (<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;479.99</strong></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C feature a new USB-C port as well as improved dust resistance and 20-bit 48kHz lossless audio when paired with the Apple Vision Pro. Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-189-2/">AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Return to Best-Ever &#36;189 Price on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-return-to-best-ever-189-price-on-amazon.2420798/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Gains Over 50 Movies for a Limited Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time.2420796/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 06:29:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> today gained over 50 movies, adding to its back catalog of content for a limited time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/apple-tv-plus-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-812603" /><br/>
The collection includes a large number of popular and classic titles. Subscribers can access the movies in a "<a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/collection/limited-time-great-movies-on-apple-tv/edt.col.65de7e7a-b668-4e8f-97ba-20be203b91e9">Great Movies on Apple TV+</a>" section in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app. Some titles are also available in 3D. Movies in the collection include:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="left50"><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>21 Jump Street</li><br/>
  <li>300</li><br/>
  <li>American Sniper</li><br/>
  <li>Argo</li><br/>
  <li>Bad Boys</li><br/>
  <li>Black Hawk Down</li><br/>
  <li>Captain Phillips</li><br/>
  <li>Catch Me If You Can</li><br/>
  <li>Con Air</li><br/>
  <li>Draft Day</li><br/>
  <li>Edge of Tomorrow</li><br/>
  <li>Ferris Bueller's Day Off</li><br/>
  <li>Fight Club</li><br/>
  <li>Failure to Launch</li><br/>
  <li>Fast & Furious 6</li><br/>
  <li>Fast Five</li><br/>
  <li>Good Burger</li><br/>
  <li>Gravity</li><br/>
  <li>Horrible Bosses</li><br/>
  <li>How To Lose A Guy In 10 Days</li><br/>
  <li>I Am Legend</li><br/>
  <li>Jurassic World</li><br/>
  <li>Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom</li><br/>
  <li>Kill Bill Volume 1</li><br/>
  <li>Kill Bill Volume 2</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
</div><div class="right50"> <br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Knocked Up</li><br/>
  <li>Mad Max: Fury Road</li><br/>
  <li>Mean Girls</li><br/>
  <li>Men In Black</li><br/>
  <li>Minority Report</li><br/>
  <li>Old School</li><br/>
  <li>Saving Private Ryan</li><br/>
  <li>Spider-Man</li><br/>
  <li>Spider-Man 2</li><br/>
  <li>Star Trek</li><br/>
  <li>Star Trek: Into Darkness</li><br/>
  <li>Star Trek Beyond</li><br/>
  <li>The Accountant</li><br/>
  <li>The Bodyguard</li><br/>
  <li>The Hurt Locker</li><br/>
  <li>The Prestige</li><br/>
  <li>The Proposal</li><br/>
  <li>The Wolf of Wall Street</li><br/>
  <li>Titanic</li><br/>
  <li>Training Day</li><br/>
  <li>Two Weeks Notice</li><br/>
  <li>Wyatt Earp</li><br/>
  <li>Zodiac</li><br/>
  <li>Zombieland</li><br/>
  <li>Zoolander</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
</div><div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
This is not the first time that Apple has added movies from other studios to its video streaming service, but it does seem to be the biggest single addition of a collection of classic movies. The entire <a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/collection/limited-time-great-movies-on-apple-tv/edt.col.65de7e7a-b668-4e8f-97ba-20be203b91e9">"Great Movies on Apple TV+" collection</a> is available for a limited time for subscribers in the United States only.<br/>
<br/>
Ridley Scott's historical action epic "Napoleon" is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/napoleon-apple-tv-plus-march-1/">now streaming</a> on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; following its run in theatres. Unlike the other titles added today, Napoleon is an Apple Original Film and will remain on the platform.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time/">Apple TV+ Gains Over 50 Movies for a Limited Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time.2420796/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Chip Details of 16 Upcoming Apple Devices Revealed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed.2420792/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 05:40:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The chip details of 16 new Apple devices have been discovered, according to technical information posted on X earlier today by a private account with a proven track record of sharing accurate information about Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Apple-Silicon-Teal-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-767478" /><br/>
Eight unreleased Apple devices with the A14 Bionic, A17 Pro, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chips were among the list of chip identifiers (CPIDs). There are two upcoming A14 Bionic and A17 Pro devices, and four upcoming &zwnj;M2&zwnj; devices. <em>MacRumors</em> believes they relate to the following products:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>A14 Bionic</strong>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> (11th-generation) in Wi-Fi and Wi-Fi + Cellular configurations. The model number does not correlate to what the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; (11th-generation) is expected to have, so it may be a modified &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; (10th-generation) in Wi-Fi and Wi-Fi + Cellular configurations instead, or potentially a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> with a display.</li><br/>
<li><strong>A17</strong>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> (seventh-generation) in Wi-Fi and Wi-Fi + Cellular configurations. This may be the A17 Pro chip or an A17 variant.</li><br/>
<li><strong>M2</strong>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> (sixth-generation) in 10.9- and 12.9-inch display sizes and in Wi-Fi and Wi-Fi + Cellular configurations.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
If they relate to a new entry-level &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; model, the chip identifiers suggest that the device will not receive a chip upgrade in its next incarnation. The current, 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; already contains an A14 Bionic chip. The chances of this device being a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a display are slim due to model number trends, but the possibility cannot be ruled out.<br/>
<br/>
The current, sixth-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; model contains the A15 Bionic and some previous speculation suggested that the device would be most likely to feature the A16 Bionic in its next generation, so an A17 chipset would be a significant upgrade. <br/>
<br/>
There were also eight more identifiers for two unreleased chips that likely relate to the four models in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup and the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> in 11- and 13-inch display sizes. The next-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is widely rumored to launch later this month and feature the M3 chip that Apple first introduced in October 2023. However, the sequence of identifiers raises the unexpected possibility of the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; containing the M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
The information suggests that the entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup will feature the same A18 chip, corroborating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">previous reports</a>. The source who posted the information told <em>MacRumors</em> that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will still likely feature a chip branded as an "A18 Pro," even though the entire lineup of chips features the same CPID. The standard "A18" chip in the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus may have some binned or disabled modules to differentiate it.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, the source posted which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/">iPad</a> models will be supported by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. The account prefers to keep a low profile, but much of its previously posted information and many of its claims have been proven to be true.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed/">Chip Details of 16 Upcoming Apple Devices Revealed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed.2420792/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Watch Ultra With MicroLED Display Indeed Canceled</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/kuo-says-microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-display-indeed-canceled.2420791/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 05:19:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/kuo-says-microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>TrendForce</category>
		<category>microLED Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this week, Apple supplier ams OSRAM announced it would "re-assess its microLED strategy" after a "cornerstone project" was "unexpectedly cancelled." Counterpoint Research's Display Supply Chain Consultants informed <em>MacRumors</em> that this project <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/">related to the rumored Apple Watch with a microLED display</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo today <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1763552745280426119">commented</a> on the matter, saying that Apple has indeed canceled the project for the "foreseeable future." The analyst said that microLED production costs are currently "too high" for the project to be "economically viable."<br/>
<br/>
"My latest survey indicates that Apple has canceled the Micro LED Apple Watch projects because Apple thinks that Micro LED can't add significant value to this product, and the production costs are too high to make it economically viable," said Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
ams OSRAM was Apple's exclusive LED chip supplier for the project at the time it was canceled, according to Kuo. Apple has "no plans" to mass-produce microLED devices for the "foreseeable future," the analyst said.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo described the cancellation as a "major setback" for Apple, and he said many employees involved with microLED development have been laid off.<br/>
<br/>
While the project may be shelved for now, Apple likely still hopes to eventually transition to microLED technology in the future. Taiwanese research firm <a href="https://www.trendforce.com/presscenter/news/20240301-12054.html">TrendForce today said</a> that while ams OSRAM was Apple's "sole chip supplier" for the Apple Watch Ultra project, Taiwan and South Korea have a "robust lineup of manufacturers for Micro LED chips, backplanes, and related transfer processes," so there are other suppliers that Apple could partner with in the future. In any case, it appears that Apple's first microLED device is several years away.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trendforce/">TrendForce</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/kuo-says-microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled/">Kuo: Apple Watch Ultra With MicroLED Display Indeed Canceled</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-display-indeed-canceled.2420791/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Boosts Chrome&#039;s Web Search Suggestions on Mobile and Desktop</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/google-chrome-new-web-search-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-boosts-chromes-web-search-suggestions-on-mobile-and-desktop.2420784/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:04:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/google-chrome-new-web-search-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google has <a href="https://blog.google/products/chrome/google-chrome-update-february-2024/">announced</a> a trio of new Chrome browser features for desktop and mobile that aim to provide more helpful suggestions when searching the web, even over poor data connections.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
On desktop, users who are signed into Chrome and open a new tab will now see suggestions in the search field related to their previous searches based on similar things others are looking for. For example, if you recently searched for "Japchae," you might see suggestions for other popular Korean dishes.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, Google says it has also improved image results. Previously, Chrome only displayed images for search suggestions in the address bar that matched a specific product users were looking for. Now on iOS and Android, Chrome will show images for broader shopping categories and products based on simple searches. <br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Chrome on Android and iOS now has improved on-device capabilities that will give users search suggestions even when they have a poor network conntection. Google claims this will also mean more helpful suggestions when Incognito Mode is enabled.<br/>
<br/>
Google says the three new features are now gradually being rolled out to Chrome users. The changes follow last week's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/22/google-chrome-mac-help-me-write-ai/">launch</a> of a new generative AI-based "Help me Write" feature that is available for Chrome browser for desktops.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/google-chrome-new-web-search-features/">Google Boosts Chrome&#039;s Web Search Suggestions on Mobile and Desktop</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-boosts-chromes-web-search-suggestions-on-mobile-and-desktop.2420784/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10 New Things Your iPhone Can Do in Next Week&#039;s iOS 17.4 Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/10-things-iphone-can-do-next-ios-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-in-next-weeks-ios-17-4-update.2420783/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 01:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/10-things-iphone-can-do-next-ios-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will this month release iOS 17.4, its biggest iPhone software update of the year so far, featuring a number of features and changes that users have been anticipating for quite a while.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-17.4-Everything-New-Your-iPhone-Can-Do-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938472" /><br/>
Below, we've listed 10 new things that your iPhone will be able to do after you've installed the update, which is projected to arrive by March 7. When the day arrives, be sure to check Settings ➝ General ➝ Software Update on your device to get downloading.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>1. Generate Podcast Transcripts</h2><br/>
Apple is adding <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-search-transcripts-podcasts-app/">audio transcripts to the Podcasts app</a> for iPhone, meaning you'll be able to read along to your favorite podcasts as they are spoken. If you're familiar with lyrics in Apple Music, it's very similar.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/podcast-app-transcript.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932875" /><br/>
You can also search the auto-generated podcast transcripts for specific words or phrases and jump to that point in the conversation, where you can then tap to skip to the audio track.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2. Protect Messages Against Quantum Attacks</h2><br/>
Apple is bringing a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/ios-17-4-adds-groundbreaking-imessage-feature/">cryptographic security feature</a> to iMessage called PQ3. This "groundbreaking" and "state-of-the-art" protocol provides "extensive defenses against even highly sophisticated quantum attacks," according to Apple. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
Apple's iMessage service already supports end-to-end encryption, but Apple recognizes that existing cryptographic protocols used by messaging apps rely on mathematical problems that could potentially be solved by future quantum computers. The PQ3 protocol is Apple's solution to mitigate that risk.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>3. Support for Next-Generation CarPlay</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">Next-generation CarPlay</a> is set to launch in the U.S. later in 2024, and iOS 17.4 brings support for a slew of new apps, including climate control, tire pressure, rear-view camera feed, electric vehicle charging status, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-CarPlay-Dash.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934995" /><br/>
When Apple first announced next-generation CarPlay, it said committed automakers included Acura, Audi, Ford, Honda, Infiniti, Jaguar, Land Rover, Lincoln, Mercedes-Benz, Nissan, Polestar, Porsche, Renault, and Volvo. Apple has not yet said if any next-generation CarPlay features will be made available in vehicles with classic CarPlay support. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>4. Siri Reads Incoming Messages in Other Languages</h2><br/>
Previously in iOS 17, ‌Siri‌'s interaction with Messages was limited to one option – the ability for ‌Siri‌ to automatically send your dictated messages without asking you to confirm them first.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-messaging-with-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932819" /><br/>
In iOS 17.4, however, ‌Siri‌ can also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/siri-read-messages-another-language/">read messages to you in another language</a> different to the primary language that ‌Siri‌ listens to and responds in. It's a neat option to have if you are bilingual, for example, or you're learning a new language.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>5. Stolen Device Protection Away From Home</h2><br/>
To make it harder for a thief to access passcode-protected data on a stolen iPhone, Apple in iOS 17.3 included Stolen Device Protection. With the feature enabled, Face ID or Touch ID is required to access passwords in iCloud Keychain, Lost Mode settings, options for erasing the device, and making purchases in Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932874" /><br/>
In addition to the new biometric requirements, the feature also imposes a one-hour security delay on actions like changing an Apple ID password. New in iOS 17.4 is a supplemental option that only requires a security delay when your device is located <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-stolen-device-protection/">away from familiar locations</a>, such as your home or office.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6. Live Activity for Stopwatch</h2><br/>
For some reason, Apple previously never offered Live Activity support for when you start a stopwatch in the Clock app, until now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stopwatch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933379" /><br/>
In iOS 17.4, any running Stopwatch now shows up in the Dynamic Island and on the Lock Screen, where there are controls for pausing the Stopwatch, clearing it, and starting a new lap.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>7. Generate Apple Cash Virtual Card Numbers</h2><br/>
iPhone owners running iOS 17.4 will be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/12/ios-17-4-beta-apple-cash-virtual-number/">generate a virtual card number</a> for spending Apple Cash when Apple Pay isn't an online option.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-cash-virtual-card-number.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935966" /><br/>
An Apple Cash pre-paid card allows users to send peer-to-peer Apple Pay payments to friends and family, transfer money to bank accounts, pay off their Apple Card, or spend money online via Apple Pay. With the new virtual card feature, Apple Cash users will be able to spend their balance even if Apple Pay is not supported by an online store.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>8. App Support for Cloud Gaming Services</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4, streaming game apps will finally be allowed on the ‌App Store‌ worldwide, which means services like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW can be offered as standalone ‌iPhone‌ and ‌iPad‌ apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/xbox-cloud-gaming-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-806504" /><br/>
Apple previously only allowed cloud gaming services to be offered via the web, but dedicated apps that let users stream games from servers will soon be permitted. Mini-app, mini-games, chatbots, and plug-ins will also be able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9. Set a Contactless Payment Provider</h2><br/>
In iOS 17.4, third-party payment applications and banks can utilize the NFC chip in iPhones to enable contactless payments directly through the device in the European Economic Area, bypassing the need for Apple Pay or the Wallet app. Users in this region will have the ability to choose a primary contactless payment service, which is triggered at payment terminals or by double-pressing the iPhone's Side button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/11/apple-pay-contactless-terminal.jpg" alt="" width="1064" height="499" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-718443" /><br/>
Within the EU, the Settings app will allow users to select and manage their preferred contactless payment provider. This area also lists all apps that have been authorized for contactless payment functionality. Additionally, users in the EU will have the option to replace the default Wallet application on their iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10. Support for Alternative App Stores</h2><br/>
App developers in the EU will be able to offer alternative app stores or install their apps through alternative stores. This means users in the EU will be able to set their preferred alternative app store as the default app store on their device, rather than Apple's own App Store. EU users will see an option for this in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Shazam-Authentication-App-Store-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937777" /><br/>
In addition, a Screen Time setting will allow parents to decide whether their children's devices are able to install apps from alternative app marketplaces. Users in the EU will also get a pop up warning when an app from an alternative app store contains malware.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/10-things-iphone-can-do-next-ios-update/">10 New Things Your iPhone Can Do in Next Week&#039;s iOS 17.4 Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-in-next-weeks-ios-17-4-update.2420783/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 M3 MacBook Air Refresh: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m3-macbook-air-refresh-what-to-expect.2420765/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 14:17:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1709255855/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2024 MacBook Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">the MacBook Pro line</a> with M3 chips late last year, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> has yet to be refreshed with the new hardware. That could change as soon as late March, with rumors suggesting an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Mac-centric event is in the works.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-purple-february.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936772" /><br/>
We're expecting new versions of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, and this guide highlights everything we know about the upcoming machines.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="size_and_design">Size and Design</h2><br/>
As of last year, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is available in two sizes instead of one. Apple makes a 13.6-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and a 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, so consumers can choose between favoring portability or screen size.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is going to refresh both versions of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;. The look of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; was last updated in June of 2022, and there are no rumors of design changes this time around. Apple will continue to use the same flat MacBook Pro-style body that was introduced in 2022, with full-size black Magic Keyboard, large Force Touch trackpad, dual USB-C ports, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, Thunderbolt charging, slim bezeled display, and aluminum chassis.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898576" /><br/>
The only difference between the two models in terms of design will be the display size.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is available in silver, space gray, starlight, and midnight, which is a new dark blue color. We could see the three standard colors and another special color, or a whole new color lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="updated_m3_chip">Updated M3 Chip</h2><br/>
With no design changes planned, chip updates will be the main focus of the refresh. The current &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models use the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, with Apple planning to upgrade the machines with the M3 chip that was first introduced in the MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Chip-Apple-Event-Slide.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920110" /><br/>
The M3 chip is built on Apple's next-generation 3-nanometer process, which basically means that it offers better performance and power efficiency than the 5-nanometer &zwnj;M2&zwnj;. For context, there are 25 billion transistors in the M3 chip, up from 20 billion in the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
CPU benchmarks indicate that the M3 is approximately 17 percent faster than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; when it comes to single-core tasks, and 21 percent faster at multi-core tasks. GPU performance is up approximately 15 percent, but there are other GPU improvements that give the M3 chip a notable boost.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip has a new GPU architecture that uses Dynamic Caching, which basically means that tasks use the exact amount of memory that they need and adapt in real-time for maximum utilization. The result is improved performance for GPU-intensive apps and games.<br/>
<br/>
For games and 3D software, the M3 chip supports hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading. Hardware-based ray tracing is faster than software-based ray tracing, so any game or app that uses ray tracing will perform better. Complex lighting effects won't take up as many system resources, speeding up rendering times.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that almost all Mac games do not support ray tracing, so for gaming, this is a feature that will be useful in the future rather than immediately. For 3D tasks in apps like Blender, there will be speed improvements.<br/>
<br/>
There's a new media engine in the M3 chip that supports AV1 decode. AV1 is a video codec that streaming platforms are using for higher-quality video content at a low bitrate. AV1 is becoming increasingly popular for 4K and 8K videos, and AV1 decoding is another good future proofing feature to have even for those that don't need it immediately.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_upgrades">Other Upgrades</h2><br/>
The next &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are likely to get Wi-Fi 6E support, allowing them to connect to the 6GHz Wi-Fi band offered by compatible 6GHz routers. There's a good chance battery life will be improved thanks to the upgrade to M3 chip technology.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="worth_updating">Worth Updating?</h2><br/>
If you have an &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, it's not going to be worth updating to the M3 version because the improvements aren't notable enough. You won't see design changes, and while the M3 is better, it's not <em>that</em> much better.<br/>
<br/>
Most people who have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip may not want to update either, but there's more to gain with the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; to M3 upgrade both in terms of performance and in design. The &zwnj;M1&zwnj; machines used the prior &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; design, so updating to M3 gets you the sleek new look.<br/>
<br/>
For those coming from an older Intel-based &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; or another Intel-based machine, the M3 will be a radical improvement.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
We're expecting to see new M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models introduced sometime in March or April, and signs right now point toward a launch at the end of March. We don't yet have details on a potential Apple event, but we should be hearing more in the next few weeks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air/">Apple&#039;s 2024 M3 MacBook Air Refresh: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m3-macbook-air-refresh-what-to-expect.2420765/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Beta Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-6e188/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-beta-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2420754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 11:41:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-6e188/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced a new beta firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, both the USB-C and Lightning versions. The new firmware is version 6E188, up from the prior 6B34 firmware <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b34/">released in December</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not often provide details or notes on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware, so it is unclear what's new. Note that this software is <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/install-beta/#airpods-beta">limited to developers</a> at the current time. <br/>
<br/>
There are no clear cut instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the firmware update, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-6e188/">Apple Releases New Beta Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-beta-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2420754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra With MicroLED Display Seemingly &#039;Canceled&#039; For Now</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-display-seemingly-canceled-for-now.2420753/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 11:26:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>microLED Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple supplier ams OSRAM on Wednesday <a href="https://ams-osram.com/news/press-releases/revised-microled-strategy">announced</a> it would "re-assess its microLED strategy" after a "cornerstone project" was "unexpectedly cancelled" that day. The company's stock plunged nearly 40% following the news, earlier <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/02/29/rumored-apple-watch-ultra-with-micro-led-might-be-dead">shared by <em>AppleInsider</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
Counterpoint Research's <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/">Display Supply Chain Consultants</a> told <em>MacRumors</em> that it believes this project related to the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display</a>. The research firm said low production yields, along with high costs and risk, are likely the primary reasons for the project being canceled with ams OSRAM. The firm said it remains to be seen if Apple looks for another supplier, or sticks with OLED displays for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
ams OSRAM said "discussions with the related customer are ongoing," so an Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display is not completely ruled out, and it may just be further delayed. The device was expected to launch in 2025 or 2026, depending on the source, but it may take even longer to be released, if ever, given this latest development.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is believed to have been actively developing microLED technology since it acquired California-based company LuxVue in 2014. Benefits of microLED displays compared to OLED displays typically include increased brightness, improved power efficiency, higher contrast ratio, and more, but the technology is still expensive.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/">Apple Watch Ultra With MicroLED Display Seemingly &#039;Canceled&#039; For Now</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-display-seemingly-canceled-for-now.2420753/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Setapp Will Be One of iPhone&#039;s First Alternative App Marketplaces in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/setapp-will-be-one-of-iphones-first-alternative-app-marketplaces-in-eu.2420747/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:33:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Setapp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[MacPaw today <a href="https://macpaw.com/news/setapp-ios-beta-announcement">announced</a> that <a href="https://setapp.com">Setapp</a> will be available as an alternative app marketplace on the iPhone in the EU starting in April. Those wanting access to the beta version can <a href="https://setapp.com/join-waitlist">join a waitlist</a>, and developers interested in the platform can apply <a href="https://setapp.com/for-ios-developers">on this page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Setapp-iOS.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938882" /><br/>
Alternative app marketplaces are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">among the several changes</a> that Apple is implementing in the EU with iOS 17.4, in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
On the Mac, Setapp is a popular subscription-based service that provides users with access to a curated collection of dozens of popular apps for &#36;9.99 per month. This includes apps like Ulysses, iStat Menus, Spark Mail, Unite, Yoink, and more. Starting with iOS 17.4 and later, Setapp will be available directly on the iPhone in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
MacPaw said the Setapp Mobile beta will offer a "carefully selected assortment of apps":<blockquote>• <strong>Productivity and Business Tools:</strong> Boost your efficiency with tools for managing your schedule, staying on track, personalizing your internet experience, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Creative and Design Software:</strong> Unlock your creative potential with intuitive tools designed for photo animation, document creation, and more.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Lifestyle and Productivity:</strong> Improve your daily routines with apps that help you build better habits, stay updated with the latest news, and efficiently manage your notes and ideas.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Utility Apps:</strong> Make everyday tasks easier with applications that enable you to share files effortlessly, monitor your spending, and streamline your idea organization process.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Specialized Professional Tools:</strong> Engage with advanced applications tailored for detailed document searches, comprehensive database management, and more.</blockquote>MacPaw is one of the first companies to announce plans to offer an alternative app marketplace on the iPhone in the EU, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/epic-games-store-ios-eu/">along with Epic Games</a>. Setapp subscribers on the Mac can already access a collection of iOS apps with a QR code system, and the alternative app marketplace will offer a more streamlined experience. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release iOS 17.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/ios-17-4-release-date/">on or before March 6</a>, the deadline for complying with the Digital Markets Act. For additional details about the changes coming to the App Store and more in the EU, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">read our previous coverage</a>. The changes do not apply outside of the EU, nor do they apply to iPadOS in any country.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/setapp/">Setapp</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/">Setapp Will Be One of iPhone&#039;s First Alternative App Marketplaces in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/setapp-will-be-one-of-iphones-first-alternative-app-marketplaces-in-eu.2420747/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MagSafe Duo Charger Hits All-Time Low Price of &#36;79.99, MagSafe Charger on Sale for &#36;27.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/magsafe-duo-charger-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/magsafe-duo-charger-hits-all-time-low-price-of-79-99-magsafe-charger-on-sale-for-27-99.2420730/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:21:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/magsafe-duo-charger-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot today has a couple of <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">deals on Apple accessories</a>, including low prices on the MagSafe Charger and MagSafe Duo Charger. Additionally, Amazon has steep discounts on FineWoven and Silicone Cases for iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/magsafe-duo-perspective-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1332" height="750" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-770700" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Both of the MagSafe Chargers in this sale are in brand new condition and come with a one year Apple manufacturer limited warranty. You'll find an estimated delivery between March 7 and March 11, although those dates may change depending on your location.<br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is a match for the best-ever price on the accessory. The MagSafe Duo Charger can simultaneously charge an iPhone via MagSafe and an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot also has the MagSafe Charger for <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-24%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_25"><strong>&#36;27.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;39.00. This beats Woot's previous price on the accessory by &#36;2 and is one of the lowest prices that we've tracked so far in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/magsafe-charger-new-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-846479" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-24%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_25"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;27.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there are <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">plenty of other deals</a> in the Woot sale, including the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_20">Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock</a> for &#36;34.99 (&#36;44 off) and the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-band-milanese-loop-3%3Fref%3Dw_gw_zl_bs_3">Apple Watch Milanese Loop</a> for &#36;36.99 (&#36;62 off). You'll also find USB-C cables, previous generation Apple Watches, iPhone cases, Apple Watch bands, and more at a discount. <br/>
<br/>
Finally, over at Amazon there is also a large collection of FineWoven and Silicone Cases on sale for the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max. You can find these for as low as &#36;23.81 right now on Amazon, and no coupon codes are required to get these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;27.61, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWZ9JC9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Silicone Case</a> - &#36;27.34, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9FJTK%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;36.64, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHXDVMXJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Plus Silicone Case</a> - &#36;23.81, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2XFLN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Silicone Case</a> - &#36;33.96, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1HZST%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Max FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;51.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWVCV1Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Max Silicone Case</a> - &#36;34.84, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/magsafe-duo-charger-low-price/">MagSafe Duo Charger Hits All-Time Low Price of &#36;79.99, MagSafe Charger on Sale for &#36;27.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/magsafe-duo-charger-hits-all-time-low-price-of-79-99-magsafe-charger-on-sale-for-27-99.2420730/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: AI Server Industry Aiming to Win Business From Apple</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business-from-apple.2420728/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:00:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>TrendForce</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AI server makers are hoping to obtain orders from Apple ahead of its highly anticipated unveiling of new AI features later this year, according to Taiwanese research firm <a href="https://www.trendforce.com/presscenter/news/20240229-12048.html">TrendForce</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Server manufacturer Supermicro is reportedly "aggressively expanding" its efforts to secure AI-related orders from Apple. The company has the potential to double its shipments of AI servers this year, supported by orders from existing clients including CoreWeave and Tesla.<br/>
<br/>
Late last year, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-ai-server-spending-2024/">reported</a> that Apple is expected to spend around &#36;4.75 billion on servers to support its AI technology in 2024, up from &#36;620 million in 2023. The company could purchase up to 20,000 servers this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is widely expected to announce a range of new AI features at WWDC later this year as part of the preview of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and its other software updates. At its annual shareholder meeting yesterday, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that the company will "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/">break new ground</a>" in generative AI in 2024. "We believe it will unlock transformative opportunities for our users," he added.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trendforce/">TrendForce</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business/">iOS 18: AI Server Industry Aiming to Win Business From Apple</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business-from-apple.2420728/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expands Do-It-Yourself Repair Program to M3 Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-self-service-repair-m3-macs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-do-it-yourself-repair-program-to-m3-macs.2420691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 05:26:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-self-service-repair-m3-macs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Self Service Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon expand its self-service repair program to the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, M3 14-inch MacBook Pro, and M3 16-inch MacBook Pro, according to a trio of support documents published today. <strong>(Update: Parts and manuals for M3 Macs are now available — see below).</strong><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Self-Service-Repair-MacBook.jpeg" alt="" width="3920" height="2205" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938858" /><br/>
First introduced in the U.S. in 2022, Apple's repair program lets customers purchase genuine Apple parts and tools. Apple also provides manuals so that customers can repair their devices without having to visit an Apple retail location or an Apple Authorized Service Provider. Repairs have been available for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/22/apple-expands-self-service-repair-program-to-macbook-air-and-macbook-pro/">Apple's notebooks</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/20/apple-self-service-repair-mac-desktops/">desktops</a> since 2022, but repair components and instructions for the M3 models were just made available.<br/>
<br/>
The support document covering the M3 MacBook Pro models details replacing the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/103908">bottom casing of a MacBook</a>, the parts needed to make a repair, and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/103897">what tools</a> are necessary to complete the repair. For the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, Apple provides a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/105134">detailed list of part numbers</a> required for various repairs on the display, logic board, fans, housing, and more.<br/>
<br/>
At the time of writing, some of the part numbers listed in the support documents are not available on Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair</a> Store, but we will likely see them added soon. It is not clear when Apple plans to announce the expansion of the repair program to M3 Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks <a href="https://twitter.com/nicolas09F9">Nicolás Álvarez</a>!)</em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Update: Now Live</h2><br/>
Following our report, Apple has added parts for the 14-inch MacBook Pro, 16-inch MacBook Pro, and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with M3, M3 Pro, and/or M3 Max chips to its <a href="https://selfservicerepair.com/en-US/order">self-service repair store</a> in the U.S. and select European countries. Apple has also published <a href="https://support.apple.com/en_US/manuals/maclaptops">repair manuals for these MacBook Pro</a> and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en_US/manuals/macdesktops">iMac</a> models on its website.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://nr.apple.com/dv7I5H2Ih6">press release</a>, Apple announced a few related changes.<br/>
<br/>
First, it is making Apple Diagnostics available for M3 Macs in the U.S. early next month:<blockquote>Launched late last year for iPhone and Mac, Apple Diagnostics troubleshooting sessions give customers the same ability as Apple Authorized Service Providers and Independent Repair Providers to test devices for optimal part functionality and performance, as well as identify which parts may need repair.</blockquote>Second, Apple is making the System Configuration process easier for all Mac models in all countries where the self-service repair program is available:<blockquote>Mac users will no longer need to contact the Self Service Repair support team to run the final step of a repair, but the team will still be available to assist as needed. The updated process will become available early next month in all countries where Self Service Repair is supported.</blockquote><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-self-service-repair-m3-macs/">Apple Expands Do-It-Yourself Repair Program to M3 Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-do-it-yourself-repair-program-to-m3-macs.2420691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Sales in China Increasingly Dependent on Promotions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-sales-in-china-increasingly-dependent-on-promotions.2420725/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 05:20:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple resellers in China are offering discounts on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models by as much as &#36;180, indicating an unusually lengthy drop in demand, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-29/apple-s-iphone-steeply-discounted-in-china-on-weak-demand">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iphone-15-pro-box.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918442" /><br/>
According to the media outlet, Alibaba's Tmall is trying to drive sales of the premium handsets by offering them at less than the roughly &#36;120 discount Apple offered around the same time last year. <br/>
<br/>
The discounts follow Apple's own <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">rare price reductions</a> on its website ahead of the Lunar New Year holiday in February. Apple has since returned to selling its &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup at original prices.<br/>
<br/>
The promotions indicate Apple's latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> generation is struggling to achieve the same popularity of previous models in China. Apple sales in China dropped 13% to &#36;20.8 billion in the quarter ended December, falling short of the &#36;23.5 billion predicted by analysts.  <br/>
<br/>
Strong interest in Android phones with generative AI features are believed to be fueling the trend, which is expected to deepen throughout 2024. "The pressure was mainly coming from other Android vendors as we saw Apple decline by around 10% year-on-year in the month while Huawei grew triple-digits over the same period, IDC analyst Will Wong told <em>Bloomberg</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's next major software update,‌ ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, is expected to include a slew of new AI features, while some AI capabilities are rumored to be exclusive to upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. But it's unclear how game-changing the features will prove to be, and whether they will arrive in time to revive the slump in &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/">iPhone 15 Sales in China Increasingly Dependent on Promotions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-sales-in-china-increasingly-dependent-on-promotions.2420725/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iPod Hi-Fi Launched 18 Years Ago – and Lasted Just 554 Days</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago-–-and-lasted-just-554-days.2420717/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 02:54:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Reflecting on the iPod Hi-Fi, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2006/02/28/ipod-hi-fi-introduced-plus-leather-ipod-cases/">launched</a> 18 years ago, many long-time readers may remember it as Apple's ambitious foray into the home audio market, long before smart speakers were a thing. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipod-hi-fi.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938838" /><br/>
Priced at &#36;349, it promised audiophile-quality sound within a compact design, offering home audio without the clutter of traditional stereo components. It featured a built-in Universal Dock for iPods, providing a seamless integration that allowed users to charge their device while playing music. <br/>
<br/>
With its capability to produce a wide frequency range and room-filling sound without distortion, the iPod Hi-Fi combined Jony Ive's minimalist design aesthetic and high-quality audio performance. Its versatility was further highlighted by the inclusion of an Apple Remote, and the option for AC or battery power, making it portable. <br/>
<br/>
Many products in the iPod series achieved remarkable success, but the iPod Hi-Fi wasn't one of them. The device was praised for its big rich sound, bass response, and ease of use, but its high price was a turn-off for many Apple device users. Also, the connector prominently positioned atop the speaker unit exposed docked iPods to potential knocks and damage. <br/>
<br/>
Despite its innovative features, the iPod Hi-Fi remained a niche product in Apple's lineup​​, and the combination iPod dock/speaker system never took off. Apple discontinued it on September 5, 2007, just 554 days after its launch.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago/">Apple&#039;s iPod Hi-Fi Launched 18 Years Ago – and Lasted Just 554 Days</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago-–-and-lasted-just-554-days.2420717/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Adapt William Gibson&#039;s Cyberpunk Novel &#039;Neuromancer&#039; for TV+</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/william-gibson-neuromancer-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adapt-william-gibsons-cyberpunk-novel-neuromancer-for-tv.2420714/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 02:04:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/william-gibson-neuromancer-apple-tv/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on a TV adaptation of William Gibson's acclaimed 1984 cyberpunk sci-fi novel <em>Neuromancer</em>, the company <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-announces-neuromancer-new-drama-based-on-the-multi-award-winning-science-fiction-novel-by-william-gibson/">announced</a> on Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/neuromancer.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938829" /><br/>
The new 10-episode drama will be created by Graham Roland and JD Dillard as a co-production between Skydance Television and Anonymous Content. "Neuromancer" will also be produced by Drake's DreamCrew Entertainment, with Roland serving as show runner and Dillard set to direct the pilot episode.<br/>
<br/>
From the TV+ <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-announces-neuromancer-new-drama-based-on-the-multi-award-winning-science-fiction-novel-by-william-gibson/">press release</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>The series will follow a damaged, top-rung super-hacker named Case who is thrust into a web of digital espionage and high stakes crime with his partner Molly, a razor-girl assassin with mirrored eyes aiming to pull a heist on a corporate dynasty with untold secrets.<br/>
<br/>
"We're incredibly excited to be bringing this iconic property to Apple TV+," said creators and executive producers Roland and Dillard. "Since we became friends nearly 10 years ago, we've looked for something to team up on, so this collaboration marks a dream come true. 'Neuromancer' has inspired so much of the science fiction that's come after it and we're looking forward to bringing television audiences into Gibson's definitive 'cyberpunk' world."<br/>
<br/>
</blockquote>The debut novel by Gibson, <em>Neuromancer</em> has been praised as one of the first and most-respected works within the cyberpunk genre and has received numerous accolades, including the Nebula Award, the Philip K. Dick Award and the Hugo Award. The novel served as the first book in the "Sprawl" trilogy and was followed by <em>Count Zero</em> and <em>Mona Lisa Overdrive</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Gibson's work introduced a gritty, technologically saturated view of the future that was revolutionary at the time. The author's vision introduced the now-familiar concepts of cyberspace (a term Gibson is credited with popularizing), virtual reality, and AI, presenting them in a way that was both innovative and prophetic.<br/>
<br/>
Apple TV+ has become something of a sanctuary for unique science fiction, featuring everything from renowned novels such as "Foundation" and "Silo" to original series like "For All Mankind" and "Severance." Apple TV+‌ received a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-tv-price-increasing-significantly/">price increase</a> in October, and the service now costs &#36;9.99 per month in the U.S. for new and existing subscribers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/william-gibson-neuromancer-apple-tv/">Apple to Adapt William Gibson&#039;s Cyberpunk Novel &#039;Neuromancer&#039; for TV+</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adapt-william-gibsons-cyberpunk-novel-neuromancer-for-tv.2420714/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spaces Hosts on X Can Now Broadcast Video During a Chat Session</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/x-spaces-enables-video-feeds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spaces-hosts-on-x-can-now-broadcast-video-during-a-chat-session.2420711/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 01:25:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/x-spaces-enables-video-feeds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spaces, or live audio chat sessions on Twitter (now X), now support video, owner Elon Musk announced on Wednesday by reposting a <a href="https://x.com/cb_doge/status/1762865068671176773?s=20">video tutorial</a> by the user DogeDesigner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
When hosts create a new Spaces session, they will see a new option to "enable video," and can use their phone's front or back-facing cameras, in either landscape or portrait mode, for their video feed. <br/>
<br/>
Currently, only hosts can turn on video, making them front and center of attention, while co-hosts and listeners are represented by icons surrounding the broadcast. Users have to join the Spaces session to view the video, just as they do to listen in.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: Video Spaces are now live on <br><br>Here&#39;s how to host a video space: <a href="https://t.co/PgYHiq0jhU">pic.twitter.com/PgYHiq0jhU</a></p>&mdash; DogeDesigner (@cb_doge) <a href="https://twitter.com/cb_doge/status/1762865068671176773">February 28, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Video Spaces are distinct from X's live broadcasting feature, which lets users stream video to their profile and followers' timelines. The latter is more akin to the old Periscope functionality that Twitter supported back in its heyday.   <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/x-spaces-enables-video-feeds/">Spaces Hosts on X Can Now Broadcast Video During a Chat Session</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spaces-hosts-on-x-can-now-broadcast-video-during-a-chat-session.2420711/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Spent More Than &#36;10 Billion on Apple Car Before Canceling Project</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-car-10-billion-spent/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-spent-more-than-10-billion-on-apple-car-before-canceling-project.2420692/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 17:13:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-car-10-billion-spent/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple spent more than &#36;10 billion working on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a> over the last decade, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/02/28/technology/behind-the-apple-car-dead.html">The New York Times</a></em> that details the issues the project faced during development. Apple first launched the project in 2014 and let it flounder for more than a decade before <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">calling it off</a> earlier this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774148" /><br/>
Money was spent on research and development, along with the thousands of Apple engineers and car experts that worked on the project. Some employees within Apple are said to have suspected that the endeavor was likely to fail from the beginning, and they referred to the car as "the Titanic disaster" instead of its "Project Titan" codename.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> signed off on the project, but members of the car team knew that it was going to be close to impossible. An electric vehicle with self-driving capabilities would need to cost at least &#36;100,000, and it would have razor thin margins and stiff competition.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple reportedly held discussions with Elon Musk about a possible purchase of Tesla, the company decided that building its own car made more sense than attempting to integrate Tesla into Apple. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/02/19/tesla-ceo-acquisition-unlikely/">Way back in 2014</a>, Musk said that he had "conversations" with Apple, but he said at the time that an acquisition seemed "very unlikely." <br/>
<br/>
Apple was never able to find the right leader for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project. As we detailed in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/">look back at the Apple Car's history earlier today</a>, the project had four different leads and was scaled up and scaled back several times over the course of the last 10 years. According to <em>The New York Times</em>, the ultimate reason that it failed was because Apple was simply unable to develop the software and algorithms for a car with autonomous driving.<br/>
<br/>
The more than 2,000 employees that worked on the car project are being redistributed, some will join other teams at Apple to work on AI and other technologies, and some will be laid off. Apple will take what it learned from the car project and apply it to other devices like AI-powered AirPods with cameras, robot assistants, and augmented reality.<br/>
<br/>
More on the downfall of the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; and some of the technologies that Apple came up with can be found in the <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/02/28/technology/behind-the-apple-car-dead.html">full <em>The New York Times</em> report</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-car-10-billion-spent/">Apple Spent More Than &#36;10 Billion on Apple Car Before Canceling Project</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-spent-more-than-10-billion-on-apple-car-before-canceling-project.2420692/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Car History - Where Did Development Go Wrong?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-car-history-where-did-development-go-wrong.2420682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 14:19:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history&#038;post_date=1709169559/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After spending a decade <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">developing an autonomous car</a>, Apple this week decided it was time to pull an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpower/">AirPower</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">shut down the project</a>. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a> is no more, and Apple is no longer planning to release an Apple-branded electric vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774145" /><br/>
The hundreds of engineers and car experts who were working on the vehicle will be laid off or distributed to other teams within Apple, including the AI team. The &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; is one of the longest running rumors that we've been reporting on without a product materializing, so we thought we'd take a look back at some of the key moments in the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;'s history to provide some insight into what went wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2015_-_early_development">2015 - Early Development</h2><br/>
In early 2015, a van leased to Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/04/mysterious-apple-car/">surfaced on the streets</a> of Concord, California with LiDAR equipment on its roof. Apple had been using vans like this for mapping purposes, but the hardware looked similar to hardware being used by companies testing self-driving software. This one vehicle sighting ended up sparking a slew of rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2015/04/winningappleconceptcar1.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="450" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-445134" /><em><div class="center-wrap">An imagined <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/04/07/designers-fanciful-apple-car-concepts/">Apple Car concept</a></div></em><br/>
That same month, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/09/apple-project-tesla-competitor/">unnamed Apple employee</a> told <em>Business Insider</em> that Apple would "give Tesla a run for its money," and <em>Financial Times</em> claimed that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/13/apple-automotive-research-lab/">was recruiting</a> automotive technology and vehicle design experts to work in a "top-secret research lab." <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/13/apple-working-on-electric-car/">then broke a story</a> with in-depth details on the hundreds of employees working on an Apple-branded minivan-like electric vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
There were a number of other key headlines and details shared in 2015.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> reportedly approved the self-driving car project in 2014.</li><br/>
 <li>At the time, the project was led by Steve Zadesky, Apple VP of Product Design and a former Ford engineer. It was overseen by Dan Riccio, Apple's SVP of hardware engineering.</li><br/>
 <li>In 2015, <em>Bloomberg</em> said that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/19/apple-car-production-2020/">hoping to produce the car</a> by 2020. Later, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/21/apple-car-development-speeds-up/">the WSJ said</a> it could be ready as soon as 2019.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple was said to be meeting with Magna Steyr, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/03/05/bmw-denies-i3-apple-car-report/">BMW</a>, and automotive companies as it sought a partner.</li><br/>
 <li><em>The Guardian</em> published a report that Apple wasn't just working on an electric vehicle, it was working on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/08/14/apple-car-test-track-discussions/">autonomous vehicle</a>. The report also said that Apple had prototypes ready for testing, which wasn't accurate.</li><br/>
 <li>Former General Motors CEO Dan Akerson said that Apple was underestimating the difficulty of operating in the car business. "They have no idea what they're getting into," he said.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple hired a ton of vehicle experts from automotive companies and from companies with expertise in autonomous vehicles.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple's "secret" car headquarters <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/03/13/apple-car-hq-sunnyvale/">were located</a> in Sunnyvale, California, close to the Infinite Loop campus.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2016_and_2017_-_first_signs_of_strife_lead_to_major_upheaval">2016 and 2017 - First Signs of Strife Lead to Major Upheaval</h2><br/>
The first hints of trouble with the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project surfaced in January 2016, with &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; lead Steve Zadesky <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/01/22/apple-car-steve-zadesky-to-leave-apple/">departing the company</a>. Around this time, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/01/08/apple-car-cars-auto-domains/">registered several domain names</a>, including apple.car and apple.auto.<br/>
<br/>
Former Apple SVP of technologies Bob Mansfield came out of retirement <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/07/28/apple-car-autonomous-driving-system/">to head up the project</a>, and under his direction, rumors suggested that Apple was focusing on an autonomous driving system with the aim of partnering with a car manufacturer in the future. Apple kept aggressively hiring, and at this time, split development into the hardware for the car and the software that would run on it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/04/Apple-Car-front-side.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-498042" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Another &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; concept from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/04/14/motor-trend-apple-car-renders/">Motor Trend</a></div></em><br/>
With the transition to Mansfield's leadership, hundreds of employees were fired or reassigned, and in late 2016, there was a major upheaval. Apple "abandoned" plans to build its own vehicle and gave Mansfield's team <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/10/17/apple-late-2017-deadline-self-driving-system/">a 2017 deadline</a> to prove the feasibility of a self-driving system.<br/>
<br/>
In early 2017, white Lexus RX450h SUVs outfitted with LiDAR equipment and piloted by Apple employees <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/04/27/apple-self-driving-lexus-suv-spotted/">were spotted in the Bay Area</a>, and Apple has used these vehicles to test its autonomous driving systems up until now. Apple was also rumored to be testing its self-driving technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/11/28/apple-autonomous-vehicles-arizona-test-site/">at a facility in Arizona</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple's Self-Driving Car Spotted on 101 in Palo Alto" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DtQcNHw-w8M" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Apple at this time was also working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/08/22/apple-self-driving-campus-shuttle/">building an autonomous shuttle</a> in partnership with Volkswagen to ferry employees to the Infinite Loop campus, but that was nixed.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; made the unusual decision to confirm that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/06/13/tim-cook-confirms-apple-autonomous-driving/">working on autonomous driving</a>. "We're focusing on autonomous systems," Cook said. "It's a core technology that we view as very important." He went on to say that it was the "mother of all AI projects," describing it as "one of the most difficult AI projects actually to work on."<br/>
<h2 id="2018_and_2019_-_full_car_shelved_quiet_work_on_autonomous_driving_systems">2018 and 2019 - Full Car Shelved, Quiet Work on Autonomous Driving Systems</h2><br/>
In 2018, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/05/14/apple-expands-self-driving-car-fleet/">continued to expand</a> the number of SUVs it was using to test autonomous driving software. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; would be Apple's next "star product" and that it would launch in 2023 to 2025. Kuo claimed it would revolutionize the auto market, likening it to the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
2018 was a quiet year for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; as Apple worked on self-driving systems behind the scenes, but toward the end of the year there was speculation that the car project was back on due to the hiring of former <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/08/10/former-tesla-lead-engineer-returns-to-apple/">Ford lead engineer Doug Field</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In 2019, there were little hints that the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; was still in the works. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/17/apple-car-next-generation-lidar-sensors-report/">had talks</a> with LiDAR sensor suppliers, looking for advanced designs. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/25/apple-acquires-self-driving-car-startup-drive-ai/">also purchased</a> self-driving vehicle startup Drive.ai.<br/>
<br/>
Mid-year, there was a fun rumor that Jony Ive had wanted to design the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/28/jony-ive-apple-car-without-steering-wheel/">without a steering wheel</a>, a concept that would resurface later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2020_and_2021_-_another_leadership_shakeup_renews_interest_in_apple_car">2020 and 2021 - Another Leadership Shakeup Renews Interest in Apple Car</h2><br/>
2020 was the year of the pandemic, and for 11 months, we heard nothing about the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;. Behind the scenes though, the project was undergoing another leadership change. Bob Mansfield was out, and &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; development <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/apple-car-join-giannandrea/">shifted to John Giannandrea</a>, Apple's AI chief, with Doug Field overseeing day-to-day operations.<br/>
<br/>
In December, rumors suggested an Apple-branded vehicle <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/21/apple-car-production-rumored-2024/">was back on</a>, and that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/09/apple-car-tsmc-chips/">allegedly in talks</a> with well-known automotive electronics suppliers.<br/>
<br/>
2021 brought numerous rumors of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/10/apple-hyundai-apple-car-deal/">Apple partnership with Hyundai</a> for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;, and Hyundai even confirmed the relationship before walking it back. The deal <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/05/apple-pauses-car-talks-hyundai-kia/">ultimately dissolved</a>, perhaps because of Hyundai's lack of discretion. Apple held talks with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/05/apple-car-kia-talks-georgia-assembly/">multiple Japanese automakers</a>, but no partnership materialized. For a time, there were rumors that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/02/kuo-apple-car-use-hyundai-e-gmp-platform/">Apple would use</a> Hyundai's E-GMP electric battery platform, but that didn't happen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/csm_hyundai-ev-platform-apple-car.jpg" alt="" width="1345" height="618" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-781438" /><br/>
Toward the end of the year, Doug Field left Apple, and there was yet another leadership change, with Apple Watch chief Kevin Lynch taking over under John Giannandrea.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2022_and_2023_-_steering_wheel-free_design_rumored_as_project_loses_focus">2022 and 2023 - Steering Wheel-Free Design Rumored as Project Loses Focus</h2><br/>
In 2022, &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; rumors heated up after <em>The Information</em> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/11/apple-car-design-rumors/">published a report</a> suggesting that Apple was working on a design with four seats that faced inward, a curved ceiling, and large seat-back screens that raised and lowered. There was talk of a car without a steering wheel or pedals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2015/02/canoo-interior-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1333" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826229" /><em><div class="center-wrap">&zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; was rumored to have a design similar to the Canoo, pictured in the image above. Canoo's self-driving car has no steering wheel and a limousine-like interior.</div></em><br/>
The same report said that Apple's self-driving technology was lacking, with Apple's SUVs hitting curbs, having trouble staying in their lanes, and struggling to navigate streets. One vehicle reportedly almost ran into a person.<br/>
<br/>
Late in 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em> said that Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/apple-car-project-scaled-back-delayed/">again abandoned plans</a> for a fully autonomous vehicle, instead aiming for a self-driving mode that worked on highways. Apple was said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/apple-car-pricing-2026-launch/">planning an Apple Car launch for 2026</a>, offering a scaled back version of the vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
Rather than the fantastical design without a steering wheel, the car was said to have a more traditional design and a price point around &#36;100,000.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors about the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; dried up in 2023 and we heard little about it all year. In September 2023, Apple analyst &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj; said the project had "lost all visibility," and he warned that without an acquisition, Apple would not have a chance of producing a car within the next several years.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2024_-_apple_car_in_trouble">2024 - Apple Car in Trouble</h2><br/>
In January 2024, <em>Bloomberg</em> said that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-car-scaled-down-2028-launch/">had scaled back the Apple Car design</a> a <strong>second</strong> time, forgetting plans of more advanced autonomous functionality. Apple wanted the car to be able to drive on its own on highways, but that was too ambitious. Instead, Apple settled for driver-assistance features similar to how Tesla vehicles operate, with the car offering steering and brake/acceleration support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/vanamara-apple-car-concept3.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="808" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828956" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/12/10/apple-car-3d-render-based-on-patents/">Apple Car concept</a> based on Apple's patented designs</em></div><br/>
While Apple had been aiming for a 2026 launch, with the new project changes, that was pushed to 2028. <em>Bloomberg</em> warned that if Apple decided it was unable to provide an electric vehicle with this more limited feature set, executives might cancel the project.<br/>
<br/>
Just a month after that report, Apple executives decided to go ahead and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">give up on the Apple Car</a>, focusing instead on AI. Some &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; employees will move to Apple's generative AI team, while others will be laid off or will need to apply for new positions within Apple.<br/>
<br/>
As of now, the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; joins two other canceled Apple projects - <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/03/29/apple-officially-cancels-airpower/">the AirPower</a> charging mat nixed in 2019 and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> set that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/05/18/apple-nixed-plans-for-television-set/">rumored for several years</a> right around 2014.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="wrap-up">Wrap-Up</h2><br/>
Looking back at the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;'s history, it's clear that the multiple leadership changes and almost yearly redirects of the project ultimately led to Apple's decision to end work on developing a vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
Apple executives were never quite convinced of the viability of an &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; because of the enormous cost and safety risk involved with autonomous driving capabilities, and there was no one at Apple that was able to bring it to fruition.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/">Apple Car History - Where Did Development Go Wrong?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-car-history-where-did-development-go-wrong.2420682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
