<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 12:02:43 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reinstates Epic Games EU Developer Account, Paving the Way for Alternative App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-reinstates-epic-games-developer-account-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reinstates-epic-games-eu-developer-account-paving-the-way-for-alternative-app-store.2421412/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:29:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-reinstates-epic-games-developer-account-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today reversed a decision to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-explains-terminating-epic-games-account/">shut down Epic Games' developer account</a> in the European Union, and the account has now been reinstated. In a statement to <em>MacRumors</em>, Apple said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> has committed to following the rules, allowing Epic Sweden to be reaccepted into the Apple Developer Program.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite-apple-logo-2.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-755952" /><br/>
<blockquote>Following conversations with Epic, they have committed to follow the rules, including our DMA policies. As a result, Epic Sweden AB has been permitted to re-sign the developer agreement and accepted into the Apple Developer Program.</blockquote><br/>
When Apple terminated the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Sweden developer account earlier this week, it effectively prevented &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; from developing an alternative app marketplace for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in the European Union. Apple claimed that the account had been terminated because &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; had previously breached its contractual obligations, and that the court decision in the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; v. Apple legal battle gave it the right to shut down any &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; account at any time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phil-schiller/">Phil Schiller</a> <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/site/en-US/news/apple-terminated-epic-s-developer-account">engaged in a conversation</a> with &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; CEO Tim Sweeney where he asked Sweeney for written assurance that &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; would adhere to the new rules for alternative app marketplaces, but Apple did not feel that Sweeney's response was thorough enough. Apple claimed that Epic is "verifiably untrustworthy," with the Cupertino company also citing negative comments from Tim Sweeney about Apple's Digital Marketplace Act (DMA) compliance.<br/>
<br/>
There was immediate public blowback from Apple's decision to kill the account, especially because the emails from Apple made it look like the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; account was terminated because of Sweeney's criticism. From Schiller's email:<br/>
<blockquote>In the past, Epic has entered into agreements with Apple and then broken them. For example, you testified that Epic Games, Inc. entered into the Developer Program with full understanding of its terms, and then chose to intentionally breach the agreement with Apple. You also testified that Epic deliberately violated Apple's rules, to make a point and forfinancial gain. More recently, you have described our DMA compliance plan as "hot garbage," a "horror show," and a "devious new instance of Malicious Compliance." And you have complained about what you called "Junk Fees" and "Apple taxes."<br/>
<br/>
Your colorful criticism of our DMA compliance plan, coupled with Epic's past practice of intentionally violating contractual provisions with which it disagrees, strongly suggest that Epic Sweden does not intend to follow the rules.</blockquote><br/>
The European Union <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/eu-probes-apple-termination-epic-account/">quickly stepped in</a> and asked Apple for "further explanations" on why it had shut down the EU &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; developer account, a move that likely led Apple to reconsider its decision. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; in a statement to <em>MacRumors</em> said that Apple's response demonstrates that the European Commission plans to act swiftly to enforce the DMA, and that the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; store is coming to Europe.<br/>
<blockquote>Apple has told us and committed to the European Commission that they will reinstate our developer account. This sends a strong signal to developers that the European Commission will act swiftly to enforce the Digital Markets Act and hold gatekeepers accountable. We are moving forward as planned to launch the Epic Games Store and bring Fortnite back to iOS in Europe. Onward!</blockquote><br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; announced plans for an alternative app marketplace shortly after Apple introduced support for alternative app stores in the iOS 17.4 beta. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; has pledged to bring Fortnite and other games to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; through its own dedicated storefront, but specific timing for the launch of the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store for iOS has not yet been provided.<br/>
<br/>
Though &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is working on an alternative app marketplace, the company has criticized Apple's compliance with the DMA. Sweeney has called Apple's plan a "devious new instance of Malicious Compliance" and has said that &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; will continue to "argue to the courts and regulators that Apple is breaking the law."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-reinstates-epic-games-developer-account-eu/">Apple Reinstates Epic Games EU Developer Account, Paving the Way for Alternative App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reinstates-epic-games-eu-developer-account-paving-the-way-for-alternative-app-store.2421412/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPad From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-ipad-march/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-ipad-from-grid-studio.2421410/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:13:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-ipad-march/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		<category>Grid Studio</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 256GB 10.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with WiFi and cellular connectivity. GRID Studio is a company that creates framed wall art by recycling Apple products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/grid-studio-4s-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940326" /><br/>
<a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a> buys old iPhones, taking them apart and arranging each component carefully under glass to turn a hodgepodge of parts into something new. Each piece of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is labeled, with interesting device details and facts about Apple's history added in for art that's sure to appeal to Apple enthusiasts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/grid-studio-4s-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940327" /><br/>
This week, GRID Studio is having a spring sale, and <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE4s">the GRID 4S</a> is available for just &#36;99, down from &#36;170. It's a good price on a pivotal part of Apple's past, featuring all of the components from the 2011 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4S.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/grid-studio-4s-4.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940328" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4S was the last &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; introduced during Apple co-founder Steve Jobs' lifetime, and it was the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> released without Jobs. It was the fifth &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that Apple came out with, and in the name, the "S" stood for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4S was the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that included Apple's personal assistant.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/grid-studio-4s-5.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940329" /><br/>
Compared to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4S included an upgraded A5 chip, an 8-megapixel camera, and up to 64GB of storage. It ran iOS 5, a major operating system update that brought features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> and iMessage. All of the internal components from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4S are thoughtfully arranged in GRID Studio's piece, and there's even a look at the default app arrangement that was available at the time.<br/>
<br/>
The GRID 4S measures in at 11.7 by 16.5 inches, the same size as an A3 sheet of paper. It features a white background with a black frame, which allows it to match with any decor. GRID Studio also has a <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/collections/iphone">range of other iPhone pieces available</a>, with a 15 percent discount on everything this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/grid-studio-4s-6.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940330" /><br/>
We have one 256GB 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; with WiFi and cellular connectivity for a lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/UaV54/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (March 8) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on March 15. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after March 15 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/grid-studio/">Grid Studio</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-ipad-march/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPad From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-ipad-from-grid-studio.2421410/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple&#039;s New MacBook Air With M3!</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apples-new-macbook-air-with-m3.2421408/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 09:49:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/is-the-m3-macbook-air-a-good-upgrade/id1602394741?i=1000648508039">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">new MacBook Air</a> models featuring the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3gOdWKrudB8?si=LUpcNTKxMEo2AxZT" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We delve into the new machines' features, exploring <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">upgrades</a> such as the M3 chip, improved microphones, and more versatile external display support. We discuss the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>'s ideal configurations and key buying decisions, weighing the new machines up against the MacBook Pro, and take a look at where the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; could be headed next amid reports of an significant <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/30/oled-macbook-air-now-in-development/">upgrade to OLED display technology</a> in the future. We also discuss the rest of Apple's rumored announcements for March, which include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/2024-ipad-pro-what-to-expect/">new OLED iPad Pro models</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/">new Apple Pencil</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/27/new-ipad-pro-and-redesigned-magic-keyboard/">redesigned Magic Keyboard</a> accessory. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple's decision to cancel its long-rumored electric vehicle project.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-air/">The MacRumors Show: Apple&#039;s New MacBook Air With M3!</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apples-new-macbook-air-with-m3.2421408/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: Comparing the Generations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-generations-compared/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-buyers-guide-comparing-the-generations.2392779/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 09:15:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-generations-compared&#038;post_date=1709928900/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> has undergone some major changes in recent years, including the switch to Apple silicon, a complete redesign, and the introduction of a 15-inch model, making it all the more important to consider if now is a good time to upgrade or if an older model will suffice for your needs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898579" /><br/>
Following its latest refresh, Apple discontinued the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; from 2020 and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; from 2023. Now, customers can choose between the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; from 2022 for &#36;999, and the M3 13- and 15-inch MacBook Airs that were just introduced for &#36;1,099 and &#36;1,299, respectively. <br/>
<br/>
See the breakdown below for each new feature, change, and improvement that was added with each &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; model since 2018 compared to its direct predecessor:<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="macbook_air_m3_2024">MacBook Air (M3, 2024)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>M3 Chip</li><br/>
<li>15% faster Neural Engine</li><br/>
<li>Support for AV1 decode</li><br/>
<li>New GPU architecture</li><br/>
<li>Dynamic Caching</li><br/>
<li>Hardware-accelerated ray tracing</li><br/>
<li>Hardware-accelerated mesh shading</li><br/>
<li>Support for up to two external displays when the lid is closed</li><br/>
<li>Voice Isolation and Wide Spectrum microphone modes</li><br/>
<li>Enhanced voice clarity in audio and video calls</li><br/>
<li>Wi-Fi 6E</li><br/>
<li>Anodization seal to reduce fingerprints with Midnight finish</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="macbook_air_m2_20222023">MacBook Air (M2, 2022/2023)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Thinner design with flat lid, rounded bottom edges, and uniform thickness</li><br/>
<li>13.6- or 15.3-inch Liquid Retina display</li><br/>
<li>Apple &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip</li><br/>
<li>Up to 10-core GPU</li><br/>
<li>Hardware-accelerated H.264, HEVC, ProRes and ProRes RAW</li><br/>
<li>ProRes encode and decode engine</li><br/>
<li>Up to 24GB unified memory</li><br/>
<li>100GB/s memory bandwidth</li><br/>
<li>500 nits brightness</li><br/>
<li>1080p <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> HD camera</li><br/>
<li>Four-speaker sound system or six-speaker sound system with force-cancelling woofers </li><br/>
<li>3.5mm headphone jack with support for high-impedance headphones</li><br/>
<li>Bluetooth 5.3</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> 3</li><br/>
<li>Fast-charge capable with available 70W USB‑C Power Adapter</li><br/>
<li>Available in Silver, Space Gray, Starlight, and Midnight</li><br/>
<li>1.24 kg (2.7 pounds) or 1.51 kg (3.3 pounds)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="macbook_air_m1_2020">MacBook Air (M1, 2020)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Apple &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip</li><br/>
<li>8-core CPU</li><br/>
<li>Up to 8-core GPU</li><br/>
<li>Media engine</li><br/>
<li>Hardware-accelerated H.264 and HEVC</li><br/>
<li>Video decode engine </li><br/>
<li>Video encode engine</li><br/>
<li>16-core Neural Engine</li><br/>
<li>Up to 16GB unified memory</li><br/>
<li>62.5GB/s memory bandwidth</li><br/>
<li>Wide colour (P3)</li><br/>
<li>Image signal processor with computational video</li><br/>
<li>Up to 18-hour battery life</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="macbook_air_intel_2020">MacBook Air (Intel, 2020)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Up to Intel Core i7 processor</li><br/>
<li>Intel Iris Plus Graphics GPU</li><br/>
<li>Up to 2TB storage</li><br/>
<li>Magic Keyboard</li><br/>
<li>Bluetooth 5.0</li><br/>
<li>1.29 kg (2.8 pounds)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="macbook_air_intel_2018">MacBook Air (Intel, 2018)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Tapered "wedge" design</li><br/>
<li>13.3-inch Retina display</li><br/>
<li>Up to Intel Core i5 processor</li><br/>
<li>Up to 4-core CPU</li><br/>
<li>Intel UHD Graphics 617</li><br/>
<li>Up to 16GB memory</li><br/>
<li>Up to 1.5TB storage</li><br/>
<li>Butterfly Keyboard</li><br/>
<li>400 nits brightness</li><br/>
<li>Full standard colour (sRGB)</li><br/>
<li>720p &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; HD camera</li><br/>
<li>Stereo speakers </li><br/>
<li>3.5mm headphone jack</li><br/>
<li>Wi‑Fi 6</li><br/>
<li>Bluetooth 4.2</li><br/>
<li>Up to 12-hour battery life</li><br/>
<li>Available in Silver, Space Gray, and Gold</li><br/>
<li>1.25 kg (2.75 pounds)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; users have very little reason to upgrade to an M3 model unless they need absolute peak performance and don't want to buy a MacBook Pro, or perhaps if they purchased the 13-inch machine in 2022 and are now interested in the 15-inch M3 model.<br/>
<br/>
Most &zwnj;M1&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; users will stand to benefit from upgrading to the M3 model, especially if they are looking for a bigger screen and opt for the 15-inch model. These users would gain a much more modern design, a larger and brighter display, better performance, faster memory, a 1080p camera, improved speakers, &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; 3, fast-charging, and more. Nevertheless, some &zwnj;M1&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; users may be better off waiting for the next major refresh if they are still happy with the machine, and upgrading is not essential.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/">13-Inch vs. 15-Inch M2 MacBook Air Buyer's Guide</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For those who have an Intel-based &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, either of the generations currently on sale represent a highly worthwhile upgrade spearheaded by Apple silicon for a major performance improvement and upgrading is recommended, with many of the above upgrades quickly stacking up.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-generations-compared/">MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: Comparing the Generations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-buyers-guide-comparing-the-generations.2392779/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Air and iPad Pro Could Both Feature Landscape FaceTime Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-and-ipad-pro-could-both-feature-landscape-facetime-camera.2421402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 09:04:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a> models could include a front-facing camera positioned on the side of the device so that it is upright when in a landscape orientation, individual rumors suggest.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Pro-2024-Landscape-Camera-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940262" /><br/>
Currently, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models in Apple's lineup feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> camera on the top of the device, which puts the camera off-center when taking a &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; call in landscape mode. <br/>
<br/>
Seemingly recognizing the issue, Apple on the 10th-generation ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>‌ relocated the front-facing camera to the side of the device so that it would be usable in landscape mode rather than portrait mode. Apple has not launched an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; since, but it appears that Apple could be making this change on future iPads as well.<br/>
<br/>
In January of this year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/">code discovered in iOS 17.4</a> suggested the next &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; could adopt a similar design for the &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; camera. "During ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>‌ setup, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; needs to be in landscape with the camera at the top of the screen," read the code. <br/>
<br/>
Now, occasional leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/n/刹那数码">Instant Digital</a> on the Chinese social platform Weibo has claimed that this change is also coming to the two rumored new versions of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, in both 10.9 and 12.9-inch sizes.<br/>
<br/>
How Apple has achieved this switch to a landscape &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; camera on the new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models is unclear, since the second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> connects to both the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; using an inductive magnetic charger along the same side. <br/>
<br/>
But with Apple rumored to be launching a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; alongside the updated iPads, Apple may have come up with a solution to the issue. Either way, we should find out soon. Both the new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;OLED &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; Pro&zwnj; models are expected to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">as soon as this month</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">iPad Air and iPad Pro Could Both Feature Landscape FaceTime Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-and-ipad-pro-could-both-feature-landscape-facetime-camera.2421402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: First Discounts Hit M3 MacBook Air Alongside Rare HomePod Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-3-8-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-first-discounts-hit-m3-macbook-air-alongside-rare-homepod-sales.2421400/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 08:44:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-3-8-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week saw the launch of Apple's latest notebook, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">the M3 MacBook Air</a>, and Best Buy has the first discount for My Best Buy Plus/Total members. You can also find record low prices on HomePod, HomePod mini, MacBook Air, and the MagSafe Duo Charger in this week's best deals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0002.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847992" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/samsung-viewfinity-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940238" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;750 off Samsung ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;750 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;849.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Early in the week, Samsung introduced a discount on the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, and today it's been discounted even more during the Discover Samsung sale. You can get this monitor for the new all-time low price of &#36;849.99, down from &#36;1,599.99. There are also <a href="https://howl.me/clIpsUUt4NJ">deals on other monitors</a>, smartphones, smartwatches, tablets, and more in Samsung's sale.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, when you <a href="https://howl.me/clM4GKBZeXm">sign up to learn more</a> about Samsung's upcoming TV and audio product lineup, you can get &#36;100 off your purchase. The new slate of Samsung TVs and audio equipment is set to be unveiled on March 21, and this &#36;100 discount offer will be available through that date.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/m3-macbook-air-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940237" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;50 off M3 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clLur9sCFjw">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Discounts available only to My Best Buy Plus/Total members.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLur9sCFjw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00 </div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLutG0IgBi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,249.00 </div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Following the introduction of the 13-inch and 15-inch M3 MacBook Air this week, Best Buy became the first retailer with discounts on the new notebooks. The only caveat is that you'll need a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership to take advantage of the sales, which have &#36;50 off these models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M1 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/m1-macbook-air-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940236" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;250 off 13-inch M1 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clLm50orOos">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/best-buy-13-inch-m1-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLm50orOos"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple discontinued the 13-inch M1 MacBook Air this week, but Best Buy has it at the all-time low price of &#36;749.99 in all colors today, down from &#36;999.99. Although nearly four years old, this version of the MacBook Air still has an Apple silicon chip and should be perfect for anyone who wants to prioritize saving money over having the latest and greatest product.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MagSafe</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/magsafe-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940235" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;54 off MagSafe Duo and &#36;12 off MagSafe Charger</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">Woot</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/magsafe-duo-charger-new-low-price/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;54 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;74.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-21%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_28"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;12 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;26.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get Apple's MagSafe Duo Charger for the all-time low price of &#36;74.99 right now at Woot, down from &#36;129.00. Woot also has the MagSafe Charger for &#36;26.99, which is a solid second-best price. Both chargers are in new condition and come with a one year Apple limited warranty, and the MagSafe Charger comes in bulk packaging.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomePod</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/homepod-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940234" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;30 off HomePod and HomePod mini</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clM4IKgsT6J">Best Buy</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clM4I60rOhV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>HomePod mini for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clM4IKgsT6J"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>HomePod for &#36;269.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Best Buy today introduced the first discounts on the HomePod mini and HomePod that we've seen in months, and both are at all-time low prices. You can get the HomePod mini for &#36;79.99 in all colors and the second generation HomePod for &#36;269.99 in both colors.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-3-8-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: First Discounts Hit M3 MacBook Air Alongside Rare HomePod Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-first-discounts-hit-m3-macbook-air-alongside-rare-homepod-sales.2421400/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro CAD Renders Reveal Button Design Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/iphone-16-pro-renders-reveal-button-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-cad-renders-reveal-button-design-changes.2421395/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 08:08:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/iphone-16-pro-renders-reveal-button-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>91Mobiles</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The alleged design of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> was today showcased in new CAD renders shared by <a href="https://www.91mobiles.com/hub/iphone-16-pro-cad-renders-exclusive/"><em>91Mobiles</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-pro-cad-renders.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-940247" /><br/>
The drawings show a design that is similar to that of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, with a small number of changes relating to some of the buttons. The Action button is slightly longer, now resembling a similar length to one of the volume buttons, but with a slightly wider shape to distinguish it. The all-new "Capture" button is present on the left-hand side of the device where the mmWave antenna was located on previous models. While it is a similar length to the Side button, it is completely flush with the device.<br/>
<br/>
<em>91Mobiles</em> previously revealed accurate CAD renders of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/14/iphone-13-pro-thicker-and-larger-rear-camera/">iPhone 13 Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/16/iphone-14-pro-cad-renders-no-notch/">iPhone 14 Pro</a>, but its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/17/apple-watch-series7-cad-larger-display/">Apple Watch Series 7 designs</a> were ultimately incorrect. The website recently shared renders purporting to depict the design of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/">upcoming 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/03/iphone-se-4-design-revealed-in-cad-renders/">fourth-generation iPhone SE</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In January, <em>MacRumors</em> provided the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pro-design/">first look at the design of the iPhone 16 Pro</a>, including a Capture button that is flush with the side of the device, which was today broadly corroborated by <em>91Mobiles</em>' CAD file. <em>MacRumors</em> subsequently obtained information suggesting that while Apple tested a longer Action button design, it has since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-iphone-16-pro-action-button-tweaks/">scrapped the idea</a> and the Action button is now expected to look virtually the same as on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The main change to the design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max is rumored to be larger displays, increasing from 6.1- to 6.3-inches and 6.7- to 6.9-inches, respectively. Following a significant redesign with the switch to a titanium frame and more rounded edges on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; last year, little else is expected to change with the look of the new devices this year this year. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is expected to launch in the fall. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/91mobiles-com/">91Mobiles</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/iphone-16-pro-renders-reveal-button-changes/">iPhone 16 Pro CAD Renders Reveal Button Design Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-cad-renders-reveal-button-design-changes.2421395/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Chrome Will Soon Let You Install Any Website as a Desktop App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/google-chrome-desktop-web-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-chrome-will-soon-let-you-install-any-website-as-a-desktop-app.2421386/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 06:11:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/google-chrome-desktop-web-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google Chrome will soon let you install any webpage as a desktop app on your Mac, just like Apple's Safari browser does in macOS Sonoma (via <em><a href="https://www.androidpolice.com/any-website-pwa-chrome-124/">Android Police</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
The new feature was spotted by X (Twitter) user <a href="https://twitter.com/Leopeva64/status/1765698342191780066">Leopeva64</a> in the latest <a href="https://www.google.com/chrome/canary/">Chrome Canary</a> build, which includes a new option called "Install page as app," which can be found in Settings ➝ Save and share. Websites such as YouTube and Reddit which already have their own web apps will also automatically appear as optional installs in this menu.<br/>
<br/>
Selecting the "Install page as app" option invokes a prompt to "Install app," as shown in the image below. Web apps are automatically saved in an Applications subfolder called Chrome Canary Apps, where they can be optionally dragged to the Dock in macOS. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/chrome-web-apps.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940206" /><br/>
Currently, Chrome's implementation of web apps is more sophisticated than Safari's, as it provides not only a simplified toolbar with navigation buttons, but also a pared down settings menu with options including Copy URL, Open in Chrome, Uninstall, Zoom, Print, Find and Edit, and Cast.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/14/how-web-apps-work-macos-sonoma/">Here's How Web Apps Work in macOS Sonoma</a></li></ul><br/>
The feature is thanks to Chrome's long-standing support for <a href="https://chromeos.dev/en/posts/powerful-apps-fueled-by-the-web">Progressive Web Apps (PWAs)</a>, which Google originally embraced as a replacement for Chrome apps on the Google Play store. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/chrome-web-app-2.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940208" /><br/>
Users can try out the feature before it goes live in the stable build of Chrome by downloading the latest <a href="https://www.google.com/chrome/canary/">Canary 124 update</a> and enabling two new flags. To do so, copy and paste the following links into the address bar:<br/>
<ul><li>chrome://flags/#web-app-universal-install</li><br/>
<li>chrome://flags/#shortcuts-not-apps</li></ul><br/>
Chrome 123 is currently in beta and is expected to be released to the public imminently, so PWA support for webpages won't be in the upcoming version, but the next stable build after that.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-chrome/">Google Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/google-chrome-desktop-web-apps/">Google Chrome Will Soon Let You Install Any Website as a Desktop App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-chrome-will-soon-let-you-install-any-website-as-a-desktop-app.2421386/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Eighth Retail Store in Shanghai Expected to Open This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-eighth-store-shanghai-opening/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-eighth-retail-store-in-shanghai-expected-to-open-this-month.2421377/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:09:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-eighth-store-shanghai-opening/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Retail</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/retail/jingan/">announced</a> the imminent opening of its eighth retail store in central Shanghai, China, which will be named Apple Jing'an.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-store-jing-an-shanghai.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940196" /><br/>
Located on Nanjing West Road in the Jing'an District (named after its famous ancient Jing'an Temple), Apple Jing'an will become the 57th Apple store in mainland China. Local reports suggest it will be the second largest store in the city.<br/>
<br/>
Embracing a floral theme, the <a href="https://x.com/Edourdoo/status/1765962370537722150?s=20">storefront</a> is currently draped in a veil of blooming flowers. To celebrate the opening, Apple has also made a special wallpaper for Apple devices <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/jingan/images/wallpaper/Apple_JingAn_Wallpaper_Mac.jpg">available to download</a> on its China website.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet revealed when the store will begin to welcome customers, but local reports suggest it will open its doors later this month.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is currently grappling with a significant slump in demand for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in the country, with a recent report by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/china-iphone-sales-slump-early-2024/">CounterPoint Research</a> suggesting &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales dropped by 24 percent in the first six weeks of 2024 alone.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/retail/">Retail</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-eighth-store-shanghai-opening/">Apple&#039;s Eighth Retail Store in Shanghai Expected to Open This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-eighth-retail-store-in-shanghai-expected-to-open-this-month.2421377/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Produce 8.5 Million OLED iPad Pro Models This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-produce-8-5-million-oled-ipad-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-produce-8-5-million-oled-ipad-pro-models-this-year.2421374/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:32:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-produce-8-5-million-oled-ipad-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has ordered an initial 8.5 million OLED display panels from South Korean suppliers for its upcoming redesigned iPad Pro models, which are expected to arrive <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">as soon as this month</a>. The refresh will mark the biggest design update to the Pro lineup since 2018.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/iPad-Pro-OLED-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853666" /><br/>
Apple is relying on different OLED display suppliers for the upcoming ~11-inch and ~13-inch iPad Pro models, with Samsung Display exclusively producing ~11-inch panels and LG Display making the ~13-inch panels. Based on current orders, Samsung will produce 4 million units in 2024, while LG will make 4.5 million units for the year, perhaps suggesting that the larger model is forecast to be slightly more popular.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/apple-has-two-suppliers-for-oled-ipad-pro/">Industry insiders</a> claim the division of labor is due to changes in Apple's demand outlook for OLED iPad Pro models, as well as the unstable production capacity and yield of the two suppliers, which are both still getting to grips with Apple's requirement for new panel technologies. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to be aiming for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/oled-ipad-lightweight-design-and-image-quality/">"unrivaled" display quality</a>, as well as a design that cuts down on the thickness and weight of its ‌iPad Pro models. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/2024-ipad-pro-cad-drawings/">Recent leaked CAD drawings</a> of the upcoming models offer a better idea of just how thin the tablets will be. The larger ‌iPad Pro‌, for example, will be over 1mm thinner.<br/>
<br/>
The number of OLED panels Apple orders from Samsung and LG may change after production of the initial quantity, depending on fluctuations in production yield and possible adjustments to Apple's demand forecast for the new ‌OLED ‌iPad‌ Pro‌ models. Apple's latest shipments forecast is said to have been a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-planning-to-sell-fewer-oled-ipad-pros/">decrease</a> from the 10 million units that were projected for 2024 last year.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/oled-ipad-pro-price-lower-than-first-thought/">OLED iPad Pro Price Hikes May Be Lower Than Early Reports Suggested</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple's ‌iPad Pro‌ models are also expected to be upgraded with faster 3-nanometer M3 chips, and MagSafe charging is a possibility. Apple is also expected to sell the devices with a new Magic Keyboard and an upgraded Apple Pencil. For all the details, refer to our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
(Via <em><a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240308PD202/ipad-pro-samsung-display-_sdc-lgd-display-panel.html">DigiTimes</a></em>.)<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/apple-produce-8-5-million-oled-ipad-pro/">Apple to Produce 8.5 Million OLED iPad Pro Models This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-produce-8-5-million-oled-ipad-pro-models-this-year.2421374/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Windows Migration Assistant Upgraded for macOS Sonoma 14.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/windows-migration-assistant-macos-sonoma/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/windows-migration-assistant-upgraded-for-macos-sonoma-14-4.2421369/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:00:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/windows-migration-assistant-macos-sonoma/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		<category>Windows 10</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to releasing the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/">macOS Sonoma 14.4 update</a> on Thursday, Apple also released a new version of its <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/DL2105?locale=en_US">Windows Migration Assistant software</a> for PCs to include compatibility with the latest version of macOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/migration-assistant.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940183" /><br/>
Version 3.0.0.0 of the utility provides support for users looking to migrate their data from a PC running Windows 10 or later to Apple's latest Mac operating system. The assistant transfers users' contacts, calendars, email accounts, and more from a Windows machine and migrates the data to the appropriate places in macOS. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/DL2080">Version 2.4.5.0</a> remains available for users whose Mac is running macOS Ventura, macOS Monterey, or a version of macOS Sonoma earlier than 14.4. Versions of Windows Migration Assistant for macOS Big Sur and earlier also remain available. The macOS version of Migration Assistant lives in the Applications/Utilities folder.<br/>
<br/>
Apple advises users to turn off any antivirus, firewall, or VPN software until the transfer of information is complete. For more information, consult <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT204087">Apple's updated support article</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/windows-10/">Windows 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/windows-migration-assistant-macos-sonoma/">Windows Migration Assistant Upgraded for macOS Sonoma 14.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/windows-migration-assistant-upgraded-for-macos-sonoma-14-4.2421369/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Update to HomePod Software 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/homepod-software-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-update-to-homepod-software-17-4.2105572/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:55:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/homepod-software-update&#038;post_date=1709902500/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Like iPhones, iPads, Macs, the Apple Watch, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> are updated with new software on a regular basis. The most recent update was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/">released on March 7</a>, and enables <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> to learn what your preferred media service is. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/HomePod-2-and-HomePod-Mini.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890072" /><br/>
By default, updates are installed on your &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; devices automatically, but there's also a way to force an update if new software is released. However, Apple's auto-update function isn't typically immediate, so it can sometimes be handy to have a way to manually install software when you know an update has become available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/update-homepod-17.4.jpg" alt="home" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940180" /><br/>
Locating &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; updates and checking on the software version you have installed is pretty simple, but it's not entirely intuitive because the update function is buried in the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
The following steps show you how to update your &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; on devices running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> and later.<br/>
<ol><br/>
<li>Open the <strong>Home</strong> app.</li><br/>
<li>Tap on the icon that looks like three dots in the upper right corner.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Home Settings</strong> in the dropdown menu that appears.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap <strong>Software Update</strong> to see if there are any available updates.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Once you've selected "Software Update," you'll be able to see the current version of the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software that you have installed, along with available updates, and you can toggle off automatic updates if you want.<br/>
<br/>
If there is an available update, you just need to tap the <strong>Install</strong> button to update your &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;. If you have multiple HomePods in your home, each one will be updated at the same time through this software update feature. If you're registered for &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; Beta Updates, a menu option will also appear here for updating individual HomePods.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/homepod-software-update/">How to Update to HomePod Software 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-update-to-homepod-software-17-4.2105572/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Air Models Now Available for Same-Day Pickup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/m3-macbook-air-now-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-models-now-available-for-same-day-pickup.2421360/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:19:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/m3-macbook-air-now-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting today, Apple's refreshed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models with M3 chips are available for same-day or next-day pickup at Apple Stores, with no pre-order required. Online orders are also beginning to arrive to customers today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
Customers across the United States, Canada, Europe, Asia, and other regions can now place an order on Apple's website or in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> app and arrange for in-store pickup at a local retail location.<br/>
<br/>
To order a product with &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; pickup, add the product to your bag on Apple.com, proceed to checkout, select the "I'll pick it up" option, enter your ZIP code, choose an available &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; location, and select a pickup date. Payment is completed online, and a valid government-issued photo ID and the order number may be required upon pickup.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the M3 chip, the new 13-inch and 15-inch ‌&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models‌ offer Wi-Fi 6E, Voice Isolation and Wide Spectrum microphone modes, enhanced voice clarity in audio and video calls, and a more fingerprint-resistant finish with the Midnight color option. They also now support up to two external displays when the laptop lid is closed, increasing from just a single external display on the previous Apple silicon models.<br/>
<br/>
There are no major external design changes to the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, which continue to be available in Midnight, Starlight, Space Gray, and Silver colors. Pricing for the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; starts at &#36;1,099, while the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; starts at &#36;1,299.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/m3-macbook-air-now-available/">M3 MacBook Air Models Now Available for Same-Day Pickup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-models-now-available-for-same-day-pickup.2421360/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Air Models Now Arriving to Customers in New Zealand and Australia</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/m3-macbook-air-new-zealand-australia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-models-now-arriving-to-customers-in-new-zealand-and-australia.2421330/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:10:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/m3-macbook-air-new-zealand-australia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It is Friday, March 8 in New Zealand and Australia, which means customers who pre-ordered one of the new machines in those two countries are receiving their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><br/>
Introduced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">on Monday of this week</a>, the updated 13.6-inch and 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are equipped with the same M3 chip that was introduced in the MacBook Pro late last year.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer's Guide: All Differences Compared</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There are no external changes to the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, with Apple instead focusing on internal updates. The M3 chip is up to 30 percent faster than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip in terms of CPU performance, and there are notable GPU improvements with Apple adding support for Dynamic Caching, hardware-accelerated ray tracing, hardware-accelerated mesh shading, and support for AV1 decode.<br/>
<br/>
Other improvements to the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; include support for two external displays when the machine is used in clamshell mode, support for Wi-Fi 6E, enhanced voice clarity for audio and video calls, and a new anodization seal to reduce fingerprints on the Midnight finish.<br/>
<br/>
Apple retail stores in Australia are selling the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; machines, and there is plenty of stock for walk-in customers. Apple does not operate stores in New Zealand, so customers in that country need to order online.<br/>
<br/>
Following New Zealand and Australia, sales and deliveries of the new ‌&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models will launch in Asia, the Middle East, Europe, and finally, North America.<br/>
<br/>
We'll be sharing a hands-on review of the new M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; in the morning after picking up one of the new devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/m3-macbook-air-new-zealand-australia/">M3 MacBook Air Models Now Arriving to Customers in New Zealand and Australia</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-models-now-arriving-to-customers-in-new-zealand-and-australia.2421330/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New M3 MacBook Air Models to Have Day-One macOS Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/macbook-air-day-one-macos-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-m3-macbook-air-models-to-have-day-one-macos-update.2421325/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:16:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/macbook-air-day-one-macos-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models that are set to be released tomorrow will have a day-one update, according to <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937843" /><br/>
Both the 13.6-inch and 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models that are set to launch tomorrow are running a special build of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3, with a version number of 23D2057.<br/>
<br/>
Users will be prompted to update to &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 tomorrow, as the software saw a public release today. Given the timing of the software's launch and the debut of the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, Apple was not able to get the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 update installed on them.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are priced starting at &#36;1099 for the 13-inch version and &#36;1299 for the 15-inch version. Customers who pre-ordered will receive their machines on March 8, which is also when the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models will be available in Apple retail locations.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/macbook-air-day-one-macos-update/">New M3 MacBook Air Models to Have Day-One macOS Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-m3-macbook-air-models-to-have-day-one-macos-update.2421325/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Developing New Accessibility Features for iOS 18 and macOS 15</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/ios-18-macos-15-accessibility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developing-new-accessibility-features-for-ios-18-and-macos-15.2421321/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:32:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/ios-18-macos-15-accessibility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Accessibility</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With every operating system release, Apple aims to make apps more accessible and easier to navigate by providing a variety of new accessibility features and settings. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> (Codename Crystal) and macOS 15 (Codename Glow) will be no exception, and work on accessibility-related enhancements is well underway.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-18-Roundup-Article.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-924585" /><br/>
Through our industry sources, <em>MacRumors</em> has obtained information on some of the key accessibility improvements Apple has in store for its userbase. Apple is working on several new accessibility features along with improvements to existing settings, both of which should be available later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Adaptive Voice Shortcuts</h2><br/>
This feature will allow users to map a unique spoken phrase to an accessibility setting. Users will be given the option to create a custom phrase and select the accessibility setting they wish to toggle by speaking said phrase. By using Adaptive Voice Shortcuts, users will be able to toggle existing accessibility features such as VoiceOver, Voice Control, Zoom and so on.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New "Categories" Section for Live Speech</h2><br/>
The Live Speech feature, which is already present in Apple's operating systems, will receive a new section for user-created categories. Users will be able to organize phrases into categories of their choosing. When creating a category, users will be given the option to name their category and choose from a selection of around 20 different icons. Once a category has been created, users will then be able to add their desired phrases.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Apps Will Support Custom Font Sizes</h2><br/>
Apple intends to expand app support for adjustable Text Size, which is an existing feature. Located within the "Display" section of the "Accessibility" settings pane, the option allows users to choose custom font sizes for individual apps and select their preferred font size for reading.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> currently supports custom font sizes for the following five apps:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Calendar<br/>
<li>Finder<br/>
<li>Mail<br/>
<li>Messages<br/>
<li>Notes</ul><br/>
<br/>
With macOS 15, this feature will expand support to five additional apps:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Books<br/>
<li>News<br/>
<li>Stocks<br/>
<li>Tips<br/>
<li>Weather</ul><br/>
<br/>
Speaking to <em>MacRumors</em>, sources familiar with custom font sizes have said that Apple is internally testing an option to alter the font size of the menu bar within macOS, but it is unclear if the company will make this option available to end users. We were also told that Apple has additional accessibility features in the works, one of which utilizes on-device eye tracking, though further details were not available at the time of writing. More information should come to light as OS development continues in preparation for WWDC 2024.<br/>
<br/>
It is important to note that while these features are in development, it does not necessarily mean we will see them later this year. Apple has been known to cancel various projects that do not meet their standards, for one reason or another. For additional information on what to expect with this year's new OS releases, check out our dedicated rumor roundup for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/accessibility/">Accessibility</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/ios-18-macos-15-accessibility/">Apple Developing New Accessibility Features for iOS 18 and macOS 15</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developing-new-accessibility-features-for-ios-18-and-macos-15.2421321/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Let EU iPhone Users Delete Safari and More Easily Transition to Android</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-eu-safari-android-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-let-eu-iphone-users-delete-safari-and-more-easily-transition-to-android.2421315/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:42:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-eu-safari-android-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to adding support for alternative app marketplaces and alternative payment methods in the European Union, Apple is making several other changes to comply with the terms of the Digital Markets Act. Apple today outlined some of its upcoming plans in a DMA Compliance Report [<a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/dma/dma-ncs.pdf">PDF</a>].<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/transfer-to-android.jpg" alt="" width="1240" height="698" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940141" /><br/>
Apple is going to make it easier for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users to switch over to another operating system in the European Union. Apple says it is working on a solution that will help mobile operating system providers create "more user-friendly solutions" for transferring data from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to a non-Apple phone. The solution will be available by fall 2025, after which point companies like Samsung and Google will be able to offer better tools for transferring data from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
EU &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will be able to remove Safari from their devices entirely starting at the end of 2024, with an alternate browser able to take the place of Safari. As part of this plan, Apple is developing a browser switching solution for exporting and importing browser data into another browser on the same device. Apple has already began supporting alternative web browser engines, another DMA requirement.<br/>
<br/>
To improve interoperability between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and other smartphone platforms, Apple is allowing third-party payment apps to access the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s NFC chip for contactless payments that are not done through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, plus it is allowing developers to submit requests for additional interoperability.<br/>
<br/>
Interoperability requests are evaluated on a case-by-case basis to determine whether they are under the scope of the DMA, and if an effective interoperability solution can be developed.<br/>
<br/>
Developers in the EU are able to <a href="https://www.cedr.com">request additional mediation</a> that goes beyond the standard App Review Board evaluation. Developers who want to contest unsuccessful appeals to the App Review Board can request mediation, a process that Apple says is "EU-based, easily accessible, impartial, independent, and free-of-charge."<br/>
<br/>
All of these changes are limited to developers and users in the European Union as they are required by the Digital Markets Act.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-eu-safari-android-changes/">Apple to Let EU iPhone Users Delete Safari and More Easily Transition to Android</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-let-eu-iphone-users-delete-safari-and-more-easily-transition-to-android.2421315/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4.2421310/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:14:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4, the fourth major update to the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that launched last September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 comes over a month after &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3, an update that brought collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" /><br/>
The ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌‌ 14.4‌ update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings. There's also a macOS 13.6.5 release for those who are still running macOS Ventura and a macOS 12.7.4 release for those who have macOS Monterey installed.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4, Apple is introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/">new emoji characters</a> and adding support for reading Podcast Episode text in full with search support. There are new features for Business Updates in Messages, along with a toggle for showing only icons for websites in the Safari Favorites Bar. Apple's release notes for the update are below. <blockquote>macOS Sonoma 14.4 introduces new emoji as well as other features, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Emoji</strong><br/>
- New mushroom, phoenix, lime, broken chain, and shaking heads emoji are now available in emoji keyboard<br/>
- 18 people and body emoji support facing the opposite direction<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update also includes the following improvements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Podcasts Episode text can be read in full, searched for a word or phrase, clicked to play from a specific point and used with accessibility features such as Text Size, Increase Contrast, and VoiceOver<br/>
- Business Updates in Messages for Business let you get updates that you've opted into, like order status, flight notifications, fraud alerts or other transactions from trusted businesses<br/>
- Safari Favorites Bar adds an option to show only icons for websites<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>More information on the features that have been introduced in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; to date can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">found in our macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4.2421310/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 10.4 With Fix for Ghost Touch Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-4-with-fix-for-ghost-touch-bug.2421309/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:13:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.4, the fourth update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-watchos-10/">released in September</a>. watchOS 10.4 comes over a month after watchOS 10.3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-watchos-10-3/">a minor update</a> that brought a new watch face.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌‌.4 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later by opening it up and going to General &amp; Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.4 adds support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/">new emoji characters</a> that were also added to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, including lime, edible brown mushroom, phoenix, broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
There is also a Setting to disable the Double Tap feature on Apple Watch when using Vision Pro, and an option to double tap to show an expanded notification. Apple also included a fix for a bug that could cause some users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-touch-screen-issue/">experience "ghost touches" on the display</a>, a problem that was affecting the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's release notes for the update are below:<blockquote>watchOS 10.4 includes new features, improvements, and bug fixes, including:<br/>
- Tap to Show Full Notification setting now allows you to double tap to expand the notification<br/>
- Using Apple Pay with Confirm with AssistiveTouch will require a passcode for additional security and will not support double clicking the side button<br/>
- Resolves an issue that causes some users to experience false touches on the display<br/>
- Fixes an issue that prevents contacts from syncing to Apple Watch for some users<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote><br/>
More on the features that have been added in &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; to date can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">found in our dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-4/">Apple Releases watchOS 10.4 With Fix for Ghost Touch Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-4-with-fix-for-ghost-touch-bug.2421309/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases HomePod Software 17.4 With Music Preference Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4-with-music-preference-update.2421308/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 10:13:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new software for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, debuting &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; Software 17.4. The update comes over a month after the last &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-Midnight-Closeup-Feature-Purple-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-881769" /><br/>
With &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; Software 17.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is able to learn what a user's preferred media service is, eliminating the need to set a third-party app as the default or include an app name when asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to play content.<blockquote>This update enables Siri to learn your preferred media service, so you no longer need to include the name of the media app in your request.</blockquote>Apple has removed the Home app option that let users select a default media service as a result of the new feature addition. The change brings the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; in line with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, which already offer the option to provide a default music service selection to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; when making a song request for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party apps that work directly with the ‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌ include YouTube Music, Deezer, Pandora, TuneIn, and iHeartRadio. Streaming music services need to support ‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌ for the feature to work, and not all do, such as Spotify. You can play Spotify content on the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; by asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, but it routes the song through the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Along with ‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌ support for a preferred music service, the ‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌ 17.4 update also includes performance and stability improvements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4/">Apple Releases HomePod Software 17.4 With Music Preference Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-4-with-music-preference-update.2421308/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
