<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 13:03:21 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPads or Not? iPad Revenue Predicted to Sharply Drop in Q4 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-revenue-to-decline-in-q4-2023-morgan-stanley/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipads-or-not-ipad-revenue-predicted-to-sharply-drop-in-q4-2023.2407760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:38:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-revenue-to-decline-in-q4-2023-morgan-stanley/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Morgan Stanley</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's quarterly iPad revenue will significantly decline in the fourth quarter of 2023 on a year-over-year basis, according to estimated figures shared today by Erik Woodring, an analyst at investment firm Morgan Stanley.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-mini-and-Air-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915872" /><br/>
Morgan Stanley estimates that Apple will report iPad revenue of &#36;7.2 billion in the fourth quarter of 2023, which would be a decline of approximately 23% compared to the &#36;9.4 billion that Apple reported for the segment in the year-ago quarter.<br/>
<br/>
The year-ago quarter will be a tough comparison for iPad revenue, according to Morgan Stanley, as Apple announced updated iPad Pro models and the 10th-generation iPad last October. Over the weekend, two reports indicated that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">Apple plans to announce updated iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad models this week</a>, although some credible sources like <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman have cast doubt on this rumor.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear if Morgan Stanley expects new iPads to launch this month, but given the firm expects iPad revenue to significantly decline this quarter, the firm is at least not expecting any iPad updates that are major enough for revenue growth. Only minor changes are expected for the next iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad whenever the devices are released, including an M2 chip for the iPad Air and an A16 Bionic chip for the iPad mini.<br/>
<br/>
There are also rumors of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/">third-generation Apple Pencil with interchangeable magnetic tips</a> for drawing, technical drawing, and digital painting.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to release any new iPads this year. If that trend continues for the remainder of 2023, it would be the first calendar year with no new iPads released in the device's 13-year history. The two reports expecting new iPad models this week said Apple's announcement would likely be on Tuesday, so we'll see what happens tomorrow.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/morgan-stanley/">Morgan Stanley</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-revenue-to-decline-in-q4-2023-morgan-stanley/">New iPads or Not? iPad Revenue Predicted to Sharply Drop in Q4 2023</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipads-or-not-ipad-revenue-predicted-to-sharply-drop-in-q4-2023.2407760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker&#039;s Pre-Black Friday Sale Takes Up to 50% Off Popular USB-C Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ankers-pre-black-friday-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-pre-black-friday-sale-takes-up-to-50-off-popular-usb-c-accessories.2407752/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 08:44:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ankers-pre-black-friday-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're over a month away from Black Friday, but as always we're already seeing a few retailers kick off very early "pre-Black Friday" events. Today that includes Anker, which is offering <a href="https://howl.me/ckNTaeRyl5Y">up to 50 percent off select charging accessories</a>, as well as a buy one, get one half off sitewide through October 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-snowflakes-october.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917102" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In terms of the BOGO sale, you'll need to purchase two charging products that are not already discounted in order to get the discount. If two or more items are purchased, Anker will automatically take 50 percent off the least expensive item.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTaeRyl5Y"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 50% OFF</div>Anker's Pre-Black Friday Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are plenty of other Anker accessories with straight cash discounts right now on Anker's website and on Amazon as well. All of the accessories listed below have codes that will be applied once you add them to your cart, and there are a few products being matched at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Wall Chargers</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTihynVor">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTdoG6VVS">67W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;59.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469063005">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNThhu2KvF">150W 4-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;88.00, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTkDolYuU">Prime 240W 4-Port Desktop Charger</a> - &#36;169.99, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Portable Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTeKlQeKI">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.50, down from &#36;29.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK77HJ">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTo2cHQpF">PowerCore 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;36.52, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTnSeYEIs">PowerCore 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09W2H224F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469574520">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTlSZyqr4">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTmKHIliZ">PowerCore 26,000 mAh</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTckazLPK">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469007512">Amazon</a>]</li></ul> As we get closer to Black Friday on November 24, be sure to keep an eye on our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, which will track all of the best Apple and Apple-related deals of the season. You can also head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ankers-pre-black-friday-sale/">Anker&#039;s Pre-Black Friday Sale Takes Up to 50% Off Popular USB-C Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-pre-black-friday-sale-takes-up-to-50-off-popular-usb-c-accessories.2407752/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Rumored to Feature These Four Upgrades</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades.2407749/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 08:32:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>Magic Keyboard</category>
		<category>BOE</category>
		<category>Naver</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		<category>Setsuna Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> will feature four main upgrades and changes, according to a Weibo leaker with an early track record for disclosing accurate information about Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iPad-mini-review-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="4114" height="2314" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-818321" /><br/>
The account, known as "<a href="https://weibo.com/u/5143897135">Instant Digital</a>," claims that the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will feature four key differences, with no other other notable improvements other than the following changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>A16 Bionic Chip</h3><br/>
The next-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will apparently sport the A16 Bionic chip, offering a modest upgrade over the current model that features the A15 Bionic.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/iphone-15-a16-bionic.jpg" alt="" width="2030" height="1142" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-912526" /><br/>
The A16 Bionic would put the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; on par with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro, &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus. The chip would deliver around 10% better performance, 50% more GPU memory bandwidth, and a new image processor (ISP) compared to the current model. The chip upgrade is by far the most widely reported upgrade rumored for the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Upgraded Front and Rear Cameras</h3><br/>
Instant Digital also claims that the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will receive upgraded front and rear cameras, but further details about what exactly this will entail are unclear.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/ipad-mini-rear-camera.jpg" alt="" width="1300" height="825" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-816896" /><br/>
The current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; has a 12-megapixel rear camera with an ƒ/1.8 aperture and a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide front-facing camera with an ƒ/2.4 aperture. This is the same front and rear camera unit used across all of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> models at the moment.<br/>
<br/>
The change could take the form of a tangible upgrade to the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s camera hardware, or it could encompass software features like Photonic Engine, which has not yet been offered on any &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models. ProRes video recording, Audio zoom, stereo audio recording, Portrait mode, and Portrait Lighting support are all plausible upgrades in this area.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>New Color Options</h3><br/>
The seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will be available in a selection of new color options, Instant Digital claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/ipad-mini-6-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="1953" height="1186" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-816894" /><br/>
The current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is available in Space Gray, Starlight, Pink, and Purple. Apple could retain some of these colors and swap one or two out for new options, or it could overhaul the entire selection. It is not clear what new finishes could be in store, but it is possible Apple could take inspiration from the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s Black, Blue, Green, Yellow, and Pink <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-color-options/">color options</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Display With Reduced 'Jelly Scrolling' Effect</h3><br/>
Last week, Instant Digital said that the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s screen assembly will be rotated to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">reduce the effect of "jelly scrolling"</a> that some users complain about with the current model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/ipad-mini-9.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-818328" /><br/>
"Jelly scrolling" refers to screen tearing, which can cause text or images on one side of the screen to appear to be tilted downwards because of a mismatch in refresh rates. It can cause one side of the display to look as if it is responding faster than the other side in a visual disturbance that is hard to ignore once noticed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the phenomenon is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">normal behavior</a> for LCD iPads. Since LCD screens refresh line by line, there is a tiny delay between when the lines at the top and lines at the bottom are refreshed. But while this may be normal behavior for LCD screens, it can appear more obvious when observed on the ‌‌&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s smaller screen‌‌.<br/>
<br/>
Users have generally only complained about jelly scrolling when the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">in portrait orientation</a>. The issue is not reproducible in landscape orientation when scrolling, indicating this is a vertical refresh issue. According to the latest rumor, Apple plans to rotate the screen assembly to reduce the jelly scrolling effect in portrait orientation. Whether it will now become more prominent when the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is in landscape orientation is yet to be seen, but Instant Digital simply claims that the effect is reduced on the new model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Next-Generation iPad Pro Details</h2><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, Apple is planning a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/27/new-ipad-pro-and-redesigned-magic-keyboard/">complete revamp</a> of its Magic Keyboard accessory for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; that makes the device more laptop-like.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/11/m1-ipad-pro-magic-keyboards.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1350" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-795764" /><br/>
The updated version of the Magic Keyboard for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will apparently offer a larger trackpad, addressing criticisms of the current model, and "makes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> look even more like a laptop than the current setup." The area around the keyboard itself will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">made of aluminum</a>, resembling the top case of MacBooks, to provide a sturdier structure. The exterior shell of the keyboard will retain the silicone cover material used on the current model and a single USB-C port. Gurman mused that the redesign using more premium materials could lead Apple to raise the accessory's &#36;299 price point.<br/>
<br/>
Now, Instant Digital claims that the next-generation Magic Keyboard will also be 100% carbon neutral thanks to its redesign and use of different materials. Last month, Apple unveiled its first carbon neutral products: The aluminium <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> when paired with a new Sport Loop, as well as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> when paired with a new Trail Loop or Alpine Loop. The company plans for all of its products to be carbon neutral by 2030. <br/>
<br/>
The next-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to feature OLED displays, in a significant first for Apple's tablet lineup. Instant Digital added that Apple plans to use Samsung's Gen 6 OLED panel production lines to supply displays for the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models. Chinese supplier BOE is also apparently still trying to obtain orders from Apple for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; OLED displays, and is currently trying to improve the quality and suitability of its panels. The devices are not expected to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/05/11-inch-13-inch-ipad-pro-oled-mid-2024/">until next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will New iPads Launch This Week?</h2><br/>
Instant Digital's discussion of the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s features comes in anticipation of a new model that could be announced as soon as tomorrow. Last week, the Weibo user said that seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is among several devices that Apple could launch this month. A modified first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> with a USB-C connector instead of Lightning and the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip are also apparently on the table for announcement toward the end of October. <br/>
<br/>
After evidence of a refreshed first-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with a USB-C connector was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/ios-17-1-apple-pencil-usb-c/">discovered in iOS 17.1 beta code</a>, Instant Digital said that "Apple has not given up on the original &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, and a USB-C version is expected to be coming soon." The account has also recently discussed a third-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; model.<br/>
<br/>
Over the weekend, multiple websites <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">made independent claims</a> that Apple plans to announce updated &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, and entry-level &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models this week, citing sources. Instant Digital has been making claims about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/">new iPad models set to launch this month</a> since early September.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223238155365&navType=by">post</a> on the Korean social media site Naver from a user with a track record for posting Apple rumors also shared information from a different <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223238155365&navType=by">Weibo user</a>, separate to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">reporting over the weekend</a> about new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models being released this week, claiming that the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; models will be available starting this week.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these reports, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s &zwnj;Mark Gurman&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">yesterday said</a> that new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, and entry-level &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models are all in development with faster chips, but believes they "won't happen this month." Similarly, Apple supply chain analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> recently remarked "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/kuo-new-ipads-unlikely-to-launch-this-year/">new iPad models are unlikely before the year's end</a>." <br/>
<br/>
Interestingly, a report from <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></em> yesterday claimed that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/">third-generation Apple Pencil</a> with a replaceable magnetic tip is more likely to be announced instead of new iPads. Last month, the leaker known as "Majin Bu" said the new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; would feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/apple-pencil-3-could-feature-magnetic-tips/">interchangeable magnetic tips</a> for drawing, technical drawing, and digital painting.<br/>
<br/>
As a result, the exact picture of what to expect this month is unclear. At the start of the month, <em>MacRumors</em> learned about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/trade-in-changes-may-indicate-new-mac-this-month/">imminent changes</a> to Apple's trade-in policies that could align with the launch of new products. Overall, the rumor mill is currently quite a mixed picture when it comes to details about new Apple product launches this month, but two things are for sure: Almost all of the chatter relates to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; accessories, and it will not be long before we know for sure whether Apple really is going to launch anything this month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-keyboard/">Magic Keyboard</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/boe/">BOE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/naver/">Naver</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/setsuna-digital/">Setsuna Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades/">iPad Mini 7 Rumored to Feature These Four Upgrades</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades.2407749/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Online Store Now Available in Chile</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-online-store-now-available-in-chile.2407177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Chile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/10/apple-store-online-launches-in-chile-to-bring-customers-new-shopping-options/">announced</a> that its online store is now available in Chile, providing customers located in the country with a way to purchase iPhones, Macs, iPads, and more directly from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Chile.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917034" /><br/>
As in other countries, Apple's Chilean online store offers a full range of Apple products and accessories, with shopping assistance from Apple Specialists, a trade-in program for iPhone sales, free one-on-one online training sessions with certain product purchases, build-to-order Mac options, and multiple payment options including financing.<br/>
<br/>
Previously, customers in Chile could only purchase Apple products through third-party Apple Authorized Distributors. Apple's online store allows customers from Chile to purchase from Apple directly and have their orders shipped for free to all regions in the country.<br/>
<br/>
"We're thrilled to be expanding in Chile with the launch of the Apple Store online," said Deirdre O'Brien, Apple's Senior Vice President of Retail. "We love creating magical experiences for our customers, and whether they're looking to unleash creativity or embrace an entrepreneurial spirit, we now have an incredible Apple experience for everyone in Chile who wants to discover and shop for our amazing products, including the all new iPhone 15 lineup and Apple Watch Series 9."<br/>
<br/>
Apple says customers in Chile will be able to pre-order the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max starting October 20.<br/>
<br/>
<em>This story was originally published on October 11 and updated on October 16.</em><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chile/">Chile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/">Apple&#039;s Online Store Now Available in Chile</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-online-store-now-available-in-chile.2407177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Planning System for Retail Stores to Update iPhone Software With No Need to Open Box</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/retail-stores-to-update-iphones-with-new-system/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-planning-system-for-retail-stores-to-update-iphone-software-with-no-need-to-open-box.2407729/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 05:32:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/retail-stores-to-update-iphones-with-new-system/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Retail</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to implement an innovative new system that allows retail store staff to wirelessly update iPhones inside their sealed boxes, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Store-Vancouver-Canada.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-901784" /><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-15/apple-october-2023-executive-promotions-new-vps-of-retail-software-operations-lnrh4t94">most recent "Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman outlined how Apple plans to tackle brand new iPhones being sold in retail stores with outdated software. For example, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup shipped with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, but iOS 17.0.1 was already available upon its launch and the devices required a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/warning-update-your-iphone-15-to-ios-17-0-2/">update to iOS 17.0.2</a> to fix an issue that prevented the transfer of data directly from another <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> during the setup process.<br/>
<br/>
Apple wants customers to receive iPhones with the latest version of iOS to avoid users having to update themselves, especially if important updates have been pushed to address high-profile bugs. Before the end of the next year, Apple will apparently provide a new system to retail stores to address this. It features a "proprietary pad-like device" that retail store staff can place a sealed &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; box on top of. The system then wirelessly turns on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, updates its software to the latest version, and powers it off, with no need to open the device's packaging.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/retail/">Retail</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/retail-stores-to-update-iphones-with-new-system/">Apple Planning System for Retail Stores to Update iPhone Software With No Need to Open Box</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-planning-system-for-retail-stores-to-update-iphone-software-with-no-need-to-open-box.2407729/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Four New MacBooks on Schedule for Launch in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024.2407722/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:45:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Four new MacBook models with M3-series chips are on schedule to launch next year, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-MacBook-Pro-M2-Feature-Blue-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-881249" /><br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-15/apple-october-2023-executive-promotions-new-vps-of-retail-software-operations-lnrh4t94">latest "Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that new 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models featuring the M3 Pro and M3 Max chips have now reached design validation testing (DVT), meaning that the devices are nearing mass production. He believes that progress on the new machines indicates that they are likely to launch between early 2024 and the spring, which would mirror the approximate time frame in which the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max MacBook Pro models launched earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
New 13- and 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models with the M3 chip have also apparently reached engineering verification testing (EVT), an earlier production testing phase on prototype devices. Gurman says this puts the next-generation MacBook Airs on schedule for launch between the spring and summer of next year at the earliest, which could also mirror the time frame of the current models' launches that took place at WWDC in June 2022 and 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024/">Four New MacBooks on Schedule for Launch in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024.2407722/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Low-Cost Vision Pro Model to Drop EyeSight and M-Series Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/low-cost-vision-pro-to-drop-eyesight/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-low-cost-vision-pro-model-to-drop-eyesight-and-m-series-chip.2407719/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 03:56:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/low-cost-vision-pro-to-drop-eyesight/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming low-cost variant of the Vision Pro headset will lose out on features including EyeSight and an M-series chip, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/vision-pro-headset-1.jpg" alt="" width="2698" height="1518" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898460" /><br/>
Both <em>The Information</em> and <em>Bloomberg</em> have previously claimed that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/apple-cheaper-ar-vr-headset/">working on a more affordable version</a> of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset. The initial version set to launch early next year will be priced at &#36;3,500, placing it out of reach of many Apple customers. <br/>
<br/>
In the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-15/apple-october-2023-executive-promotions-new-vps-of-retail-software-operations-lnrh4t94">latest edition</a> of his "Power On" newsletter, Gurman explained that Apple has planned to launch a cheaper mixed-reality headset since before the announcement of Vision Pro and is now actively funneling resources toward the lower-end device. The company has apparently shifted staff away from developing a standalone AR glasses product toward the lower-cost headset. Apple has purportedly discussed pricing it at around &#36;1,500 to &#36;2,500.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously mentioned that Apple plans to bring down the price of the headset using lower resolution displays and a chip designed for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, rather than the Mac. Now, he also believes that Apple is likely to remove EyeSight, Vision Pro's external display that shows the wearer's eyes, as well as reduce the number of cameras and sensors on the device.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also reiterated his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/vision-pro-2-focusing-on-size-weight-lenses/">report from last week</a> that Apple is continuing work on the second-generation of the fully fledged Vision Pro headset, featuring a slightly smaller and lighter design to make it more comfortable to wear. Apple is also exploring integrating prescription lenses directly into the device to simplify its design.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/low-cost-vision-pro-to-drop-eyesight/">Gurman: Low-Cost Vision Pro Model to Drop EyeSight and M-Series Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-low-cost-vision-pro-model-to-drop-eyesight-and-m-series-chip.2407719/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Pencil 3 With Magnetic Tips Likely to Be Announced Instead of New iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-pencil-3-with-magnetic-tips-likely-to-be-announced-instead-of-new-ipads.2407677/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:11:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac Otakara</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">multiple reports</a> have indicated that Apple plans to announce updated iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad models this week, <a href="https://www.macotakara.jp/rumor/entry-45469.html">Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em></a> believes a third-generation Apple Pencil is more likely to be announced instead of new iPads.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Apple-Pencil-2-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-883692" /><br/>
An excerpt from the report, computer translated by Bing:<blockquote>MacOTAKARA believes that rather than an update to the iPad itself, the Apple Pencil 3 will be launched, which will come with a replaceable magnet tip.</blockquote>Last month, leaker "Majin Bu" said the new Apple Pencil would feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/apple-pencil-3-could-feature-magnetic-tips/">interchangeable magnetic tips</a> for drawing, technical drawing, and digital painting.<br/>
<br/>
The second-generation Apple Pencil was announced on October 30, 2018. It comes with one non-magnetic tip, with <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MLUN2AM/A/apple-pencil-tips-4-pack">replacement tips</a> available. The second-generation Apple Pencil attaches magnetically to 2018 and newer iPad Pro models, 2020 and newer iPad Air models, and the latest iPad mini. In the U.S., it is priced at &#36;129.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also continues to sell the first-generation Apple Pencil with a Lightning connector for the tenth-generation entry-level iPad and some older iPad models. It has been rumored that this Apple Pencil model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/ios-17-1-apple-pencil-usb-c/">might be updated with a USB-C connector soon</a>. The original Apple Pencil was released in November 2015 for &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman today said Apple is making progress on new iPad models, but he believes that the release of these devices "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">won't happen this month</a>."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/">Report: Apple Pencil 3 With Magnetic Tips Likely to Be Announced Instead of New iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-pencil-3-with-magnetic-tips-likely-to-be-announced-instead-of-new-ipads.2407677/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Rumored to Announce New iPads This Week, But Gurman Says Release &#039;Won&#039;t Happen This Month&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-rumored-to-announce-new-ipads-this-week-but-gurman-says-release-wont-happen-this-month.2407640/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:09:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>9to5Mac</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is making progress on new iPad and MacBook models, but <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-15/apple-october-2023-executive-promotions-new-vps-of-retail-software-operations-lnrh4t94"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> believes that the release of these devices "won't happen this month."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-mini-and-Air-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915872" /><br/>
"More often than not, the company debuts new laptops and iPads in October — about a month after the latest iPhone and watch get out the door," said Gurman, in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-15/apple-october-2023-executive-promotions-new-vps-of-retail-software-operations-lnrh4t94"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today. "And while I reported in July that Apple was planning such a release this year, the latest indications are that it won't happen this month."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman went on to say that new iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad models are all in development with faster chips, but he does not believe that "updates of any significance are imminent." This wording is more vague compared to his above claim that iPad releases "won't happen this month" whatsoever.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/kuo-new-ipads-unlikely-to-launch-this-year/">new iPad models are unlikely before the year's end</a>." If this claim is accurate, 2023 would be the first calendar year with no new iPads announced in the device's 13-year history.<br/>
<br/>
As for MacBooks, Gurman expects the next 14-inch MacBook Pro, 16-inch MacBook Pro, 13-inch MacBook Air, and 15-inch MacBook Air models to launch in the first half of 2024. He did not comment on the iMac or other Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iPads This Week?</h2><br/>
<a href="https://superchargednews.com/2023/10/14/apple-launching-new-ipads-this-week/"><em>Supercharged</em></a> and <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/10/15/apple-to-announce-new-ipad-models-this-week-featuring-upgraded-chips/"><em>9to5Mac</em></a> this weekend both independently reported that Apple plans to announce updated iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad models this week, citing sources. Both publications said the iPad Air will be updated with the M2 chip, and said the iPad mini will be updated with the A16 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
It should be a fascinating week ahead for the rumor mill. Who will be right? We will soon find out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/9to5mac-com/">9to5Mac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">Apple Rumored to Announce New iPads This Week, But Gurman Says Release &#039;Won&#039;t Happen This Month&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-rumored-to-announce-new-ipads-this-week-but-gurman-says-release-wont-happen-this-month.2407640/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Rumor Recap: Larger Displays, Capture Button, 5G Advanced, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/iphone-16-pro-rumor-recap-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-rumor-recap-larger-displays-capture-button-5g-advanced-and-more.2407563/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/iphone-16-pro-rumor-recap-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</a> are still around 11 months away from launching, there are already several rumors about the devices. Below, we have recapped new features and changes expected for the devices so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
These are some of the key changes rumored for the iPhone 16 Pro models as of October 2023:<ul><li><strong>Larger displays:</strong> The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be equipped with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>, respectively, according to Ross Young, CEO of Display Supply Chain Consultants. The devices are expected to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/iphone-16-pro-to-feature-taller-aspect-ratio/">taller aspect ratios</a> as part of this change. By comparison, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max have 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch displays, respectively.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Capture Button:</strong> Apple plans to include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">new "Capture Button"</a> on all iPhone 16 models, according to pre-production information obtained by <em>MacRumors</em>. The button would be located below the power button, but its purpose is unknown. It has been speculated that it could be a dedicated shutter button for the camera.</li><br/>
<li><strong>48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens:</strong> The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">upgraded 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera lens</a> for higher-resolution photos with more detail when shooting in 0.5× mode, according to Jeff Pu, a tech analyst at Hong Kong investment firm Haitong International Securities.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Wi-Fi 7 support:</strong> The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">support Wi-Fi 7</a>, according to Pu. This would enable the devices to send and receive data over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously, resulting in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. Wi-Fi 7 is expected to offer peak data transfer speeds of over 40 Gbps, a 4× increase over Wi-Fi 6E.</li><br/>
<li><strong>A18 Pro chip:</strong> Apple's next-generation A18 Pro chip is expected to be manufactured with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, known as N3E</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>5G Advanced:</strong> iPhone 16 Pro models will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">equipped with Qualcomm's Snapdragon X75 modem</a> for faster and more power efficient 5G connectivity, according to Pu. The modem supports the "5G Advanced" standard, which has been described as "the next phase of 5G" and an "evolution towards 6G."</li><br/>
<li><strong>5x optical zoom on Pro model:</strong> The iPhone 15 Pro Max's tetraprism lens system with 5x optical zoom will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">expand to both the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</a>, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.</li></ul>Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 Pro models in September 2024. Additional details about the devices should surface over the coming months, so be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/"><strong>keep tabs on our iPhone 16 roundup</strong></a> for the latest information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/iphone-16-pro-rumor-recap-october/">iPhone 16 Pro Rumor Recap: Larger Displays, Capture Button, 5G Advanced, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-rumor-recap-larger-displays-capture-button-5g-advanced-and-more.2407563/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 17.1 Coming Soon, iPhone 16 Pro Rumors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/top-stories-ios-17-1-coming-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-17-1-coming-soon-iphone-16-pro-rumors-and-more.2407547/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/top-stories-ios-17-1-coming-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're now more than a month past the big iPhone 15 introduction, but things are still chugging along with Apple news and rumors, led by the iOS 17.1 and related updates that will be bringing some changes later this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/top-stories-14oct2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916908" /><br/>
There have also been a number of new rumors about the iPhone 16 and the Mac lineup, while we had a couple of special guests on the most recent episodes of The MacRumors Show, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17.1 to Launch by October 24</h2><br/>
Apple this week made the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/">third beta of iOS 17.1</a> available to developers and public beta testers. The main change in this beta is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/">tweaked behavior for the Action button</a> on iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.1-Feature-Fall-Muted.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915266" /><br/>
iOS 17.1 is expected to be released to the public later this month alongside watchOS 10.1 and more. We've put together a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-features-list/">list of eight new features and changes included in the software update</a>. Notably, there is a tweak to cellular performance for the iPhone 12 in France due to a regulatory ruling, and regulators there have revealed that the update will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/">made available to the public by October 24</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Pro Expected to Support Faster '5G Advanced'</h2><br/>
The next-generation iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">equipped with Qualcomm's latest Snapdragon X75 modem</a> for faster and more power efficient 5G, according to tech analyst Jeff Pu. However, he expects the lower-end iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus models to stick with the Snapdragon X70.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
Qualcomm says the Snapdragon X75 modem <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">supports the latest "5G Advanced" standard</a>, which is described as "the next phase of 5G" and an "evolution towards 6G."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will Apple Release New Macs Soon? Here's What the Latest Rumors Say</h2><br/>
Apple often releases new Macs in the fall, but whether that will happen this year is far from certain. It's the second week of October now, and there is still no sign that Apple will be hosting an event this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-wwdc-2022-feature-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-882438" /><br/>
To help clear things up, this week we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/will-apple-release-new-macs-this-year/">recapped all of the latest rumors about Macs</a>. The next big feature expected for Macs is the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m3/">M3 chip</a>, which is expected to be a 3nm chip like the A17 Pro chip in the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
Things are constantly changing, of course, and even since that recap a new rumor has surfaced claiming we could see <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/">updated iMac models with M2 and M2 Pro chips</a> in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The MacRumors Show: Former Apple Executive Mike Bell Talks AirPort, CarPlay, and More</h2><br/>
Last week, we had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">YouTuber and content creator Sara Dietschy</a> joining Dan and Hartley on The MacRumors Show to discuss some of her favorite Apple accessories and more, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">former Apple executive Mike Bell made an appearance</a> this week to talk about some of his projects during his time at Apple, his current work at Lucid Motors, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/The-MacRumors-Show-Mike-Bell-Talks-AirPort-CarPlay-and-More-Thumb-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916852" /><br/>
Listen to ‌The MacRumors Show‌ on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player, or <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD8VmuL7qc7ii5uyjzSRk3UM7KI_c4qC5">watch a video version on our YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</h2><br/>
Apple this week introduced new firmware for both the AirPods Pro 2 with Lightning port and the ‌AirPods Pro‌ 2 with USB-C port. The new firmware is 6A303, up from the 6A301 update that was released in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913276" /><br/>
Apple's release notes only mention unspecified bug fixes and other improvements, so we don't know details on what's new, but there are likely some refinements to new ‌AirPods Pro‌ 2 features added in iOS 17 such as Adaptive Audio, Conversation Awareness, and Personalized Volume.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/oct-12-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/14/top-stories-ios-17-1-coming-soon/">Top Stories: iOS 17.1 Coming Soon, iPhone 16 Pro Rumors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-17-1-coming-soon-iphone-16-pro-rumors-and-more.2407547/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>2024 Apple TV: All the Rumors So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2024-apple-tv-all-the-rumors-so-far.2407485/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:19:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv&#038;post_date=1697242772/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2024 Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on a new version of the 4K <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and rumors suggest that it could launch as soon as 2024, two years after the launch of the current model. This guide includes details on everything that we expect to see in the 2024 &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-tv-4k-design-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796083" /><br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple has not notably changed the design of the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; in several years, and that's not going to change in 2024. We are not expecting any updates to the form factor, and it will continue to use the same slimmed-down black plastic body from the current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869858" /><br/>
<h2 id="a_new_chip">A New Chip</h2><br/>
The current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K has the same A15 Bionic chip that was in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> lineup, and we're expecting a new A-series chip for the 2024 &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;. Apple doesn't design chips exclusively for the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, so it's likely that the next-generation model will use the same A16 chip from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
There is also the possibility that the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K will have the A17 Pro chip used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, as that would give the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; the capability to play console-quality games, a rumor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/22/2021-apple-tv-rumors/">from years back</a>. The A17 Pro is Apple's first 3-nanometer chip, and it includes a 6-core GPU that's able to support hardware-accelerated ray tracing for the first time, enabling games with more realistic graphics. Several console games like Resident Evil 4 and Death Stranding will be coming to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; thanks to the A17 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
At the same time, it is worth noting that the A17 Pro chip may ultimately be too expensive for Apple to include in an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, especially as there are rumors that Apple is aiming for a lower price point.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="wi-fi_6e_or_wi-fi_7">Wi-Fi 6E or Wi-Fi 7</h2><br/>
It could make sense for Apple to bring new, more modern Wi-Fi protocols to the next-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, but we haven't heard rumors about this. The current &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models support Wi-Fi 6E and rumors suggest Apple will adopt Wi-Fi 7 for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as soon as next year.<br/>
<br/>
Current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K models support Wi-Fi 6, but upping that with at least Wi-Fi 6E would allow the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; to take advantage of the faster 6GHz band for improved streaming and content download speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_connectivity">Other Connectivity</h2><br/>
Apple offers both a Wi-Fi only &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K and a Wi-Fi + Ethernet model, and that could continue with the next-generation model. We could also see the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; adopt Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; is expected to continue to offer Thread integration and support for Matter when used as a home hub for smart home products.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="pricing">Pricing</h2><br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said last year that he expects the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; to be more affordable, and that a price under &#36;100 would be the "sweet spot." Pricing on the current &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K starts at &#36;129 for 64GB storage and Wi-Fi only connectivity, so it is not hard to imagine that Apple could introduce a new model at a lower price point or, alternatively, keep the current model as a lower-cost option alongside a new model with updated capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
Apple is said to be planning to release the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; in the first half of 2024, which would perhaps see it debut at a spring event somewhere around March or April. In the past, Apple has introduced &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K models in September 2017, May 2021, and November 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="future_apple_tv_innovations">Future Apple TV Innovations</h2><br/>
Apple is rumored to be working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/18/apple-work-on-apple-tv-homepod-continues/">some sort of product</a> that would combine the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; functionality, a smart speaker, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> camera in one device, but it's been over a year since we last heard about it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/AppleTV-and-HomePod-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793543" /><br/>
There are also rumors of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-smart-home-display/">Apple smart home display</a> that would serve as a central hub for controlling smart home products, and there is a possibility that it could have &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; functionality. This product could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-smart-home-ipad-display/">launch as soon as 2024</a>, but it is distinct from the next-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K that is also in development.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="guide_feedback">Guide Feedback</h2><br/>
Have questions about the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K or want to offer feedback on this guide? <a href="mailto:guides@macrumors.com">Send us an email here</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv/">2024 Apple TV: All the Rumors So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2024-apple-tv-all-the-rumors-so-far.2407485/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 to Launch by October 24</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-to-launch-by-october-24.2407467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:30:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming iOS 17.1 update is set to be released to the public by October 24, according to <a href="https://www.anfr.fr/liste-actualites/actualite/iphone-12-informations-sur-la-mise-a-jour-preparee-par-apple">the French regulatory group ANFR</a> (via <em><a href="https://iphonesoft.fr/2023/10/13/anfr-revele-date-sortie-maximale-ios-17-1-iphone-12-das-eleve">iPhoneSoft</a></em>). The release date was shared on the ANFR's website in an update outlining Apple's plan to address radiation levels in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912333" /><br/>
"Apple has committed to deploy an update in France," reads a translation of the update, which is in French. "This fix will be available to all users no later than October 24."<br/>
<br/>
Apple earlier this week confirmed that iOS 17.1 will include a tweak that will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-iphone-12-radiation-fix/">lower iPhone 12 radiation levels</a>. Back in September, France ordered Apple to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/france-orders-end-to-iphone-12-sales-radiation/">stop selling the iPhone 12</a> and "fix" devices to bring them into compliance with European electromagnetic radiation standards. The order came after the ANFR found that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12's Specific Absorption Rate (SAR) came in at 5.74 watts per kilogram, above the limit set by the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the ANFR made an error in its radiation tests, using a testing protocol that did not account for the off-body detection mechanism in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. iPhones have a built-in feature that allows them to increase their transmit power when not held on the body for optimized cellular performance.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the off-body detection has been "thoroughly tested and verified internationally to be an effective mechanism to comply with SAR requirements," bur nevertheless, the company has agreed to disable this feature on iPhones in France.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 is safe to use "and always has been." After the iOS 17.1 update, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models in France will no longer increase their transmit power when the off-body state is detected, so coverage in areas where cellular signal is low may cause lower cellular performance in some use cases.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 17.1 update brings a number of other changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system, including an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> favorites system, support for AirDrop over the internet, new options to see bank and card balances in the Wallet app, changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Action Button and more, with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-1-beta-features/">full list available in our iOS 17.1 features guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/ios-17-1-launch-by-october-24/">iOS 17.1 to Launch by October 24</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-to-launch-by-october-24.2407467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iMac With M2 and M2 Pro Chips Could Arrive Soon, Says Latest Conflicting Rumor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imac-with-m2-and-m2-pro-chips-could-arrive-soon-says-latest-conflicting-rumor.2407466/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:21:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>Mac Otakara</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The next-generation 24-inch iMac will likely be available with M2 and M2 Pro chip options, Thunderbolt 4 ports, Wi-Fi 6E support, and Bluetooth 5.3 support, according to a report today from <a href="https://www.macotakara.jp/macintosh/entry-45460.html">Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Hello-Tim-Cook-iMac.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-885129" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has repeatedly claimed that the next 24-inch iMac <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/05/new-imac-advanced-development/">will be equipped with the M3 chip</a>, so it's unclear if the information reported today is accurate. It is possible that Apple's plans have changed, but no other sources have indicated that the iMac will be updated with M2 and M2 Pro chips as of yet.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Mac Otakara</em> notes that some custom 24-inch iMac configurations are facing up to one-month shipping delays on Apple's online store in the U.S., but this has been the case for a while now, and there is no guarantee that an iMac refresh is imminent.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/kuo-first-m3-macbooks-unlikely-2023/">unlikely that Apple would release any new MacBooks with the M3 chip this year</a>, but a new iMac has not been ruled out this year. Apple is not expected to hold an event this October, so if there were to be a new iMac this month, it would likely be announced in a press release on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, rumors about which chip the new iMac will have and when the computer will be released remain in a state of flux. The only certain thing is that October continues to roll along without any product announcements from Apple so far.<br/>
<br/>
The current 24-inch iMac with the M1 chip was released in May 2021.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/">iMac With M2 and M2 Pro Chips Could Arrive Soon, Says Latest Conflicting Rumor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imac-with-m2-and-m2-pro-chips-could-arrive-soon-says-latest-conflicting-rumor.2407466/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 14-Inch MacBook Pro and Accessories From Plugable</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-14-inch-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-14-inch-macbook-pro-and-accessories-from-plugable.2407464/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:00:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-14-inch-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		<category>Plugable</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://plugable.com/">Plugable</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 14-inch MacBook Pro and several accessories to go along with it, including the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/tbt4-udx1">Plugable Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station</a>, the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ams-5in1e">MagSafe-Compatible Plugable USB-C 5-in-1 Hub</a>, and the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ps-epr-140c1">Plugable 140W USB-C GaN Power Adapter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-docking-station-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916860" /><br/>
Plugable is a well-established company that is best known for its docking stations, but it makes all kinds of adapters, cables, hubs, chargers, and SSDs for Macs, PCs, and other devices. Just this month, Plugable released the aforementioned Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station as its latest dock product, and it has all of the latest technologies that you want for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://plugable.com/products/tbt4-udx1">Available for &#36;289.95</a>, the Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station is equipped with a total of 11 ports, including two Thunderbolt 4 ports, 4 10Gb/s USB-A ports (one of which can be used for charging accessories), an SD card slot, audio in/out, an HDMI 2.0 port, and a 2.5GB/s Ethernet port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-docking-station-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916859" /><br/>
There's also a Thunderbolt 4 host port that provides 96W charging, which is enough power even for Apple's 16-inch MacBook Pro. Dual 4K 60Hz displays are supported, or a single 8K 30Hz display (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>/<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro/Max chips). The Thunderbolt ports can be used to charge accessories like iPhones and iPads at 15W with power distribution, so if you have two devices charging at 15W, your Mac will get 66W.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-docking-station-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916861" /><br/>
If you just need a few extra ports at an affordable price, the &#36;33 <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ams-5in1e">USB-C 5-in-1 Hub Designed for MagSafe</a> delivers. You'll need two USB-C ports to plug in this accessory, but it a cutout for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> port lets you continue to charge with the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; port on Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; MacBook Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-hub-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916862" /><br/>
The 5-in-1 Hub adds two 5Gb/s USB-A ports, a 40Gb/s USB-C port with up to 100W pass-through charging, a combination audio port, and a Gigabit Ethernet port. Up to a 6K 60Hz display is supported.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-hub-2.jpg" alt="" width="3013" height="1695" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916864" /><br/>
For charging Apple devices like the MacBook Pro, Plugable has the <a href="https://plugable.com/products/ps-epr-140c1">&#36;50 140W USB-C GaN Power Adapter</a>, which has the right output to fast charge all Apple devices up to the 16-inch MacBook Pro (note that you'll need Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Cable for the 16-inch model). Because it's using GaN technology and a flip-out plug, this is a compact charger that's ideal for travel, and it's smaller than the power adapter that comes with the 16-inch MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/plugable-power-adapter.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916865" /><br/>
We have one amazing Plugable prize pack to give away to a <em>MacRumors</em> reader. It includes a 14-inch &zwnj;M2&zwnj; MacBook Pro with 16GB RAM and 512GB storage, the Plugable Thunderbolt 4 Docking Station, the 5-in-1 USB-C Hub, and the 140W USB-C GaN Power Adapter. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/FtpQE/plugable-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Plugable Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (October 13) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on October 20. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after October 20 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/plugable/">Plugable</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/macrumors-giveaway-plugable-14-inch-macbook-pro/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win a 14-Inch MacBook Pro and Accessories From Plugable</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-14-inch-macbook-pro-and-accessories-from-plugable.2407464/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods, MacBook Air, Beats, and More at All-Time Low Prices in Wake of Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-13-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-macbook-air-beats-and-more-at-all-time-low-prices-in-wake-of-prime-day.2407459/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 09:33:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-13-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's October Prime Day happened this week, and although it's now over, we're tracking a few leftover discounts on popular Apple products. This weekend, you can still get Prime Day pricing on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, AirPods 2, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0012.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848002" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airpods-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916843" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;49 off the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C and AirPods 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-airpods-pro-2-usb-c/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C/MagSafe Case) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One of the biggest deals of the week came from Amazon, which is taking &#36;49 off the all-new AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case. It's available for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;249.00. Earlier in the week, the earbuds were priced at &#36;189.00, but that Prime Day deal has expired and the new sale is still a solid second-best price on the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/samsung-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916842" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;300 off Samsung monitors</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/samsung-viewfinity-s9-5k-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>Smart Monitor M80C for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>ViewFinity S9 Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Over at Samsung, the retailer introduced record low prices on a pair of its best monitors this week. The ViewFinity S9 5K Display is available for &#36;1,299.99 (&#36;300 off) and the Smart Monitor M8 is available for &#36;499.99 (&#36;200 off).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beats</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/beats-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916841" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;170 off Beats headphones</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us0%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/the-new-beats-studio-pro-half-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us0%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>Beats Studio Pro for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Cancelling-Earbuds-Built-Bluetooth-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB096SSCV5K%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1_sspa"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Beats Studio Buds for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09JL65GNM%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us2%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Beats Fit Pro for &#36;159.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Major Beats deals arrived at Amazon this week, headlined by nearly half off the brand new Beats Studio Pro. You can get these headphones for &#36;179.99, down from &#36;349.99, along with sales on Beats Studio Buds and Beats Fit Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916840" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker's best USB-C accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119398550">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/best-apple-deals-still-get-prime-day/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Although many of Anker's Prime Day deals have expired, there are still a few options available for anyone looking to purchase USB-C chargers and accessories for a new iPhone 15.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK6DDL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1697119464293">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119264712">67W 3-Port USB-C Wall Charger</a> - &#36;47.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C5QY4BL2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1697119578723">67W 6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;52.79 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSGH355C%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119264713">140W 6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;87.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697119398550">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916839" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;80 off the 9th generation iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-ipad/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The week's best iPad deal centered on the 9th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad, which hit &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00. This is a match of the best price we've ever seen on this tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>15-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/15in-mba-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916838" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;250 off the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-15-inch-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-Inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best MacBook-related deal this week was on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, which was marked down by &#36;250 across every model on Amazon. You can still get these deals today, including the 256GB notebook for &#36;1,049.00 and the 512GB notebook for &#36;1,249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/13in-mba-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916837" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;200 off the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/ckFMqvF4y1f">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-best-apple-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckFMqvF4y1f"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>256GB for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckFMufbzGMu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>512GB for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon wasn't the only retailer providing all-time low discounts on Apple products this week, with Best Buy discounting the 256GB 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air to &#36;899.00, down from &#36;1,099.00. You can also get the 512GB notebook at a record low price of &#36;1,199.00.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-13-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods, MacBook Air, Beats, and More at All-Time Low Prices in Wake of Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-macbook-air-beats-and-more-at-all-time-low-prices-in-wake-of-prime-day.2407459/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Former Apple Executive Mike Bell Talks AirPort, CarPlay, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell-talks-airport-carplay-and-more.2407456/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 09:18:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Lucid Senior Vice President of Digital and former Apple Executive <a href="https://lucidmotors.com/company/leadership/michael-bell">Mike Bell</a> joins us on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/former-apple-executive-mike-bell-talks-airport-carplay/id1602394741?i=1000631231829">The MacRumors Show</a> to discuss the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, AirPort, Vision Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ixsvh_MAJVY?si=cXKfUDsIVhqnZS96" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Mike worked at Apple from 1991 to 2007 and played a significant role in development of hardware products like the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, AirPort, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, as well as software features like Boot Camp. After leaving Apple, he worked at Palm, Intel, and Rivian, and now leads digital at luxury electric automaker Lucid.<br/>
<br/>
We reflect on the success of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; since Mike's work to deliver the original model and where it stands today. We also look at Apple's Vision Pro headset and consider whether it will catch on. Mike discusses AirPort, a personal-favorite product that he led, how he feels about its discontinuation, and whether Apple is likely to return to the product line in the future.<br/>
<br/>
We talk through the process and importance of integrating Apple &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; in Lucid vehicles, as well as the challenges involved in bringing new digital features to EVs. We also discuss Mike's experience of working at Apple as a senior decision-maker in the 1990s and 2000s, how the company changed in the formative period in which he was there, similarities between Lucid and Apple, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player. Watch a video version of the show <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD8VmuL7qc7ii5uyjzSRk3UM7KI_c4qC5">on the <em>MacRumors</em> YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about some of our favorite Apple accessories with YouTuber and content creator Sara Dietschy.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is now on X (formerly Twitter) <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@macrumorsshow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast!<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for more episodes, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/09/iphone-14-event-reactions-with-luke-miani/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the show, and let us know what subjects you would like the podcast to cover in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">The MacRumors Show: Former Apple Executive Mike Bell Talks AirPort, CarPlay, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell-talks-airport-carplay-and-more.2407456/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>HomePod Mini Now Three Years Old: Here&#039;s What to Expect From the Next Generation</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old-heres-what-to-expect-from-the-next-generation.2407441/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 06:58:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple announced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> three years ago today at its "Hi, Speed" event alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 Pro, offering a small form-factor version of its smart speaker for the first time, with a price tag of just &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/homepod-mini-thumb-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-770560" /><br/>
Less than half a year after announcing the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/12/apple-discontinuing-homepod/">discontinued</a> the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, leaving the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; as the company's only smart speaker until earlier this year when Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-announces-new-homepod/">relaunched the full-size HomePod</a> form factor. The newly reintroduced &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; offers a large number of features that were previously exclusive to the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;, including an Apple Watch S-series chip, a U1 ultra wideband chip, Thread support, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/homepods-now-feature-temperature-humidity-sensor/">temperature and humidity sensor</a>, and a larger backlit touch surface that illuminates from edge to edge.<br/>
<br/>
Apple refreshed the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; with color in 2021, adding Blue, Yellow, and Orange options, but the device has remained otherwise unchanged since its introduction. It is now among the oldest devices that Apple still sells, surpassed only by the Pro Display XDR and second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>What Next for the HomePod mini?</h3><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> was first to highlight Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/07/new-homepod-mini-and-high-end-homepod/">work on a second-generation HomePod mini</a> in August 2022. Gurman has since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/22/gurman-apple-not-working-on-new-homepod-mini/">expressed skepticism</a> about what a new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could offer since "the latest &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; doesn't include any major new functions that aren't already in the &#36;99 mini." <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/f1602608757.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="445" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-763787" /><br/>
A second-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could conceivably introduce a lower-latency Handoff experience with the second-generation ultra wideband chip, improved sound and microphones, and the S7, S8, S9, or S10 chip. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> requests are now processed locally on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> thanks to the improved performance of the S9 chip, so bringing the same hardware to the next-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could considerably boost &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s responsiveness. A new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; could also see specification upgrades, such as Wi-Fi 6E support.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; currently contains the S5 chip from the Apple Watch Series 5 and first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>. 2024 will likely see the introduction of the S10 chip in the next-generation Apple Watch, so that's the most advanced chip Apple could feasibly give the device if it launches before late 2025.<br/>
<br/>
The 2023 &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; contains the S7 chip, the same chip used in 2021's Apple Watch Series 7. Despite the introduction of the S8 chip in late 2022 in the Apple Watch Series 8, Apple Watch Ultra, and second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, Apple elected to use the S7 chip. This suggests it isn't certain that Apple will use its latest S-series chip in the second-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/s9-chip-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1501" height="844" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913379" /><br/>
The S6, S7, and S8 chips are all fundamentally the same and based on the A13 Bionic chip. The S9 chip, on the other hand, is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/apple-watch-series-9-updated-chip/">based on the A15 Bionic chip</a>, leading to major performance and efficiency improvements. The S6, S7, or S8 chip would still be a notable upgrade for the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;, but the S9 or S10 chip would offer even more substantial enhancements.<br/>
<br/>
It also seems highly likely that a new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; will come in a refreshed selection of color options. The current device is available in Space Gray, Blue, Yellow, White, and Orange. With the reintroduced full-size &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, Apple swapped Space Gray for Midnight, so a similar switch seems likely for the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; at a minimum.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Release Date</h3><br/>
In February, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that Apple will begin mass shipments of the second-generation &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/03/homepod-mini-2-shipping-next-year/">in the second half of 2024</a>, which seems likely given the age of the current model and apparent active development on a new version for over a year.<br/>
<br/>
It is also possible that Apple could wait to introduce a new &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; until the debut of a third-generation full-size &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, especially if it includes new features. Apple is developing an updated version of the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; that will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">7-inch display</a>, according to &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj;. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a 7-inch display is expected to come out <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/20/homepod-with-screen-delayed-next-year/">next year at the earliest</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old/">HomePod Mini Now Three Years Old: Here&#039;s What to Expect From the Next Generation</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-mini-now-three-years-old-heres-what-to-expect-from-the-next-generation.2407441/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Jelly Scrolling&#039; Rumored to Be Reduced on iPad Mini 7 Thanks to Rotated Screen Assembly</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/jelly-scrolling-rumored-to-be-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7-thanks-to-rotated-screen-assembly.2407432/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:46:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		<category>Setsuna Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>'s screen assembly will be rotated to reduce the effect of "jelly scrolling" that some users complain about with the current model, according to a Weibo leaker with an early track record for disclosing accurate information about Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/ipad-mini-9.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-818328" /><br/>
The account, known as "<a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/NnyGqvZHU#comment">Instant Digital</a>," claims that in addition to reduced jelly scrolling, the new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will also feature the A16 Bionic chip and front camera improvements.<br/>
<br/>
"Jelly scrolling" refers to screen tearing, which can cause text or images on one side of the screen to appear to be tilted downwards because of a mismatch in refresh rates. It can cause one side of the display to look as if it is responding faster than the other side in a visual disturbance that is hard to ignore once noticed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the phenomenon is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">normal behavior</a> for LCD iPads. Since LCD screens refresh line by line, there is a tiny delay between when the lines at the top and lines at the bottom are refreshed. But while this may be normal behavior for LCD screens, it can appear more obvious when observed on the ‌‌&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s smaller screen‌‌.<br/>
<br/>
Users have generally only complained about jelly scrolling when the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">in portrait orientation</a>. The issue is not reproducible in landscape orientation when scrolling, indicating this is a vertical refresh issue. According to the latest rumor, Apple plans to rotate the screen assembly to reduce the jelly scrolling effect in portrait orientation. Whether it will now become more prominent when the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is in landscape orientation is yet to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
The seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is among several devices that Apple could launch this month, the Weibo user goes on to claim. A modified first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> with a USB-C connector instead of Lightning and the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip are also apparently on the table for announcement toward the end of October. After evidence of a refreshed first-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with a USB-C connector was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/ios-17-1-apple-pencil-usb-c/">discovered in iOS 17.1 beta code</a>, Instant Digital said that "Apple has not given up on the original &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, and a USB-C version is expected to be coming soon."<br/>
<br/>
The "Instant Digital" account has shared accurate standalone rumors about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">Yellow iPhone 14 spring refresh</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted back glass</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/future-iphone-could-capture-spatial-photos-videos/">spatial video capture</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and more. That being said, questions remain about how much of the information shared by the user is original or accurate, but until a more long-term track record is established their rumors are worth highlighting.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/setsuna-digital/">Setsuna Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">&#039;Jelly Scrolling&#039; Rumored to Be Reduced on iPad Mini 7 Thanks to Rotated Screen Assembly</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/jelly-scrolling-rumored-to-be-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7-thanks-to-rotated-screen-assembly.2407432/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>California AirTag Lawsuit Widened to Include Dozens More Stalking Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/airtag-lawsuit-widened-stalking-cases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/california-airtag-lawsuit-widened-to-include-dozens-more-stalking-cases.2407426/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 04:45:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/airtag-lawsuit-widened-stalking-cases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTags</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is facing an expanded class action lawsuit in federal court in San Francisco by more than three dozen victims allegedly terrorized by stalkers using Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a>, reports <em><a href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2023/10/apple-airtags-triggered-explosion-of-stalking-reports-nationwide-lawsuit-says/">ArsTechnica</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/airtag-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-798036" /><br/>
The complaint targets Apple alleged negligence in allowing &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; to become "one of the most dangerous and frightening technologies employed by stalkers" since they can be easily used used to determine "real-time location information to track victims."<br/>
<br/>
The complaint is a revised version that was brought before a Californian judge in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/women-sue-apple-over-airtags/">December 2022</a> by two women, one of which claims her ex-boyfriend used an AirTag to track her without her consent. Since then, plaintiffs allege that there has been an "explosion of reporting" showing that &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; are often used for stalking.<br/>
<br/>
To evidence its claims, the complaint cites more than 150 police reports in the United States as of April 2022, as well as an upsurge in international stalking cases involving &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;. Plaintiffs argue that Apple has not done enough to reduce potential harms, which they claim can include financial ruin and in extreme cases murder. <br/>
<br/>
There have been multiple news stories about &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; being used for vehicle theft, stalking, and other nefarious purposes, which has led Apple to make several updates to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/10/airtag-updates-unwanted-tracking/">how AirTags work</a> to prevent criminals from taking advantage of them.<br/>
<br/>
When setting up an AirTag, for example, Apple shows warnings to thwart malicious use. The warning makes it clear that the AirTag is linked to an ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>‌, that using it to track people is a crime, and that law enforcement can request identifying information about the owner of the AirTag, which Apple will readily provide.<br/>
<br/>
With an April 2022 software update, Apple made the AirTag sound louder, also to help cut down on stalking attempts. Apple also added safety features that include Precision Finding, improved display alerts, and louder sounds that are designed to make ‌&zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;‌ more difficult to use for people-tracking purposes. Additionally, Apple released the "Tracker Detect" app that allows Android users to scan for &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; to make sure there are none around.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these updates, plaintiffs have alleged that &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; remain dangerous. For instance, one Georgia resident quoted by <em>ArsTechnica</em> reported that she and her daughter were being stalked by someone using &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; within the past two weeks "without knowing by whom or why." Although she cannot locate the &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;, she receives daily alerts from Apple and chimes from the &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; that confirm that the &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj; are still there. These chimes only signal to the victim that she's being perpetually watched. "Every day, I am reminded that me and my daughter are not safe," added the victim in the complaint.<br/>
<br/>
The complaint alleges that Apple violated federal and state laws by negligently releasing a defective product, and has been unjustly enriched while invading the privacy of those victim unwittingly being tracked on its devices. Plaintiffs are seeking damages to all persons in the US who own iOS or Android devices, which includes classes of users who were stalked, as well as those who were allegedly at risk of stalking. <br/>
<br/>
The complaint also seeks a court order "enjoining Apple from further unlawful, unfair, and/or fraudulent practices with respect to the design, manufacture, and release into the market of its &zwnj;AirTags&zwnj;."<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to move to dismiss the lawsuit by October 27, the deadline by which the company must respond to the amended complaint.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airtags.232">AirTags</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/airtag-lawsuit-widened-stalking-cases/">California AirTag Lawsuit Widened to Include Dozens More Stalking Cases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/california-airtag-lawsuit-widened-to-include-dozens-more-stalking-cases.2407426/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
