<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:03:08 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Ends Repair Relationship With Samsung</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/ifixit-samsung-repair-relationship-ends/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-ends-repair-relationship-with-samsung.2427235/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:20:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/ifixit-samsung-repair-relationship-ends/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Device repair company iFixit is ending its repair relationship with Samsung, iFixit <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/96162/were-ending-our-samsung-collaboration">announced in a blog post</a> today. The partnership is being dissolved <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/31/samsung-ifixit-self-repair-partnership/">after a two-year period</a> because iFixit and Samsung have been unable to negotiate a new deal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933041" /><br/>
iFixit said that it wanted to build a repair-friendly ecosystem for independent businesses and consumers with its Samsung Repair Hub, something that it has not been able to do. The company says it ultimately doubts "Samsung's commitment to making repair more accessible."<br/>
<br/>
Samsung used iFixit to facilitate a self-repair program for its customers, with iFixit offering step-by-step repair guides for replacing display assemblies, back glass, charging ports, and other components. iFixit says that there were continual obstacles working with Samsung, including the high price of components.<br/>
<br/>
Repair parts "were so costly" that customers ended up replacing their devices rather than repairing them. Batteries and screens, for example, were in pre-glued bundles and customers could not replace a battery without also swapping out the screen, which is a much more expensive repair. iFixit was also unable to provide parts to repair shops at prices and quantities "that made business sense," and iFixit CEO Kyle Wiens told <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/samsung/2024/5/23/24162135/ifixit-end-samsung-repair-parts-deal">The Verge</a></em> that Samsung limited iFixit to selling no more than seven parts per customer within a three-month period.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung never even shipped iFixit components for the Galaxy S23 series, the Z Flip 5, and the Z Fold 5, and has not sent anything since the S22 lineup launched. Samsung is instead selling components for its latest smartphones through Encompass. A <a href="https://www.404media.co/samsung-requires-independent-repair-shops-to-share-customer-data-snitch-on-people-who-use-aftermarket-parts-leaked-contract-shows/">separate report from <em>404 Media</em></a> gives further insight into Samsung's repair requirements, with a leaked contract suggesting that independent repair shops must give Samsung the contact information and other details of every customer that has a repair done. Samsung's contract also has a clause that requires repair shops to "immediately disassemble" any smartphone that has been previously repaired with aftermarket parts.<br/>
<br/>
Starting in June, iFixit will no longer be Samsung's designated third-party parts and tools distributor. Existing repair information won't be removed from iFixit, but iFixit also will no longer collaborate with Samsung to develop new repair manuals. iFixit plans to continue to sell parts and repair kits for Samsung devices using OEM parts when available as well as aftermarket components, which is similar to what it does for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> replacement parts.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung previously worked with iFixit to <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/50450/samsung-galaxy-upcycling-unlocked-smartphone-smarthome-project">announce a Galaxy Upcycling</a> program that ultimately never materialized, so this is iFixit's second failed Samsung venture. "We clearly didn't learn our lesson the first time, and two years ago we let them convince us they were serious about embracing repair," reads the iFixit blog.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit said that it "tried to make this work," but Samsung was profiting from unpaid work on repair guides. Ultimately, iFixit is "bummed" and won't let "one bad apple spoil the bunch." iFixit is <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/collaborations">still working with</a> Google, Valve, Lenovo, Motorola, Microsoft, and others on repair ventures.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung will likely bring more of its self-repair options in house, mirroring what Apple does. Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/11/17/apple-launches-self-service-repair/">a Self Service Repair program</a> that was introduced in 2021, with Apple offering repair manuals and components so customers can do their own repairs.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/ifixit-samsung-repair-relationship-ends/">iFixit Ends Repair Relationship With Samsung</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-ends-repair-relationship-with-samsung.2427235/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pixelmator Pro Gains AI-Powered Background Removal Tool</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/pixelmator-ai-background-removal-tool/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pixelmator-pro-gains-ai-powered-background-removal-tool.2427230/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:32:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/pixelmator-ai-background-removal-tool/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular photo editing app Pixelmator Pro was today updated with an overhauled set of AI-powered masking tools that make it easier than ever to make selective edits. Masking was "reengineered from the ground up" in the new 3.6 version of Pixelmator Pro, so it's quicker to create and refine masks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/pixelmator-pro-hide-background.jpg" alt="" width="1488" height="837" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952158" /><br/>
There is a new Hide Background option that uses AI to nondestructively remove the entire background from an image with a click. The tool detects the subject of the image and adds a background mask to hide the rest of what's in the photo.<br/>
<br/>
Masking a layer or creating a mask from a layer can now be done with a double click on the canvas with the Arrange tool, and then there are controls available for resizing and repositioning the mask. Pixelmator says this makes it easier to do things like round image corners or crop individual layers in multi-layer compositions.<br/>
<br/>
Tools for refining masks are now located at the bottom of the screen whenever a mask is selected or created, so it's faster to adjust transparency, change edge softness, invert the mark, add a new mask, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Pixelmator has also gained support for vector masks, so layers can be masked into specific shapes. Adding a vector mask causes the area inside the vector shape to remain visible, while other areas are hidden. Masking a layer can be done by selecting a shape from the Mask menu at the top of the layers sidebar or creating a mask with the Pen tool. Vector masks are editable, so each point can be adjusted just like a regular shape.<br/>
<br/>
The new features are available for free to current Pixelmator Pro users. Pixelmator Pro is priced at &#36;50 and it can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a>. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pixelmator-pro/id1289583905?mt=12">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/pixelmator-ai-background-removal-tool/">Pixelmator Pro Gains AI-Powered Background Removal Tool</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pixelmator-pro-gains-ai-powered-background-removal-tool.2427230/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Search the Web With a Phone Call Using This New Arc Search Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/arc-search-call-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/search-the-web-with-a-phone-call-using-this-new-arc-search-feature.2427227/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:17:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/arc-search-call-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Arc Search from The Browser Company was today updated with a new "Call Arc" feature that's designed to let you conduct a search in a gesture that mimics a phone call. To use the feature, open up Arc Search, raise the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to your ear, and ask a question.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1eiRhBRVt_s" title="Call Arc | For questions on the go" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The gesture of raising the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to your ear activates the search option, and answers are provided verbally, so the entire voice-based search experience makes it look as if you're simply talking on the phone.<br/>
<blockquote>Arc Search now has voice-activated search, triggered by holding your phone to your ear and saying your query -- just like you're making a phone call. Upon using Call Arc, you'll instantly hear your search results, accompanied by an animated smiley face! You can also click "Read More" to access full Browse for Me results for each query.</blockquote>After asking a question, Arc Search will play hold music briefly before providing a verbal answer and standing by for another question. The interface of the voice search resembles a phone call interface with a smiley face, an end call option, and a "speaker" option to have results spoken aloud.<br/>
<br/>
Arc Search <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/arc-search-iphone-app-ai/">first launched in January</a> as search app that incorporates AI to present search results in a curated, easy-to-read format. It has a minimalist browser interface where users can conduct a standard search or use the "browse for me" option to get an AI-summarized list of results to a query, similar to what you might get from a Chatbot.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/arc-search-voice-search.jpg" alt="" width="5356" height="3013" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952153" /><br/>
Browse for Me is powered by large language models (LLMs) from OpenAI and others, and there's also a "pinch to summarize" feature that works with any webpage and an option to enable a reader mode to get rid of cruft on websites.<br/>
<br/>
Arc Search is available for free on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and requires iOS 16 or later. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/arc-search/id6472513080">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/arc-search-call-feature/">Search the Web With a Phone Call Using This New Arc Search Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/search-the-web-with-a-phone-call-using-this-new-arc-search-feature.2427227/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS 15 System Settings to Get Design Overhaul</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/macos-15-system-settings-design/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-15-system-settings-to-get-design-overhaul.2427223/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 12:51:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/macos-15-system-settings-design/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a> update that is set to debut at WWDC in June, Apple plans to rearrange "menus and app UIs," according to a report from <em><a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/05/23/system-settings-getting-shuffled-again-in-macos-15-among-other-ui-tweaks?utm_medium=rss">AppleInsider</a></em>. The System Settings app, which was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/06/macos-ventura-system-settings-app/">last updated with macOS Ventura</a>, will get one of the biggest updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macOS-15-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942568" /><br/>
With macOS Ventura, Apple renamed the System Preferences app to System Settings, introducing a design similar to the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. System Settings in &zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj; is said to feature a new organizational system based on "priority and overall importance."<br/>
<br/>
The Notifications and Sound categories in System Settings will be moved lower in the list, with General settings moved up right under Network settings. Apple plans to move the existing Wallpaper and Displays sections into the same section with General settings, and Privacy and Security will be paired with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> and Password and other relevant settings. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and Spotlight will be paired with Internet Accounts and Game Center.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also reportedly plans to redesign the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; menu bar icon, making a flat black and white icon to replace the current colorful icon, and there are said to be design changes coming to Calculator (a more iOS-like design) and Safari (a unified menu for page controls). Other rumored &zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj; changes include a Printable Account Recovery Summary option, a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> preference pane, and a "modern" user interface for AirDrop.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's annual Worldwide Developers Conference keynote is set to take place on Monday, June 10, and it will see Apple unveil &zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, tvOS 18, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2, and watchOS 11.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/macos-15-system-settings-design/">macOS 15 System Settings to Get Design Overhaul</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-15-system-settings-to-get-design-overhaul.2427223/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook With Foldable Display Will Actually Have 18.8-Inch Screen, Analyst Says</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-with-foldable-display-will-actually-have-18-8-inch-screen-analyst-says.2427206/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:59:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		<category>Foldable MacBook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Less than two hours after Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/20-inch-foldable-macbook-crease-free-rumor/">MacBook with either an 18.8-inch or 20.2-inch foldable screen</a> would launch in 2026, display industry expert Ross Young has said the device will indeed feature around an 18.8-inch screen.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Foldable-Screen-MacBook-Concept-Astropad.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952144" /><em>A foldable-screen MacBook concept <a href="https://astropad.com/blog/foldable-mac-screen/">by Astropad</a></em></div><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1793657931910816161">post on social media platform X</a>, limited to his paying subscribers, Young said he expects the device to be equipped with an 18.76-inch display instead of a 20.25-inch display for "cost reasons." In a folded position, Kuo said an 18.8-inch MacBook would be similar in size to a traditional 13-inch or 14-inch MacBook.<br/>
<br/>
It is expected that a MacBook with a foldable screen would feature an all-screen design with a virtual keyboard, but exact design details have yet to be rumored.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said Apple is aiming to make the foldable screen "as crease-free as possible," and he said this could result in the device being nearly as expensive as Apple's Vision Pro headset, which starts at &#36;3,499. He also said the foldable-screen MacBook will be equipped with Apple's next-generation M5 chip, which has yet to be announced.<br/>
<br/>
It seems like a foldable-screen MacBook is still a few years away, and Apple will firm up its plans for the device as its launch gets closer.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-macbook/">Foldable MacBook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">MacBook With Foldable Display Will Actually Have 18.8-Inch Screen, Analyst Says</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-with-foldable-display-will-actually-have-18-8-inch-screen-analyst-says.2427206/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces &#039;Tap to Pay on iPhone&#039; Now Available in Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-launches-in-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-canada.2427199/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:47:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-launches-in-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/newsroom/2024/05/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-canada/">announced</a> that "Tap to Pay on iPhone" is available in Canada starting today through select payment platforms in the country.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/Apple-Tap-to-Pay-iPhone.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836277" /><br/>
Tap to Pay on iPhone allows businesses to accept contactless payments on an iPhone, with no additional point-of-sale hardware like a Square Terminal required. The feature allows customers to pay by simply tapping their iPhone or Apple Watch, contactless credit card or debit card, or other contactless payment option on the merchant's iPhone. Payment is securely completed using the same NFC technology behind Apple Pay.<br/>
<br/>
Businesses in Canada can offer Tap to Pay on iPhone through iPhone apps offered by Adyen, Moneris, Stripe, and Square. In the coming months, Apple said Aurus, Chase, Fiserv, and Helcim will also offer the feature in the country.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said Tap to Pay on iPhone will be available at Apple Store locations across Canada, and at merchants such as Sephora, later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Launched in 2022, Tap to Pay on iPhone is <a href="https://developer.apple.com/tap-to-pay/regions/">also available in</a> the U.S., Australia, Brazil, France, Japan, the Netherlands, Taiwan, the U.K., and Ukraine.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-launches-in-canada/">Apple Announces &#039;Tap to Pay on iPhone&#039; Now Available in Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-canada.2427199/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon and Best Buy Take Up to &#36;300 Off Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/300-off-m3-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-and-best-buy-take-up-to-300-off-apples-m3-macbook-pro.2427198/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:03:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/300-off-m3-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a few discounts on Apple's 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX1NXX6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmjldMyz4px">Best Buy</a>, including multiple record low prices on the notebook. Shoppers should note that at Best Buy, you'll need a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership in order to see the final deal prices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-blue-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935646" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The most notable discount is on the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro (16GB RAM/1TB) for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX1NXX6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,799.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,999.00 [<a href="https://howl.me/cmjldMyz4px">matched at Best Buy</a>]. There's also the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro (8GB RAM/512GB) for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JLWJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,449.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.00 [<a href="https://howl.me/cmjlfPdWVBS">matched at Best Buy</a>], which is a second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX1NXX6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch M3 MacBook Pro (16GB/1TB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for an upgraded model, Amazon has the 14-inch M3 Max MacBook Pro (1TB) for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;2,899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;3,199.00. This is an all-time low price on the high-end MacBook Pro, and at &#36;300 off it's one of the steepest discounts we've seen on the late 2023 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch M3 Max MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;2,899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Amazon has one notable discount on the larger 16-inch MacBook Pro. You can get the M3 Pro/36GB RAM/512GB 16-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5L3PPZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;2,599.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;2,899.00. This one is only available in Silver, and it has a delivery estimate of May 25 for Prime members, or May 28 for regular shipping.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5L3PPZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>16-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro (36GB/512GB) for &#36;2,599.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/300-off-m3-macbook-pro/">Amazon and Best Buy Take Up to &#36;300 Off Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-and-best-buy-take-up-to-300-off-apples-m3-macbook-pro.2427198/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>20-Inch MacBook With Nearly &#039;Crease-Free&#039; Foldable Screen Rumored</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/20-inch-foldable-macbook-crease-free-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/20-inch-macbook-with-nearly-crease-free-foldable-screen-rumored.2427196/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:48:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/20-inch-foldable-macbook-crease-free-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Foldable MacBook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LG is aiming to begin mass production of display panels for a MacBook with a 20.2-inch or an 18.8-inch foldable screen in the fourth quarter of 2025, according to information shared today by Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/space-black-mbp.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="902" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919458" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple%E7%9A%84%E9%A6%96%E6%AC%BE%E6%8A%98%E7%96%8A%E7%94%A2%E5%93%81-%E5%85%A8%E8%9E%A2%E5%B9%95%E6%8A%98%E7%96%8Amacbook%E8%AA%BF%E6%9F%A5%E6%9B%B4%E6%96%B0-apples-first-folding-product-the-full-screen-foldable-macbook-0a78c2772568">post on Medium</a>, Kuo said Apple is aiming to make the foldable screen "as crease-free as possible," which will require the use of high-cost components. As a result, he said the foldable MacBook could be nearly as expensive as Apple's Vision Pro headset, which starts at &#36;3,499. The 16-inch MacBook Pro currently starts at &#36;2,499.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo estimated that foldable MacBook shipments will exceed one million units in 2026, suggesting that the device will launch in around two years from now.<br/>
<br/>
He expects the device to feature Apple's next-generation M5 chip, which has yet to be announced.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo is one of three sources to have mentioned a 20-inch MacBook, alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/31/apple-foldable-notebook-2025/">display industry analyst Ross Young</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/apple-20-inch-display-future-macbook-pro/">Korean website <em>The Elec</em></a>. However, there is no guarantee that the device progresses beyond the prototyping stage.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-macbook/">Foldable MacBook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/20-inch-foldable-macbook-crease-free-rumor/">20-Inch MacBook With Nearly &#039;Crease-Free&#039; Foldable Screen Rumored</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/20-inch-macbook-with-nearly-crease-free-foldable-screen-rumored.2427196/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: iPads Retained and Repurposed Much More Often Than iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/ipads-retained-more-often-than-iphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-ipads-retained-and-repurposed-much-more-often-than-iphones.2427194/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:17:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/ipads-retained-more-often-than-iphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> owners are more likely to keep or repurpose their old devices compared to iPhones, according to data from <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/apple-customers-also-just-hang-on">Consumer Intelligence Research Partners</a> (CIRP).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Fanned-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-869880" /><br/>
The data, covering the twelve months ending in March 2024, shows that 67 percent of repeat &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; buyers keep their old iPads or pass them on to family and friends. This is a notable contrast to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users, where only 41 percent keep or hand down their previous phones. About one-third of old iPads are handed down to family members or friends, compared to about 10 percent of old iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
This suggests that iPads, even when they are replaced, remain highly desirable and usable, which diminishes the urgency to upgrade to a newer model. This behavior contrasts with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users, who are much more likely to trade in their old devices. Nearly half of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; upgraders trade in their previous phones, taking advantage of the secondary market and higher trade-in values. In contrast, fewer than 10 percent of &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; upgraders opt for trade-ins.<br/>
<br/>
23 percent of &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; upgraders report replacing their old devices due to loss, theft, or damage, whereas only six percent of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; upgraders cite these reasons. This indicates that iPads are frequently replaced out of necessity rather than a desire to upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/cirp-ipad-upgrades-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="827" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-952052" /><br/>
CIRP's report also sheds light on the upgrade cycles for these devices. Forty percent of &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users wait three years or more before upgrading, a figure that has steadily increased over recent years. This is in stark contrast to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users, who typically upgrade more frequently and are influenced by a much stronger trade-in market.<br/>
<br/>
These trends suggest that iPads continue to serve valuable roles within households even after being replaced by newer models. The secondary market for refurbished iPads appears to be much less developed than that for iPhones, possibly due to the high retained value that old iPads provide to their owners. While Apple may prefer customers to be motivated to upgrade to the latest models for their new features, the data indicates that many &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; upgrades are still driven by necessity rather than desire.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/ipads-retained-more-often-than-iphones/">Report: iPads Retained and Repurposed Much More Often Than iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-ipads-retained-and-repurposed-much-more-often-than-iphones.2427194/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>5 Reasons to Use OpenAI&#039;s ChatGPT App for Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/5-reasons-to-use-openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-reasons-to-use-openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac.2427193/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:07:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/5-reasons-to-use-openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On May 13, OpenAI during its Spring Update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/chatgpt-mac-app/">announced</a> that it would be releasing a desktop ChatGPT app for the Mac in the "coming weeks," and said that ahead of a wider launch it had started rolling out the app to some ChatGPT Plus subscribers. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/chat-gpt-mac-app.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952028" /><br/>
After testing the app for a few days, we thought it was worth sharing some reasons why ChatGPT users may find that the Mac app is a useful addition to their AI-assisted workflow. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Access the ChatGPT Launcher</h2><br/>
For a while now, it's been possible to use OpenAI's chatbot on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> via the official <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/chatgpt/id6448311069">ChatGPT iOS app</a>, but most desktop users have relied on visiting the website in a browser. Thanks to ChatGPT for Mac, things feel a lot more integrated. Using the keyboard shortcut Option + Space, you can instantly invoke the app's Launcher and ask the conversational AI to help you with some task or project, but you also get fast access to several other key features. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/6chatgpt-mac-app.jpg" alt="" width="1104" height="290" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951957" /><br/>
The small window that appears on your desktop feels similar to when you invoke Spotlight (Command + Space) in macOS: It floats above any windows or apps that you have open and feels just as convenient. A paperclip button lets you include a file or photo that you may want to get help with, and adding an attachment sends it to ChatGPT where you can ask follow-up questions in a dedicated app window.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Take a Screenshot</h2><br/>
Clicking the paperclip icon also brings up some useful additional options, such as the ability to take a screenshot of any open app window (even if it's off-screen) or your entire desktop, and query it with ChatGPT. For example, we queried a screenshot of a recent <em>MacRumors</em> article covering <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-music-reveals-top-10-albums/">Apple Music's Top 10 Albums of All Time</a>, and asked ChatGPT to provide a summary of top critics' reviews for each album, which it duly did.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/1chatgpt-mac-app-screenshot.jpg" alt="" width="2940" height="1912" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952035" /><br/>
On another occasion, we got ChatGPT to extract the text from a dropdown selection menu on Apple's website and format it in HTML as an unordered list, which it did in seconds. From proofing an open document to getting troubleshooting help, it's easy to imagine all manner of scenarios where this feature could help save time and improve productivity.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/2chatgpt-mac-app-screenshot.jpg" alt="" width="2940" height="1912" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952036" /><br/>
Currently, it's not possible to directly query ChatGPT about what is shown on your Mac's screen, but OpenAI says this feature is coming in a future update. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Take a Photo</h2><br/>
"Take a Photo" is another option that you can access via the paperclip button. Clicking it automatically brings up the current output of your Mac's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> camera or an attached webcam. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/chatgpt-photo.jpg" alt="" width="1752" height="1458" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952039" /><br/>
This is useful if you just want to hold an object in front of your Mac that you'd like to query. However, you can also select the camera of your nearby &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which gives you more freedom to move around and line up the subject of your photo more carefully. <br/>
<br/>
The only problem right now is that the shutter button remains on the camera feed on your Mac's screen, rather than switching to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. This is probably an oversight that OpenAI will rectify soon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Customize ChatGPT</h2><br/>
In the app's settings (accessed via ChatPGT ➝ Settings… in the menu bar when the app's main window is active) there are several options that let you customize how ChatGPT works. You can control whether or not OpenAI uses your content to train its models, as well as change the desktop launcher keyboard shortcut and enable/disable GPT capabilities including web browsing, DALL·E image generator, and Code Interpreter. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/chatgpt-mac-customization.jpg" alt="" width="2940" height="1912" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952040" /><br/>
You can also add custom instructions that influence how ChatGPT responds (also known as prompt engineering). So you can make responses more formal or more casual, or specify how long or short they should be. You can also personalize ChatGPT to cosplay a certain profession or character. If you want it to respond like an academic thesis advisor, or Samuel L Jackson, for example, you can specify that in settings.<br/>
<br/>
The main app window also lets you access your conversation history and switch between any custom GPTs you have parked in your sidebar. Not only that, you can choose which version of ChatGPT you wish to query. For example, the introduction of the new multimodal GPT-4o model enhances response times, improves reasoning capabilities, and offers a better understanding of images and other content types.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Voice Chat</h2><br/>
When interacting with ChatGPT in the app's main window, there are buttons to dictate your query or alternatively start a two-way voice chat with the bot. In theory it sounds great, but in practice there's a delay between responses, and you have to wait for ChatGPT to stop speaking before you can give it a follow-up query or command. It's also not possible to access other features like taking a photo via voice. Fortunately, there's more to come on this front.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/chatgpt-voice-mac.jpg" alt="" width="1582" height="972" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952041" /><br/>
At OpenAI's Spring Update, the company demoed ChatGPT's new real-time voice conversation feature, which includes the ability to interrupt the chatbot and redirect the conversation. As of writing, the ChatGPT Mac app does not support these features, but OpenAI says we should see them added to GPT-4o in the coming weeks.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summing Up</h2><br/>
If you are a regular user of ChatGPT on Mac, using OpenAI's official app should be your go-to method of interactig with the AI chatbot. For a first version, the client is surprisingly polished, and invoking the Launcher via a keyboard shortcut makes using ChatGPT quicker and easier than ever before. It also offers a peek into a possible future where ChatGPT is fully integrated with Apple's operating systems.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/4chatgpt-mac-app.jpg" alt="" width="1020" height="478" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951955" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/apple-finalizing-deal-openai-chatgpt-ios-18/">Apple Wrapping Up OpenAI Deal to Bring ChatGPT Features to iOS 18</a></li></ul><br/>
Note that the ChatGPT Mac app is currently only available to <a href="https://openai.com/index/chatgpt-plus/">Plus subscribers</a> (&#36;20 per month), and only a limited subset of those users have been offered the download so far. We will say that there are download links to the app floating around on social media, and there is a fairly reliable way for any Plus subscriber to bypass the waitlist and get it to work. But if you have the patience to wait in line, OpenAI says the ChatGPT Mac app will be available to both subscribers and free users in the near future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/5-reasons-to-use-openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac/">5 Reasons to Use OpenAI&#039;s ChatGPT App for Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-reasons-to-use-openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac.2427193/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Bing, Copilot, DuckDuckGo, ChatGPT Search Down on Microsoft Outage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/bing-copilot-duckduckgo-chatgpt-search-down/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bing-copilot-duckduckgo-chatgpt-search-down-on-microsoft-outage.2427186/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:04:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/bing-copilot-duckduckgo-chatgpt-search-down/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		<category>Bing</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A significant Microsoft outage has affected several key services, including Bing.com, Copilot for web and mobile, Copilot in Windows, ChatGPT internet search, and DuckDuckGo. The disruption began around 3.00 a.m. Eastern Time, primarily impacting users in Asia and Europe.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/microsoft-bing-chatgpt.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884498" /><br/>
User <a href="https://x.com/netblocks/status/1793597163035115998">reports</a> and <em>MacRumors</em>' tests indicate that attempts to access Bing.com result in either a blank page or a 429 HTTP code error. Notably, the Bing search functionality remains operational if accessed directly via a <a href="https://www4.bing.com/">specific URL</a>, though the homepage remains inaccessible. <br/>
<br/>
For users needing to perform searches on Bing, accessing the search engine directly through the alternative URL is a workaround. However, Copilot services are entirely offline across all platforms, including the website, app, and Windows integration.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-outage-affects-bing-copilot-duckduckgo-and-chatgpt-internet-search/">Bleeping Computer</a></em>, ChatGPT internet search and DuckDuckGo are also experiencing disruptions due to their reliance on the Bing API. DuckDuckGo users encounter an error message stating, "There was an error displaying the search results. Please try again." Despite the widespread impact, Microsoft has not yet issued a statement, though OpenAI has acknowledged the ChatGPT internet search issues on its <a href="https://status.openai.com/">support page</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bing/">Bing</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/bing-copilot-duckduckgo-chatgpt-search-down/">Bing, Copilot, DuckDuckGo, ChatGPT Search Down on Microsoft Outage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bing-copilot-duckduckgo-chatgpt-search-down-on-microsoft-outage.2427186/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>X Confirms Plan to Make &#039;Likes&#039; Private, Remove Likes Tab From Profiles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/x-twitter-to-make-likes-private/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-confirms-plan-to-make-likes-private-remove-likes-tab-from-profiles.2427177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 02:02:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/x-twitter-to-make-likes-private/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Social media platform X (formerly Twitter) will soon stop showing public "likes" on users' profile pages, the company has said. The plan was confirmed on Wedndesday by X engineers, after <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris uncovered a flag in X's iOS app revealing the coming change.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
Perris found that turning off the flag completely removes the "Likes" tab from all user profiles. His discovery was <a href="https://x.com/aaronp613/status/1793047277440815421">shared on X</a>, which was then reposted and subsequently confirmed by X engineers.<br/>
<br/>
"Yeah, we are making likes private," <a href="https://x.com/wanghaofei/status/1793096366132195529">responded</a> X's director of engineering Haofei Wang. "Public likes are incentivizing the wrong behavior. For example, many people feel discouraged from liking content that might be 'edgy' in fear of retaliation from trolls, or to protect their public image.<br/>
<br/>
"Soon you'll be able to like without worrying who might see it," Wang continued. "Also a reminder that the more posts you like, the better your For you algorithm will become," he added.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Yeah, we are making likes private.<br><br>Public likes are incentivizing the wrong behavior. For example, many people feel discouraged from liking content that might be &quot;edgy&quot; in fear of retaliation from trolls, or to protect their public image.<br><br>Soon you’ll be able to like without… <a href="https://t.co/vPGllc4pB0">https://t.co/vPGllc4pB0</a></p>&mdash; Haofei (@wanghaofei) <a href="https://twitter.com/wanghaofei/status/1793096366132195529?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 22, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
To clear up some confusion among users, X senior software engineer Enrique Barragan also responded with a <a href="https://x.com/enriquebrgn/status/1793140173913641271">post</a>, saying that users will still be able to see who liked their posts, as well as the like count for all posts, replies, and so on. The change involves hiding which posts other people liked, which means removing the Liked tab on public profiles.<br/>
<br/>
X Premium subscribers have been able to optionally hide the Likes tab on their profile, but the platform is set to take it away wholesale. It's not clear when the change will be rolled out, but once it does, everyone on X, including owner Musk – who has received blowback in the past for liking controversial posts – will be able to like whatever they want without it being made public.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/x-twitter-to-make-likes-private/">X Confirms Plan to Make &#039;Likes&#039; Private, Remove Likes Tab From Profiles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-confirms-plan-to-make-likes-private-remove-likes-tab-from-profiles.2427177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 M4 Mac Mini: What We Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m4-mac-mini-what-we-know.2427154/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:28:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini&#038;post_date=1716424106/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>M4 Mac mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working to refresh the entire Mac lineup with chips in the M4 series, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> could get an update as soon as late 2024. Apple is expected to skip the M3 chip, going straight from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> to M4.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946149" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Mini-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything that we know about the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; refresh so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple hasn't changed the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; design in many years, and there are no rumors of a design update coming in 2024. Apple did make the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; a little bit thicker and lighter when it was refreshed in 2023, and that same design will likely be used for the 2024 model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said in January that the "next new &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;" will have the same "form factor design." Back in 2021, there were rumors that Apple was working on a &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; with a plexiglass top and other design changes, but that device never materialized.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; is Apple's smallest, most portable desktop machine, measuring in at 7.75 inches square and 1.41 inches thick. The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; is meant to be connected to a standalone display, keyboard, and mouse, and it does not ship with those accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="m4_chip">M4 Chip</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be equipped with Apple's M4 and M4 Pro chips, with Apple skipping the M3 line entirely and going from &zwnj;M2&zwnj; to M4.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the M4 chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, and the chip is built on a second-generation 3-nanometer technology. Compared to the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, the M4 chip offers 50 percent faster CPU performance and up to 4x faster rendering performance.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 chip features a 10-core CPU and a 10-core GPU. There is a variant of the M4 with a 9-core CPU, but Apple is unlikely to use it in the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;, instead reserving it for the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There is also a more advanced 16-core Neural Engine and the GPU supports hardware-accelerated ray tracing, a feature not available with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;. According to Apple, the Neural Engine in the M4 chip is an "absolute powerhouse for AI."<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know details on the M4 Pro because that chip is not expected to come out until later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; will be refreshed alongside the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/when-to-expect-the-first-m4-macs/">in late 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; was last refreshed in January 2023, so it will be close to two years old when it is updated. Apple often does Mac refreshes in October or November, so we could see the M4 &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; sometime in that timeframe.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/">Apple&#039;s 2024 M4 Mac Mini: What We Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m4-mac-mini-what-we-know.2427154/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Anker&#039;s Latest 3-in-1 Power Bank is a Versatile On-the-Go Powerhouse</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/anker-3-in-1-power-bank/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ankers-latest-3-in-1-power-bank-is-a-versatile-on-the-go-powerhouse.2427150/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:11:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/anker-3-in-1-power-bank&#038;post_date=1716423106/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Anker</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular accessory brand Anker has just launched a new <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1637%3Fvariant%3D43609981550742">10K version of its 3-in-1 power bank</a> that offers up to 30 watts of charging power, a convenient display to quickly view exact charge status, an integrated USB-C cable for both input and output, and built-in folding prongs to recharge directly from a power outlet. I've recently been testing one of these Anker power banks out, and it has become a must-have accessory for my gear bag.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-front.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951991" /><br/>
Competitively priced at &#36;44.99, the 10,000 mAh capacity means I can charge up my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max more than one and a half times while on the go, which is plenty for a long day out or even a weekend trip where easy access to power might be iffy. And the 30-watt charging speed means it'll charge my devices up quickly, meaning spending less time with my phone awkwardly tethered to a power bank while I'm out and about. A quick charge during a lunch or dinner  is more than enough to keep my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> topped off for the remainder of the day.<br/>
<br/>
The integrated USB-C cable is only 10 inches (0.25 meters) long, which feels just about right for hooking things up without having to deal with excess cable. And the fact it's integrated into the power bank means there's no chance of losing or forgetting the cable.<br/>
<br/>
As with some other recent Anker power banks with integrated cables, the cable on this one also serves as a convenient lanyard for the power bank that cleverly uses the USB-C connector to hold things together. It will let you keep the power bank on your wrist if needed, or clipped to a bag or other item to help make it easier to find. While I do have some concerns over the long-term stress of using the USB-C cable in this way, so far in my testing on this bank and similar ones from Anker, the cable and connector have proven durable enough and Anker claims the cable has been tested to withstand at least 10,000 bends over its lifetime.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-prongs.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952002" /><br/>
That integrated cable not only provides for rapid charging of a connected device, but it can also be used to quickly recharge the power bank itself, so if you've got a convenient USB-C power adapter or a laptop available, you can easily charge off of one of those. But even more conveniently, folding prongs allow the power bank to be recharged straight from most power outlets in the U.S., Canada, Japan, and anywhere else that uses Type A/B plugs and sockets. The folding prongs also allow the power bank to easily offer passthrough charging, recharging both the power bank and a connected device simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the integrated USB-C cable and the folding prongs, there's a third power option on this power bank, and that's a dedicated USB-C port that can support both input and output. This of course requires you to bring along a separate cable, but it offers the ability to charge multiple devices simultaneously. Both the integrated cable and the USB-C port support up to 30 watts input and output, although that output will be split if you have multiple devices charging simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-side.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951992" /><br/>
In my testing, it took about two hours to charge the power bank to full from empty, regardless of whether I used the built-in prongs or a USB-C power source of at least 30 watts. Going in the opposite direction, the power bank took about two hours to charge my &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max from 10% up to full, although it reached 80% within 50 minutes with the final 20% taking around 70 minutes at a slower rate to prevent overcharging. Anker's ActiveShield 2.0 temperature monitoring also helps protect devices from damage during charging.<br/>
<br/>
After delivering that 90% charge to my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, the power bank still had 47% of its own battery charge left, so I can get around 1.75 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charges out of a fully charged power bank. With the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max carrying a 4,441 mAh battery and the power bank including a 10,000 mAh battery, you might think it could recharge the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at least twice, but energy loss within the battery cells and circuitry and during the transfer process reduces that figure as is true of any power bank.<br/>
<br/>
Anker has been integrating status displays into a number of recent charging products, and this 3-in-1 power bank is no exception. When it's off, the display is invisible below the glossy surface of the power bank, but while charging other devices, being charged itself, or at the press of a button on the side of the bank, it lights up to show the exact percentage of charge remaining in the power bank. When the power bank  is charging, a green LED next to the display flashes, letting you know at a glance that power is flowing to the bank's battery. The display is easily readable indoors, but does get tougher to read outdoors in bright sunlight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-3-in-1-power-bank-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951993" /><br/>
The power bank's overall design is a relatively simple plastic brick shape but with some visual interest in the form of a glossy front with some Anker branding and the display hidden beneath the surface, a matte back with a substantial amount of small regulatory and informational text, and ribbed sides.<br/>
<br/>
Along those sides, you'll find the folding prongs on one side, the attachment point for the integrated cable, the USB-C port, and a button to manually activate the display on the opposite side, and a small bracket where the integrated cable loops through to create the lanyard on the top. The power bank measures approximately 4.25 x 2.0 x 1.2 inches (10.8 x 5.1 x 3.0 cm) and weighs approximately 8.8 ounces (250 grams), so it's reasonably pocketable but a bit on the thick side, so some may feel more comfortable carrying it in a bag rather than in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
The Anker 10K 3-in-1 power bank is available in five colors: Truffle Black, Pastel Pink, Ice Lake Blue, Classic White, and Lilac Purple. It's priced at &#36;44.99 at both <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX4992Z8%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1716409644147">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1637%3Fvariant%3D43609981550742">Anker's own site</a>, with a promo currently offering 15% off the purchase of two select charging accessories. A <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1636%3Fvariant%3D43449917210774">smaller 5K version</a> featuring a similar design but with a slightly different layout of the various features is available for &#36;39.99.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Anker provided MacRumors with the 3-in-1 Power Bank for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anker/">Anker</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/anker-3-in-1-power-bank/">Review: Anker&#039;s Latest 3-in-1 Power Bank is a Versatile On-the-Go Powerhouse</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ankers-latest-3-in-1-power-bank-is-a-versatile-on-the-go-powerhouse.2427150/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Disney Shares Trailer for Immersive Vision Pro Marvel Story</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-marvel-immersive-story/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-shares-trailer-for-immersive-vision-pro-marvel-story.2427144/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:49:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-marvel-immersive-story/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Disney</category>
		<category>Disney Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Disney today shared a trailer for the hour-long interactive and immersive Disney+ Marvel story that is set to come to the Vision Pro on Thursday, May 30.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Marvel Studios' What If...? - An Immersive Story Official Trailer ILM Immersive &amp; Disney+" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lLk-IkPktMo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The Disney+ original from Marvel Studios is connected to the "What If...?" animated series and it will be released as a standalone app for the Vision Pro.<blockquote>What If... You Were Chosen? Step into the Multiverse and harness the power of the Infinity Stones in this reality-bending story from Marvel Studios, ILM Immersive, and Disney+.<br/>
<br/>
The Multiverse is in danger and The Watcher needs your help. Dangerous variants are hunting Infinity Stones and altering the fate of not only their realities, but yours as well. To save the fate of the Multiverse, you'll need to use your own hands to learn mystic spells, defend your allies in epic battles, and more. But, be careful... everything might not be all that it seems.</blockquote>What If...? reimagines events from the Marvel Cinematic Universe in unexpected ways, and on the Vision Pro, fans will be able to step into the lead role of an immersive story that transforms the space around them.<br/>
<br/>
There are multiversal variants of key Marvel characters, chances to learn mystic arts, and an opportunity to harness the power of the Infinity Stones. Marvel says that users will "cross between augmented and virtual reality" while going through the narrative adventure, interacting with the world using their hands and eyes.<br/>
<br/>
The What If...? experience features new and iconic "breathtaking environments" from the Marvel Cinematic Universe, with impressive visuals and support for spatial audio.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro immersive story is set to come out on Thursday, May 30.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney/">Disney</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney-plus/">Disney Plus</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-marvel-immersive-story/">Disney Shares Trailer for Immersive Vision Pro Marvel Story</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-shares-trailer-for-immersive-vision-pro-marvel-story.2427144/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What the Golf on Apple Vision Pro Gains New Levels</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-what-the-golf-levels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-the-golf-on-apple-vision-pro-gains-new-levels.2427133/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 11:00:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-what-the-golf-levels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> game What the Golf? for the Vision Pro is being updated with a slew of new content, with Apple adding 15 new areas with more than 100 spatial levels and 200 challenges to complete.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LaJ5yzmlNYs" title="WHAT THE GOLF? - Apple Vision Pro Launch Trailer" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen data-thumb-size="hqdefault"></iframe></div><br/>
What the Golf? is, as the name suggests, a mini golf game aimed at people who hate golf. The goal is to get the ball to the hole, and every hole has a twist with different game mechanics to overcome.<br/>
<br/>
The game has been around on iOS, iPadOS, and macOS since 2019, plus it launched on Vision Pro in February, but there is new content to play on the Vision Pro this week. Apple says players will experience more cowboys, portals, eggs, crabs, sneaky cardboard boxes, and more.<br/>
<br/>
On the Vision Pro, a pinch of the fingers lets users set up the perfect shot, with the golf course able to be played anywhere in the home. What the Golf? can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> on the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
Other &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; titles getting updates this week include Ridiculous Fishing EX, Tamagotchi Adventure Kingdom, Solitaire Stories, and Fruit Ninja Classic.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/vision-pro-what-the-golf-levels/">What the Golf on Apple Vision Pro Gains New Levels</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-the-golf-on-apple-vision-pro-gains-new-levels.2427133/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;189 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-for-just-189-on-amazon.2427121/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 08:33:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is just &#36;10 higher compared to the all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-gen-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-865510" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's also available in all three aluminum colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This model of the Apple Watch SE launched in September 2022 and remains Apple's most affordable Apple Watch. The Apple Watch SE lacks some of the upgraded features you'll find in some Series 9 or Ultra 2 models, like temperature sensing and ECG functionality, but it will otherwise provide you with all key Apple Watch features, and at the cheapest price possible.<br/>
<br/>
Finally, we're also tracking a solid deal on one model of the Apple Watch Ultra 2. You can get the model with the Green/Grey Trail Loop (S/M) for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;714.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;799.00. Discounts on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 have been rare over the past few weeks, and this deal beats the average discounted price by about &#36;15.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/">Get the 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;189 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-for-just-189-on-amazon.2427121/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>T-Mobile Announces Price Increases for Some Older Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/tmobile-raising-prices-of-some-older-plans/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-announces-price-increases-for-some-older-plans.2427116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:43:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/tmobile-raising-prices-of-some-older-plans/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile today revealed that it will be increasing the monthly prices of some of its older plans in the U.S. by &#36;2 to &#36;5 per line.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/T-Mobile-Generic-Feature-Pink-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951944" /><br/>
Affected customers will receive a text message from T-Mobile if their plan will be receiving a price increase, which will take effect next month. Affected plans appear to include certain T-Mobile ONE, Simple Choice, and Magenta plans.<br/>
<br/>
In its text message to customers, T-Mobile said this is the first time that it has changed the prices of some of its monthly plans in "nearly a decade."<br/>
<br/>
"We're adjusting prices to respond to rising costs, but we are committed to offering low prices and the best value in postpaid wireless," <a href="https://x.com/TMobileHelp/status/1793280595076005912">said T-Mobile</a>, in response to a customer inquiry on social media platform X. "We offer customers more for every dollar they spend than ever before, especially when you consider taxes & fees included."<br/>
<br/>
In an <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tmobile/comments/1cxyp7k/tmobile_to_raise_the_cost_of_older_rate_plans_by/">alleged memo</a> shared with T-Mobile employees today, the carrier said "costs and inflation have risen over the past decade," but touted that it still offers the "lowest prices versus AT&T and Verizon" after the price increases. T-Mobile also ensured that customers on these older plans will retain all of their "benefits and perks."<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile did not immediately respond to our request for more information.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/tmobile-raising-prices-of-some-older-plans/">T-Mobile Announces Price Increases for Some Older Plans</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-announces-price-increases-for-some-older-plans.2427116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M1 MacBook Air Drops to Low Price of &#36;699 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops-to-low-price-of-699-on-amazon.2427113/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:09:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is selling the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5KWB9H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;699.00</a>, down from the original price of &#36;999.00. This is an overall solid second-best price on this version of the MacBook Air, and it's the first time the computer has been in stock at a steep discount in weeks.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850533" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/M1-MacBook-Air-Deals-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2125" height="1195" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The model that Amazon has for &#36;699.00 is the entry-level version with 8GB Unified Memory, an 8-core CPU, a 7-core GPU, and a 256GB SSD. You can get both the Gold and Silver colorways at this price, with delivery as soon as May 24 if you have Amazon Prime.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5KWB9H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple discontinued the M1 MacBook Air back in March, which is why we're seeing such low prices on remaining inventory. The M1 MacBook Air first came out in 2020, so it is four years old at this point, but the Apple silicon chip is still more than adequate for day-to-day tasks. As the M1 MacBook Air is no longer being manufactured, available supply is likely to dry up soon. <br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops/">Apple&#039;s M1 MacBook Air Drops to Low Price of &#36;699 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m1-macbook-air-drops-to-low-price-of-699-on-amazon.2427113/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best M4 iPad Pro Cases Currently Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/m4-ipad-pro-cases-covers-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-m4-ipad-pro-cases-currently-available.2427109/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:45:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/m4-ipad-pro-cases-covers-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/m4-ipad-pro-hands-on/">launched</a> its new 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro models on May 15, and there's still a notable lack of cases available for the device. For new owners wanting to protect their pricey investment from scuffs or an accidental drop, we've shortlisted a handful of options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m4-iPad-Pro-Horizontal-Feature-Purple-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950742" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><br/>
<br/>
We would have included the popular <a href="https://www.zugucase.com">Zugu brand</a> in this shortlist, but the company says it is still working on new cases for the M4 iPad Pro and plans to make them available in June or July. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Burton Goods Magnetic Leather Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/burton-goods-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951869" /><br/>
A full-grain leather case with a soft microfiber lining, Burton Goods' slim but pricey case props up to offer multiple viewing angles, and the front flap supports the iPad Pro's sleep/wake function. Equipped with "rare-earth magnets," it also includes a magnetic tab that folds back when not in use and secures an Apple Pencil Pro during transit. There's an internal leather pocket for storing a few documents, and it's topped off with a hand-stitched French hem. The <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-11?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">11-inch</a> model costs &#36;169.95, while the <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-13?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">13-inch</a> version comes in at &#36;179.95. Burton Goods is the recent new venture of Brian Holmes, former Pad & Quill president. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-11?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Burton Goods 11" Magnetic Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-leather-ipad-case-m4-ipad-pro-13?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Burton Goods 13" Magnetic Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>Torro Leather Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/torro-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951870" /><br/>
Handcrafted using cowhide leather, Torro's case offers one of the more elegant finishes out of the cases listed here. The inner frame is designed for optimal shock absorption to protect against drops and impacts, while flexible sides aim to make it easy to insert and remove the iPad. It offers three adjustable standing angles, the highest angle for watching videos and the lowest for a stable surface to type or use your Apple Pencil. It also includes an indented groove on the side of the frame for charging Apple Pencil Pro, as well as the USB-C, and 2nd Gen Apple Pencils. Lastly, the front cover supports the iPad's sleep/wake feature. Pre-orders are open for the <a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-11-leather-case-5th-gen">11-inch</a> (&#36;74.99) and <a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-13-leather-case">13-inch</a> (&#36;89.99) versions, and the cases ship by May 30.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-11-leather-case-5th-gen"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Torro 11" Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://torrousa.com/products/ipad-pro-13-leather-case"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Torro 13" Leather Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>Otterbox Statement Series Studio Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/otterbox-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951871" /><br/>
The Statement Series Studio Case is slim and features a soft, durable fabric finish. The adjustable stand offers a range of viewing angles for typing, streaming, drawing, or video calls. Its front detaches to save space while working or commuting. There's also decent corner protection to save the screen in the event of a drop, and it includes a dedicated space to store your Apple Pencil. It's a pricey option though: The <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHB2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-blue">11-inch</a> model is &#36;89.95, while the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHC2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-gray">13-inch</a> version is &#36;99.95. Color options are limited to Blue and Gray.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHB2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-blue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Otterbox 11" Studio Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRHC2ZM/A/otterbox-statement-series-studio-case-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-gray"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Otterbox 13" Studio Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>UAG Metropolis SE Series Folio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/uag-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951872" /><br/>
The Metropolis SE Series is foremost designed for protection, and has a robust and durable design. Constructed with a lightweight composite material and a soft, impact-resistant core, this case is engineered to withstand significant drops. The corners also provide additional defense against scratches and dents in the event of accidental falls. The folio cover doubles as a stand, and the case also features a smooth PU exterior that's easy to wipe clean, while the Apple Pencil holder supports Apple Pencil pairing and charging. UAG says the case has been tested for medical environments, and can be sanitized with medical-grade wipes and disinfectants repeatedly without compromising its integrity. Available in Cloud Blue, Black, Bordeaux, and Olive colors, the Metropolis SE comes in <a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-11-5th-gen-2024-folio-case/">11-inch</a> (&#36;69.95) and <a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-13-7th-gen-2024-folio-case/">13-inch</a> (&#36;79.99) versions. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-11-5th-gen-2024-folio-case/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">UAG 11" Metropolis SE Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.urbanarmorgear.com/products/metropolis-se-series-ipad-pro-13-7th-gen-2024-folio-case/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">UAG 13" Metropolis SE Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>ESR Rebound Magnetic Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/esr-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951875" /><br/>
Essentially a cheap version of Apple's Smart Folio, this could serve as an interim option until more quality cases become available. The front trifold cover supports sleep/wake mode and can be folded into two stand positions, one for viewing and another for writing. Unlike Apple's case, the ESR alternative includes a magnetic flap that secures and charges your Apple Pencil while you're on the move. Constructed entirely from TPU (a flexible, rubber-like plastic), it has strong magnets that securely hold the iPad Pro in place. While it may not have the premium feel of higher-end cases, it is lightweight, sturdy, and provides easy access to the tablet's ports and buttons. Both <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHHTHNF">11-inch</a> (&#36;19) and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHKJYVX%2F">13-inch</a> (&#36;24) versions are available.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHHTHNF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">ESR 11" Rebound Magnetic Case</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FESR-Powerful-Magnetic-Attachment-Protection%2Fdp%2FB0CRHKJYVX%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">ESR 13" Rebound Magnetic Case</div></a></div><br/>
<h2>Apple Smart Folio Case</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-smart-folio-case-ipad-pro-m4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951881" /><br/>
Apple's Smart Folio has been a staple accessory for quite some time, and is known for its elegant design rather than its protective capabilities. It's not cheap, but thanks to some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/new-ipads-added-magnets-smart-folio-case/">additional magnets</a>, the latest version boasts a wider range of viewing angles. The front cover offers sleep/wake functionality and can fold to create a convenient stand. It attaches magnetically to the back, eliminating the need for snaps and providing minimal edge protection. Available in three colors — black, white, and denim blue — the Smart Folio is available in both <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW983ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-black">11-inch</a> (&#36;79) and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWK23ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-white">13-inch</a> (&#36;99) variants.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW983ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-black"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Apple 11" Smart Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWK23ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-white"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Apple 13" Smart Folio</div></a></div><br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/m4-ipad-pro-cases-covers-available/">Best M4 iPad Pro Cases Currently Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-m4-ipad-pro-cases-currently-available.2427109/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
