<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 08:04:00 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s How the Apple Card Savings Account&#039;s Interest Rate Compares to Major Competitors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/apple-card-savings-rate-comparison/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-the-apple-card-savings-accounts-interest-rate-compares-to-major-competitors.2444119/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:24:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/apple-card-savings-rate-comparison/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the U.S., the Apple Card offers a high-yield savings account option, allowing you to earn far more interest on your money compared to the average bank's basic savings account. Apple's account offers an APY of 4.1% as of writing, and while that is a competitive rate, it is not the absolute best offer available at this time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-card-savings-account-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928948" /><br/>
The chart below compares the Apple Card saving account's rate to some other popular high-yield savings accounts in the U.S., as of writing.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Provider</th><br/>
 <th>Maximum APY*</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ally</td><br/>
 <td>3.85%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Discover</td><br/>
 <td>3.9%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>American Express</td><br/>
 <td>3.9%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Capital One</td><br/>
 <td>3.9%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Citizens Bank</td><br/>
 <td>3.9%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Card Savings</strong></td><br/>
 <td><strong>4.1%</strong></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Marcus by Goldman Sachs</td><br/>
 <td>4.1%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Barclays</td><br/>
 <td>4.1%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Synchrony</td><br/>
 <td>4.1%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>PNC Bank</td><br/>
 <td>4.15%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>SoFi</td><br/>
 <td>4.2%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Betterment</td><br/>
 <td>4.25%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wealthfront</td><br/>
 <td>4.25%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>UFB Direct</td><br/>
 <td>4.31%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Fierce</td><br/>
 <td>4.5%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>CIT Bank</td><br/>
 <td>4.55% (on &#36;5,000+)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<small>* Advertised APYs as of November 27, 2024, excluding promotional rates and affiliate bonuses. Minimum balance requirements and other conditions vary per account. APYs can change at any time, so we cannot guarantee the accuracy of the rates listed above.</small><br/>
<br/>
Apple launched its savings account <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/apple-card-savings-account-launching-today/">in April 2023</a>, in partnership with Goldman Sachs. The account can be opened and managed in the Wallet app on the iPhone, and it has no fees, no minimum deposits, and no minimum balance requirements. You must have an Apple Card, be a U.S. resident, and be at least 18 years old to open an account.<br/>
<br/>
The account allows Apple Card holders to earn interest on their Daily Cash cashback balance, and on funds deposited via a linked bank account or an Apple Cash balance. The maximum balance allowed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-card-savings-1-million-limit/">is now &#36;1 million</a>, up from &#36;250,000.<br/>
<br/>
When the account first became available, Apple and Goldman Sachs offered an APY of 4.15%, but the rate has fluctuated in line with U.S. Federal Reserve benchmark rate changes. The rate increased three times, reaching a peak of 4.5% in early 2024, but it has since been cut three times and has stood at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/10/apple-card-savings-account-rate-cut/">4.1% since early October</a>. Apple has yet to change the rate after the Federal Reserve's latest rate cut in early November.<br/>
<br/>
To open a savings account in the Wallet app, tap on your Apple Card, tap on the circle with three dots at the top of the screen, tap Daily Cash, and select Set Up Savings.<br/>
<br/>
Goldman Sachs reportedly plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">end its consumer lending partnership with Apple</a>, but it is unclear if this will have any impact on Apple Card holders. JPMorgan, owner of Chase Bank, reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/17/jpmorgan-chase-apple-card-talks/">could take over</a> as Apple's financial partner.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/apple-card-savings-rate-comparison/">Here&#039;s How the Apple Card Savings Account&#039;s Interest Rate Compares to Major Competitors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-the-apple-card-savings-accounts-interest-rate-compares-to-major-competitors.2444119/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Black Friday Streaming Deals Include Big Savings on Disney+, Hulu, Paramount+, and Peacock</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/black-friday-streaming-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/black-friday-streaming-deals-include-big-savings-on-disney-hulu-paramount-and-peacock.2444118/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:11:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/black-friday-streaming-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We've been focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/">deals on physical products</a> over the past few weeks, but Black Friday is also a great time of year to purchase a streaming membership. Some of the biggest services have great discounts for new and select returning members this week, including Disney+, Hulu, Paramount+, and Peacock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/new-streaming-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979917" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Disney+ and Hulu</h2><br/>
Starting with the <a href="https://disneyplus.bn5x.net/c/153062/564546/9358?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.hulu.com%2FGMA"><strong>Disney+ and Hulu bundle</strong></a>, you can get Hulu (with ads) and Disney+ (with ads) for &#36;2.99 per month for an entire year, down from the regular &#36;10.99 per month price. This offer is valid for new and eligible returning Hulu/Disney+ subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://disneyplus.bn5x.net/c/153062/564546/9358?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.hulu.com%2FGMA"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">72% OFF PER MONTH</div>Disney+ and Hulu Bundle for &#36;2.99/month</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
As usual, this offer will revert to the regular &#36;10.99 per month price (or then-current regular monthly price) at the end of your first year. Shoppers have until 11:59 p.m. PST on December 2 to take advantage of this offer.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, if you just want Hulu (with ads), you can get it for &#36;0.99 per month for a year, down from &#36;9.99 per month.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Paramount+</h2><br/>
You can get either <a href="https://paramountplus.qflm.net/c/153062/175360/3065?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.paramountplus.com%2F"><strong>Paramount+ Essential or Paramount+ with Showtime</strong></a> for &#36;2.99 per month for your first two months this Black Friday. Paramount+ Essential is typically priced at &#36;7.99 per month, while Paramount+ with Showtime is typically priced at &#36;12.99 per month.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://paramountplus.qflm.net/c/153062/175360/3065?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.paramountplus.com%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 76% OFF</div>Paramount+ for &#36;2.99/month</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should remember that this deal is only for the first two months of your Paramount+ subscription, and after that period it will return to its regular pricing structure. Paramount+ is only focusing on monthly plans this Black Friday, and there are no deals on annual plans.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Peacock</h2><br/>
Peacock has one of the best all-around streaming deals this week. You can get a <a href="https://www.peacocktv.com/"><strong>full year of Peacock (premium annual plan)</strong></a> for &#36;19.99, down from &#36;79.99. You can also opt to pay &#36;1.99 per month for six months. This plan includes ads.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.peacocktv.com/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">75% OFF</div>Peacock for &#36;19.99/year</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This sale will run through December 2, and is available to new and select returning customers.<br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/black-friday-streaming-deals/">Black Friday Streaming Deals Include Big Savings on Disney+, Hulu, Paramount+, and Peacock</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/black-friday-streaming-deals-include-big-savings-on-disney-hulu-paramount-and-peacock.2444118/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Do More Single-Handedly With Double Tap on Apple Watch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/using-the-double-tap-feature-on-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/do-more-single-handedly-with-double-tap-on-apple-watch.2444105/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 04:15:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/using-the-double-tap-feature-on-apple-watch&#038;post_date=1732720512/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Double Tap</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Watch Series 9, Series 10, and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models include a multi-functional Double Tap gesture that you might not know about or haven't yet got around to trying. Here's everything Double Tap can do, and how you can make the most of it on your Apple Watch. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/double-tap.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979840" /><br/>
Double Tap is a gesture-based feature for Apple Watch models that lets you control watch functions by tapping your thumb and index finger together twice. The feature aims to make it easier to navigate the Apple Watch when you have only one hand free, like when you're walking a dog, carrying groceries, or holding a cup of coffee.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What Double Tap Can Do</h2><br/>
Double Tap's functionality is pretty simple. You raise your watch to wake, and then you double tap your thumb and index finger together to control what's happening on the screen of your watch. <br/>
<br/>
By default, Double Tap selects the primary button in whatever app you're in. So for example, if you get a call, you can double tap to answer, and use it to hang up when you're done. Likewise, if you're watching/listening to media, you can pause it and resume it (or skip). You can also use the gesture from your Apple Watch face to navigate through your Smart Stack, widget by widget.<br/>
<br/>
Some other use cases: If you've set a timer, double-tapping will pause it. Performing the gesture again will resume the countdown, and when the timer goes off, a double-tap will stop it. Similarly, you can use it to do other everyday things like snooze alarms, trigger the Camera Remote app's shutter button, and dismiss notifications.<br/>
<br/>
In watchOS 11, Double Tap can also be used to scroll through navigable content in any Apple app, including the Weather and Messages. You can even use a double tap to dismiss a timer that has ended.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-watchos-11-double-tap.jpg" alt="" width="700" height="396" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979841" /><br/>
As you might expect, the gesture is also set up to assume your other hand is preoccupied. If you receive a text, for instance, a double tap lets you reply with a voice message, while another double tap sends the message.<br/>
<br/>
Here's a rundown of everything you can do with Double Tap:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Open the Smart Stack from the watch face, and then Double Tap again to scroll through widgets one by one.</li><br/>
 	<li>Answer phone or FaceTime calls.</li><br/>
 	<li>Hang up phone or FaceTime calls.</li><br/>
 	<li>When you get an iMessage, Double Tap to view it, and then Double Tap again if you need to scroll.</li><br/>
 	<li>Reply to a Message using dictation and then send it with Double Tap.</li><br/>
 	<li>Act on notifications - Apple says a Double Tap on an incoming notification will activate the primary action, such as snoozing a reminder or replying to a message.</li><br/>
 	<li>Pause, resume, and end a timer.</li><br/>
 	<li>Stop and resume the stopwatch.</li><br/>
 	<li>Snooze an alarm.</li><br/>
 	<li>Play and pause music, podcasts, or audiobooks (or skip a track, depending on settings).</li><br/>
 	<li>Change to the Elevation view in the Compass app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Start or stop automatic Workout reminders when a workout is detected.</li><br/>
<li>Take a photo with the Camera Remote.</li><br/>
<li>Record a voice memo in the Voice Memo app.</li><br/>
<li>Change Flashlight modes.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
In the Apple Watch Settings app, under Gestures, you can opt to change the playback option from play/pause to skip, and the Smart Stack option from Advance (swaps through the widgets) to Select (opens a widget's associated app). If you have Apple Vision Pro, you'll also find an option to ignore double tap gestures when you're wearing the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Set Up Double Tap</h2><br/>
If Double Tap is disabled on your watch, you will need to enable it manually for it to work. This can be done from your wrist or in the Watch app on iPhone, and both menus include options to customize Media Playback and Smart Stack functionality. <br/>
<br/>
Note that to enable Double Tap, setup involves giving watchOS permission to disable some Accessibility options, including Assistive Touch, Zoom with Hand Gestures, VoiceOver with Hand Gestures, and Quick Actions. If Double Tap is enabled but is not working for you, disabling it and then turning it back on can help in some circumstances. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>On Apple Watch:</h3><br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Gestures</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Double Tap</strong>, then toggle on the switch next to <strong>Double Tap</strong> on the next screen.</li><br/>
<li>If prompted, tap <strong>Turn off Accessibility Features</strong> at the bottom of the on-screen alert.</li><br/>
<li>Choose your preferred setting for "Playback" (<strong>Play/Pause</strong> or <strong>Skip</strong>) and "Smart Stack" (<strong>Advance</strong> or <strong>Select</strong>).</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/enable-double-tap2.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915348" /><br/>
<br/>
<h3>On iPhone:</h3><br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Watch</strong> app.</li><br/>
<li>With the "My Watch" tab selected, tap <strong>Gestures</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Double Tap</strong>, then toggle on the switch next to <strong>Double Tap</strong> on the next screen.</li><br/>
<li>If prompted, tap <strong>Turn off Accessibility Features</strong> in the on-screen alert.</li><br/>
<li>Choose your preferred setting for "Playback" (<strong>Play/Pause</strong> or <strong>Skip</strong>) and "Smart Stack" (<strong>Advance</strong> or <strong>Select</strong>).</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/enable-double-tap1.jpg" alt="settings" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915349" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple says Double Tap is enabled by the S9 chip's faster Neural Engine, which is why the feature is only available on the Series 9 and later and the Ultra 2. Apple said it developed an algorithm that detects the "unique signature" of tiny wrist movements and changes in blood flow when the index finger and thumb are tapped together.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-hand-gestures-control-apple-watch/">How to Use Hand Gestures to Control Your Apple Watch</a></li></ul><br/>
If you own an earlier Apple Watch model that doesn't support Double Tap, you can always try a similar but more limited accessibility feature called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-hand-gestures-control-apple-watch/">AssistiveTouch</a>, which is available on the Apple Watch Series 4 and newer.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/double-tap/">Double Tap</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/using-the-double-tap-feature-on-apple-watch/">Do More Single-Handedly With Double Tap on Apple Watch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/do-more-single-handedly-with-double-tap-on-apple-watch.2444105/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sales Stall Despite Global Smartphone Market Recovery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/iphone-sales-stall-global-market-idc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-stall-despite-global-smartphone-market-recovery.2444103/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 03:43:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/iphone-sales-stall-global-market-idc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>IDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple experienced minimal iPhone growth in 2024 despite a significant rebound in the global smartphone market, according to <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prUS52757624">new data published by IDC</a>. Worldwide smartphone shipments increased 6.2% to reach 1.24 billion units, but iPhone shipments grew by just 0.4% during the same period.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-16-Apple-Store.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-976828" /><br/>
The tepid performance underlines Apple's challenges in key markets like China, where domestic rivals are gaining ground through aggressive pricing and technological innovation. Chinese manufacturers like Xiaomi and Huawei are investing heavily in hardware and software development as well as custom processor designs, with Huawei recently launching its new Mate 70 phone featuring its own home-grown chips.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, Android device makers collectively drove the market's recovery, achieving 7.6% growth mostly through strong performance in emerging markets across Asia Pacific, Latin America, the Middle East, and Africa. These manufacturers appear to have succeeded by offering more affordable devices, with an average selling price of &#36;295 compared to Apple's &#36;1,000-plus premium iPhone positioning.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the slower growth, Apple maintained its position as the industry's profit leader through its premium pricing strategy. According to IDC, the Apple's prospects may improve in 2025, with a forecast of 3.1% growth for iOS devices compared to 1.7% for Android smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/IDC-Worldwide-Smartphone-Market-Forecast-to-Grow-6.2-in-2024-Fueled-by-Robust-Growth-for-Android-in-Emerging-Markets-and-China-According-to-IDC-2024-Nov-F-1.jpg" alt="" width="647" height="562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979835" /><br/>
Overall, the broader smartphone market's recovery was driven by pent-up demand for device upgrades in regions with lower smartphone penetration. However, IDC analysts noted that even heavily marketed features like generative AI have failed to significantly impact consumer demand or drive early upgrades, which doesn't bode well for the impact of Apple Intelligence on iPhone sales going into 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/idc/">IDC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/27/iphone-sales-stall-global-market-idc/">iPhone Sales Stall Despite Global Smartphone Market Recovery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-stall-despite-global-smartphone-market-recovery.2444103/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M2 iPad Air Black Friday Deals Include &#36;100 Off Nearly Every Model at Best Buy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/m2-ipad-air-black-friday-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m2-ipad-air-black-friday-deals-include-100-off-nearly-every-model-at-best-buy.2444054/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:33:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/m2-ipad-air-black-friday-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yesterday we shared a collection of discounts on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/m4-ipad-pro-black-friday-deals/">Apple's M4 iPad Pro at Best Buy</a>, and today we're shifting focus to the M2 iPad Air. Best Buy has <a href="https://howl.link/8p4q8hifl174m">&#36;100 off nearly every model</a> of this tablet, and you won't need a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership to see the deals. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipad-air-m2-bulbs.jpeg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978799" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Prices start at &#36;499.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air. This sale has both 11-inch and 13-inch models at record low discounts, and there are cellular devices discounted as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/8p4q8hifl174m"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M2 iPad Air Black Friday Deals at Best Buy</div></a></div><h3>11-inch iPad Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/zoei8o0s5wzyz">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;499.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/7cx93jsb8woiz">256GB  Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;599.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/zpk08cv5gw771">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/dzcd43pdi5k66">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;999.00 (&#36;100 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>13-inch iPad Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/m4yg3fmm93aw1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;699.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/u7ezf43luy0ch">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/5vg71c34ifrpz">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;999.00 (&#36;100 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/m2-ipad-air-black-friday-deals/">M2 iPad Air Black Friday Deals Include &#36;100 Off Nearly Every Model at Best Buy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m2-ipad-air-black-friday-deals-include-100-off-nearly-every-model-at-best-buy.2444054/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Has Scaled Back (PRODUCT)RED Color Option Over Past Few Years</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-has-scaled-back-productred/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-has-scaled-back-product-red-color-option-over-past-few-years.2444052/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:10:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-has-scaled-back-productred/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>(PRODUCT)RED</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Since 2006, Apple has partnered with the (RED) brand to raise money for The Global Fund, an organization that aims to combat diseases such as HIV/AIDS, tuberculosis, and malaria in Africa. Through this partnership, Apple has long offered a <a href="https://www.apple.com/product-red/">(PRODUCT)RED color option</a> for some products, but it has scaled back this effort over the past few years.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/PRODUCT-RED-Products.jpg" alt="" width="1312" height="738" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979760" /><br/>
The only current-generation (PRODUCT)RED product that Apple sells new is the iPhone SE 3, which is expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/iphone-se-4-expected-to-launch-in-march/">discontinued in March</a>. Beyond that, its only remaining (PRODUCT)RED products are the iPhone 14 and a handful of older iPhone cases.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not offer any iPhone 15 models in (PRODUCT)RED, and that trend has continued with iPhone 16 models so far. It did offer the aluminum Apple Watch Series 9 in (PRODUCT)RED last year, but that device has since been discontinued, and the color option is not available for the Apple Watch Series 10. Apple also discontinued the (PRODUCT)RED version of the Sport Band that was available alongside the Series 9.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, Apple has used different branding for newer Beats products available in red, such as Statement Red and Transparent Red.<br/>
<br/>
Does this mean Apple is slowly phasing out the (PRODUCT)RED brand? It's hard to say for sure yet, as the color could return from time to time more selectively. The number of products available in (PRODUCT)RED has certainly dwindled over the past two years, though, so the future of the color seems to be in jeopardy.<br/>
<br/>
Apple continues to support The Global Fund through its annual Apple Pay donation program, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-pay-world-aids-day-donation-campaign/">returns from November 29 through December 8</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/productred/">(PRODUCT)RED</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-has-scaled-back-productred/">Apple Has Scaled Back (PRODUCT)RED Color Option Over Past Few Years</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-has-scaled-back-product-red-color-option-over-past-few-years.2444052/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Donation Campaign for World AIDS Day Returns This Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-pay-world-aids-day-donation-campaign/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-donation-campaign-for-world-aids-day-returns-this-friday.2444042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 09:09:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-pay-world-aids-day-donation-campaign/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		<category>(PRODUCT)RED</category>
		<category>World AIDS Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that it will again donate &#36;5 for every purchase made using Apple Pay on Apple.com, through the Apple Store app, or at an Apple Store to <a href="https://www.theglobalfund.org/">The Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria</a> from November 29 through December 8. Apple said its donation this year will be capped at &#36;3 million.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-Pay-RED-2023.jpg" alt="" width="1694" height="954" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924555" /><br/>
The Global Fund aims to combat diseases such as HIV/AIDS, tuberculosis, and malaria throughout the developing world. Apple says its donation to the organization will continue to "help fund critical health programs that save lives."<br/>
<br/>
Apple runs this donation campaign ahead of World AIDS Day on December 1 each year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has supported The Global Fund for 18 years through its partnership with the (RED) brand, co-founded by U2 singer Bono. Apple offers some products in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/product-red/">(PRODUCT)RED</a> color, and a portion of the proceeds from every one of these products sold by Apple goes to The Global Fund. Apple said it has raised more than &#36;250 million to date.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/productred/">(PRODUCT)RED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/world-aids-day/">World AIDS Day</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-pay-world-aids-day-donation-campaign/">Apple Pay Donation Campaign for World AIDS Day Returns This Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-donation-campaign-for-world-aids-day-returns-this-friday.2444042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Drops Price of Black Apple Watch Ultra 2 to &#36;699.99 for Black Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/black-apple-watch-ultra-2-699/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-drops-price-of-black-apple-watch-ultra-2-to-699-99-for-black-friday.2444040/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:52:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/black-apple-watch-ultra-2-699/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is taking &#36;99 off a collection of Black Apple Watch Ultra 2 smartwatches this week, now priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZ13GG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;699.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. You will need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see these discounts at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/apple-watch-ultra-2-holiday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975579" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale beats the previous all-time low price by about &#36;20, and Amazon has most of the new Black Apple Watch Ultra 2 models on sale at this price. This includes models with the Ocean Band, Trail Loop, and Alpine Loop. If you're interested in the model with the Milanese Loop, it's on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHPYSGJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;819.00</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZ13GG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Black) for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/black-apple-watch-ultra-2-699/">Amazon Drops Price of Black Apple Watch Ultra 2 to &#36;699.99 for Black Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-drops-price-of-black-apple-watch-ultra-2-to-699-99-for-black-friday.2444040/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Porsche Still Has No Imminent Plans to Launch Next-Generation CarPlay Despite 2023 Preview</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/porsche-no-next-generation-carplay-in-near-term/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/porsche-still-has-no-imminent-plans-to-launch-next-generation-carplay-despite-2023-preview.2444039/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:42:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/porsche-no-next-generation-carplay-in-near-term/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In late 2023, Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed what next-generation CarPlay could look like</a> in its vehicles, with a pair of images showing a custom instrument cluster and more. However, the luxury automaker has yet to release any vehicles that support the software nearly a year later, and it sounds like it still has no imminent plans to do so.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1540" height="854" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927564" /><br/>
A spokesperson for Porsche today informed <em>MacRumors</em> that the automaker plans to maintain its current level of CarPlay integration in the "near term." Porsche supports standard CarPlay, and while some of its vehicles like the Taycan offer additional features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/17/porsche-taycan-apple-maps-ev-routing/">EV routing in Apple Maps</a>, that is not next-generation CarPlay.<br/>
<br/>
Aston Martin also previewed its next-generation CarPlay design alongside Porsche last year, but it has yet to release any vehicles that support the system.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's website continues to say that the first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay support will "arrive in 2024," but no vehicles support the software yet. Apple and automakers have just over a month remaining to meet that 2024 timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first previewed next-generation CarPlay <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/06/apple-announces-multi-display-carplay/">in June 2022</a>, promising deeper integration with the instrument cluster and climate controls, support for multiple displays across the dashboard, a dedicated FM radio app, widgets, and more. The interface can be tailored to each specific vehicle model and automaker's brand identity.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><br/>
When it unveiled next-generation CarPlay, Apple said committed automakers included Acura, Audi, Ford, Honda, Infiniti, Jaguar, Land Rover, Lincoln, Mercedes-Benz, Nissan, Polestar, Porsche, Renault, and Volvo. Nearly two and a half years have gone by since Apple shared that list, however, so it is unclear if it remains fully accurate.<br/>
<br/>
It is still very possible that next-generation CarPlay ends up launching this December, and recent activity suggests that Apple is still making preparations. Earlier this month, a few <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/11/ios-18-2-beta-next-generation-carplay-icons/">redesigned next-generation CarPlay icons</a> appeared in iOS 18.2 beta code, and Apple filed to protect its next-generation CarPlay designs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/next-generation-carplay-images-in-eu/">in the European Union</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been adding next-generation CarPlay references to iOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">since iOS 17</a>, so it is unclear what the minimum iOS version requirement will be for the system. In any case, we expect iOS 18.2 to be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/12/ios-18-2-potential-release-date/">on December 9</a>. Hopefully, Apple will finally announce next-generation CarPlay availability details at some point next month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/porsche-no-next-generation-carplay-in-near-term/">Porsche Still Has No Imminent Plans to Launch Next-Generation CarPlay Despite 2023 Preview</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/porsche-still-has-no-imminent-plans-to-launch-next-generation-carplay-despite-2023-preview.2444039/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;99 Off iPad Mini 7 With Return of All-Time Low Prices, Starting at &#36;399.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/amazon-takes-99-off-ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-99-off-ipad-mini-7-with-return-of-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-399-99.2444038/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:01:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/amazon-takes-99-off-ipad-mini-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week is providing record low prices on multiple models of the new iPad mini 7, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3YF38G%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;499.00. All of the deals on the iPad mini 7 in this article require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipad-mini-7-holiday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975856" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has all four colors of the 128GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 on sale at this all-time low price, and it's a sale we haven't seen in a few weeks. You can also get the 512GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3XHBH9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;699.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00, although it's currently listed as temporarily out of stock. You can still purchase it now at this record low price and Amazon will ship it when it's back in stock.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3YF38G%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3XHBH9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>512GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
These iPad mini 7 discounts are part of Amazon's Black Friday discounts, which also include other iPads like the 9th and 10th generation iPads, M4 iPad Pro, and the M2 iPad Air. You can find more information about these deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/23/9-best-black-friday-ipad-2024/">Best Black Friday iPad Deals</a> guide, and check out our overall <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/">Best Black Friday Apple Deals</a> guide for everything else currently on sale.<br/>
<br/>
We're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/amazon-takes-99-off-ipad-mini-7/">Amazon Takes &#36;99 Off iPad Mini 7 With Return of All-Time Low Prices, Starting at &#36;399.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-99-off-ipad-mini-7-with-return-of-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-399-99.2444038/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>When to Expect New M4 MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-new-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-and-mac-pro-models.2444033/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:08:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/30/apple-announcements-m4-imac-mac-mini-macbook-pro/">fall 2024 Mac announcements</a> have included new iMac, Mac mini, and MacBook Pro models, all of which debuted with variants of Apple's M4 chip. Apple intends to update the rest of its Mac lineup with M4 series processors over the next 12 months, which will make it the first time that Apple has used the same chip generation across all of its Macs. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/M4-M4-Pro-vs-M4-Max-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-973089" /><br/>
This means we can expect new M4 versions of MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro models next year. Here's what the latest rumors tell us about when each machine will launch, and what kinds of upgrades we can expect for them.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m3-macbook-air-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950298" /><br/>
Apple in March 2024 launched updated 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models equipped with Apple's M3 chip, and the company will soon start production of M4 versions ahead of an early 2025 launch, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. There are no new design changes planned for the MacBook Air models, and the focus will be on the M4 chip, but the base model will come with at least 16GB of RAM, after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/30/macbook-air-now-starts-with-16gb-ram/">updated the base M3 model to 16GB</a>, up from 8GB. An M4 MacBook Air could also feature a new 12MP Centre Stage camera with Desk View support, an improvement over the current 1080p FaceTime HD camera, given that both the new M4 iMac and M4 MacBook Pro models also debuted with the upgraded camera. The machines will arrive next year between January and March. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Mac Studio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Studio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2672" height="1503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946114" /><br/>
Apple plans to refresh the Mac Studio after the M4 MacBook Air has been released in early 2025. It will be equipped with a variation of the M4 processor  likely an M4 Ultra or Max chip. The current model comes in both M2 Max and M2 Ultra variants. Given that the Mac mini with M4 Pro chip and Apple's latest high-end MacBook Pro models include Thunderbolt 5 ports, it's certain that the Mac Studio will also adopt them. Mark Gurman claims that the Mac Studio was on track to be updated alongside the MacBook Air, but it is now going to see a refresh <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/m4-macbook-air-production-beginning-soon/">between March and June</a>. In previous reports, he said the Mac Studio would come out in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-studio-m4-mac-pro-2025/">mid-2025</a>, so it is unclear what has changed. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Mac Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Pro-Feature-Warm-2.jpg" alt="" width="2672" height="1503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948229" /><br/>
Apple last updated the Mac Pro in June 2023, adding an M2 Ultra chip and officially completing the transition away from Intel chips. Apple will refresh the Mac Pro in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/m4-macbook-air-production-beginning-soon/">summer of 2025</a>, according to Mark Gurman. Like the Mac Studio, the next Mac Pro will skip the M3 series. Instead it will be equipped with the highest-end version of the M4 chip, codenamed "Hidra." Based on the description of the chip, it could be positioned as an "Ultra" or "Extreme" chip. Gurman has said the M4 Ultra chip in the next Mac Pro will "probably" have up to a 32-core CPU and up to an 80-core GPU, which would be double the M4 Max's up to 16-core CPU and up to 40-core GPU. The next Mac Pro is expected to feature Thunderbolt 5 ports. It could also support up to 512GB of memory, a notable increase over the current 192GB limit. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Series Performance</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-MacBook-Pro-M4-chip-series-3up.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-974019" /><br/>
Like the M3, the M4 is built on a 3nm process, but with enhancements from Apple supplier TSMC for improved performance and power efficiency. The M4 also includes an improved Neural Engine that fuels accelerated AI workloads. Apple says it is the company's most powerful Neural Engine ever, capable of 38 trillion operations per second.<br/>
<br/>
Geekbench 6 benchmark results have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/m4-max-chip-geekbench-benchmark-results/">surfaced</a> for Apple's new M4 Pro and M4 Max chips in the new Mac mini and MacBook Pro models, so we have some indications of performance. In the new Mac mini and MacBook Pro models, the highest-end variants of the M4 Pro and M4 Max both outperform the highest-end M2 Ultra chip in the Mac Studio and Mac Pro: The M4 Max is up to 25% faster than the M2 Ultra in terms of peak multi-core CPU performance. M4 Pro's impressive performance gains are partly due to the M3 Pro being a very minor upgrade over the M2 Pro chip last year. Meanwhile, the M4 Max is up to 20% faster than the M4 Pro when it comes to peak multi-core CPU performance. <br/>
<br/>
In terms of graphics performance, Geekbench 6 results <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/m4-pro-m4-max-graphics-benchmarks/">indicate</a> that the M4 Pro and M4 Max are up to around 40% and 25% faster for graphics than the M3 Pro and M3 Max chips, respectively. Notably, the 16-inch MacBook Pro with the highest-end M4 Max with a 40-core GPU has up to 85% as fast graphics as the Mac Studio with the highest-end M2 Ultra chip with a 76-core GPU, even though it has 36 fewer GPU cores.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro-2/">When to Expect New M4 MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-new-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-and-mac-pro-models.2444033/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Faces Daily Fines in Brazil Over App Store Payment Restrictions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/brazil-apple-lift-third-party-app-payment-limits/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-faces-daily-fines-in-brazil-over-app-store-payment-restrictions.2444030/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:41:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/brazil-apple-lift-third-party-app-payment-limits/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Brazil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Brazil's antitrust regulator has ordered Apple to remove App Store restrictions on third-party payment systems and allow developers to market alternative payment options for in-app purchases. Apple has 20 days to comply or face daily fines of &#36;43,000.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/app-store-awards-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876046" /><br/>
The ruling by the Council for Economic Defense (Cade) comes in response to a 2022 complaint filed by MercadoLibre, Latin America's largest e-commerce platform. The company accused Apple of abusing its monopolistic position by requiring developers to use Apple's own payment system and preventing them from redirecting users to external payment options.<br/>
<br/>
Under the new requirements, Apple must permit app developers to implement tools allowing customers to make purchases outside the Apple ecosystem. This includes enabling the use of hyperlinks to external websites and allowing developers to market third-party products and services within their apps.<br/>
<br/>
The Brazilian case mirrors similar antitrust concerns raised in the EU. In March 2024, the European Commission <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/eu-fines-apple-2-billion/">fined Apple 1.8 billion</a> (&#36;1.95 billion) for restricting music streaming apps from informing users about cheaper subscription options outside the App Store. That ruling followed a complaint by Spotify in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
MercadoLibre's original complaint, filed in both Brazil and Mexico, argued that Apple's restrictions particularly harm smaller competitors while benefiting large integrated digital companies. The e-commerce giant's SVP general counsel, Jacobo Cohen Imach, criticized Apple's practices as creating an "artificial tilt towards integrated ecosystems."<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazil-antitrust-body-rules-apple-must-lift-restrictions-in-app-payments-2024-11-26/">Reuters</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/brazil/">Brazil</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/brazil-apple-lift-third-party-app-payment-limits/">Apple Faces Daily Fines in Brazil Over App Store Payment Restrictions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-faces-daily-fines-in-brazil-over-app-store-payment-restrictions.2444030/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Faces Complex Approval Process in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-intelligence-complext-approval-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-faces-complex-approval-process-in-china.2444025/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:00:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-intelligence-complext-approval-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is experiencing challenges as it attempts to launch Apple Intelligence in China, with regulators cautioning that foreign companies face a "difficult and long process" for approval unless they partner with local firms, according to a new <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8ce6715a-0614-4c8b-9bc2-5f4174519f9f">Financial Times</a></em> report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
A senior official at the Cyberspace Administration of China told the <em>FT</em> that foreign device makers would find a "simple and straightforward approval process" if they utilize already-approved large language models (LLMs) from Chinese companies, rather than attempting to implement their own AI systems.<br/>
<br/>
The regulatory situation has reportedly prompted Apple to engage in discussions with several Chinese tech companies, including search giant Baidu, ByteDance, and AI startup Moonshot, to potentially power Apple Intelligence features in devices sold in mainland China.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO Tim Cook arrived in China on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/tim-cook-visits-china-third-time-this-year/">Monday</a> to attend a CEO summit with Chinese Premier Li Qiang, in what could be an attempt by Cook to personally navigate the complex regulatory landscape. During his previous visit to Beijing, Cook acknowledged the specific regulatory requirements, stating that Apple was "working hard" to bring Apple Intelligence to Chinese consumers.<br/>
<br/>
The company has been gradually rolling out Apple Intelligence features in the US and elsewhere since October, with things like Writing Tools and enhanced Siri using a combination of on-device processing and its Private Cloud Compute servers, along with OpenAI's ChatGPT for more complex queries. But if Apple can't secure approval for its own AI models in China, it may need to rely on Chinese partners' LLMs to host AI features on devices sold there.<br/>
<br/>
According to JP Morgan analyst Samik Chatterjee, the regulatory uncertainty could delay the launch of Apple Intelligence in China until "well into the second half of 2025" or later, unless Apple adopts a flexible approach involving multiple Chinese partnerships to expedite approval.<br/>
<br/>
China represents 17% of the company's revenue but saw an 8% decline in sales over the past year. The company faces increasing competition from Huawei, which has already integrated its own AI features into its latest smartphones.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-intelligence-complext-approval-china/">Apple Intelligence Faces Complex Approval Process in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-faces-complex-approval-process-in-china.2444025/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Adds SearchGPT Option to Apple&#039;s Shortcuts App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/openai-searchgpt-shortcuts-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-adds-searchgpt-option-to-apples-shortcuts-app.2444001/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:51:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/openai-searchgpt-shortcuts-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The newest version of the ChatGPT app from OpenAI adds a new "Open SearchGPT" option to the Shortcuts app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. For those that have access to SearchGPT, tapping on the shortcut launches the ChatGPT app and invokes the web search feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/searchgpt-shortcuts.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979576" /><br/>
OpenAI added ChatGPT Search to ChatGPT in late October, introducing improved AI-based internet searches. SearchGPT is meant to search the web "in a much better way than before," offering up links to relevant web sources along with more contextual information and support for follow-up questions.<br/>
<br/>
SearchGPT is available to those who have ChatGPT Plus and ChatGPT Teams, with OpenAI planning to roll out support to free users in the coming months. <br/>
<br/>
To access the SearchGPT action in Shortcuts, you'll need the latest version of the ChatGPT app, which was released yesterday.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/openai-searchgpt-shortcuts-app/">OpenAI Adds SearchGPT Option to Apple&#039;s Shortcuts App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-adds-searchgpt-option-to-apples-shortcuts-app.2444001/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Now Upload Videos Directly to YouTube With iOS Share Sheet Integration</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/youtube-share-sheet-integration/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-upload-videos-directly-to-youtube-with-ios-share-sheet-integration.2443997/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:30:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/youtube-share-sheet-integration/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>YouTube</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube this week reintroduced support for the iOS Share Sheet, which means that it's now possible to share videos from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app and other video apps directly to YouTube.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/youtube-share-sheet-integration.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979573" /><br/>
Using the YouTube Share Sheet integration automatically imports a video to YouTube, where it can be edited and then uploaded to YouTube Shorts. Sharing a video to YouTube via the Share Sheet was an option in a prior version of the YouTube app, but it was removed back in 2018. Until this week, there was no option to use native sharing to upload to YouTube. <br/>
<br/>
YouTube updated its app to version 19.47.7 yesterday, but did not mention the new Share Sheet integration. You'll need the latest version of the app to use the feature. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube/">YouTube</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/youtube-share-sheet-integration/">You Can Now Upload Videos Directly to YouTube With iOS Share Sheet Integration</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-upload-videos-directly-to-youtube-with-ios-share-sheet-integration.2443997/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Adds Live Location Sharing to Direct Messages</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/instagram-dm-live-location-sharing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-adds-live-location-sharing-to-direct-messages.2443984/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:37:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/instagram-dm-live-location-sharing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram <a href="https://about.instagram.com/blog/announcements/new-instagram-dm-features-update">today announced</a> several updates for direct messages on its platform, including location sharing, nicknames, new sticker packs, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/instagram-location-sharing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979565" /><br/>
There's now an option to share a live location with a friend for up to one hour on Instagram, which can be used for locating friends when getting together in real life. There's also an option to pin a spot to a map for coordinating meetups.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram says that locations can only be shared privately in DMs, either in a chat with just one other person or a group chat. All live locations will expire after an hour, and the feature is turned off by default. Only people in the chat can see your location, and location information cannot be forwarded to other chats. Instagram's blog post says that users should be "mindful" of their privacy and only share their location with real-life friends.<br/>
<br/>
DMs in Instagram can be customized with nicknames, which appear in DM chats. Users can set nicknames for themselves or their friends, simplifying lengthy usernames to make them easier to recognize. Creating a nickname can be done by tapping on the chat name at the top of a conversation and then tapping on Nicknames and the username of the person.<br/>
<br/>
Along with location sharing and nicknames, Instagram has also added 17 sticker packs with 300 new stickers that can be used in DMs. There is a new option to favorite a sticker, and a new DM sticker tray.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/instagram-dm-live-location-sharing/">Instagram Adds Live Location Sharing to Direct Messages</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-adds-live-location-sharing-to-direct-messages.2443984/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next-Generation CarPlay Images With Audi Logo Appear in EU Database</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/next-generation-carplay-images-in-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-generation-carplay-images-with-audi-logo-appear-in-eu-database.2443980/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:38:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/next-generation-carplay-images-in-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this month filed next-generation CarPlay images <a href="https://euipo.europa.eu/eSearch/#details/designs/015079704-0001">with the EU's Intellectual Property Office</a>, as it seeks to protect the design of the upcoming software system there. It is yet another sign that next-generation CarPlay might finally be nearing launch, after a few <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/11/ios-18-2-beta-next-generation-carplay-icons/">redesigned icons for the system showed up in iOS 18.2 beta code</a> earlier this month.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><em>Porsche's preview of next-generation CarPlay from December 2023</em></div><br/>
The images show various next-generation CarPlay instrument cluster and interface designs, including a few with what appears to be the logo for German automaker Audi. When it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/06/apple-announces-multi-display-carplay/">first previewed next-generation CarPlay</a> in June 2022, Apple said Audi was committed to offering it, but the automaker has yet to confirm any specific plans.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Next-Generation-CarPlay-EU-Image-Filings.jpg" alt="" width="7766" height="3749" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979556" /><em>A few of the next-generation CarPlay images filed in the EU</em></div><br/>
The database entries were discovered by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has already shown off what next-generation CarPlay looks like several times, so the images do not show anything we have not seen before, but the timing of the filings is notable. <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/carplay/">Apple's website</a> continues to say that the first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay support will "arrive in 2024," but it has yet to provide a more specific timeframe. Aston Martin and Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed next-generation CarPlay vehicle designs</a> in December 2023, but neither automaker has released any vehicles with support yet.<br/>
<br/>
With just over a month left in the year, some are beginning to wonder if Apple will still meet its stated 2024 timeframe for next-generation CarPlay. So, it is reassuring that Apple is still working towards a launch behind the scenes.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/next-generation-carplay-images-in-eu/">Next-Generation CarPlay Images With Audi Logo Appear in EU Database</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-generation-carplay-images-with-audi-logo-appear-in-eu-database.2443980/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Black Friday Accessory Deals: Save on Chargers, Keyboards, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/black-friday-accessory-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/black-friday-accessory-deals-save-on-chargers-keyboards-and-more.2443978/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:59:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/black-friday-accessory-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're officially in Black Friday week, and deals have begun in full force on Amazon and other retailers online. If you're looking for Apple products, our dedicated post on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday deals available now</strong></a> covers every Apple device on sale right now. In this article, we're focusing on accessories for smartphones and computers, as well as a few extras like LEGO sets on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/accessory-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979512" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Highlights of the sale includes Eufy's popular <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1732558738181">SmartTrack Card</a>, which is down to &#36;16.88 for Black Friday, down from &#36;29.99. This device is Apple Find My-compatible and is slim enough to fit in a wallet. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV4WNKHT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1EU2DMVHLSNCO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1EU2DMVHLSNCO_1732558772201">Twelve South's HiRise 3 Deluxe</a> is also back on sale for &#36;119.99, down from &#36;149.99, and it provides simultaneous charging for an iPhone, AirPods, and Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
There are plenty more deals in this sale, including a huge collection of Jackery portable power stations at their best ever prices. We're also tracking an array of Logitech computer accessories, including mice, keyboards, and webcams. Some of these sales will require you to clip an on-page coupon, but for the most part all of these deals have been applied automatically on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Charging Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/jackery-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979519" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2NU1FYZEFA24K%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2NU1FYZEFA24K_1732559630685">Jackery Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;169.00, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1CDWV12ADVGRD%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1CDWV12ADVGRD_1732559827170">Jackery Solar Generator 240 with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.TMZJ84LM6J1V%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.TMZJ84LM6J1V_1732559685244">Jackery Explorer 1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;399.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1JG4JW0TOXKN%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1JG4JW0TOXKN_1732559658230">Jackery Expansion Battery Pack 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;479.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3A51Q181GJIHI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3A51Q181GJIHI_1732559927847">Jackery Solar Generator Explorer 500</a> - &#36;479.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3UYWTK1L3TQJI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3UYWTK1L3TQJI_1732559882309">Jackery Explorer 3000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETEDJYKMSV69%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETEDJYKMSV69_1732559784230">Jackery Solar Generator 4000 Kit</a> - &#36;2,599.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYQBR7Y9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETEDJYKMSV69%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETEDJYKMSV69_1732559784230">Jackery Solar Generator 2000 Plus Kit</a> - &#36;3,399.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;6,599.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Mobile Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/twelve-south-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979518" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1732558738181">Eufy SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;16.88, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV4WNKHT%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1EU2DMVHLSNCO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1EU2DMVHLSNCO_1732558772201">Twelve South HiRise 3 Deluxe</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Storage Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/samsung-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979517" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHFS9K14%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0_1732559154265">Samsung T9 Portable SSD 2TB</a> - &#36;199.00, down from &#36;299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/q4aczxh635u86">Samsung T5 EVO Portable SSD 4TB</a> - &#36;229.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/5vsxbo1qhyw6x">Samsung T5 EVO Portable SSD 8TB</a> - &#36;429.99, down from &#36;654.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BHJF2VRN%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0_1732559196404">Samsung 990 PRO 1TB PCIe Internal SSD</a> - &#36;92.46, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/oha6gs6csihw0">Samsung 990 PRO 2TB PCIe Internal SSD</a> - &#36;169.99, down from &#36;249.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/q05x3jsdevcmi">Samsung 990 PRO 4TB PCIe Internal SSD</a> - &#36;269.99, down from &#36;464.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08RK2SR23%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0_1732559280588">Samsung 980 PRO 2TB PCIe Internal SSD</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;204.95</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Audio/Video Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/audio-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979516" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV4J899R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0_1732559227468">Samsung HW-Q910D Soundbar with Dolby Audio</a> - &#36;897.99, down from &#36;1,287.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV9LXY7M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.YI4YEU0SJOO0_1732563374268">SAMSUNG OLED 4K S95D TV</a> - &#36;3,497.99 for 77"; &#36;2,297.99 for 65"; &#36;1,897.99 for 55"</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Solo-Buds-Compatibility-Built%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB14QS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Beats Solo Buds</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Cancelling-Earbuds-Built-Bluetooth-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB096SV8SJG%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Buds</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;149.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Pill-2024-release-Compatible%2Fdp%2FB0D4SX9RC6%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Pill</a> - &#36;99.95, down from &#36;149.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Solo-Ear-Headphones-Compatible%2Fdp%2FB0DDQLGDY3%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Solo 4</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;199.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Cancelling-Compatibility-Microphone-Headphones%2Fdp%2FB0C2W1KLSS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Buds +</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;169.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBeats-Studio-Pro-Personalized-Compatibility%2Fdp%2FB0C8PT7DF5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Beats Studio Pro</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Computer Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/logitech-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979515" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB00ADBY98A%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732558822269">Logitech M317 Wireless Mouse</a> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB014EUQOGK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732559035819">Logitech K400 Plus Wireless Keyboard with Touchpad</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;27.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB072JX77X6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732558867633">Logitech MK335 Wireless Keyboard</a> - &#36;29.74, down from &#36;34.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BPY4ZQXG%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732558897249">Logitech MX Anywhere 3S Wireless Mouse</a> - &#36;67.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB01AROOL12%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732558926084">Logitech MK235 Wireless Keyboard</a> - &#36;17.99, down from &#36;24.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB000UXZQ42%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732558951119">Logitech H390 Wired Headset</a> - &#36;17.99, down from &#36;24.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CBPNWCVS%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732559072641">Logitech MK540 Wireless Keyboard and Mouse</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB006JH8T3S%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732558982452">Logitech HD Pro Webcam</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09NBWWP79%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3C1TPPOEVEV8Z_1732559007571">Logitech Brio PRO X 4K Webcam</a> - &#36;144.99, down from &#36;169.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>LEGO Sets</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/lego-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979514" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV2FC2V1%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559358556">Marvel Spider-Man Advent Calendar</a> - &#36;31.49, down from &#36;44.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CV2DXF71%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559586371">Disney Advent Calendar</a> - &#36;31.49, down from &#36;44.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXQ64WP4%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559397960">Star Wars Ahsoka Tano's T-6 Jedi Shuttle</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSRG23RY%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559488199">DREAMZzz Stable of Dream Creatures</a> - &#36;53.00, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSRF1VHN%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559550244">Creator Main Street 3-in-1 Set</a> - &#36;102.99, down from &#36;139.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BBYRH7P8%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559577091">Star Wars The Razor Crest UCS</a> - &#36;416.79, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSRFQLD6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3T1R3HFWQY7IA_1732559457835">Technic Liebherr Crawler Crane</a> - &#36;595.99, down from &#36;699.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/black-friday-accessory-deals/">Black Friday Accessory Deals: Save on Chargers, Keyboards, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/black-friday-accessory-deals-save-on-chargers-keyboards-and-more.2443978/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;149 During Amazon&#039;s Black Friday Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/apple-watch-se-new-record/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-apple-watch-se-for-just-149-during-amazons-black-friday-sale.2443975/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 11:29:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/apple-watch-se-new-record/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is discounting the Apple Watch SE to the new all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;149.00</strong></a> this week, down from &#36;249.00. This is about &#36;20 cheaper than the previous record low price, and Amazon has the sale in two colors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/apple-watch-se-holiday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-975584" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Specifically, you can get this sale in the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZJVYY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Starlight Aluminum Case with Lake Green Sport Loop</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Starlight Aluminum Case with Starlight Sport Band</a>. All of the other colors are sitting at the usual &#36;169.00 discount price on Amazon, which is still a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;149.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/apple-watch-se-new-record/">Get Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;149 During Amazon&#039;s Black Friday Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-apple-watch-se-for-just-149-during-amazons-black-friday-sale.2443975/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 Get Massive &#36;95 Discount for Black Friday, Available For Just &#36;153.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/airpods-pro-2-95-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-get-massive-95-discount-for-black-friday-available-for-just-153-99.2443972/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:00:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/airpods-pro-2-95-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday deals keep rolling in, and today we're tracking a new record low price on the AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) on Amazon. You can get these headphones for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;153.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-pro-bulbs.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923440" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Before Black Friday 2024, these were typically priced around &#36;189.99 on sale, so today's price is a massive discount on the AirPods Pro 2. The AirPods Pro 2 were updated in 2023 with USB-C, and also feature Active Noise Cancellation, Apple's H2 chip, and Spatial Audio.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;95 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;153.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/apple-black-friday-deals-now-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/airpods-pro-2-95-discount/">AirPods Pro 2 Get Massive &#36;95 Discount for Black Friday, Available For Just &#36;153.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-get-massive-95-discount-for-black-friday-available-for-just-153-99.2443972/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
