<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 03:00:52 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Can&#039;t Release Old App for Customers Unhappy With Design Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/sonos-not-rereleasing-old-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-cant-release-old-app-for-customers-unhappy-with-design-changes.2434045/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/sonos-not-rereleasing-old-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos won't be able to re-release its old app to appease customers that have been dissatisfied with the new version of the app, Sonos CEO Patrick Spence today said on Reddit <em>(via <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/20/24224754/sonos-ceo-old-s2-app-re-release-cant-be">The Verge</a>)</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
Spence said that he was "hopeful" the old app would be able to be re-released up until "very recently" as an alternative for people having issues, but Sonos found that doing so would ultimately make the issues worse because of backend updates to cloud servers and the software that runs on speakers.<br/>
<blockquote>Everything has been on the table in terms of finding the fastest path to fixing your systems. In fact, until very recently I'd been hopeful that we could re-release the old app (S2) as an alternative for those of you that are having issues that we've not yet resolved.<br/>
<br/>
The trick of course is that Sonos is not just the mobile app, but software that runs on your speakers and in the cloud too. In the months since the new mobile app launched we've been updating the software that runs on our speakers and in the cloud to the point where today S2 is less reliable &amp; less stable then what you remember. After doing extensive testing we've reluctantly concluded that re-releasing S2 would make the problems worse, not better. I'm sure this is disappointing. It was disappointing to me.</blockquote><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/sonos-bring-back-old-app/">Earlier this month</a>, <em>The Verge</em> reported that Sonos was considering bringing back the original version of its app, and Sonos was reportedly hopeful that allowing customers to revert to the old app would provide an interim solution as the company works to improve the new app. It sounds like that plan has been scrapped, which is unfortunate for customers who are having problems with the redesign.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">redesigned version of its app</a> back in May, and it has turned out to be a disaster for the company. Sonos customers quickly found that the new app lacked several key features and was riddled with bugs, and there have been ongoing complaints for months.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/">issued an apology</a> in July and shared an outline of future update plans that will see missing features returned in September and October. In August, Sonos said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/sonos-delays-product-launces-to-fix-app/">it would delay</a> two upcoming product launches planned for 2024 to focus on improving the app.<br/>
<br/>
In today's Reddit post, Spence said that the "original architect of the Sonos platform" has been put back in charge, and that the company has also "pulled together the very best and most experienced engineers" that it has to work on the app until it is fixed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/sonos-not-rereleasing-old-app/">Sonos Can&#039;t Release Old App for Customers Unhappy With Design Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-cant-release-old-app-for-customers-unhappy-with-design-changes.2434045/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Photography Awards Highlight Best Images of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-photography-awards-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-photography-awards-highlight-best-images-of-2024.2434042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:42:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-photography-awards-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Every year, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Photography Awards (IPPA) selects the best photographs captured with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and the 2024 award winners <a href="https://www.ippawards.com/?v=7516fd43adaa">were announced today</a>. Many of this year's winning images were taken with Apple's most recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Blue-Three-Quarters-Perspective-Camera-Closeup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909012" /><br/>
The grand prize image features a boy at an aquarium, with the photo shot in black and white using an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iphone-photography-award-main-winner.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="795" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962058" /><br/>
The first place image includes a group of swimmers at a lifeguard camp from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 Pro Pro Max, while the second place image features children in Cambodia shot on an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/first-place-ippa-winner-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="600" height="761" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962059" /><br/>
There are also winners across a number of categories, including abstract, animals, architecture, children, cityscape, landscape, lifestyle, nature, people, portrait, series, still life, travel, and other. All of the winning images can be <a href="https://www.ippawards.com/2024-winning-photographers/?v=7516fd43adaa">viewed on the IPPA website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
IPPA has been running the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Photography Awards since 2007, and 2024 marks the 17th annual competition. The contests are open to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users worldwide, and images can be edited with iOS apps. It is worth noting that it costs money to send in a photo, but Apple devices are provided as prizes.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-photography-awards-2024/">iPhone Photography Awards Highlight Best Images of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-photography-awards-highlight-best-images-of-2024.2434042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for Beats Studio Pro With Audio Sharing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro-with-audio-sharing.2434041/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:30:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Beats Studio Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware for the Beats Studio Pro over-ear headphones. The Beats Studio Pro can be updated to firmware version 2C301, up from the prior 2B68 firmware that was installed on the headphones at launch. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/beats-studio-pro-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903700" /><br/>
Today's firmware update introduces support for audio sharing, a feature that was not available at launch. Audio sharing is designed to allow two people to listen to music from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The Share Audio… option was not there on the old 2B68 firmware. <a href="https://t.co/5xLX46lElP">pic.twitter.com/5xLX46lElP</a></p>&mdash; Jonathan Forsander (@jforsander) <a href="https://twitter.com/jforsander/status/1826027992134595029?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 20, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple introduced the Beats Studio Pro headphones <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/beats-studio-pro-debut/">just over a year ago</a>, marking an update to the original Studio headphones that made the Beats brand popular. The &#36;350 Beats Studio Pro headphones feature Active Noise Cancellation support, Personalized Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking, multiple audio profiles, and improved audio quality with better bass performance compared to prior models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not include an Apple audio chip in the Beats Studio Pro, instead opting for a custom Beats chip that provides better feature parity between iOS and Android devices. The Beats chip supports one-touch pairing and setup, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> integration, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> support, but automatic switching between devices is not available.<br/>
<br/>
As with all of Apple's headphone and earbud products, firmware updates for the Beats Studio Pro are delivered over-the-air. Firmware will be installed while the Beats headphones are charging and are in Bluetooth range of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, or Mac that's connected to Wi-Fi.<br/>
<br/>
On Android devices, users will need to download the Beats app for Android and connect the Android device to a power outlet to initiate a firmware update. There is no word on what's new in the firmware.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats-studio-pro/">Beats Studio Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro/">Apple Releases New Firmware for Beats Studio Pro With Audio Sharing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-studio-pro-with-audio-sharing.2434041/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Major &#039;National Public Data&#039; Leak Worse Than Expected With Passwords Stored in Plain Text</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/npd-data-leak-plain-text/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-national-public-data-leak-worse-than-expected-with-passwords-stored-in-plain-text.2434039/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:42:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/npd-data-leak-plain-text/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this month, data broker National Public Data (NPD) announced that there had <a href="https://nationalpublicdata.com/Breach.html">been a major data breach</a> that saw hackers obtain millions of names, email addresses, phone numbers, social security numbers, and mailing addresses stored in its database. NPD is a company that does employee background checks, aggregating public data from numerous sources and selling it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-security-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1145" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796484" /><br/>
NPD's security was clearly lacking to allow for the breach in the first place, but a new report from <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2024/08/national-public-data-published-its-own-passwords/"><em>KrebsOnSecurity</em></a> suggests that an NPD sister site made an even more grievous error, hosting an easily accessible plaintext archive with usernames and passwords.<br/>
<br/>
RecordsCheck.net, a site affiliated with NPD that hosts much of the same information, had a "members.zip" file that was downloadable until yesterday. It had source code and plain text usernames and passwords for RecordsCheck users, including logins belonging to NPD's founder, Salvatore Verini. The logins that were made available through RecordsCheck allowed access to the same data that was available via NPD.<br/>
<br/>
After being alerted by KrebsOnSecurity, RecordsCheck removed the file, and NPD is shutting down the site, according to Verini. He told the KrebsOnSecurity that the file had an "old version of the site with non-working code and passwords."<br/>
<br/>
There are websites <a href="https://www.npdbreach.com/">that are available</a> to see if your information was leaked in the NPD breach, and it is advisable to lock down your credit.<br/>
<br/>
The NPD leak included decades of information, including data from people who are now deceased. 137 million email addresses <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2024/08/nationalpublicdata-com-hack-exposes-a-nations-data/">were leaked</a>, as were 272 million social security numbers. A lawsuit has <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/social-security-number-leak-npd-breach-what-to-know/">since been filed</a> against NPD.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/npd-data-leak-plain-text/">Major &#039;National Public Data&#039; Leak Worse Than Expected With Passwords Stored in Plain Text</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-national-public-data-leak-worse-than-expected-with-passwords-stored-in-plain-text.2434039/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Gives Customers 45 Days to Extend AppleCare+ Coverage After Expiration</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/applecare-coverage-extension-period-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-gives-customers-45-days-to-extend-applecare-coverage-after-expiration.2434031/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:21:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/applecare-coverage-extension-period-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AppleCare</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in August increased the period in which customers can extend their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ coverage after it expires. Apple used to allow coverage to be extended for 30 days after the end of the original &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan, but that has now changed to 45 days.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/applecare-apple-care-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1896" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828594" /><br/>
The <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/101560">AppleCare+ extension support document</a> says that customers have 45 days to sign up for a new &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan after existing coverage expires, with options for extending plans by 24 months, 36 months, monthly, or on an annual basis until canceled.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans can be extended for 45 days after expiration in Australia, Austria Canada, Denmark, Finland, France, Germany, Ireland, Italy, Japan, the Netherlands, New Zealand, Norway, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, the United Kingdom, and the United States. In China, there is still a 30-day limit.<br/>
<br/>
An upfront &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Apple Watch is eligible for updated coverage that renews monthly or annually, while upfront &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans for Mac can be enrolled in a new coverage plan that renews on an annual basis.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who want to renew their expired &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans can go to <a href="https://mysupport.apple.com/">Apple's support website</a> to see if their devices are eligible. Apple does not guarantee that &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ can be renewed, and it does not alert customers when &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ is expiring unless required by law.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ expiration dates can be checked in the Settings app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, in the System Settings app on a Mac, or <a href="https://mysupport.apple.com/">on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/applecare-coverage-extension-period-increase/">Apple Now Gives Customers 45 Days to Extend AppleCare+ Coverage After Expiration</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-gives-customers-45-days-to-extend-applecare-coverage-after-expiration.2434031/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OnePlus Buds Pro 3 vs. AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2.2434021/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:58:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>OnePlus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Chinese company OnePlus is debuting new earbuds today, with a feature set that pits them against the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>. The OnePlus Buds Pro 3 look and sound a lot like Apple's AirPods, and while they lack some of the Apple-esque magic integration, they're more affordable at &#36;179.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c4d9oj0Z43o" title="These Headphones Sound BETTER than AirPods Pro!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Design wise, the OnePlus earbuds resemble the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, featuring an in-ear silicone design and a stem. The stem is silver, though, and unlike Samsung's recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a>, you won't mistake these for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; due to the unique case design of the OnePlus Buds Pro 3. Fit is close to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; because of the silicone tips, and they're comfortable to wear. Squeeze gestures can be used on the stem to play/pause music, skip tracks, replay a track, and adjust volume.<br/>
<br/>
The case has an oval shape that's wider and more rounded than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; case, plus it's covered in a faux leather material that gives it a more distinct look.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may have added a USB-C case to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 in 2023, but the initial launch was in 2022, so it's no surprise that other companies are starting to surpass the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; in terms of sound quality. The OnePlus Buds Pro 3 have better out-of-the-box sound than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, even though there's no option for adjusting EQ.<br/>
<br/>
There's a solid balance between bass and higher frequencies with full sound and good separation of tracks. Sound is crisp, and the high-end notes are clear. there are two DACs per earbud, one that's focused on the tweeter and the other on the woofer, which is what gives that balanced sound.<br/>
<br/>
The Active Noise Cancellation works well, and it's on par with ANC from other high-end earbuds. The ANC is adaptive and can adjust based on your surroundings, so ambient sounds can come through when you need them to. The ANC isn't as standout as the sound quality, but it's more than adequate.<br/>
<br/>
Battery lasts for up to 43 hours, which is 13 hours longer than the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, and there is ear detection when using the earbuds with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. As for the microphones, call quality is solid.<br/>
<br/>
OnePlus sells Android-based devices, so these earbuds are designed for Android smartphones rather than the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. You're not going to get the useful AirPods features like quick connect and automatic device swapping, and that's a major downside. You also won't get spatial audio unless these are paired with a Google Pixel phone that supports the feature.<br/>
<br/>
For Apple device users, the OnePlus Buds Pro 3 are just standard Bluetooth earbuds, but if that's all you need, you might like what OnePlus has to offer.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oneplus/">OnePlus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2/">OnePlus Buds Pro 3 vs. AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oneplus-buds-pro-3-vs-airpods-pro-2.2434021/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434012/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:08:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the seventh beta of upcoming an upcoming macOS 15 Sequoia update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-6/">release of the sixth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which allows you to control your locked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac. You can open and use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, interact with notifications, and drag and drop files between your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
There are new options for window tiling, and dragging a window to the edge of the display will suggest a tiled location to make it easier to use multiple apps at once. Apple is adding a Passwords app for managing passwords, Safari can summarize websites, surface key information, and Notes has support for live audio transcription and math equations.<br/>
<br/>
All of the Apple Intelligence features coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> will also be available in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, but Apple does not plan to add these until later in the beta testing process. Apple Intelligence includes Writing Tools for editing, proofreading, and summarizing text in apps, and an Image Playground allows for AI images to be created from prompts.<br/>
<br/>
Custom emoji or "Genmoji" can be created for any situation and used just like emoji, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting much smarter. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do more in apps and will better understand requests, especially those made in regard to on-screen content.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/">Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434012/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:07:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the seventh betas of upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-6-to-developers/">release of the sixth betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;/&zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;‌ Developer Beta setting. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta. The &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; beta track is now separate from the iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1 beta track, with the .1 betas adding support for Apple Intelligence on devices that are able to run the features. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; introduces Apple Intelligence, a set of AI features that are built deeply into the operating system. Apple Intelligence won't be coming until later in the beta testing process, but it includes features for refining and editing writing, generating images and emoji, and most notably, improving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and search. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is gaining a better understanding of natural language, improved contextual awareness, and the personal assistant will integrate with ChatGPT to answer more complex queries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features are limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and iPads with an M-series chip, but there are a number of other features that are coming. Apple is allowing users to rearrange Home screen apps to have open spaces, plus there's a dark mode for app icons and tinting options.<br/>
<br/>
The Control Center is customizable and third-party developers can add controls for their apps, with the Lock Screen Flashlight and Camera icons able to be replaced or removed. Messages is gaining Rich Communication Services support to improve conversations with Android users, the option to schedule texts to be sent later, new text effects, messages over satellite when there's no cellular, and the option to use any emoji for Tapback responses.<br/>
<br/>
There's a dedicated Passwords app for logins, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, and verification codes, and there's now an option to lock and hide apps, which means they can't be opened without secondary <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication even when your phone is unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
Safari has a highlights feature that summarizes articles and surfaces key information on websites, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app interface has been overhauled, and there's a new Tap to Cash feature for privately and securely transferring money using Apple Cash. Other features include equation solving and voice memo transcription in Notes, a game mode for improving game performance, and an option to respond to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on AirPods with head gestures.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will release &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; to the public this fall.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Seventh Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh visionOS 2 Beta to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-seventh-visionos-2-beta-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-visionos-2-beta-to-developers.2434013/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:04:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-seventh-visionos-2-beta-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the seventh beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> update to developers, with the beta coming a week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-visionos-2-beta-6-to-developers/">after the sixth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955607" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app on their device, going to the Software Update Section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; is able to take the depth information from 2D photos and turn them into 3D photos using advanced machine learning. Apple says that the feature is meant to add depth to photos to make memories more immersive.<br/>
<br/>
There are new hand gestures for activating the Home View and Control Center, and the Home View is also now customizable with apps able to be rearranged. Travel Mode now includes support for trains, and Guest User profiles are now saved for 30 days so guests don't have to do the setup process every time they try out the headset.<br/>
<br/>
Later in the year, Mac Virtual Display will support higher resolution and larger sized virtual displays, which Apple says will be equivalent to two 4K monitors side by side. With an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> update, the Vision Pro can serve as an &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; receiver, so content from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac can be shared to the headset.<br/>
<br/>
The Mindfulness app can track and respond to breathing patterns using the camera for an improved meditation experience, and the Vision Pro supports Bluetooth mice with &zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-seventh-visionos-2-beta-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Seventh visionOS 2 Beta to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-visionos-2-beta-to-developers.2434013/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of watchOS 11 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-watchos-11-to-developers.2434014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:03:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the seventh beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-6-to-developers/">the sixth beta</a> was released. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Thumb-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955941" /><br/>
To install the ‌&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; introduces a new Vitals app that aggregates health metrics collected during sleep like heart rate and respiratory rate, providing day-to-day health insights to track whether something has changed. There's also a Training Load feature for monitoring the intensity of workouts and how that impacts the body over time.<br/>
<br/>
The Smart Stack has been updated with new widgets and support for Live Activities and Translate, plus it is better able to suggest widgets based on time and daily routine. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face includes suggestions for the best images to use, and the Check In safety feature now works with Workouts.<br/>
<br/>
Activity Rings can be customized to change the goals for each day, and there is an option to pause for rest days or when ill without losing an activity streak. Double Tap now works for navigating through apps with one hand, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> lets users create their own walking and hiking routes.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-7/">Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of watchOS 11 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-watchos-11-to-developers.2434014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of tvOS 18 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-tvos-18-to-developers.2434015/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the seventh beta of the upcoming tvOS 18 refresh to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-6-to-developers/">the sixth beta came out</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-tv-4k-new-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953895" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 18 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 adds an InSight feature to the TV app, and it is able to provide real-time information about actors, music, and more in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> shows and music. Enhanced Dialogue has been refined with machine learning and computational audio so it is better able to boost vocal clarity over background noise and music, plus it is now available on built-in TV speakers, AirPods, and other Bluetooth devices.<br/>
<br/>
Subtitles will now show up automatically when relevant, such as when the TV's volume is muted, a show or movie is rewound, or when the language of a show doesn't match the device language.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include 21:9 aspect ratio support for projectors, new screen savers and improved controls for swapping screen savers, and support for Live Captions during <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls through an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-7/">Apple Seeds Seventh Beta of tvOS 18 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-seventh-beta-of-tvos-18-to-developers.2434015/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Custom 5G Modem Could &#039;Change the Way iPhone Looks and Works&#039; in the Long Term</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-custom-modem-could-change-way-iphone-works/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-custom-5g-modem-could-change-the-way-iphone-looks-and-works-in-the-long-term.2434003/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:13:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-custom-modem-could-change-way-iphone-works/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is investing billions of dollars into developing an in-house cellular modem, but the project is not expected to yield immediate improvements for users, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Apple-5G-Modem-Feature-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="2240" height="1260" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-788396" /><br/>
In last week's <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-08-18/why-is-apple-building-own-modem-company-plays-long-game-in-dropping-qualcomm-lzzk8616">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that, unlike the transition to Apple silicon, the company's first custom modem will not offer noticeable benefits for users. Individuals within Apple apparently "acknowledge that customers don't really care who makes the modem in their phone" and "it's hard to tell how big the benefits will be in the near term."<br/>
<br/>
Instead, Apple is looking to play "the long game, hoping its modem will evolve into a more advanced component that could ultimately change the way an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> looks and works." <br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Down the road, there are plans for Apple to fold its modem design into a new wireless chip that handles Wi-Fi and Bluetooth access. That would create a single connectivity component, potentially improving reliability and battery life.<br/>
<br/>
There's also the possibility that Apple could one day combine all of this into the device's main system on a chip, or SoC. That could further cut costs and save space inside the iPhone, allowing for more design choices.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Apple has used modems designed by Qualcomm for over a decade, but moved to design its own following a legal battle over royalties and patents in 2018. Since then, it has faced issues with performance and overheating, and the component's debut has been pushed back until next year at the earliest. Its rollout is expected to take place on a gradual basis, starting with more niche devices and expanding across the lineup over the period of a few years. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-custom-modem-could-change-way-iphone-works/">Apple&#039;s Custom 5G Modem Could &#039;Change the Way iPhone Looks and Works&#039; in the Long Term</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-custom-5g-modem-could-change-the-way-iphone-looks-and-works-in-the-long-term.2434003/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Discounts Entire M2/M3 MacBook Air Lineup With Up to &#36;250 Off and All-Time Low Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/amazon-entire-macbook-air-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-entire-m2-m3-macbook-air-lineup-with-up-to-250-off-and-all-time-low-prices.2433994/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:09:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/amazon-entire-macbook-air-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is back this week with a big sale <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">across the MacBook Air lineup</a>, including both the M2 and M3 MacBook Air models. You can find many of the same deals being <a href="https://howl.me/cmVaWxMWwLT">matched at Best Buy</a>, and you won't need a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership in order to see the discounts this time around.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macbook-air-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-961113" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the M2 MacBook Air, Amazon is offering &#36;200 off both models of the 2022 notebook. Prices start at &#36;799.00 for the 256GB M2 MacBook Air in all colors, and increase to &#36;999.00 for the 512GB MacBook Air in Midnight. In regards to the former model, this is a match of the all-time low price for this MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><h2>13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/15-inch-m3-macbook-air.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947373" /><br/>
<br/>
For the newer models, Amazon is taking &#36;250 off the 13-inch M3 MacBook Air with multiple all-time low prices. You can get the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;849.00 in every color, down from &#36;1,099.00. Both 512GB models are on sale as well with best-ever prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BNQC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><h2>15-Inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Finally, Amazon also has the 15-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;249-&#36;250 off every model. These start at &#36;1,049.99 for the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air, down from &#36;1,299.00, and again include both 512GB models. Overall, every 15-inch M3 MacBook Air deal from Amazon this week represents all-time low prices on each model, and two of them will require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/amazon-entire-macbook-air-discounts/">Amazon Discounts Entire M2/M3 MacBook Air Lineup With Up to &#36;250 Off and All-Time Low Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-entire-m2-m3-macbook-air-lineup-with-up-to-250-off-and-all-time-low-prices.2433994/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Offering Free Three-Month Trial for a Limited Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-music-free-three-month-trial/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-offering-free-three-month-trial-for-a-limited-time.2433983/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 05:56:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-music-free-three-month-trial/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is offering an extended <a href="https://offers.applemusic.apple/2024-three-month-offer">three-month free Apple Music trial</a> for new users over the summer, provided they haven't been a subscriber to the streaming service before.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962031" /><br/>
‌Apple Music‌ typically offers a one-month free trial for new subscribers since it was shortened from three months in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/04/apple-music-one-month-trial/">2022</a>, so this deal is worth grabbing if you are curious about the service. <br/>
<br/>
Note that this offer is for new subscribers only. If you are not currently a subscriber to Apple Music, and you have never previously subscribed to Apple Music or Apple One, or had access to Apple Music through a Family plan, you are eligible for this offer.<br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://www.engadget.com/deals/apple-music-is-currently-offering-new-subscribers-three-months-free-185834470.html?src=rss">Engadget</a></em> spotted the offer, which is running until September 23. After the trial ends, the service will automatically renew for &#36;11 per month, so it's a good idea to set a reminder in case you don't want to continue paying for access.<br/>
<br/>
To redeem the offer, open the Apple Music app on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac and sign in with your Apple ID. If the offer doesn't appear immediately after launching the app, go to the Home tab where it will appear, then tap Accept Now.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-music-free-three-month-trial/">Apple Music Offering Free Three-Month Trial for a Limited Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-offering-free-three-month-trial-for-a-limited-time.2433983/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPhone 16 Thermal Design High on Buyers&#039; Wishlist, Survey Suggests</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pre-launch-survey-overheating/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-thermal-design-high-on-buyers-wishlist-survey-suggests.2433980/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 04:49:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pre-launch-survey-overheating/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>SellCell</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A recent survey conducted by <a href="https://www.sellcell.com/blog/iphone-16-pre-launch-survey/">SellCell</a> suggests that a significant majority of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users are planning to upgrade to the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series, with many expressing a preference for a better thermal design to prevent overheating issues. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Pro-Mock-Article.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924441" /><br/>
The survey, which polled over 2,000 US-based &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; owners (1,000 males and 1,000 females), found that 61.9% of respondents plan to purchase an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model upon release.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive pricing emerged as the most crucial factor, with 30.9% of respondents citing it as the primary influence on their decision to upgrade. But it was improved heat management that turned out to be another key area of interest, with 26.8% of users hoping for better thermal performance to prevent overheating issues. <br/>
<br/>
Shortly after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max were released last September, some customers began to experience an issue with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/">devices overheating</a>. Apple eventually mitigated the problem with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/04/apple-releases-ios-17-0-3/">iOS 17 update</a>, but &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to be equipped with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/23/internal-change-to-iphone-16-models-expected-to-reduce-overheating/">new thermal design</a> to address potential overheating.<br/>
<br/>
The SellCell survey also revealed significant interest in Apple Intelligence capabilities for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;. A striking 82.1% of respondents expressed willingness to wait up to a month after release for the AI features to be fully implemented. Apple plans to release Apple Intelligence features in an iOS 18.1 update that is expected to arrive in October.<br/>
<br/>
Another intriguing finding was the interest in larger displays for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; series. Despite the current &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max already boasting a 6.7-inch screen, over half of the respondents (54.9%) indicated they would welcome even bigger iPhones. The finding chimes with expectations that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/iphone-16-display-sizes/">slightly bigger displays</a>.<br/>
<br/>
However, there was a notable gender divide on the issue of display size. The majority of men (62.1%) were in favor of larger displays, while women are more evenly split, with 47.8% expressing interest in bigger screens. Some female respondents cited concerns about handling and holding larger devices comfortably.<br/>
<br/>
For those who said they won't be buying the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, most people (34.2%) cited the expense as the reason, closely followed by people who won't invest because they are keeping their existing phone (34.1%).<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/iphone-16-launch-everything-we-know/">iPhone 16 Launch Is Less Than One Month Out – Here's Everything We Know</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple is expected to announce its new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup next month at an event that could take place on Tuesday, September 10, although Apple has not yet provided official confirmation of the date.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sellcell/">SellCell</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pre-launch-survey-overheating/">New iPhone 16 Thermal Design High on Buyers&#039; Wishlist, Survey Suggests</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-thermal-design-high-on-buyers-wishlist-survey-suggests.2433980/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Has New FaceTime Backgrounds Showcasing Apple Park</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/macos-sequoia-new-facetime-backgrounds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-has-new-facetime-backgrounds-showcasing-apple-park.2433978/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:30:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/macos-sequoia-new-facetime-backgrounds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>FaceTime</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the second beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 has added a set of new backgrounds for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls that showcase features of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macos-sequoia-facetime-backgrounds.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962006" /><br/>
There are nine backgrounds in all, featuring iconic locations around the company's circular headquarters in Cupertino, California, which should be familiar to anyone who has watched a recent Apple event.<br/>
<br/>
For example, one shows &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj;'s rainbow arch, based on the company's rainbow apple logo and erected as a tribute to its late co-founder Steve Jobs, who helped conceptualize the spaceship-like design of the main building on the campus prior to his death.<br/>
<br/>
In &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, there are other new built-in backgrounds that can be used for &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; and other video calls to blur out and hide what's behind you. These include different color gradients and the ability to use photos from your photo library.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; has also gained the ability to preview what you're going to share in a video call when using screen sharing. Video calling apps will now give you a small preview of what will be shared before you okay the sharing process, which is useful to double check that you're not sharing information you don't want everyone to see. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/will-my-mac-run-macos-sequoia/">Will My Mac Run macOS Sequoia?</a></li></ul><br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 is currently in its second developer beta phase and is expected to arrive for all users with supporting Macs later this year, following the release of &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15. Apple has split <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/does-my-iphone-support-apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> into a separate set of betas because these features will not be available in the initial launch version of ‌&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;‌.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/macos-sequoia-new-facetime-backgrounds/">macOS Sequoia Has New FaceTime Backgrounds Showcasing Apple Park</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-has-new-facetime-backgrounds-showcasing-apple-park.2433978/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Models to Be Assembled in India for the First Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pro-assembled-india-first-time/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-be-assembled-in-india-for-the-first-time.2433971/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 02:01:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pro-assembled-india-first-time/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>India</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is making the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max in India for the first time this year as it looks to diversify production beyond China, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-20/apple-s-first-made-in-india-iphone-pro-models-coming-this-year">Bloomberg</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iphone-16-pro-india-packaging.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961999" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Tear-off tab packaging for &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; (Image source: <a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/Ot9ycj5AZ">Weibo</a>)</em></div> <br/>
Apple has reportedly been considering producing its high-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Pro models in India for the last couple of years, and has now decided to manufacture the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max models in India. <br/>
<br/>
Initially, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models will be imported into the country, but Apple will start local assembly for both the domestic market and exports shortly after launch in mid-September, once the new product introduction (NPI) process is complete.<br/>
<br/>
Training is said to be already underway for thousands of workers at Foxconn's factory in southern Tamil Nadu state as it rushes to produce the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models as close to the global launch as possible.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/14/when-is-the-iphone-16-coming-out/">When Is the iPhone 16 Coming Out?</a></li></ul><br/>
Last year, Apple had India-made <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models ready on launch day, with locally made &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus models becoming available shortly after.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/india/">India</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pro-assembled-india-first-time/">iPhone 16 Pro Models to Be Assembled in India for the First Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-be-assembled-in-india-for-the-first-time.2433971/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 512GB 14-Inch MacBook Pro Gets Massive &#36;500 Discount, Priced at &#36;1,499</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apples-14-inch-macbook-pro-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-512gb-14-inch-macbook-pro-gets-massive-500-discount-priced-at-1-499.2433938/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:56:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apples-14-inch-macbook-pro-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a new all-time low price on the 512GB M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro, which has hit <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNLtwB0NL"><strong>&#36;1,499.00</strong></a> at <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNLtwB0NL">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a>, down from &#36;1,999.00. This beats the previous low price by &#36;100, and is available to all Best Buy shoppers without the need of a membership.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-purple-february.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936771" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
We're also tracking a few more 14-inch MacBook Pro discounts at both Best Buy and Amazon this week, including both M3 Pro and M3 Max models. You can get the 1TB M3 Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNPqm6oAK"><strong>&#36;2,099.00</strong></a> (&#36;300 off) and the 1TB M3 Max for <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNPLwopvW"><strong>&#36;2,899.00</strong></a> (&#36;300 off).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmUNLtwB0NL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;500 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (512GB M3 Pro) for &#36;1,499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the larger models, you can also find a solid record low price on the 512GB M3 Pro 16-inch MacBook Pro right now. It's available for <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNRokDLUg"><strong>&#36;1,999.00</strong></a> at <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNRokDLUg">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a>, down from &#36;2,499.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmUNRokDLUg"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;500 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (512GB M3 Pro) for &#36;1,999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apples-14-inch-macbook-pro-discount/">Apple&#039;s 512GB 14-Inch MacBook Pro Gets Massive &#36;500 Discount, Priced at &#36;1,499</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-512gb-14-inch-macbook-pro-gets-massive-500-discount-priced-at-1-499.2433938/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Re-Releases iOS 17.6.1 With Advanced Data Protection Bug Fix [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-re-releases-ios-17-6-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-re-releases-ios-17-6-1-with-advanced-data-protection-bug-fix-updated.2433936/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:24:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-re-releases-ios-17-6-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released an updated version of iOS 17.6.1, with the new software coming a week and a half after the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/07/apple-releases-ios-17-6-1/">original iOS 17.6.1 update</a>. The new version has a build number of 21G101, up from 21G93.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960873" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-17.6.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
iOS 17.6.1 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings &gt; General &gt; Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the iOS 17.6.1 update addresses an issue that could prevent the enabling or disabling of Advanced Data Protection. It is not clear what is different between the new version of the software and the original version.<br/>
<blockquote>This update includes important bug fixes and addresses an issue that prevents enabling or disabling Advanced Data Protection.</blockquote><br/>
The Advanced Data Protection bug impacted a small number of users. Those who tried to turn Advanced Data Protection on and weren't able to get it enabled saw an error message and it was clear it wasn't active. Affected users who tried to turn it off saw it disabled in the interface, though it was actually still active for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> data.<br/>
<br/>
Both of those bugs have been fixed in the update. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users who had the bug that prevented Advanced Data Protection from properly turning off will see a notification that asks them to confirm the decision to turn the feature off after installing iOS 17.6.1. Apple says that the few users who experienced this bug had an expected level of security or more, in the situation where ADP did not turn off as expected.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> The re-released iOS 17.6.1 update is available over the air on devices that are updating from older versions of iOS, including iOS iOS 12 and iOS 16. If you already had iOS 17.6.1 installed or another version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, you will not see the update with the 21G101 build number, nor will devices that have iOS 13, iOS 14, or iOS 15 installed. It fixes an issue that could prevent access to Apple Fitness+.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-re-releases-ios-17-6-1/">Apple Re-Releases iOS 17.6.1 With Advanced Data Protection Bug Fix [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-re-releases-ios-17-6-1-with-advanced-data-protection-bug-fix-updated.2433936/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 10.6.1 With Apple Fitness+ Bug Fix</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-releases-watchos-10-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-6-1-with-apple-fitness-bug-fix.2433935/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:14:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-releases-watchos-10-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.6.1, a minor update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that came out in September. watchOS 10.6.1 comes three weeks <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-watchos-10-6-with-bug-fixes/">after watchOS 10.6</a>, which was another bug fix update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/watchOS-10-feature-multicolor.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898580" /><br/>
‌‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌‌‌.6.1 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later by opening it up and going to General > Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the watchOS 10.6.1 update fixes an issue that could prevent access to the Apple Fitness+ service.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-releases-watchos-10-6/">Apple Releases watchOS 10.6.1 With Apple Fitness+ Bug Fix</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-6-1-with-apple-fitness-bug-fix.2433935/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
