<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:03:18 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Features: What&#039;s New in iOS 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-features-whats-new-in-ios-17-4.2421157/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 14:28:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features&#038;post_date=1709688516/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the iOS 17.4 update that brings some major changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> (and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>) in Europe. Many of the biggest changes in iOS 17.4 are limited to people in the European Union, but there new additions in the update that are available worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932462" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
In this article, we've rounded up everything new in iOS 17.4.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="eu_changes">EU Changes</h2><br/>
Apple is changing the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps operate in the European Union in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act. These changes are included in iOS 17.4, but are limited to countries that are in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833990" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" /><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="alternative_app_stores_and_new_app_store_terms_eu">Alternative App Stores and New App Store Terms (EU)</h3><br/>
App developers in the EU can opt to offer alternative app stores or install their apps through alternative stores, and Apple has a whole new fee structure that goes along with this change. There's a new business structure that developers can opt in to, which applies to both apps distributed in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and apps that are distributed through alternative means.<br/>
<br/>
App developers using the new system will need to pay a standard fee of 0.50 euros per user per year, with the first million installs offered for free. Apps distributed through alternative app stores will have no commission. Apps distributed through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will pay a reduced 17 percent commission, or 10 percent for those in the small business program or for user subscriptions older than a year.<br/>
<br/>
Developers can choose not to opt in to the new system and can use the existing system with the same 15/30 percent commission that's available elsewhere in the world. Apple has a fee calculator to help developers determine what they'll pay with the existing setup, with the new setup, with the new setup using alternative app stores, and with the new setup using the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Users are able to set their preferred alternative app store as the default app store on their device if desired. EU users will see an option for this in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
There are a huge number of behind-the-scene changes that are enabling this feature in the EU, with updates to all kinds of system messaging. Users in the EU will, for example, get a pop up warning when an app from an alternative app store contains malware, and there are new screens for verifying the information from an alternative app.<br/>
<br/>
A Screen Time setting will allow parents to decide whether their children's devices are able to install apps from alternative app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="alternative_payment_options_eu">Alternative Payment Options (EU)</h3><br/>
Apple is also allowing apps to use alternative payment options in their apps, and there is no longer a requirement to use in-app purchase. Developers who distribute apps through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and use an alternative payment option will see a three percent discount in their &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; fees.<br/>
<br/>
Developers who distribute through alternative apps and also use an alternative payment option will pay Apple no fees beyond the set 0.50 euro fee per user.<br/>
<br/>
With alternative payments, purchases for digital goods and services can be made directly in an app or a developer can choose to link to their website to have a user make a payment. Apple is requiring developers to use a known, secure payment provider.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="third-party_browser_updates_eu">Third-Party Browser Updates (EU)</h3><br/>
After updating to iOS 17.4, EU users that open Safari will see a pop up that allows them to choose a new default browser option from a list of the most popular browsers on iOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also allowing alternative browser engines, and will not limit browsers like Chrome to the WebKit engine.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="nfc_access_eea">NFC Access (EEA)</h3><br/>
Third-party payment apps and banks have access to the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in iOS 17.4, and can offer contactless payments directly on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; without using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> or the Wallet app in the European Economic Area. Users can set a default contactless payment provider that activates at tap-to-pay terminals or when the Side button on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is pressed twice.<br/>
<br/>
The option for setting a default contactless payment provider is available in the Settings app in the European Economic Area, and this section will also provide details on all apps that have requested and been granted contactless payment access.<br/>
<br/>
EEA users can also change the default Wallet app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="web_apps_eu">Web Apps (EU)</h3><br/>
Apple initially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/ios-17-4-nerfs-web-apps-in-the-eu/">restricted the functionality</a> of Progressive Web Apps (PWAs) in the European Union in iOS 17.4, but after a negative response from EU users, Apple walked the decision back.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> Web Apps will no longer be disabled, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-walks-back-decision-to-disable-eu-web-apps/">but WebKit is required</a>. Web apps added to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from a browser that does not support WebKit will not work.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="gaming_app_changes_worldwide">Gaming App Changes (Worldwide)</h2><br/>
Streaming game apps are now allowed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; worldwide, which means services like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW can be offered as standalone &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously only allowed cloud gaming services to be offered via the web, but dedicated apps that let users stream games from servers are now permitted.<br/>
<br/>
Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_emoji">New Emoji</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 introduces new emoji characters that include lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932812" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-New-Emoji-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1077" /><br/>
There are also 18 people and body emojis that now have the option to face in either direction.<br/>
<br/>
These emoji are part of the Unicode 15.1 update that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ios-17-future-emoji/">approved in September 2023</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messaging_with_siri">Messaging with Siri</h2><br/>
The Automatically Send Messages setting under <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> &amp; Search has been renamed "Messaging with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;," and there is an option to set &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to read incoming messages in a specific language like Spanish, French, German, Chinese, and many more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932819" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-messaging-with-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
The change does not update the primary language that &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; listens in and responds to, but is limited to message playback.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="podcasts_and_music">Podcasts and Music</h2><br/>
The "Listen Now" tabs in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and Podcasts apps have been renamed to "Home."<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932818" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-music-home.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Podcasts also uses the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Now Playing bar when collapsed.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="podcast_transcripts">Podcast Transcripts</h2><br/>
The Podcasts app now offers transcripts, similar to how lyrics work in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app. You can follow along with an episode as the text is highlighted in sync with the audio.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932875" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/podcast-app-transcript.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Podcast transcripts are available in English, Spanish, French and German, and the transcripts support searching for a specific word or phrase.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="music_recognition">Music Recognition</h2><br/>
Songs that have been identified with music recognition can be added to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Playlists, the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Library, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_imessage_security_protocol">New iMessage Security Protocol</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Apple is introducing a "state-of-the-art" <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-announces-imessage-security-upgrade/">post-quantum cryptographic protocol</a> for iMessage called PQ3.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" /><br/>
PQ3 protects against "Harvest Now, Decrypt Later" attacks where a malicious actor collects encrypted data with the hope of decrypting it with a quantum computer at some point in the future. Quantum computers are expected to eventually be able to make large-scale calculations that would allow them to decrypt content secured with traditional encryption methods, but that won't be possible with PQ3.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_15_battery_health">iPhone 15 Battery Health</h2><br/>
Apple in iOS 17.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-iphone-15-battery/">changed the Battery interface</a> in the Settings app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models. These devices now show Battery Health with a readout such as "Normal," for a quick at-a-glance way to see the status of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937223" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ios-17-4-battery-health-optimization-iphone-15.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Tapping into the battery health readout shows the battery cycle count, manufacture date, and first use will be listed. This information was previously hidden in the General &gt; About section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also updated the support information for the battery, as the company retested and found that the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; battery can maintain 80 percent of its original capacity <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-raises-iphone-15-advertised-battery-lifespan/">at 1,000 complete charge cycles</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stolen_device_protection">Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
In the Stolen Device Protection section of the Settings app, there is now an option to require a security delay always or only when away from familiar locations.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932874" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple says that this feature is designed to give users the option for increased security in all locations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stopwatch_live_activity">Stopwatch Live Activity</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 adds a Live Activity function for the Stopwatch feature on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. When activated through the Clock app, the Stopwatch now shows up in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> and on the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933379" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stopwatch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
There are controls for pausing the Stopwatch, clearing it, and starting a new lap.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="call_identification">Call Identification</h2><br/>
Call identification in iOS 17.4 displays Apple-verified business names, logos, and department names when the information is available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_for_business">Messages for Business</h2><br/>
With Messages for Business, businesses can provide opt-in information for order statuses, flight notifications, fraud alerts, and other transactions.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_tv_app">Apple TV App</h2><br/>
The "How to Watch" section in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app that shows where a movie or TV show can be viewed now has a list interface rather than a card interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933405" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-how-to-watch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<h2 id="app_store">App Store</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s Purchase feature now shows account-wide purchase history for an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>. It includes TV and movie purchases, music purchases, subscriptions, and app purchases, and it is the same interface that is available when accessing the purchase information for any &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933406" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/app-store-purchase-history-ios-17-4.jpg" alt="" width="5289" height="2975" /><br/>
Apps are still listed, but under a new "Apps" section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="clock_widget">Clock Widget</h2><br/>
There's a new City Digital Clock widget that can be added to the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935544" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ios-17-4-city-digital.jpg" alt="" width="5344" height="3006" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_cash_virtual_card_numbers">Apple Cash Virtual Card Numbers</h2><br/>
In the Wallet app, Apple Cash users can generate a virtual card number to make purchases when &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; is not an option.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935966" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-cash-virtual-card-number.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="real-time_apple_card_apple_savings_and_apple_cash_budget_app_integration">Real-Time Apple Card, Apple Savings, and Apple Cash Budget App Integration</h2><br/>
Apple in iOS 17.4 is giving third-party budget apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/">real-time information</a> on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, Apple Cash, and Apple Savings accounts transactions for up-to-the-minute budget reporting.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hand_gesture_reactions_in_video_apps">Hand Gesture Reactions in Video Apps</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4, there's a new API for developers that can be used to turn off hand gesture reactions in video calls. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> added a gesture reactions that are enabled by default in all video calling apps, leading to awkwardness when moving the hands in certain ways during serious calls.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900390" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/ios-17-facetime-effects.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1070" /><br/>
Online therapists and other professionals have had to add disclaimers about the feature, as there was no way to turn it off on the provider's end. Following iOS 17.4 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, developers can turn off the fireworks, confetti, and other options in their apps. Users were already able to turn off reactions on their iPhones, iPads, and Macs in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hey_siri">Hey Siri</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4, the option to say &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; instead of Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is now available for French, German, and Spanish speakers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="carplay_instrument_cluster_update">CarPlay Instrument Cluster Update</h2><br/>
In supported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> vehicles, there's now an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> option to show information about upcoming turn-by-turn maneuvers in the instrument cluster. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; users will be able to swap the display type between the main and instrument cluster by tapping on the map configuration button located in the upper right of the main Maps screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908367" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/volvo-s60-drivers-apple-maps.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The option is available in vehicles that support the dual-screen &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; experience.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="next-generation_carplay_support">Next-Generation CarPlay Support</h2><br/>
Next-generation &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; is set to launch in the U.S. later in 2024, and code in iOS 17.4 references eight new &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Car Camera:</strong> This app will display the vehicle's rear-view camera feed.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Charge:</strong> For electric vehicles, this app will display battery level, charging status, time remaining until the battery is fully charged, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Climate:</strong> This app will provide access to a vehicle's climate controls within &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, allowing you to adjust the temperature of the A/C or heating system, fan speed, heated seats, heated steering wheel, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Closures:</strong> This app will display if any of the vehicle's doors are opened, and it might also display vehicle warning symbols.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Media:</strong> This app will provide access to FM and AM radio station controls within &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, along with other media options like SiriusXM. It is unclear if SiriusXM will offer satellite connectivity, or remain limited to internet streaming. Users will be able to select from a list of music genres, such as Top 40 and Rock.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Tire Pressure:</strong> This app will display air pressure for each of the vehicle's tires, and provide low pressure, high pressure, and flat tire warnings.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Trips:</strong> This app will provide a variety of driving-related data, including the vehicle's average speed, fuel efficiency or energy efficiency, the total time elapsed and distance traveled on a trip, and more.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
An image in iOS 17.4 beta suggests that &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; will also likely display a "Goodbye" screen after the driver shuts off the vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932992" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Goodbye.jpg" alt="" width="1374" height="484" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="bug_fixes">Bug Fixes</h2><br/>
There are two bug fixes in iOS 17.4. The update addresses an issue that could cause contact images in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> to be blank, and it fixes a Dual SIM problem that could cause the number used in a group message to change from primary to secondary.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="security_updates">Security Updates</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 fix several vulnerabilities, including two that may have been actively exploited to gain access to user devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple patched an RTKit vulnerability and a WebKit vulnerability that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/">says may have been exploited</a>, so it is a good idea to update right away.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For details on all of the features that are included in the &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; update, we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">have a dedicated roundup</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">iOS 17.4 Features: What&#039;s New in iOS 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-features-whats-new-in-ios-17-4.2421157/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;500 Off Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Pro and &#36;100 Off 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m2-macbook-pro-macbook-air-deal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-pro-and-100-off-13-inch-m2-macbook-air.2421155/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 14:04:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m2-macbook-pro-macbook-air-deal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking a pair of MacBook Air and MacBook Pro deals today at B&H Photo and Best Buy, respectively. You'll find the <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1364298/SID/DFF">13-inch M2 MacBook Air for &#36;100 off</a> at B&H Photo and the <a href="https://howl.me/clLUqqn8QaV">13-inch M2 MacBook Pro for up to &#36;500 off</a> (with a membership) at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/macbook-pro-school.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905459" /><em><small>Note: Macrumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the Best Buy deals, you can get the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/clLUqqn8QaV"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> with a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model is at <a href="https://howl.me/clLUq2Iesoa"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> with this extra discount, down from &#36;1,499.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Only My Best Buy Plus/Total members can see these final deal prices.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLUqqn8QaV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;400 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Pro (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLUq2Iesoa"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;500 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Both of these represent all-time low prices on the 2022 MacBook Pro, which has the Touch Bar. Even without the exclusive My Best Buy Plus/Total discounts these remain solid deals if not quite record low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-m2-13-inch.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939833" /><br/>
Secondly, B&H Photo has the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1364298/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, which is down from &#36;999.00. Apple dropped the price of this model down to &#36;999.00 this week with the introduction of the new M3 MacBook Airs, and this is the first notable discount on that price that we've tracked.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1364298/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m2-macbook-pro-macbook-air-deal/">Get Up to &#36;500 Off Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Pro and &#36;100 Off 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-pro-and-100-off-13-inch-m2-macbook-air.2421155/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Lets Budget Apps Read Real-Time Apple Card Transaction Info</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-lets-budget-apps-read-real-time-apple-card-transaction-info.2421142/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:25:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After updating to iOS 17.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> users who want to track their real-time spending with budgeting apps will have more opportunities to do so. iOS 17.4 opens up real-time &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions to third-party apps budgeting apps beyond Mint for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/apple-card-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="1144" height="644" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-735877" /><br/>
Mint added support for the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; back in 2022, but Apple did not provide the same integration to other third-party apps. Intuit folded Mint into Credit Karma at the beginning of the year, though, leaving former users not interested in Credit Karma without a way to track their &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions. &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;, Apple Savings, and Apple Cash accounts can now be added to select budget apps.<br/>
<br/>
With Mint accounts set to shut down on March 23, Apple has expanded &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; support to other third-party apps just in time for people to adopt a new service. So far, budgeting apps <a href="https://www.monarchmoney.com/">Monarch</a>, <a href="https://www.ynab.com">YNAB</a>, and <a href="https://copilot.money">Copilot</a> have added &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; support.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/">iOS 17.4 Lets Budget Apps Read Real-Time Apple Card Transaction Info</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-lets-budget-apps-read-real-time-apple-card-transaction-info.2421142/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Gives Developers More Insight Into App Performance With Over 50 New Analytics Reports</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-new-developer-analytics-reports/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gives-developers-more-insight-into-app-performance-with-over-50-new-analytics-reports.2421140/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:45:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-new-developer-analytics-reports/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside the app ecosystem changes that Apple is making in the European Union to comply with the Digital Markets Act, Apple has introduced new analytics information that's available to developers around the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757303" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-developer-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="572" /><br/>
There are more than 50 reports that are available through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> Connect API, with these reports aimed at giving developers more insight into their app performance. Apple added &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, iOS, and CloudKit data analytics that provide hundreds of new metrics.<br/>
<br/>
Some of the new reports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-developer-analytics-expansion/">were shared</a> back when Apple's app changes were first announced in January.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Store Engagement</strong> - Apple is offering additional insight into the number of users on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; that interact with a developer's app or share it with other people.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Store Commerce</strong> - Developers can get more information on downloads, sales and proceeds, pre-orders, and transactions made with the In-App Purchase system.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Usage</strong> - Apple now provides more information on crashes, active devices, installs, app deletions, and more.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Frameworks Usage</strong> - Developers can get info on their app's interaction with iOS features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, and PhotoPicker.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Performance</strong> - Apple offers insights into how apps perform and how users are interacting with specific app features.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The CloudKit console is also being updated with data about Apple Push Notifications and File Provider.<br/>
<br/>
Apple anonymizes the data that is used in the new report options, and developers can also now grant third-party access to their performance reports.<br/>
<br/>
More information on the new analytics reports will be provided by Apple later today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-new-developer-analytics-reports/">Apple Gives Developers More Insight Into App Performance With Over 50 New Analytics Reports</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gives-developers-more-insight-into-app-performance-with-over-50-new-analytics-reports.2421140/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Make Sure to Update: iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Fix Two Major Security Vulnerabilities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-sure-to-update-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-fix-two-major-security-vulnerabilities.2421136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:02:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> owners may want to update to iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 in the near future, as the updates address two security vulnerabilities that may have been exploited to gain access to user devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
In the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214081">security support document</a> for the updates, Apple says that it "is aware of a report" that RTKit and kernel vulnerabilities may have been exploited by bad actors.<blockquote>Impact: An attacker with arbitrary kernel read and write capability may be able to bypass kernel memory protections. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited.</blockquote>Apple fixed the memory corruption issue with improved validation to patch the security hole.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 also address an Accessibility vulnerability and an issue with Safari Private Browsing that could allow locked tabs to be briefly visible while switching tab groups.<br/>
<br/>
The software updates were released this morning and are available on eligible iPhones and iPads by going to Settings > General > Software Update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/">Make Sure to Update: iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Fix Two Major Security Vulnerabilities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-sure-to-update-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-fix-two-major-security-vulnerabilities.2421136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Tweaks New EU App Store Business Terms After Developer Feedback</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-new-eu-app-store-business-terms-after-developer-feedback.2421134/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 10:41:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of iOS 17.4, Apple's app ecosystem changes in the European Union have gone into effect. Apple today said that it made some last minute updates to its terms of service after receiving feedback from developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
To distribute apps through an app marketplace, with a reduced fee to Apple, or with an alternative payment option, developers have to opt in to new business terms that accept the Core Technology Fee and other new pricing mandates. Apple did not initially provide a way for developers to try the new system and then opt back out if it does not work out, but now there is a one-time term swap option available in some circumstances.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that developers have a one-time option to terminate the new rule addendum [<a href="https://developer.apple.com/contact/request/download/alternate_eu_terms_addendum.pdf">PDF</a>] and swap back to Apple's standard business terms, though there is a catch. Developers who want to change back cannot have distributed an app through an alternative app marketplace or have used an alternative payment processing method.<blockquote>You may terminate this Addendum without also terminating the Developer Agreement one time, provided You have never had an Application be an Alternative App Marketplace (EU), be distributed through an Alternative App Marketplace (EU), use Linking Out, or use Alternative Payment Processing.</blockquote>Opt-out will be available for developers who decided to continue to distribute their apps through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> while adopting the Core Technology Fee and reduced commission option. The CTF is .50 euros per download after 1 million downloads, and the commission is 13 percent for small business owners and 20 percent for installs over 1 million (this includes the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; payment processing fee).<br/>
<br/>
Developers who want to create an alternative app marketplace <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/alternative-app-marketplace-in-the-eu/">can now do so</a> without a stand-by letter of credit for â‚¬1,000,000, which would restrict marketplace creation to large companies. Developers who have been a member of good standing in the Apple Developer Program for two continuous years or more and have an app that had more than one million first annual installs in iOS in the EU in the prior calendar year can create a marketplace without the proof of funds.<br/>
<br/>
There is also no longer a corporate entity requirement when signing up for new terms, so a large business can sign up at the developer account level rather than having to have each controlling membership approve the swap to the updated business terms.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.4 released, we should soon be seeing the first alternative app marketplaces launch. Developers are now free to adopt the new business terms, distribute their apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and use third-party payments in their apps. Note that all of these changes are limited to developers and users in the European Union.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/">Apple Tweaks New EU App Store Business Terms After Developer Feedback</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-new-eu-app-store-business-terms-after-developer-feedback.2421134/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 With EU App Changes, New Emoji, Podcast Transcripts and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-with-eu-app-changes-new-emoji-podcast-transcripts-and-more.2421124/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 10:01:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, the fourth major updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system that came out in September 2023. The software updates come over a month after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/">released iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4D8Dy0kP-Cg" title="iOS 17.4 Out Now: New Features!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update. <br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.4, Apple introduces sweeping changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps function in the European Union, paving the way for alternative app marketplaces on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, alternative payment systems on iOS and iPadOS, third-party browser engine support, and NFC access for banks and third-party payment providers. These features are limited to the EU, and the changes are not applicable in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did, however, make worldwide changes to gaming apps. Apple is now allowing cloud gaming apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW. Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to these App Store-related updates, iOS 17.4 adds new emoji characters, <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apple-introduces-transcripts-for-apple-podcasts/">transcripts for podcasts</a> in the Podcasts app, Stopwatch Live Activities, improvements to battery health reporting on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, and more. Apple's full release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote><strong>Emoji</strong><br/>
- New mushroom, phoenix, lime, broken chain, and shaking heads emoji are now available in the emoji keyboard<br/>
- 18 people and body emoji add the option to face them in either direction<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Apple Podcasts</strong><br/>
- Transcripts let you follow an episode with text that highlights in sync with the audio in English, Spanish, French and German<br/>
- Episode text can be read in full, searched for a word or phrase, tapped to play from a specific point and used with accessibility features such as Text Size, Increase Contrast, and VoiceOver<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update includes the following enhancements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Music recognition lets you add songs you have identified to your Apple Music Playlists and Library, as well as Apple Music Classical<br/>
- Siri has a new option to announce messages you receive in any supported language<br/>
- Stolen Device Protection supports the option for increased security in all locations<br/>
- Battery Health in Settings shows battery cycle count, manufacture date, and first use on iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models<br/>
- Call Identification displays Apple-verified business name, logo, and department name when available<br/>
- Business updates in Messages for Business provide trusted information for order status, flight notifications, fraud alerts or other transactions you opt into<br/>
- Apple Cash virtual card numbers enable you to pay with Apple Cash at merchants that don't yet accept Apple Pay by typing in your number from Wallet or using Safari AutoFill<br/>
- Fixes an issue where contact pictures are blank in Find My<br/>
- Fixes an issue for Dual SIM users where the phone number changes from primary to secondary and is visible to a group they have messaged<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222">https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</a></blockquote><br/>
Note that Apple's release notes in the United States do not highlight the changes in the European Union, but the update does now allow for alternative app marketplaces to be installed on iPhones in Europe. If you're in Europe and affected by the changes, you will see different release notes that include details on Apple's app ecosystem updates. <blockquote><strong>Apps in the EU</strong><br/>
Residents of the European Union will now have new options to:<br/>
<br/>
- Install apps from alternative app marketplaces<br/>
- Install web browser with alternative browser engines<br/>
- Manage your default web browser the first time you open Safari<br/>
- Use alternative payment options for apps in the App Store with the external purchases badge<br/>
- Some options require developer support</blockquote>More information on what's new in iOS 17.4 can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-beta-features/">our iOS 17.4 features guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/">Apple Releases iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 With EU App Changes, New Emoji, Podcast Transcripts and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-with-eu-app-changes-new-emoji-podcast-transcripts-and-more.2421124/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>13-Inch vs. 15-Inch MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/13-inch-vs-15-inch-macbook-air-buyers-guide.2391905/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 08:47:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1709668020/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> continues to be available in 13- and 15-inch sizes after Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">latest refresh</a> that added the M3 chip. The 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; offers almost all of the same hardware with a significantly larger display, yet there are still some key differences that are worth considering when purchasing one of the machines.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/MacBook-Air-Multiple-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-851176" /><br/>
The 13- and 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are almost exactly the same in terms of feature set and design, both sporting high-resolution Liquid Retina displays, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, two Thunderbolt ports, and much more. Both machines can be configured with the exact same amounts of memory and storage, and they are both available in the same color options. This simplifies purchasing decisions to just a few important aspects.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="key_differences">Key Differences</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>13.6-inch Liquid Retina display</td><br/>
 <td>15.3-inch Liquid Retina display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> or M3 chip</td><br/>
 <td>M3 chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts with 8-Core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>10-Core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Four-speaker sound system</td><br/>
 <td>Six-speaker sound system with force-cancelling woofers</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Integrated 52.6-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery</td><br/>
 <td>Integrated 66.5-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>30W USB-C Power Adapter (with 8-core GPU chip) or 35W Dual Port Compact Power Adapter</td><br/>
 <td>35W Dual Port Compact Power Adapter</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;999</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;1,299</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
It is important to note that while the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has a battery that is 13.9-watt-hours larger than the 13-inch model, both machines have the same 18-hour battery life. This is likely due to the increased power consumption of the larger display.<br/>
<br/>
If you plan to heavily use your laptop's built-in speakers, the 15-inch model offers a worthwhile reason to get the larger model, offering two extra speakers inside the larger chassis. The smaller &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; also misses out on the force-canceling woofers that are present in the 15-inch model, meaning that its audio isn't quite as good.<br/>
<br/>
Since size is the main difference between the two &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, prospective customers may wish to drill into the specific dimensions and weight of the machines. The 15-inch model adds 0.6 pounds (0.27 kg) and may be more difficult to get into a bag or backpack due to its larger footprint.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="dimensions">Dimensions</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>0.44 inch (1.13 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>0.45 inch (1.15 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>11.97 inches (30.41 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>13.40 inches (34.04 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Depth</th><br/>
 <td>8.46 inches (21.5 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>9.35 inches (23.76 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>2.7 pounds (1.24 kg)</td><br/>
 <td>3.3 pounds (1.51 kg)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
While the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with the M3 chip starts at &#36;1,099, making it &#36;200 cheaper than the 15-inch model, if you choose the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with a 10-core GPU, this price difference shrinks to &#36;100. If you add the 35W Dual Port Compact Power Adapter, the difference shrinks to just &#36;80. With this in mind, most users considering an M3 model should opt for the 15-inch model since it provides much more screen real-estate and better speakers.<br/>
<br/>
You should only buy the M3 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; if you specifically want a lighter, more portable device and are concerned about having to carry a device as large as the 15-inch model around. Likewise, the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is a better buy if you are price-conscious and don't need anything more than an 8-core GPU and the 30W USB-C Power Adapter. The &#36;1,099 13-inch model is still quite a bit more affordable than the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, with virtually no compromises in terms of features. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer's Guide: All Differences Compared</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is also available with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip for &#36;999. This is the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; Apple introduced in mid-2022 and it now represents an entry-level model. If affordability is your main concern, this 13-inch model is the best choice, coming in at &#36;300 less than the 15-inch M3 model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/">13-Inch vs. 15-Inch MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/13-inch-vs-15-inch-macbook-air-buyers-guide.2391905/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New MacBook Air Launching on Friday With These 5 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m3-macbook-air-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-launching-on-friday-with-these-5-new-features.2421117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 08:26:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m3-macbook-air-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">updated the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air</a> with several new features and changes. The laptops can be ordered now, with in-store availability and deliveries to customers set to begin on Friday, March 8.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><br/>
Below, we outline key new features added to the MacBook Air, including the M3 chip, Wi-Fi 6E, expanded external display support, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 Chip</h2><br/>
Both the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air are now available with Apple's latest M3 chip for faster performance and improved power efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
As expected, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/first-benchmark-result-macbook-air-m3/">early benchmark result</a> has revealed that the M3 chip is up to 20% faster than the M2 chip in the previous MacBook Air models in terms of CPU performance. These results are consistent with the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
With the M3 chip, the MacBook Air has also gained hardware-accelerated ray tracing for improved graphics rendering in games, along with AV1 video decoding.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Two External Displays</h2><br/>
While previous MacBook Air models with Apple silicon officially support only one external display, the new models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-two-displays-lid-closed/">support two external displays</a>. However, a second display can only be used when the MacBook Air's lid is closed.<br/>
<br/>
When the lid is open, the new models support one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz. When the lid is closed, a second display with up to 5K resolution at 60Hz can be connected, according to Apple's tech specs.<br/>
<br/>
Even more displays can be connected to the MacBook Air with the use of DisplayLink adapters. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wi-Fi 6E</h2><br/>
The new MacBook Airs support Wi-Fi 6E for "up to twice as fast" wireless download speeds compared to the previous models with Wi-Fi 6, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 6E extends the capabilities of Wi-Fi 6 to the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference with a compatible device and router. The entire current-generation Mac lineup now supports Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Microphone Upgrades</h2><br/>
Apple says the microphones in the new MacBook Air models offer "enhanced voice clarity in audio and video calls" compared to the previous models. The microphones also gained support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/block-background-noise-facetime-mac/">"Voice Isolation" and "Wide Spectrum" modes</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Fingerprint Seal for Midnight Color</h2><br/>
Just <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">like the Space Black MacBook Pro</a>, the Midnight MacBook Air now features an "anodization seal to reduce fingerprints," according to Apple.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m3-macbook-air-features/">New MacBook Air Launching on Friday With These 5 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-launching-on-friday-with-these-5-new-features.2421117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Discover Samsung Spring Sale Has Massive &#36;700 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-discover-samsung-spring-sale-has-massive-700-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-and-more.2421110/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:47:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has kicked off a <a href="https://howl.me/clLNJuxoiqi">Discover Samsung Spring Sale</a>, which is set to run through the end of the week. During this event you'll find discounts on <a href="https://howl.me/clLNSBlHkaL">4K and 5K Samsung monitors</a>, including the popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and Smart Monitor M8, as well as storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/samsung-viewfinity-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939071" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for <a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. At &#36;700 off this a new all-time low price on the 2023 display, which has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also being discounted during this sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clLNM6CvUKB"><strong>&#36;349.99</strong></a> in Sunset Pink, down from &#36;699.99. Other colors, like Warm White, are priced at <a href="https://howl.me/clLNPiqsTe3"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>. This is a 4K smart monitor with a design that looks similar to the new iMac line, and it's at another new record low price during Samsung's Spring Sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/samsung-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905732" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLNM6CvUKB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;350 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up a collection of other discounts you can find during the new Discover Samsung Spring Sale below. Shoppers should note that some of these deals are timed and will only last today, while others are slated to stick around all week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2hIAozaO">27-inch Odyssey HDR10 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gYG78Q9">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;549.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gbHK6cQ">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNROoH7so">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2e77z0lE">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs/Audio</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN0R87SoM">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNZ1m9EMM">55-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNX3ZnLNR">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNXcrr7pC">The Frame</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000 on select models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNYXDQ23m">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNWfhuoAS">85-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;2,399.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Smartphones</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN3lYPzGg">Galaxy S24+</a> - Save up to &#36;1,050 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN39d8ucx">Galaxy S24 Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;1,220 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN4VDZt8i">Galaxy Z Fold5</a> - Save up to &#36;950 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN5FExalV">Galaxy Z Flip5</a> - Save up to &#36;660 with participating carriers</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/">New Discover Samsung Spring Sale Has Massive &#36;700 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-discover-samsung-spring-sale-has-massive-700-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-and-more.2421110/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Apple Pencil Rumored to Launch This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-pencil-rumored-to-launch-this-month.2421108/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 06:51:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A refreshed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> model will be announced this month, according to a rumor shared on Chinese social media.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-pencil.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939786" /><br/>
The rumor comes from Weibo user "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/setsuna-digital/">Instant Digital</a>," who notes that after over five years without an update, Apple finally plans to refresh the second-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; this month. This corroborates <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/03/no-apple-event-for-new-ipads-macs-gurman/">recent claim</a> that new Apple Pencils are on the way "in the next several weeks."<br/>
<br/>
There is a limited amount of information about what an updated â€Œ&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; might featureâ€Œ, but there have been rumors about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/apple-pencil-3-could-feature-magnetic-tips/">magnetically interchangeable tips</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/07/17/apple-pencil-color-sensor-patent/">color sampling capabilities</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/03/new-apple-pencil-allegedly-leaks/">shorter design with a glossy finish</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models with OLED displays are widely rumored to launch this month, so it would make sense for a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; to arrive alongside them. The company is also expected to introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">redesigned Magic Keyboard accessory</a>, so it seems that both of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>'s accessories may be refreshed simultaneously. <br/>
<br/>
Instant Digital has a mixed track record in terms of revealing accurate information about Apple's plans, but its claims are worth paying attention to. The source was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">first to report</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>'s Yellow spring refresh, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/future-iphone-could-capture-spatial-photos-videos/">Spatial Video</a> capture on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/04/apple-watch-series-9-basically-unchanged/">minor hardware update</a>, as well as being the only source of the only rumor claiming that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus would feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted back glass</a>. However, they also made claims about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/25/ios-17-lock-screen-apple-music-rumors/">several iOS 17 features</a> and the release of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/">new iPad Air in October 2023</a> that did not pan out.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/">New Apple Pencil Rumored to Launch This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-pencil-rumored-to-launch-this-month.2421108/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Drops to New All-Time Low Price of &#36;663.99 [Update: Expired]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-watch-ultra-2-new-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-drops-to-new-all-time-low-price-of-663-99-update-expired.2421106/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 06:44:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-watch-ultra-2-new-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking a new record low price on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 today at Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;663.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. Only the Indigo Alpine Loop in size medium is available at this best-ever price on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-watch-ultra-2-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939712" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon provides an estimated delivery date of Friday for free delivery, although Prime members should get it by Thursday. This deal beats the previous all-time low price by nearly &#36;60, and also beats many of the deal prices we've seen recently on the first generation Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;135 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;663.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are a few other Apple Watch deals going on right now for anyone interested in cheaper models. You can get the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> and the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
As of January, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">sales ban was reenacted</a> in the United States on any Apple Watch model sold by Apple that has blood oxygen sensing. While Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models purchased directly from Apple currently come with blood oxygen sensing disabled, retailers like Amazon are able to continue selling through their existing stocks that include the feature.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This deal has now expired.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-watch-ultra-2-new-low/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Drops to New All-Time Low Price of &#36;663.99 [Update: Expired]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-drops-to-new-all-time-low-price-of-663-99-update-expired.2421106/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First Benchmark Result Surfaces for MacBook Air With M3 Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/first-benchmark-result-macbook-air-m3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-benchmark-result-surfaces-for-macbook-air-with-m3-chip.2421093/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 01:53:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/first-benchmark-result-macbook-air-m3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Geekbench</category>
		<category>Benchmarks</category>
		<category>MySmartPrice</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An early benchmark result for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">new MacBook Air</a> has surfaced, providing a closer look at the M3 chip's performance in Apple's latest laptops.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/v6/cpu/5172580">Geekbench 5 result</a> spotted by <em><a href="https://www.mysmartprice.com/gear/apple-macbook-air-with-m3-chip-spotted-on-geekbench-heres-how-it-compares-with-macbook-air-m2/">MySmartPrice</a></em>, the MacBook Air with the M3 chip and 16GB of unified memory achieved a single-core score of 3,157 and a multi-core score of 12,020. The results have a "Mac15,13" identifier, which indicates they are for a 15-inch MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
For context, the previous MacBook Air with the M2 chip and 16GB of unified memory achieved a single-core score of 2,610 and a multi-core score of 10,120. The M3 chip in the new MacBook Air therefore scored approximately 20% more in single-core and 18% more in multi-core compared to the M2 chip in the earlier model, and is on par with the M3 chip in the 14-inch MacBook Pro as far as straight CPU benchmarks go.<br/>
<br/>
Featuring an 8-core CPU, up to a 10-core GPU, and support for up to 24GB of unified memory, the new MacBook Air is up to 60 percent faster than the model with M1 and up to 13x faster than the fastest Intel-based MacBook Air, according to Apple. <br/>
<br/>
Apple began accepting pre-orders for the new MacBook Air on Monday, March 4, and the first deliveries to customers and in-store availability will begin on Friday, March 8. Pricing for the new MacBook Air starts at &#36;1,099 in the United States, while the previous-generation 13-inch MacBook Air with the M2 chip remains available for &#36;999.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/geekbench/">Geekbench</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/benchmarks/">Benchmarks</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mysmartprice-com/">MySmartPrice</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/first-benchmark-result-macbook-air-m3/">First Benchmark Result Surfaces for MacBook Air With M3 Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-benchmark-result-surfaces-for-macbook-air-with-m3-chip.2421093/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sales in China Declined 24% in First Six Weeks of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/china-iphone-sales-slump-early-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-in-china-declined-24-in-first-six-weeks-of-2024.2421087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:53:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/china-iphone-sales-slump-early-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Counterpoint</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China saw a significant decline in the first six weeks of this year that saw it lose the title of China's best-selling smartphone maker to a local vendor.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/China-Weekly-Smartphone-Unit-Sales-Share-Growth-in-First-6-Weeks-of-Year-2024-vs-2023.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1157" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939686" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales dropped by 24 percent, pushing Apple down to fourth among smartphone makers in the country, according to <a href="https://www.counterpointresearch.com/insights/china-smartphone-sales-first-6-weeks-2024-double-digit-declines-for-apple-oppo-vivo/">Counterpoint Research</a>. Vivo took the top spot, thanks to its success in the budget segment of the market.<br/>
<br/>
That's despite both companies selling fewer phones, owing to a 7 percent drop in the overall Chinese market, which is suffering the effects of a nationwide deflation. <br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, Huawei saw its market share grow to 16.5 percent from 9.4 percent, thanks to the popularity of its home-grown Mate 60 series. Apple recorded a 15.7 percent market share, falling from 19 percent a year ago, according to Counterpoint's data. Overall growth is likely to remain in the red during Q1 2024 on muted spending and a few new product launches, said the analysts.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; struggled during the first few weeks of the year for several reasons, according to Counterpoint. "Primarily, it faced stiff competition at the high end from a resurgent Huawei while getting squeezed in the middle on aggressive pricing from the likes of OPPO, vivo and Xiaomi," said Senior Analyst Mengmeng Zhang. <br/>
<br/>
"Although the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> is a great device, it has no significant upgrades from the previous version, so consumers feel fine holding on to the older-generation iPhones for now," he added.<br/>
<br/>
Apple resellers in China have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/">increasingly dependent on discounts</a> to shift &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; stock in a market that has entered a general malaise. The discounts followed Apple's own <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">rare price reductions</a> on its website ahead of the Lunar New Year holiday in February. <br/>
<br/>
Apple sales in China dropped 13 percent to &#36;20.8 billion in the quarter ended December, falling short of the &#36;23.5 billion predicted by analysts, and forecasts for a quick improvement in 2024 do not look particularly optimistic.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/counterpoint/">Counterpoint</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/china-iphone-sales-slump-early-2024/">iPhone Sales in China Declined 24% in First Six Weeks of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-in-china-declined-24-in-first-six-weeks-of-2024.2421087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT for iPhone and iPad Can Now Read Responses Out Loud</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/chatgpt-read-aloud-feature-iphone-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-for-iphone-and-ipad-can-now-read-responses-out-loud.2421086/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:18:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/chatgpt-read-aloud-feature-iphone-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI has announced a new Read Aloud feature for its official ChatGPT app for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> that allows users to have the chat bot read responses out loud in one of five voice options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/chatgpt-for-iphone-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896306" /><br/>
In the app, tap and hold the chat bot's text response, and then tap Read Aloud. You can also play, pause, or rewind the readout. The feature, which is also available on the web version of ChatGPT, adds another layer of voice-based interaction, and builds on the existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/chatgpt-app-voice-chat-free-to-all/">Voice Chat feature</a>, which gives users the option of speaking conversationally with the chat bot instead of typing.<br/>
<br/>
Read Aloud can speak 37 languages and can auto-detect the language of the text that it is reading. OpenAI says the feature should enhance accessibility for users with visual impairments or reading difficulties, such as dyslexia. It also hopes Read Aloud improves engagement by personalizing the interaction, while also supporting language learning.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">ChatGPT can now read responses to you.<br><br>On iOS or Android, tap and hold the message and then tap â€œRead Aloudâ€. Weâ€™ve also started rolling on web - click the &quot;Read Aloud&quot; button below the message. <a href="https://t.co/KevIkgAFbG">pic.twitter.com/KevIkgAFbG</a></p>&mdash; OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1764712432939995549?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 4, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
As most people will know by now, ChatGPT is an AI-based chatbot that uses generative artificial intelligence to answer questions and provide advice on all manner of subjects. History is synced across devices, so you can see your ChatGPT interactions both on the web and on iOS devices, and it integrates the Whisper speech recognition system.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/chatgpt-read-aloud-feature-iphone-app/">ChatGPT for iPhone and iPad Can Now Read Responses Out Loud</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-for-iphone-and-ipad-can-now-read-responses-out-loud.2421086/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Lauds &#36;2 Billion EU Fine, Says Apple Has &#039;Muzzled&#039; Streaming Music Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services.2421067/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:27:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/eu-fines-apple-2-billion/">was today fined</a> â‚¬1.8 billion (&#36;1.95 billion) for anti-competitive conduct against rival streaming music services in the European Union, and following the ruling, Spotify has <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2024-03-04/the-european-commission-confirms-apples-anti-competitive-behavior-is-illegal-and-harms-consumers/">praised the European Commission</a> for its decision.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810756" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/General-Spotify-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" /><br/>
For context, the European Commission's investigation into Apple's practices started <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/03/13/spotify-files-complaint-vs-apple-in-europe/">due to a 2019 complaint</a> from Spotify over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> policies. Spotify has long railed against Apple's 30 percent fee, and has complained that it is unfairly disadvantaged compared to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In a blog post, Spotify says that the European Commission has sent a clear message that "Apple's behavior limiting communications to consumers is unlawful."<br/>
<blockquote>Apple's rules muzzled Spotify and other music streaming services from sharing with our users directly in our app about various benefits--denying us the ability to communicate with them about how to upgrade and the price of subscriptions, promotions, discounts, or numerous other perks. Of course, Apple Music, a competitor to these apps, is not barred from the same behaviour. By requiring Apple to stop its illegal conduct in the EU, the EC is putting consumers first. It is a basic concept of free markets--customers should know what options they have, and customers, not Apple, should decide what to buy, and where, when and how.</blockquote><br/>
It is worth noting that the scope of the investigation in Europe has changed several times. While Spotify complained over Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; fees and the requirement to use in-app purchase, the European Commission was unable to target Apple for those actions. Instead, the investigation ended up pertaining to Apple's anti-steering rules, and the rule that keeps Spotify from informing customers about lower prices on the web within the Spotify app.<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission decided that Apple's restrictions preventing developers from letting iOS users know about alternative and cheaper music subscription services available outside the app is "illegal under EU antitrust rules." The EC claims that Apple caused customers to "pay significantly higher prices for music streaming subscriptions."<br/>
<br/>
Spotify in its blog post further says that Apple has "routinely defied laws and court decisions in other markets," and that it is waiting for the next steps that will "clearly and conclusively address Apple's long-standing unfair practices." Spotify claims that it plans to continue to push against Apple until it is able to secure a "truly fair digital marketplace everywhere."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been ordered to "remove the anti-steering provisions" and keep from repeating the infringement or adopting similar practices in the future. Apple plans to appeal the decision and has claimed that the EC's view is misguided and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/22/apple-spotify-limitless-access-no-fees/">has been heavily influenced</a> by Spotify's complaints.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify will soon be able to release an app outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; with support for alternative app marketplaces coming to the EU in iOS 17.4, but the streaming music company has complained that Apple's plans <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/spotify-epic-games-apple-dma-complaint/">do not comply</a> with the DMA and that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/spotify-on-apple-eu-app-changes/">changes coming in Europe</a> are a "complete and total farce."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services/">Spotify Lauds &#36;2 Billion EU Fine, Says Apple Has &#039;Muzzled&#039; Streaming Music Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services.2421067/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Vision Pro Personas and EyeSight Improving With visionOS 1.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-eyesight-personas-improvement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-personas-and-eyesight-improving-with-visionos-1-1.2421065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:33:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-eyesight-personas-improvement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon release the first major software update for the Vision Pro, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-release-candidate/">new version of visionOS</a> will bring improvements not only to Personas, but also to the EyeSight feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
Personas and EyeSight are Vision Pro additions that many people have poked fun at since the headset's release. Personas are a digital representation of the user that's shown in video calls, while EyeSight uses an external display to show the Vision Pro wearer's eyes if there are other people in the room. Personas and EyeSight are aimed at making the Vision Pro less of an isolating experience, but neither has been particularly well-received.<br/>
<br/>
As <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/testing-personas-visionos-1-1/">we've previously shared</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1 beta makes Personas look more realistic, and Apple's release notes provided with the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 release candidate offer more insight. Specific improvements have been made to hair and makeup appearance and neck and mouth representation, and these tweaks make a big difference.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Vision Pro Persona FIXED in visionOS 1.1?" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xEixxDkYXlo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The update also apparently improves rendering of the eyes for EyeSight, which isn't something that was previously noticed during the beta testing period. EyeSight draws on the Persona feature to capture a person's eyes to show on the external display. Presumably the EyeSight feature now looks somewhat better on the Vision Pro headset, but that it's gone so under the radar suggests Apple still has more work to do.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features in the update include improvements for the virtual keyboard and the Mac virtual display.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 will be officially released as soon as this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-eyesight-personas-improvement/">Vision Pro Personas and EyeSight Improving With visionOS 1.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-personas-and-eyesight-improving-with-visionos-1-1.2421065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Siri Will Learn Your Music Preferences With HomePod Software 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/homepod-siri-music-preferences-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-will-learn-your-music-preferences-with-homepod-software-17-4.2421061/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:32:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/homepod-siri-music-preferences-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside iOS 17.4, iPadOS 17.4, and tvOS 17.4, Apple plans to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 17.4 software update that adds a small but meaningful change to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/homepod-blue-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895477" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to learn what a user's preferred media service is, which means that there won't be a need to include an app name when asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to play content or go through the process to set a default third-party app.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; users have been able to play songs, podcasts, audiobooks, and other media using supported third-party apps through a &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; request for quite some time now, but this needed to be set up in the Settings section of the Home app. The option was fairly hidden, so some &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; users might have forgotten the feature was even available. From Apple's release notes:<blockquote>This update enables Siri to learn your preferred media service, so you no longer need to include the name of the media app in your request.</blockquote>With &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.4, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will learn preferences and use those preferences to select apps. If you have YouTube Music, for example, you won't need to say "Play [song name] on YouTube Music" to bypass <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, nor will you need to set YouTube Music as your default music service in the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; already works this way on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and asks users for their preferred app when playing content for the first time. As &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has been updated to set a preference automatically, Apple has removed the Home app option that let users select a default media service.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party apps that work directly with the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; include YouTube Music, Deezer, Pandora, TuneIn, and iHeartRadio. Streaming music services need to support &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; for the feature to work, and not all do. Note that popular music service Spotify can play content through a &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; request on &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, but it uses the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to do so.<br/>
<br/>
Along with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; support for a preferred music service, the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.4 update also includes performance and stability improvements. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.4 software will see a release as soon as this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/homepod-siri-music-preferences-17-4/">Siri Will Learn Your Music Preferences With HomePod Software 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-will-learn-your-music-preferences-with-homepod-software-17-4.2421061/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has First Discounts on Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Air Exclusively for Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-first-discounts-on-apples-m3-macbook-air-exclusively-for-members.2421060/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:01:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">announced</a> the newest models of the MacBook Air, which include the M3 chip and come in 13-inch and 15-inch sizes. Just a few hours later, Best Buy now has the <a href="https://howl.me/clLuBIw32S9">first notable discounts</a> on these computers <strong>exclusively for My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total members</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
If you're a Plus/Total member, you can get &#36;50 off both the 13-inch and 15-inch M3 MacBook Air.  My Best Buy Plus and My Best Buy Total begins at &#36;49.99/year, so these new MacBook Air discounts will only make sense for people who already have paid for the service.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Discounts available only to My Best Buy Plus/Total members.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLur9sCFjw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00 </div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLutG0IgBi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,249.00 </div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With these discounts, the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air is available from &#36;1,049.00 and the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air is available from &#36;1,249.00. You'll find every new MacBook Air model on sale with Best Buy's exclusive &#36;50 discounts, including those with increased RAM.<br/>
<br/>
If you're willing to invest in a previous generation model, you can also find the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/best-buy-13-inch-m1-macbook-air/">13-inch M1 MacBook Air on sale at Best Buy</a>. We covered this deal earlier today, and it's a good option for anyone willing to sacrifice the internal upgrades of the M3 chip for a much lower price tag of &#36;749.99.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/">Best Buy Has First Discounts on Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Air Exclusively for Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-first-discounts-on-apples-m3-macbook-air-exclusively-for-members.2421060/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ups Mac Trade-In Prices Following M3 MacBook Air Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ups-mac-trade-in-prices-following-m3-macbook-air-launch.2421047/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:24:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Trade-In</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today increased the trade-in values for some Macs, with the update coming alongside the launch of new 13-inch and 15-inch M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/mac-studio-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-841118" /><br/>
Mac users who opt to trade in an old machine can get between &#36;120 and &#36;1315, with the values increased from the prior &#36;115 to &#36;1070 range. Most of the trade-in values have seen only minor increases or have stayed the same, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> has driven values up.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is now offering up to &#36;1315 when trading in a &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;, with the prior maximum at &#36;1070.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>MacBook Pro</strong> - Up to &#36;1000 (Up from &#36;990)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>MacBook Air</strong> - Up to &#36;550 (No change)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>MacBook</strong> - Up to &#36;160 (Up from &#36;150)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iMac</strong> - Up to &#36;440 (No change)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iMac Pro</strong> - Up to &#36;500 (No change)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac mini</strong> - Up to &#36;400 (Down from &#36;410)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac Studio</strong> - Up to &#36;1315 (Up from &#36;1070)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac Pro</strong> - Up to &#36;800 (Down from &#36;900)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Trade-in values vary based on the condition, year, and configuration of the Mac that's being traded in. Macs can be traded in toward the purchase of a new device or the value can be added toward an Apple Gift Card.<br/>
<br/>
Values for trading in other devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch have not changed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-trade-in/">Apple Trade-In</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/">Apple Ups Mac Trade-In Prices Following M3 MacBook Air Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ups-mac-trade-in-prices-following-m3-macbook-air-launch.2421047/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
