<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:03:04 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Turn a Live Photo into a Boomerang</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-iphone-live-photo-into-boomerang/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/turn-a-live-photo-into-a-boomerang.2426676/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 08:36:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-iphone-live-photo-into-boomerang&#038;post_date=1715970980/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Most <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users are familiar with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-photos/">Live Photos</a>, which capture 1.5 seconds of video before and after you take a picture, with the aim of adding a little bit of life and movement to still images. What some users might not know is that you can also make a Live Photo bounce back and forth like a boomerang.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/icloud-photos.jpg" alt="" width="836" height="470" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897381" /><br/>
If you're familiar with Instagram, you probably know what a boomerang is. Since introducing &zwnj;Live Photos&zwnj; in 2015, Apple has added some effects to its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app that let you turn them into fun animated clips, and the Bounce effect is basically the same thing as a boomerang. It rewinds the action backward and forward. Here's how to make one of your own on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app and select a Live Photo. (If you look under "Media Types" in the <strong>Albums</strong> section, you'll find all of your &zwnj;Live Photos&zwnj; collated in a folder of the same name.)</li><br/>
<li>With the Live Photo open, tap the <strong>LIVE</strong> icon in the top-left corner of the interface.</li><br/>
<li>From the dropdown menu that appears, choose <strong>Bounce</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/boomerang-live-photos-1.jpg" alt="Live Photos" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951332" /><br/>
<br/>
The effect you choose will be applied immediately, ready for you to share it using the Share icon in the bottom-left corner of the screen. Note that there are two other effects that you can try in &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;: Loop repeats the action in a continuous looping video, and Long Exposure simulates a DSLR-like long exposure effect by blurring motion.<br/>
<br/>
Did you know that it you get a blurry Live Photo image, you can open it up and see if other frames you captured are clearer, and then <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/make-a-new-key-photo-in-live-photos/">select a replacement "key photo" for it</a>. Click the link to learn how it's done.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-iphone-live-photo-into-boomerang/">Turn a Live Photo into a Boomerang</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/turn-a-live-photo-into-a-boomerang.2426676/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Pro Teardown Reveals Internal Design Changes, Including Apple Logo With Copper</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/m4-ipad-pro-teardown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-teardown-reveals-internal-design-changes-including-apple-logo-with-copper.2426670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:41:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/m4-ipad-pro-teardown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube channel Phone Repair Guru has shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HvW-I8EczZ4">teardown video</a> for the new 13-inch iPad Pro with the M4 chip, providing a first look at the device's internal design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/2024-iPad-Pro-Teardown.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="887" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951313" /><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HvW-I8EczZ4">Phone Repair Guru</a> tears down the new iPad Pro</em></div><br/>
During its iPad event last week, Apple said it was able to improve the thermal performance of the new iPad Pro models by nearly 20% compared to the previous-generation models by adding graphite sheets to the chassis and infusing the rear Apple logo with copper. These changes can be seen towards the end of the teardown video.<br/>
<br/>
Apple moved the front camera and Face ID components to the iPad Pro's right-side edge, which is where the new Apple Pencil Pro magnetically attaches to the device. The teardown shows some changes to the array of magnets inside the iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HvW-I8EczZ4?si=80b7dlfOM4x0iold" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Overall, the new iPad Pro has a similar internal design as the previous generation. The video provides a look at the central logic board with the M4 chip, a 10,209 mAh battery with adhesive pull tabs, quad speakers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Repair website iFixit will likely share a more in-depth teardown of the new iPad Pro soon.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad Pro launched in stores and began arriving to customers on Wednesday. In addition to the M4 chip and the relocated front camera, key new features include a brighter OLED display and thinner design compared to the previous generation. For more details about the device, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/everything-announced-may-7-event/">recap of Apple's event</a> from last week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/m4-ipad-pro-teardown/">New iPad Pro Teardown Reveals Internal Design Changes, Including Apple Logo With Copper</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-teardown-reveals-internal-design-changes-including-apple-logo-with-copper.2426670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;50 Off New Beats Solo 4 Wireless Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/best-buy-50-off-beats-solo-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-50-off-new-beats-solo-4-wireless-headphones.2426664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:20:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/best-buy-50-off-beats-solo-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy today has a <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNyGuGY1p">large collection of discounted Beats headphones</a>, headlined by the new Beats Solo 4 Wireless Headphones on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNqmg9VKf"><strong>&#36;149.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;199.99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/beats-solo-4-blue-basketball.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948598" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The Beats Solo 4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-4-launch/">launched</a> in late April and feature upgraded performance and fit, longer battery life, USB-C, 50 hours of playback, and more. All of the Beats deals at Best Buy this weekend do not require a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, and are available to all shoppers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmgNqmg9VKf"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Beats Solo 4 for &#36;149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, you can find discounts on the <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNvQxzfnV">Beats Studio Pro</a> (&#36;170 off), <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNwFyp6Rt">Powerbeats Pro</a> (&#36;40 off), <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNxezeegF">Beats Fit Pro</a> (&#36;40 off), <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNxKU3CXs">Beats Studio Buds</a> (&#36;70 off), and the <a href="https://howl.me/cmgNyp1it56">Beats Solo 3</a> (&#36;85 off).<br/>
<br/>
These sales include a few all-time low prices, with the Beats Studio Pro Wireless Noise Cancelling Over-Ear Headphones getting a particularly steep discount. At &#36;179.99, down from &#36;349.99, this price is a match for the record low price we last tracked over the 2023 holiday season.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/best-buy-50-off-beats-solo-4/">Best Buy Takes &#36;50 Off New Beats Solo 4 Wireless Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-50-off-new-beats-solo-4-wireless-headphones.2426664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing of iOS Browsers With Third-Party Engines Geofenced to EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/third-party-browser-engine-testing-geofenced-to-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-of-ios-browsers-with-third-party-engines-geofenced-to-eu.2426663/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:10:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/third-party-browser-engine-testing-geofenced-to-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Developers who want to develop browsers for iOS with third-party engines can only test their apps on devices physically located in the EU, according to <a href="https://www.theregister.com/2024/05/17/apple_browser_eu/"><em>The Register</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/webkit-vs-chromium-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-837211" /><br/>
This rule introduces a considerable barrier for developers outside the EU, who are now limited to using simulators instead of actual devices for testing their browsers. This restriction complicates the process of developing and supporting browsers with alternative engines, as on-device testing is essential to accurate performance assessment and troubleshooting. Apple's previous policy, which remains in place in other regions around the world, demands the use of WebKit for all iOS and iPadOS browsers, effectively making every browser on these platforms a variant of Safari. <br/>
<br/>
Under the Digital Markets Act (DMA), Apple was designated as a gatekeeper in the European Union, compelling the company to make changes to its policies. With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/">release of iOS 17.4</a>, Apple began allowing the use of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/third-party-default-browsers-eu-ios-17-4/">alternative browser engines within the EU</a>. However, it has now emerged that testing of browsers with third-party engines is strictly geofenced to the EU, potentially hindering the ability of developers around the world to address security issues or implement updates efficiently.<br/>
<br/>
The requirements raise some practical concerns about the feasibility of supporting a separate EU browser. Some developers have pointed out that Apple's extensive list of conditions makes it challenging to comply while also ensuring that the browser remains competitive and secure. <br/>
<br/>
The European Commission has launched an investigation into Apple's compliance with the DMA, focusing on the restrictive nature of its latest changes. The investigation seeks to determine whether Apple's requirements are designed to circumvent the spirit of the DMA by making it difficult for competitors to operate on a level playing field.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/third-party-browser-engine-testing-geofenced-to-eu/">Testing of iOS Browsers With Third-Party Engines Geofenced to EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-of-ios-browsers-with-third-party-engines-geofenced-to-eu.2426663/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED iPad Pro Users Report &#039;Grainy&#039; Displays, But It May Not Be a Defect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/oled-ipad-pro-grainy-display-reports/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pro-users-report-grainy-displays-but-it-may-not-be-a-defect.2426655/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 05:57:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/oled-ipad-pro-grainy-display-reports/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some new M4 iPad Pro models are exhibiting a visible static grain pattern across the OLED display, according to several user reports on Reddit (<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ipad/comments/1csrchw/grainy_display_on_ipad_m4/">1</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ipad/comments/1csvetg/anybody_else_have_extremely_noticeable_grain_on/">2</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ipad/comments/1cto5kp/another_grain_data_point/">3</a>) and the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/grainy-display-on-new-ipad-pro-m4.2426450/"><em>MacRumors</em> Forums</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/oled-m4-ipad-pro-grainy-display-reports.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951250" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image credit: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/grainy-display-on-new-ipad-pro-m4.2426450/page-3">MacRumors user bk215</a></em></div><br/>
Users who see the grain generally report that it is most noticeable in dark environments with the display set at a low to medium brightness while viewing content with gray or muted colors. Some have compared the effect to a photo taken on a high ISO setting that has visual noise.<br/>
<br/>
Whether this is a genuine display defect is hard to say at this point. OLED displays in general can exhibit a visual grain or a "screen-door effect" due to several factors related to the design and manufacturing process.<br/>
<br/>
The individual sub-pixels in OLED displays can vary in size and shape, contributing to an inconsistent, uneven texture or graininess. This is usually more noticeable on larger displays. Variations in the deposition of organic materials can also affect the uniformity of light emission.<br/>
<br/>
OLED displays also control brightness at the pixel level, and power management techniques can lead to minor variations in brightness across the screen. This is sometimes noticeable as a grainy effect, particularly in low-light conditions or when displaying uniform colors.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, there were similar reports of <a href="https://x.com/lafaiel/status/1761014092582777205">grainy screens on Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra smartphones</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Samsung supplies the displays for Apple's 11-inch M4 iPad Pro model, while LG Display supplies the panels for the 13-inch model. According to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/ipad-pro-delay-poor-oled-panel-yields/">March report</a> out of Korea, Samsung faced poor yields of the 11-inch panels, and was unable to meet Apple's order quantity. The shortfall led Apple to transfer some orders for the smaller panel to LG Display. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/grain-effect-oled-ipad-pro.jpeg" alt="" width="1080" height="712" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951255" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image credit: <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ipad/comments/1csvetg/anybody_else_have_extremely_noticeable_grain_on/">Reddit user Vingdoloras</a></em></div><br/>
So far most reports relate to the 11-inch iPad Pro, but there are one or two that reference the 13-inch model, so it is unclear if the potential defect – if it is indeed one – is specific to one OLED panel supplier. The reports appear to be limited to new iPad Pro models with the Standard glass option. Apple's latest iPad Pro models are also available with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/ipad-pro-nano-texture-glass/">matte nano-texture display option</a> for 1TB and 2TB storage configurations at an additional cost of &#36;100. <br/>
<br/>
Note that these reports are unrelated to a known issue we covered earlier in the week that involved <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/oled-ipad-pro-hdr-bug/">blown-out colors when viewing certain HDR content</a> on M4 iPad Pro models. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/oled-ipad-pro-grainy-display-reports/">OLED iPad Pro Users Report &#039;Grainy&#039; Displays, But It May Not Be a Defect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pro-users-report-grainy-displays-but-it-may-not-be-a-defect.2426655/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 16 Pro Max Could Feature Longer Battery Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/iphone-16-pro-max-longer-battery-life/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-16-pro-max-could-feature-longer-battery-life.2426640/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:04:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/iphone-16-pro-max-longer-battery-life/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the iPhone 16 Pro Max will use battery cells with increased energy density, according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, which will offer either longer battery life using the same battery size as that found in existing models, or equivalent battery life using a smaller battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-battery-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1333" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923492" /><br/>
In his <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/%E4%BF%A1%E7%B6%AD%E9%80%9A%E4%BF%A1%E7%82%BA%E6%96%B0%E6%AC%BEiphone-16-pro-max%E7%9A%84%E9%9B%BB%E6%B1%A0%E8%83%BD%E9%87%8F%E5%AF%86%E5%BA%A6%E5%8D%87%E7%B4%9A%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%BB%E8%A6%81%E5%8F%97%E7%9B%8A%E8%80%85-sunway-is-a-major-beneficiary-of-the-new-iphone-16-pro-9df9c5cd3913">latest supply chain survey</a>, Kuo says the energy density (Wh/kg) of the battery cells in the iPhone 16 Pro Max will increase, which "has the benefit of longer battery life with the same battery size or lower battery size with the same battery life."<br/>
<br/>
To avoid overheating the battery, Apple is using a stainless steel battery case for the first time as a thermal solution, according to Kuo.<br/>
<blockquote>Stainless steel is not as effective as aluminum in dissipating heat, but it is more robust and less susceptible to corrosion. The use of a stainless steel battery case also reduces the difficulty of removing the battery, which will help Apple comply with the European Union's requirements for mobile phone batteries' replaceability in the future.</blockquote>Sunway will reportedly be a major supplier of the stainless steel battery cases. If the mass production of this new battery design goes well, Kuo believes the design will be adopted across all iPhone 17 models next year.<br/>
<br/>
A rumor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/iphone-15-could-feature-stacked-battery-technology/">last June</a> suggested that the iPhone 16 Pro models will use stacked batteries, which can result in higher capacity and a longer lifespan, but Kuo makes no mention of the technology in his survey. Apple is expected to release the upcoming iPhone 16 lineup in four months, likely around mid-September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/iphone-16-pro-max-longer-battery-life/">Kuo: iPhone 16 Pro Max Could Feature Longer Battery Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-16-pro-max-could-feature-longer-battery-life.2426640/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches Tap to Pay on iPhone in Japan</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-japan/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-japan.2426638/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 02:47:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-japan/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Japan</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/newsroom/2024/05/apple-introduces-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-japan/">announced</a> Tap to Pay on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in Japan, allowing independent sellers, small merchants, and large retailers in the country to use ‌iPhones‌ as a payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-Tap-to-Pay-Japan-iPhone-iOS-app-digital-wallets.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951227" /><br/>
Tap to Pay first arrived in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/08/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-iphone-feature/">February 2022</a> in the US, and allows iPhones to accept payments via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, contactless credit and debit cards, and other digital wallets‌‌‌.  All transactions are encrypted, and Apple has no information about what is purchased or the person who made the purchase.<br/>
<br/>
No additional hardware or credit card machine is required‌ to use Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The feature uses NFC technology to securely authenticate the contactless payments, plus the feature also supports PIN entry, which includes accessibility options.<br/>
<blockquote>"In Japan, a country where innovation and tradition merge, new payment methods have been introduced all over the country, and at the same time, the transition from cash payment to electronic payment is progressing rapidly on the consumer side," said Jennifer Bailey, vice president of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet. "We are very pleased that through our new partnership with the payment platform, we can provide iPhone touch payment that can seamlessly support contactless payments for millions of businesses. This allows almost all iPhones in the country to be used as payment terminals without additional hardware, reducing the cost of responding to electronic payments by Japanese businesses, making it easy and secure for customers, and protecting their privacy. It will be possible to provide a contactless payment experience."</blockquote>GMO Financial Gate's stera tap app, Recruit's Air Pay Touch app, and Square's Square POS register app will be the first payment platforms in Japan to offer touch payment with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to businesses, according to Apple. Additionally, Adyen will support it in the coming months, and it will also be available at Apple Stores in Japan. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s touch payment supports contactless credit and debit cards from the four major payment networks: American Express, JCB, Mastercard, and Visa.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌‌‌‌ requires ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌‌‌‌ XS or newer models, and works for customers as any normal ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;‌‌‌‌ transaction would. Sellers just need to open up the app, register the sale, and present their ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌‌‌‌ to the buyer, who can then use an appropriate contactless payment method.<br/>
<br/>
Japan becomes the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/tap-to-pay/regions/">ninth region</a> to support Tap to Pay, following similar rollouts in the U.K., Australia, Taiwan, Brazil, Ukraine, France, and the Netherlands last year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/japan/">Japan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-japan/">Apple Launches Tap to Pay on iPhone in Japan</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-japan.2426638/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Gets Multi-Column TweetDeck-Like Web View</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/threads-tweetdeck-web-view/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-gets-multi-column-tweetdeck-like-web-view.2426602/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:06:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/threads-tweetdeck-web-view/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Threads is working on a new web view that features the option to pin customized columns, similar to the TweetDeck feature that used to be available on Twitter. Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg <a href="https://www.threads.net/@zuck/post/C7CQT2rLTeN">shared an image</a> of the new web option, which he said is currently being tested.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/threads-multi-column-view-web.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951162" /><br/>
The screenshot shows several custom columns, including a "For you" and several topic-based columns. Favorite searches, topics/keywords, accounts, saved posts, and notifications can be pinned at the current time, and there is an auto-refresh option to keep columns up to date with the newest posts.<br/>
<br/>
Twitter, now renamed to X, has a similar "X Pro" feature that has the same format as the former TweetDeck option, but it requires an &#36;8/month subscription to access. The Threads version would be free, and it could replicate much of the functionality that Twitter used to offer.<br/>
<br/>
A column-based web view that's customizable could encourage more users to adopt Threads, and it prevents Threads users from being forced into the For you feed when opening Threads on the web. According to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-16/threads-meta-s-x-competitor-is-testing-its-own-version-of-tweetdeck?srnd=infotech">Bloomberg</a></em>, Threads users that have the feature can pin up to 100 feeds to their homepage.<br/>
<br/>
As of now, the multi-column view is being tested with a small number of users.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Threads also <a href="https://www.threads.net/@mosseri/post/C6_8zLPvaFA">added a new option</a> to organize searches by recency, making it easier to find timely and relevant content on the social network.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/threads-tweetdeck-web-view/">Threads Gets Multi-Column TweetDeck-Like Web View</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-gets-multi-column-tweetdeck-like-web-view.2426602/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iMessage Down for Some Users [Update: Service Restored]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/imessage-down-for-some/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imessage-down-for-some-users-update-service-restored.2426596/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:00:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/imessage-down-for-some/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iMessage service that Apple users to send messages to one another appears to be down for some users, and messages are failing to go out or are taking an extra long time to send.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
There are numerous reports about the issue on social networks and a spike of outage reports <a href="https://downdetector.com/status/imessage/">on Down Detector</a>, but <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's System Status page</a> is not yet reporting an outage.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update</b>: Apple's status page says iMessage service has been restored, with the outage lasting approximately 45 minutes from 2:49 p.m. to 3:35 p.m. Pacific Time. Apple says <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, and Apple Messages for Business were also affected.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/imessage-down-for-some/">iMessage Down for Some Users [Update: Service Restored]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imessage-down-for-some-users-update-service-restored.2426596/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Emulators on the App Store: Game Boy, N64, PS1, PSP, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-app-store-emulators-list/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-emulators-on-the-app-store-game-boy-n64-ps1-psp-and-more.2426577/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:45:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-app-store-emulators-list/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Emulator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In April, Apple updated its guidelines to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">allow retro game emulators</a> on the App Store, and several popular emulators have already been released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Delta-Hands-On-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951130" /><br/>
The emulators released so far allow iPhone users to play games released for older consoles from Nintendo, Sony, SEGA, Atari, and others.<br/>
<br/>
A list of some popular emulators available on the App Store so far follows.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Released</h2><br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/delta-game-emulator/id1048524688">Delta</a></h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Delta-Emulator-Pokemon-Gen-3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947545" /><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/delta-game-emulator/id1048524688">Delta</a> is a well-polished emulator for several Nintendo consoles, with beautiful on-screen controller skins, support for a wide range of physical controllers, and more. Developed by Riley Testut, Delta is the successor to the GBA4iOS emulator.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Devices:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone</li></ul><br/>
iPad support is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/delta-game-emulator-coming-to-ipad/">coming soon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Consoles:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>Game Boy (all models)</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo DS</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo Entertainment System (NES)</li><br/>
<li>Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES)</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo 64 (N64)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/retroarch/id6499539433">RetroArch</a></h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/RetroArch-Sonic-iOS-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951191" /><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/retroarch/id6499539433">RetroArch</a> is a frontend that provides all-in-one access to many different emulators for consoles from Atari, Commodore, Nintendo, SEGA, Sony, and others. The app offers <a href="https://retroachievements.org/">RetroAchievements</a>, which are essentially custom challenges added on top of classic games, such as "find and collect a Fire Flower" in Super Mario Bros. for NES.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Devices:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone</li><br/>
<li>iPad</li><br/>
<li>Apple TV</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Consoles:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>Atari 2600</li><br/>
<li>Commodore 64</li><br/>
<li>PlayStation (PS1)</li><br/>
<li>PlayStation Portable (PSP)</li><br/>
<li>SEGA Genesis</li><br/>
<li>SEGA Saturn</li><br/>
<li>Game Boy (all models)</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo DS</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo Entertainment System (NES)</li><br/>
<li>Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES)</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo 64 (N64)</li></ul>RetroArch's full list of supported consoles is in the app's description <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/retroarch/id6499539433">on the App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ppsspp-psp-emulator/id6496972903">PPSSPP</a></h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-Emulator-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951200" /><br/>
PlayStation Portable emulator <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ppsspp-psp-emulator/id6496972903">PPSSPP</a> is built into RetroArch, but it is also available as a standalone app for those who want a more distilled experience.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Devices:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone</li><br/>
<li>iPad</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Consoles:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>PlayStation Portable (PSP)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/gamma-game-emulator/id6499106870">Gamma</a></h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Final-Fantasy-iOS-Emulation-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951199" /><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/gamma-game-emulator/id6499106870">Gamma</a> is an emulator for the original PlayStation. It is developed by ZodTTD, who has been creating emulators for jailbroken iPhones for around 15 years.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Devices:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone</li><br/>
<li>iPad</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Consoles:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>PlayStation (PS1)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Coming Soon</h2><br/>
<h3><a href="https://provenance-emu.com/">Provenance</a></h3><br/>
<a href="https://provenance-emu.com/">Provenance</a> is another frontend with all-in-one access to emulators for consoles from Atari, Nintendo, SEGA, Sony, and others. The app is currently available in beta via TestFlight, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/ps1-gamecube-wii-emulator-coming-to-app-store/">will be launching on the App Store soon</a>. Provenance has been in development since 2016, and it could already be sideloaded on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Devices:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone</li><br/>
<li>iPad</li><br/>
<li>Apple TV</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Supported Consoles:</strong><br/>
<ul><li>Atari 2600</li><br/>
<li>ColecoVision</li><br/>
<li>PlayStation (PS1)</li><br/>
<li>PlayStation Portable (PSP)</li><br/>
<li>SEGA Genesis</li><br/>
<li>SEGA Saturn</li><br/>
<li>SEGA Dreamcast</li><br/>
<li>Game Boy (all models)</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo DS</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo Entertainment System (NES)</li><br/>
<li>Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES)</li><br/>
<li>Nintendo 64 (N64)</li></ul>A full list of supported consoles is available <a href="https://wiki.provenance-emu.com/info/supported-systems">on Provenance's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Not Coming</h2><br/>
<h3><a href="https://dolphinios.oatmealdome.me/">Dolphin</a></h3><br/>
The popular GameCube and Wii emulator <a href="https://dolphinios.oatmealdome.me/">Dolphin</a> will not be available in the App Store, as its developers <a href="https://oatmealdome.me/blog/why-dolphin-isnt-coming-to-the-app-store/">said</a> Apple will not allow the emulator to use just-in-time (JIT) compilation, and PowerPC-based games are "basically unplayable" without it:<blockquote>The GameCube and Wii have a PowerPC-based CPU inside them. All modern Apple devices use an ARM-based CPU. It isn't possible to directly run PowerPC code on an ARM CPU, and vice versa. Therefore, if we want to run a GameCube or Wii game on an iPhone, it is necessary to translate the game's PowerPC code to ARM so that the CPU can understand it.<br/>
<br/>
Dolphin uses something called a Just-in-Time (JIT) recompiler to achieve this. Whenever the emulated console wants to run game code, Dolphin will use its JIT to translate the PowerPC code to ARM, and then execute the results.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, Apple generally does not allow apps to use JIT recompilers on iOS.</blockquote><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emulator/">Emulator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-app-store-emulators-list/">iPhone Emulators on the App Store: Game Boy, N64, PS1, PSP, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-emulators-on-the-app-store-game-boy-n64-ps1-psp-and-more.2426577/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Display Production Set to Start in June</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-16-display-production-june/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-display-production-set-to-start-in-june.2426576/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:27:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-16-display-production-june/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Production on displays destined for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models will start in June, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/DSCCRoss">display analyst Ross Young</a>. In a tweet limited to subscribers, Young said that panel production will begin next month, with the smaller-sized &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; to have the highest volume production projected for June.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Colors-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935282" /><br/>
Apple suppliers will manufacture the displays and send them off to the factories that will start assembling the finished &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max are expected to come out in September, which is Apple's typical <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> release month. The devices will look similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, but Apple is increasing the size of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will have a 6.3-inch display (up from 6.1 inches) while the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will have a 6.9-inch display (up from 6.7 inches). Display sizes for the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will not change, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will measure in at 6.1 inches while the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will have a 6.7-inch display.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features rumored for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup include a new "Capture" button for taking images and videos in landscape mode, faster A-series chips, camera updates, and Wi-Fi 7 and faster 5G modems for some models.<br/>
<br/>
More on what to expect from the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">found in our dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-16-display-production-june/">iPhone 16 Display Production Set to Start in June</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-display-production-set-to-start-in-june.2426576/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Max Get Rare &#36;99 Discount on Amazon, Available for &#36;449.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/airpods-max-99-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-get-rare-99-discount-on-amazon-available-for-449-99.2426555/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:52:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/airpods-max-99-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has one of the first &#36;99 discounts on Apple's AirPods Max since February, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> in four colors, down from &#36;549.00. Most models can deliver as soon as May 18 with Prime delivery, and May 21 for regular shipping.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Max-Discount-Feature-Warm-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895400" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
On Amazon, colors being discounted include Space Gray, Sky Blue, Silver, and Pink. AirPods Max deals above &#36;50 have been very rare in 2024, with this deal being just the second time we've tracked a &#36;99 discount so far this year. This isn't quite the all-time low price seen on the headphones, but it's still a solid discount if you've been waiting for something more notable to come along for the high-end AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to be updating the AirPods Max sometime in 2024, and the new models should be getting a USB-C port and new color options. There is only one other AirPods deal happening right now on Amazon: you can get the the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a> (&#36;49 off). <br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/airpods-max-99-discount/">AirPods Max Get Rare &#36;99 Discount on Amazon, Available for &#36;449.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-get-rare-99-discount-on-amazon-available-for-449-99.2426555/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discontinues &#039;iOS Developer University Program&#039; for Students</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/apple-ends-ios-developer-university-program/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinues-ios-developer-university-program-for-students.2426538/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:00:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/apple-ends-ios-developer-university-program/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has discontinued the iOS Developer University Program as of May 15, according to a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/programs/ios/university/">notice on its website</a> and an <a href="https://twitter.com/maxifirtman/status/1790871266221805962">email sent to program members</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-developer-app-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-795934" /><br/>
The program allowed university professors and other eligible instructors to create a development team with up to 200 students, who could create and test apps without needing to pay the usual &#36;99 annual fee for Apple Developer Program membership.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says accredited educational institutions can still enroll in the Apple Developer Program at no cost by submitting a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/fee-waiver/">fee waiver request</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/nicolas09F9">Nicolás Álvarez</a>!</em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/apple-ends-ios-developer-university-program/">Apple Discontinues &#039;iOS Developer University Program&#039; for Students</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinues-ios-developer-university-program-for-students.2426538/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M4 iPad Pro Bend Tests: Durability Equal to M2 Model Despite Thinness</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/m4-ipad-pro-bend-tests-durability/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-ipad-pro-bend-tests-durability-equal-to-m2-model-despite-thinness.2426535/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:50:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/m4-ipad-pro-bend-tests-durability/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first M4 iPad Pro bend tests are in, and the initial consensus appears to be that Apple has managed to make its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/08/ipod-nano-appears-in-new-ipad-pro-ad/">thinnest device ever</a> just as durable as the previous generation M2 iPad Pro that it replaces.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/bend-test-ipad-pro-1.jpg" alt="" width="2932" height="1646" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951054" /><br/>
Two approaches were taken in bend tests by prominent tech YouTubers. <a href="https://youtu.be/GN6ZlssqNAE">JerryRigEverything</a> for example forcibly applied pressure by bending the new device with his hands, while <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G6LSoVJZfAU">MobileReviewsEh</a> took a different tack by placing the iPad under a force meter and applying gym weights on top to exert pressure within a limited contact area.<br/>
<br/>
When bending the iPad Pro from the back in the horizontal position, JerryRigEverything found that the device held up "surprisingly well," as if "suspicious levels of black magic structural integrity" were going on. <br/>
<br/>
When forcibly bent from the back, the glass screen eventually rippled away from the frame, yet the display and operating system continued to function normally. When it came to putting pressure on the device vertically, however, it was a different story, and the iPad Pro quickly suffered a catastrophic split up the middle, originating from the USB-C port.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GN6ZlssqNAE?si=gxt-aEM6CJ8vPyu4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
JerryRigEverything then removed the display to reveal and remove the internals, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/14/ipad-pro-structural-design-avoid-bendgate/">new metal cowling</a> that runs down the middle of the device. "If Apple could add another more perpendicular spine running width-wise near the charging port, this thing probably would have survived," he added.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Oi7TMbWgJ4Y?si=m3KDYOCjnTTKZ5lE" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
JerryRigEverything concluded that the central spine of the new iPad Pro is "definitely providing enough structure for horizontal bends," and should stand up to everyday use in a backpack or luggage. In his own <a href="https://youtu.be/Oi7TMbWgJ4Y">AppleTrack</a> test, Sam Kohl agreed: "Is [its thinness] a durability risk? The answer is no. The spine that Apple put along the logic board is very good unless you are bending the corners in."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/G6LSoVJZfAU?si=d2WihToBPtAts9cD" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
After placing in excess of 70 pounds of weight on the center of the iPad Pro display until complete structural failure, MobileReviewsEh concluded that the new iPad Pro is "just as tough if not a little bit tougher" than the one it replaces, despite being 18-20% thinner than the M2 iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, another "bendgate" looks unlikely. For those unfamiliar with the controversy, Apple in 2019 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/12/19/apple-2018-ipad-pros-ship-bent/">admitted</a> to shipping its then-new models with a "very slight bend in the aluminum chassis," which it blamed on a "side effect of the manufacturing process."<br/>
<br/>
Despite videos indicating that the 2018 iPad Pro models bent more easily than other models, Apple said the bend did not worsen over time or negatively affect the iPad's performance, and that concerns over the device's durability were unfounded. Nevertheless, some iPad owners were understandably upset to find defects in devices that cost hundreds of dollars. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/m4-ipad-pro-bend-tests-durability/">M4 iPad Pro Bend Tests: Durability Equal to M2 Model Despite Thinness</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-ipad-pro-bend-tests-durability-equal-to-m2-model-despite-thinness.2426535/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Max Looks This Much Bigger Beside iPhone 15 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-16-pro-max-larger-size-comparison/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-max-looks-this-much-bigger-beside-iphone-15-pro-max.2426531/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 04:51:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-16-pro-max-larger-size-comparison/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year's upcoming iPhone 16 Pro Max is expected to get a boost in overall size from 6.7-inches to 6.9-inches, and a new image gives us a good idea of how the current iPhone 15 Pro Max compares to what could be Apple's largest ever iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-iphone-16-pro-max.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951045" /><br/>
The image above, <a href="https://x.com/zoneoftech/status/1788978232512921881">posted on X by ZONEofTECH</a>, shows a dummy model representing the ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max alongside an actual iPhone 15 Pro Max. Dummy units are designed to take the place of real devices for display or testing purposes, and therefore seek to match the dimensions and design changes of yet-to-be-released iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
With the increase in size of Apple's larger premium model rumored to be in the region of 0.2 inches, the difference is visually noticeable, but whether it will be all that significant for users in real-world use is another question. <br/>
<br/>
The smaller ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ is expected to increase from 6.1- to 6.3-inches, and with both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">iPhone 16 Pro models expected to be larger</a>, they are also expected to be taller and wider than the iPhone 15 Pro models. While thickness will remain the same, the weight is likely to increase slightly due to the larger size.<br/>
<br/>
Note that Apple is also rumored to be using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/iphone-16-even-thinner-bezels/">Border Reduction Structure (BRS) technology</a> for the iPhone 16 Pro models, which is expected to result in slimmer bezel sizes, subsequently allowing for more display space within the confines of those dimensions.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, the iPhone 16 Pro's display could be up to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/iphone-16-pro-brighter-display/">20% brighter for typical SDR content</a>, featuring up to 1,200 nits of typical SDR brightness. Taken together, those changes could add up to a substantially improved screen viewing experience.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the ‌iPhone 16‌ and ‌iPhone 16‌ Plus are expected to stay at 6.1- and 6.7-inches like their predecessors. If Apple sticks to its typical annual iPhone launch timing, the iPhone 16 lineup will be released sometime around mid-September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/iphone-16-pro-max-larger-size-comparison/">iPhone 16 Pro Max Looks This Much Bigger Beside iPhone 15 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-max-looks-this-much-bigger-beside-iphone-15-pro-max.2426531/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Speed Up iPhone Typing With This Simple Keyboard Trick</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-iphone-typing-simple-keyboard-trick/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/speed-up-iphone-typing-with-this-simple-keyboard-trick.2426526/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 03:49:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-iphone-typing-simple-keyboard-trick&#038;post_date=1715867364/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone users often find themselves toggling between different keyboard layouts to type messages, emails, or fill out forms. This can slow down communication and disrupt your flow. But there are ways to streamline the process. If this quick tip is new to you, it could revolutionize the way you type on your iPhone and save you precious time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/speed-up-iphone-typing-trick.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951032" /><br/>
Switching away from the alphabetic keyboard layout when you need to type a number or symbol is an all-too-often occurrence on ‌iPhone‌, so here's a quick tip for making the transition super-swift.<br/>
<br/>
Rather than tap the "123" key in the bottom-left corner to switch to the number/symbol keyboard, hold down on the key and then slide your finger over to the number/symbol that you want to type, then let go. <br/>
<br/>
This single action types the number/symbol <em>and</em> automatically switches you right back into the alphabetical layout, avoiding the need to perform three separate taps to achieve the same result.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/quick-switch-keyboard.jpg" alt="notes" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874091" /><br/>
So next time you find yourself needing to insert a number or symbol, remember this trick and you can type away without pause.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-iphone-typing-simple-keyboard-trick/">Speed Up iPhone Typing With This Simple Keyboard Trick</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/speed-up-iphone-typing-with-this-simple-keyboard-trick.2426526/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Trolls iPad &#039;Crush!&#039; Ad, Says &#039;We Would Never Crush Creativity&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/samsung-trolls-apple-ipad-pro-crush-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-trolls-ipad-crush-ad-says-we-would-never-crush-creativity.2426521/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 03:22:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/samsung-trolls-apple-ipad-pro-crush-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has sought to capitalize on the fallout of Apple's controversial "Crush!" ad for iPad Pro by releasing a <a href="https://x.com/SamsungMobileUS/status/1790824457365594487">Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra ad</a> that includes the tagline "Creativity cannot be crushed."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/samsung-creativity-cannot-be-crushed-ad.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951021" /><br/>
When Apple last week introduced the new M4 iPad Pro models, it showed a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ntjkwIXWtrc">video</a> of a hydraulic press crushing creative tools, including musical instruments, electronic equipment, arcade games, paint and brushes, computers, cameras, and more, with the aim of demonstrating how the iPad represents all of the tools condensed into a single device.<br/>
<br/>
This imagery sparked significant backlash from the creative community and the social media-using public, who interpreted it as a metaphor for Big Tech's destructive impact on creative industries and individual creativity.<br/>
<br/>
The negative reception was so strong that Apple decided to cancel planned TV spots for the ad and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/apple-crush-ad-apology/">publicly apologized</a>, acknowledging that the ad "missed the mark" by not aligning with their intention to celebrate and empower creatives​.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-media-max-width="560"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">We would never crush creativity. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/UnCrush?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#UnCrush</a> <a href="https://t.co/qvlUqbRlnE">pic.twitter.com/qvlUqbRlnE</a></p>&mdash; Samsung Mobile US (@SamsungMobileUS) <a href="https://twitter.com/SamsungMobileUS/status/1790824457365594487?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 15, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Seizing on a perceived marketing opportunity, Samsung has now released an ad of its own, in which a musician walks through the destructive wake of the hydraulic press and picks up a damaged guitar. The musician then sits beside an easel holding a Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra with musical notation on the screen, and proceeds to perform the piece of music. The video was <a href="https://x.com/SamsungMobileUS/status/1790824457365594487">shared on X (Twitter)</a> by Samsung with the accompanying caption, "We would never crush creativity."<br/>
<br/>
Samsung mocking Apple in its ads is nothing new. The company has mocked Apple for everything from design decisions such as the iPhone's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/08/02/samsung-mocks-apple-headphone-jack-removal/">removal of the headphone jack</a> (which it also eventually removed) to Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/15/samsung-foldable-iphone-world-cup-ad/">lack of a foldable smartphone lineup</a>. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/samsung-trolls-apple-ipad-pro-crush-ad/">Samsung Trolls iPad &#039;Crush!&#039; Ad, Says &#039;We Would Never Crush Creativity&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-trolls-ipad-crush-ad-says-we-would-never-crush-creativity.2426521/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPads Get Redesigned Magnets for More Smart Folio Viewing Angles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/new-ipads-added-magnets-smart-folio-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipads-get-redesigned-magnets-for-more-smart-folio-viewing-angles.2426518/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 02:46:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/new-ipads-added-magnets-smart-folio-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has new Smart Folio cases for its latest M4 iPad Pro and M2 iPad Air models that boast a wider range of viewing angles, and thanks to Marques Brownlee, we now know how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipad-pro-cases-2024.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949521" /><br/>
With the help of some magnet paper, MKBHD <a href="https://x.com/MKBHD/status/1790718481102434503">reveals</a> that Apple has added bigger, more cubic magnets to the M4 iPad Pro that align with a new longer rail of stripe magnets in the Folio Case, thereby achieving a wider range of viewing angle adjustment.<br/>
<br/>
The magnet paper also reveals that, because of how thin the new iPad Pro is compared to the previous generation model, Apple has had to use flatter, more circular speaker drivers, which appear to be closer to the top of the device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is selling the new <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW993ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-11-inch-m4-denim">Smart Folio for the 11-inch iPad Pro</a> in Denim, Black, and White. There's also a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWK33ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-pro-13-inch-m4-black">Smart Folio for the 13-inch iPad Pro</a> in the same color options. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-media-max-width="560"><p lang="fr" dir="ltr">Magnets <a href="https://t.co/zwHcVnICCR">pic.twitter.com/zwHcVnICCR</a></p>&mdash; Marques Brownlee (@MKBHD) <a href="https://twitter.com/MKBHD/status/1790718481102434503?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 15, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Similarly, you can get the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWK53ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-air-11-inch-m2-charcoal-gray">Smart Folio for 11-inch iPad Air</a> in Light Violet, Charcoal Gray, Sage, and Denim. There's also the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWKC3ZM/A/smart-folio-for-ipad-air-13-inch-m2-sage">Smart Folio for the 13-inch iPad Air</a> in the same color options.<br/>
<br/>
The 11-inch and 13-inch versions of the Smart Folio case for iPad Pro and iPad Air are priced at &#36;79 and &#36;99, respectively.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/16/new-ipads-added-magnets-smart-folio-case/">New iPads Get Redesigned Magnets for More Smart Folio Viewing Angles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipads-get-redesigned-magnets-for-more-smart-folio-viewing-angles.2426518/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>40 Million People Subscribe to Netflix&#039;s Ad-Supported Tier</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/netflix-ad-supported-tier-40-million/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/40-million-people-subscribe-to-netflixs-ad-supported-tier.2426475/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:08:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/netflix-ad-supported-tier-40-million/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix's ad-supported streaming tier has 40 million global monthly active users, up 35 million from a year ago, <a href="https://about.netflix.com/en/news/netflix-upfront-2024-the-year-of-growth-and-momentum">Netflix said today</a> at its Upfront advertising presentation. Netflix has 270 million total subscribers worldwide, so the majority of its users are still on the ad-free tiers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-4.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884794" /><br/>
Netflix resisted implementing an ad-supported tier for many years, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/23/netflix-ceo-confirms-ad-supported-tier/">confirmed in 2022</a> that it had plans to implement a cheaper option in order to boost revenue. The Standard with ads plan <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/04/netflix-basic-with-ads-plan-doesnt-work-apple-tv/">launched in late 2022</a>, and it has grown more popular as Netflix has increased the pricing of its ad-free tiers.<br/>
<br/>
In the United States, the Standard with ads plan is priced at &#36;6.99 per month for HD streaming on up to two devices at one time, with all but a "few movies and TV shows available." The basic ad-free plan is &#36;15.49 per month, while the premium plan is &#36;22.99 per month. Netflix's ad-supported plan does not include the option to download content for offline viewing, nor does it support spatial audio.<br/>
<br/>
According to Netflix, more than 40 percent of all signups in the countries where the ad-supported plan is available are for the ads plan. More than 70 percent of Netflix's ad-supported members watch Netflix content for more than 10 hours per month, and Netflix says subscribers are twice as likely to respond to an ad compared to subscribers of other streaming services.<br/>
<br/>
Since Netflix launched its ad-supported tier, it has partnered with Microsoft for ads, but in 2025, it will launch an in-house ad platform.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to boosting revenue through a cheaper ad-supported option, Netflix has also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/04/netflix-password-sharing-crackdown-pace/">cracked down on password sharing</a>. After putting an end to multi-household account use, Netflix saw strong subscriber growth and an increase in revenue.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/netflix-ad-supported-tier-40-million/">40 Million People Subscribe to Netflix&#039;s Ad-Supported Tier</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/40-million-people-subscribe-to-netflixs-ad-supported-tier.2426475/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>RetroArch iOS and tvOS Emulator for Atari, Commodore, Nintendo, Sega and Sony Games Now Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/retroarch-ios-emulator/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/retroarch-ios-and-tvos-emulator-for-atari-commodore-nintendo-sega-and-sony-games-now-available.2426474/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:55:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/retroarch-ios-emulator/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With Apple's decision to allow game emulators on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, several popular emulators like Delta have now launched for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. RetroArch is the latest emulator to come to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, allowing gamers to play games from a wide range of systems.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/retroarch-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950997" /><br/>
RetroArch supports multiple versions of Atari and Commodore systems, as well as the Nintendo DS, Game Boy, NES, SNES, and Virtual Boy. Multiple Sega and Sony systems are also included, as are the NEC PC Engine and Neo Geo Pocket.<br/>
<br/>
RetroArch is free to download, has no ads, and is open source. It supports save states, cheats, custom overlays, fast forward and rewind, AI translations, and RetroAchievements. RetroAchievements adds trophies to all manner of classic games, providing incentives to unlock new content and top leaderboards.<br/>
<br/>
RetroArch is fairly well-known because it was previously available on PC and Mac, it just was not able to be released for iOS devices until Apple's rule change. RetroArch is also the first console emulator that works on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, allowing games to be played with an MFi controller on a larger screen.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Classic console emulation has finally made its way to Apple TV via RetroArch - the first emulator publicly available on the App Store for tvOS. <a href="https://t.co/TYglmhbDxK">https://t.co/TYglmhbDxK</a> <a href="https://t.co/U1NZqOTRmX">pic.twitter.com/U1NZqOTRmX</a></p>&mdash; Sigmund Judge (@sigjudge) <a href="https://twitter.com/sigjudge/status/1790873751552237902?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 15, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
RetroArch can be downloaded from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; for free. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/retroarch/id6499539433">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/retroarch-ios-emulator/">RetroArch iOS and tvOS Emulator for Atari, Commodore, Nintendo, Sega and Sony Games Now Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/retroarch-ios-and-tvos-emulator-for-atari-commodore-nintendo-sega-and-sony-games-now-available.2426474/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
