<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 09:01:09 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Relay FM&#039; Podcast Network Launches Annual Fundraiser for St. Jude Children&#039;s Research Hospital</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/relay-fm-2024-st-jude-fundraiser/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/relay-fm-podcast-network-launches-annual-fundraiser-for-st-jude-childrens-research-hospital.2434601/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 08:46:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/relay-fm-2024-st-jude-fundraiser/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Relay FM</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[September is Childhood Cancer Awareness Month. To support this important cause, well-known podcast network Relay FM has launched its <strong><a href="https://relay.experience.stjude.org/">annual fundraiser for St. Jude Children's Research Hospital</a></strong>, located in Memphis, Tennessee. Since 2019, the Relay FM community has raised nearly &#36;3 million for the hospital.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Relay-St-Jude-2024-Large.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962838" /><br/>
St. Jude's <a href="https://www.stjude.org/about-st-jude/faq/what-is-st-judes-mission-statement.html">mission statement</a> is that no child is denied treatment:<blockquote>The mission of St. Jude Children's Research Hospital is to advance cures, and means of prevention, for pediatric catastrophic diseases through research and treatment. Consistent with the vision of our founder Danny Thomas, no child is denied treatment based on race, religion or a family's ability to pay.</blockquote>Relay FM has multiple Apple-related podcasts, such as <a href="https://www.relay.fm/connected">Connected</a>, hosted by Stephen Hackett, Myke Hurley, and Federico Viticci. Hackett's son received treatment at St. Jude as an infant, so this initiative is <a href="https://512pixels.net/2024/08/relay-for-st-jude-2024/">near and dear to him and his family</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Donations can be made on the <strong><a href="https://relay.experience.stjude.org/">Relay FM for St. Jude website</a></strong>, with rewards such as Relay FM stickers, wallpapers, and a macOS screensaver available above certain dollar amounts. The page outlines other ways you can get involved, such as starting your own fundraising campaign, and sharing the page also greatly helps.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/relay-fm/">Relay FM</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/relay-fm-2024-st-jude-fundraiser/">&#039;Relay FM&#039; Podcast Network Launches Annual Fundraiser for St. Jude Children&#039;s Research Hospital</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/relay-fm-podcast-network-launches-annual-fundraiser-for-st-jude-childrens-research-hospital.2434601/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Google&#039;s New Pixel 9 Pro XL</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-9-pro-xl/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-googles-new-pixel-9-pro-xl.2434598/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 08:00:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-9-pro-xl/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Google Pixel</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to unveil its new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models in September, but Google decided to move its usual October smartphone announcement to August, beating Apple to new AI-powered devices. We picked up Google's new Pixel 9 Pro XL and thought we'd compare it to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max since we don't have an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; to pit against it just yet.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9IjpbfBgdLI" title="Google Pixel 9 Pro XL vs iPhone 15 Pro Max" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Design wise, the Pixel 9 Pro XL has an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> look and feel, and Google has done a lot better matching software with a high-end smartphone design. The Pixel 9 Pro XL has a more premium design than prior Pixel models, and this is the first time that Google has done two "Pro" models like Apple. Google didn't use titanium and instead opted for stainless steel for the chassis, so the Pixel 9 Pro is bulkier and heavier than the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
Google has adopted a unique camera design for the Pixel series, and the Pixel 9 Pro XL has a camera bar with a triple-lens setup. There's a 50-megapixel wide-angle lens, a 48-megapixel telephoto lens (with 5x zoom like the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max), and a 48-megapixel ultra wide lens, pixel binned to 12-megapixels.<br/>
<br/>
That last camera is what we're expecting to see for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models, with Apple planning to adopt a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera that does better in low light. Right now, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models only have a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera. Pixel binning means that multiple pixels are combined to create a better image without a larger image size.<br/>
<br/>
We're going to save a full camera comparison for when the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max launches, but the Pixel 9 Pro XL is taking incredible photos, which is to be expected from any premium smartphone these days.<br/>
<br/>
All of the Pixel 9 smartphones have a whole host of AI features, some of which Apple can't yet match with Apple Intelligence. There's a "Reimagine" feature for adding AI objects into existing photos, which Apple has no plan to adopt. When the new Pixel phones first came out, reviewers were able to do things like add dead bodies, bombs, and blood into their images, but Google has shut that down. Google also tweaked its Pixel Studio image generation app to prevent people from using it to do things like create Nazi versions of Elmo.<br/>
<br/>
Other image capabilities include "Add Me" for putting an extra person into an image (AI artifacts included), Video Boost for improving video content, and Zoom Enhance for digital zooming in further than the 5x optical zoom with enhanced clarity.<br/>
<br/>
Google added Call Notes, which is essentially identical to the call recording option Apple introduced in the iOS 18.1 beta. You can record a phone call and get a transcription of what was said. The Pixel Weather app offers an AI roundup of local current and upcoming conditions, which is useful, and there's a surprisingly nice Screenshots app.<br/>
<br/>
If you screenshot an article or a website, the Pixel 9 will remember where the screenshot came from and it can bring you back to that website later. It doesn't work within apps, unfortunately, but it's still nice to have.<br/>
<br/>
With Gemini integrated into the Pixel 9 models instead of Google Assistant, you can have live conversations with an AI. It's definitely weird to have a chat with your phone, and that may be something that never really catches on. Plus it costs extra money because you'll need the premium version of Gemini. Overall, the Gemini integration is better with context and is more helpful than before, so it will be interesting to see how it compares to the revamped version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> that Apple is working on.<br/>
<br/>
We'll come back to the Pixel 9 Pro XL later in 2024 and 2025 to see if Apple is able to match the feature set both with the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models and with future Apple Intelligence capabilities.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-pixel/">Google Pixel</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-pixel-9-pro-xl/">iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Google&#039;s New Pixel 9 Pro XL</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-googles-new-pixel-9-pro-xl.2434598/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sketchy Rumor Claims iPhone 16 Pre-Orders Could Begin on a Thursday Instead of Usual Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-16-pre-orders-thursday-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sketchy-rumor-claims-iphone-16-pre-orders-could-begin-on-a-thursday-instead-of-usual-friday.2434593/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 07:30:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-16-pre-orders-thursday-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Macerkopf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's annual iPhone event is scheduled to take place <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">on Monday, September 9</a>. Typically, this would suggest that iPhone 16 pre-orders would begin on Friday, September 13, but <a href="https://www.macerkopf.de/2024/08/27/iphone-16-vorverkaufsstart-moeglicherweise-am-12-september/">German blog <em>Macerkopf</em></a> this week claimed it heard that the pre-orders could instead begin on Thursday, September 12. The report did not elaborate on the source of this information, nor did it provide a reason for this potential change, so skepticism is warranted.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
It is worth noting that Apple's annual iPhone event most often takes place on a Tuesday, but the upcoming event on September 9 will be the first-ever iPhone event to be held on a Monday. It is unclear if the event being held one day earlier than expected has any relation to pre-orders potentially starting one day earlier as well.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, Apple will reveal when iPhone 16 pre-orders will actually begin during its event. Will it be a Thursday or a Friday? Place your bets.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macerkopf-de/">Macerkopf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-16-pre-orders-thursday-rumor/">Sketchy Rumor Claims iPhone 16 Pre-Orders Could Begin on a Thursday Instead of Usual Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sketchy-rumor-claims-iphone-16-pre-orders-could-begin-on-a-thursday-instead-of-usual-friday.2434593/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Add Multiple Pages to Control Center</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-add-multiple-pages-control-center/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-add-multiple-pages-to-control-center.2434590/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 07:14:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-add-multiple-pages-control-center&#038;post_date=1724865287/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Control Center</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> overhauls the Control Center by letting you <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-reorder-resize-buttons-control-center/">reorder, resize, and remove buttons</a>, access a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-controls-gallery-customize-control-center/">controls gallery</a>, and add multiple screens, moving away from the single-screen layout of recent years. In this article we are going to show you how you can create dedicated pages for various control types, such as connectivity, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> devices, and Accessibility options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-pages.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958444" /><br/>
The new Control Center comes pre-configured with multiple default pages, which you can freely customize, add to, or remove. The system accommodates up to 15 separate screens, offering unprecedented flexibility when compared to previous versions of iOS.<br/>
<br/>
Navigation between these pages is easy. You can swipe up and down through Control Center, tap small icons on the right side of the display, or hold and scrub through these icons for quick access. The following steps explain how to add additional pages to your Control Center.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Swipe down from the top-right corner of the screen to launch Control Center.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the circle icon at the bottom of the icon list, which indicates a new blank page.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Add a Control</strong> to open the Controls Gallery.</li><br/>
  <li>Use the search field at the top, or browse the controls with a finger scroll to find the control that you want to include on the page, then tap it.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/control-center-multiple-screens2.jpg" alt="control center" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962779" /><br/>
  <li>Using the corner anchor, drag with your finger to expand the control if you wish.</li><br/>
  <li>When finished, tap a space on the page to exit editing mode.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/control-center-multiple-screens1.jpg" alt="control center" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962780" /><br/>
</ol>Control Center intelligently assigns icons to each page based on its content. When controls exceed the available space on a page, or if a resized control becomes too large, Control Center automatically creates a new page and relocates the excess controls. Bear in mind that the option to create a new page only appears when an existing page is approximately half full, ensuring adequate spacing between icons and maintaining a clean, organized layout.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">How to Install the Fifth iOS 18 Public Beta</a></li></ul><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> are currently in beta and expected to go on general release around mid-September. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/control-center/">Control Center</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-add-multiple-pages-control-center/">iOS 18: Add Multiple Pages to Control Center</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-add-multiple-pages-to-control-center.2434590/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;250 Off Every 15-Inch M3 MacBook Air With Record Low Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-250-off-every-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-with-record-low-prices.2434589/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 07:12:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has all-time low prices across the 15-inch M3 MacBook Air lineup, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model, down from &#36;1,299.00. You can get this model on sale in all four colors: Silver, Midnight, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/new-macbook-air-blue-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946062" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, Amazon is also discounting both 512GB models: the 8GB RAM/512GB computer is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,249.00</strong></a> and the 16GB RAM/512GB computer is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,449.00</strong></a>. Both of these are matches for record low prices on each model, and they're both available in every color.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the 13-inch M3 MacBook Air, we aren't tracking any best-ever prices right now on Amazon, with the exception of the 16GB RAM/512GB computer at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX246FNZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,249.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Otherwise, you'll find second-best prices across the 13-inch M3 MacBook Air lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air-2/">Amazon Takes &#36;250 Off Every 15-Inch M3 MacBook Air With Record Low Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-250-off-every-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-with-record-low-prices.2434589/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Pros With M4 Pro and M4 Max Chips Reportedly Being Mass Produced This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/macbook-pro-m4-pro-m4-max-production-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pros-with-m4-pro-and-m4-max-chips-reportedly-being-mass-produced-this-month.2434581/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 06:13:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/macbook-pro-m4-pro-m4-max-production-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's supply chain is beginning mass production of next-generation 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips in August, according to Taiwanese industry publication <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240826PD220/apple-market-production-supply-chain-performance.html"><em>DigiTimes</em></a>. With only a few days remaining in the month, that means that assembly of the laptops has more likely than not already begun.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
This information aligns with display industry analyst Ross Young claiming that display shipments for the next 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/">are underway</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In a May edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-12/who-will-run-apple-after-cook-leaves-a-look-at-company-s-succession-challenge-lw3j2t5z"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said "you should expect M4 Pro and M4 Max chips later this year as part of the high-end MacBook Pro." He also expects Apple to release <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/23/apple-testing-four-m4-macs/">three new Macs with the standard M4 chip later this year</a>, including a lower-end 14-inch MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini. <br/>
<br/>
October is a common month for Apple to announce new Macs, including the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips last October. If that pattern repeats itself, the next 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max chips are likely around two months away from launching.<br/>
<br/>
The standard M4 chip already debuted in the iPad Pro earlier this year, and Geekbench results showed it provided <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/m4-ipad-pro-cpu-benchmark/">up to 25% faster multi-core CPU performance</a> compared to the M3 chip. Likewise, moderate year-over-year performance and power efficiency improvements can be expected from the M4 Pro and M4 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes are expected for the next MacBook Pro models, with an OLED display in particular likely still a few years away for the laptops. Gurman said Apple is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/">planning to make the MacBook Pro thinner</a> at some point "over the next couple of years."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's last Mac-focused event was held on October 30, 2023, and there is certainly potential for another October event this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/macbook-pro-m4-pro-m4-max-production-report/">MacBook Pros With M4 Pro and M4 Max Chips Reportedly Being Mass Produced This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pros-with-m4-pro-and-m4-max-chips-reportedly-being-mass-produced-this-month.2434581/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Lays Off Around 100 Services Staff Across Apple Books and News</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-lays-off-services-staff-apple-books/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-lays-off-around-100-services-staff-across-apple-books-and-news.2434573/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 03:42:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-lays-off-services-staff-apple-books/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Books</category>
		<category>Apple News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of a "shift in priorities," Apple has made cuts to its workforce across senior VP Eddy Cue's Services division, <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-28/apple-cuts-about-100-services-jobs-as-part-of-priority-shift">Bloomberg</a></em> reports. About 100 employees impacted by the cuts were reportedly given a 60-day window to secure another position within Apple before their termination becomes effective. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-books.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962732" /><br/>
The scope of the layoffs extended beyond a single team, with some employees working across multiple departments feeling the ripple effects of Apple's apparent cost-optimization effort. The layoffs primarily affected the Apple Books app and Apple Bookstore teams, but also impacted the Apple News team, marking the fourth round of staff reductions for the company in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
According to the report, the layoffs signal that Apple Books has become less of a priority for the company, which doesn't see it as a major part of its services lineup. However, the Books app is still expected to get new features over time. As for Apple News, the layoffs were said to be an indication that it is less of a focus for Apple.<br/>
<br/>
The Services division has been a key growth driver for the company in recent years. Services now account for over 22% of Apple's sales, a significant increase from less than 10% a decade ago.<br/>
<br/>
The importance of the Services segment has been particularly evident during periods of slower device sales, helping to bolster Apple's financial performance. However, this latest move suggests that even high-performing divisions are not immune to restructuring efforts.<br/>
<br/>
These layoffs follow earlier staff reductions at Apple this year, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/apple-employee-layoffs-car-project/">closure of its ambitious self-driving car project</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">shutdown of a microLED display initiative</a>. The company also dismantled a team <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-moving-san-diego-siri-team-to-austin/">based in San Diego</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's approach to layoffs has been more measured compared to some of its Silicon Valley counterparts. Cisco Systems has announced plans to reduce its headcount by approximately 7%, while Intel is set to eliminate over 15% of its workforce. These more extensive cuts at other tech firms are largely attributed to slowing growth and a shift in focus towards AI.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-books/">Apple Books</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-lays-off-services-staff-apple-books/">Apple Lays Off Around 100 Services Staff Across Apple Books and News</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-lays-off-around-100-services-staff-across-apple-books-and-news.2434573/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 to Feature 12GB RAM, Up From 8GB in iPhone 16 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-17-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-to-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb-in-iphone-16-models.2434567/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 01:57:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-17-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next year's iPhone 17 models will come with 12GB of RAM, up from the 8GB of RAM expected across Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 models, a reputable source of accurate predictions about Apple's plans has claimed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iPhone-17-Feature-With-Full-Width-Dynamic-Island.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959827" /><br/>
Onboard memory in the existing iPhone 15 lineup is different between non-Pro and Pro models: The iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus feature 6GB of RAM, while the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max come with 8GB of RAM. This difference is said to be the reason why Apple Intelligence – Apple's AI suite of on-device features – is only currently supported by the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-iphone-15-pro-requirement-apple-intelligence/">Apple Explains iPhone 15 Pro Requirement for Apple Intelligence</a></li></ul><br/>
Since it is a requirement for Apple Intelligence, all four of Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">expected to feature 8GB of RAM</a>, as is the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/iphone-se-4-8gb-ram-apple-intelligence/">rumored iPhone SE 4</a>, which is likely to launch in the spring. However, in a <a href="https://weibo.com/1833340431/OukFVf1xQ">Weibo post</a> on Wednesday, Chinese-language user "Phone Chip Expert" said next year's iPhone 17 models will have 12GB of RAM for more advanced on-device AI applications. <br/>
<br/>
"If you're planning to switch to an AI-powered iPhone, the iPhone 17 in 2025 might be a better choice," said the leaker. "This year's iPhone 16 only has 8GB of RAM, with most of the AI processing done in the cloud. Next year's iPhone 17 will have 12GB of RAM and more edge AI applications. This is something to consider for those with a limited budget who want to upgrade their iPhone."<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-likely-iphone-16-launch-date/">iPhone 16 Likely to Launch on September 20 With These New Features</a></li></ul><br/>
Edge AI applications refer to AI processing that occurs directly on the local device, rather than relying on cloud servers. "Edge" refers to the edge of the network, meaning the data processing happens close to the data source (the device itself), rather than in a centralized location like a cloud data center.<br/>
<br/>
This isn't the first time we have heard rumors of additional RAM coming to Apple's 2025 iPhones. In a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">May 2024 research note</a> with investment firm Haitong, analyst Jeff Pu claimed that the iPhone 17 Pro and Pro Max will be equipped with 12GB of RAM, while the iPhone 17 and even the rumored iPhone 17 "Slim" or "Air" with an all-new design would stick with 8GB of RAM. However, today's leaker appears to be suggesting that all iPhone 17 models will be equipped with the additional RAM, bringing AI-capable continuity to the lineup.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-17-slim-everything-we-know/">iPhone 17 'Air': Everything We Know About Apple's Slim iPhone</a></li></ul><br/>
The leaker "Phone Chip Expert" has a track record of accurate predictions. Phone Chip Expert was the first to reveal that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/28/iphone-7-already-rumored-to-be-waterproof/">iPhone 7 would be water-resistant</a> and that the standard iPhone 14 models would continue to use the A15 Bionic chip, while the more advanced A16 chip would be exclusive to the ‌iPhone 14‌ Pro models. These forecasts were later confirmed by multiple credible sources and were proven correct when the products were released.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/10-reasons-to-wait-iphone-17/">10 Reasons to Wait for Next Year's iPhone 17</a></li></ul><br/>
More recently, "Phone Chip Expert" was the first source of information about Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-developing-its-own-ai-server-processor/">developing its own AI server processor</a> using TSMC's 3nm process, targeting mass production by the second half of 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-17-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb/">iPhone 17 to Feature 12GB RAM, Up From 8GB in iPhone 16 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-to-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb-in-iphone-16-models.2434567/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PSA: YouTube Videos Really Can Get Some Water Out of Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/youtube-videos-water-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-youtube-videos-really-can-get-some-water-out-of-your-iphone.2434544/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:44:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/youtube-videos-water-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube videos that play a low sound to vibrate water out of the speakers do, in fact, work, according to a deep dive done by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/27/24228925/remove-water-phone-youtube-vergecast">The Verge</a></em>'s David Pierce and <em>iFixit</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Apple_iphone_11-water-resistant.jpg" alt="" width="1632" height="918" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-764222" /><br/>
There are a number of YouTube videos that promise to be able to remove water from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> using sound, and Pierce wanted to find out if they do what they claimed, so he asked iFixit for some help. iFixit dunked an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> into water with UV dye, played the video, and then left it overnight to dry out.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Sound To Remove Water From Phone Speaker ( GUARANTEED )" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qhItAtZDzU8" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Playing one of the YouTube videos during this process clearly expelled water from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s speaker, and the speakers of other smartphones that were tested from Google and Nokia. The water came out in an initial burst from the sound, but it is worth noting that the video was only able to remove water from the speaker area.<br/>
<br/>
UV dye stained other areas of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; when it was opened up, so the water wasn't draining from the entire phone. The oscillating tone in the YouTube videos is able to push water out of the speaker grille, but it is not a complete fix for a water-saturated device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/water-speaker-verge-ifixit.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="538" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962603" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Water coming out of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s speaker when a low-toned sound is played, via <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/27/24228925/remove-water-phone-youtube-vergecast">The Verge and iFixit</a></div></em><br/>
On the Apple Watch, Apple has a built-in feature that uses sound to expel water from the device, but that is more effective because it is a smaller object with fewer nooks and crannies than an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's modern iPhones have IP68 water and dust resistance, with the 8 representing water resistance. IPx8 means that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> can withstand splashes, rain, and accidental dunks up to six meters in depth for 30 minutes. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; waterproofing does deteriorate over time with wear and tear, and Apple does not cover water damage, so it is best to avoid water exposure when possible.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/27/24228925/remove-water-phone-youtube-vergecast"><em>The Verge</em>'s full look</a> at how these YouTube videos work is well worth checking out.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/youtube-videos-water-iphone/">PSA: YouTube Videos Really Can Get Some Water Out of Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-youtube-videos-really-can-get-some-water-out-of-your-iphone.2434544/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mophie Launches New Powerstation Battery Packs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/mophie-launches-new-powerstation-battery-packs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mophie-launches-new-powerstation-battery-packs.2434542/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:27:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/mophie-launches-new-powerstation-battery-packs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Zagg's Mophie brand today announced new versions of its popular Powerstation Plus Mini, Powerstation Plus, and Powerstation Plus Ultra, all of which have been updated with new designs and battery capacity.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/powerstation-plus.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962648" /><br/>
The &#36;50 <a href="https://www.zagg.com/powerstation-plus-mini/">Powerstation Plus Mini</a> features a 5,000mAh battery that will provide a partial charge for most iPhones. It supports 18W charging over USB-C with the built-in cable, and 20W through an extra USB-C port.<br/>
<br/>
Mophie's &#36;80 <a href="https://www.zagg.com/powerstation-plus-2024/">Powerstation Plus</a> has a 10,000mAh battery that should provide a full charge and then some for all of Apple's iPhones, plus it is powerful enough to be used with iPads and smaller Macs. It includes an integrated 30W USB-C cable and a Lightning cable, plus there's an extra USB-C port for charging multiple devices.<br/>
<br/>
The &#36;100 <a href="https://www.zagg.com/powerstation-plus-ultra/">Powerstation Plus Ultra</a> has the same capabilities as the Powerstation Plus with 30W charging and integrated cables, but it also has folding wall prongs so that it can be plugged directly into a power outlet for charging purposes.<br/>
<br/>
All three of Mophie's new power banks support passthrough charging for connected devices and will charge an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> before transferring power to the power station. They also support two-way charging with the built-in cables, and can charge multiple devices at once. Fast charging is also supported, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> can be charged to 50 percent in 25 to 30 minutes.<br/>
<br/>
The Powerstation Plus and Powerstation Mini can be <a href="https://www.zagg.com/">purchased from the Zagg website</a>. The Powerstation Ultra will launch in September.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/mophie-launches-new-powerstation-battery-packs/">Mophie Launches New Powerstation Battery Packs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mophie-launches-new-powerstation-battery-packs.2434542/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Immersive Series &#039;Elevated&#039; Coming to Vision Pro on September 6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/vision-pro-immersive-series-elevated/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-immersive-series-elevated-coming-to-vision-pro-on-september-6.2434540/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 15:57:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/vision-pro-immersive-series-elevated/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest immersive video series for the Vision Pro is set to launch in early September. "Elevated," a new 3D experience, will be available starting on September 6. A teaser for the show with an upcoming date is listed in the Apple Immersive Video section of the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-vision-pro-elevated-immersive.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962622" /><br/>
Apple first announced Elevated in July, but did not provide launch timing for the show. According to Apple, the aerial travel series "whisks viewers around iconic vistas from staggering heights" that include volcanoes, waterfalls, and more in Hawaii.<blockquote>Gain an all-new perspective as you take aerial tours of the world's most remarkable landscapes, led by well-known guides with a special connection to each place.</blockquote>While the first episode is set in Hawaii, the second episode, coming at a later date, will feature an autumn scene in New England. Apple is working on multiple new immersive video experiences that are rolling out this year.<br/>
<br/>
Boundless, a series that launched in July, features a first episode with a hot air balloon ride. A second upcoming episode will focus on Arctic Surfing. Apple is planning to release a new immersive performance from The Weeknd, a big wave surfing sports series, a behind-the-scenes view of the 2024 NBA All-Star Weekend, and its first immersive short film called "Submerged."<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro users can watch the Apple Immersive video content from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app in Australia, Canada, Hong Kong, France, Germany, Japan, Singapore, the U.K., and the U.S. Users in China can watch the content through the Migu Video and Tencent Video apps.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/vision-pro-immersive-series-elevated/">Apple Immersive Series &#039;Elevated&#039; Coming to Vision Pro on September 6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-immersive-series-elevated-coming-to-vision-pro-on-september-6.2434540/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Lets Users Transfer Apple Music Playlists to YouTube Music</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/apple-music-youtube-music-playlist-transfer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-lets-users-transfer-apple-music-playlists-to-youtube-music.2434538/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 15:38:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/apple-music-youtube-music-playlist-transfer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers who want to transfer their playlists over to YouTube Music can now use Apple's Data and Privacy page to do so, Apple says in a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120030">new support document</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962031" /><br/>
After logging in on the Data and Privacy page, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; users can select the "Transfer a copy of your data" option to move playlists from &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; to YouTube Music. YouTube Music is the only supported music service for playlist transfers, and Apple does not offer options to transfer to services like Spotify at this time.<br/>
<br/>
To make a transfer, an active &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscription or iTunes Match subscription and an active YouTube Music account are required. Playlists that are transferred are not deleted from &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, and the transfer process can take anywhere from a few minutes to a few hours depending on how many playlists are being transferred.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has details on what can be transferred and what can't:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Only the playlists that you've created (including collaborative playlists that you own) are transferred</li><br/>
 	<li>Music files aren't transferred</li><br/>
 	<li>Non-collaborative shared playlists and curated playlists aren't transferred</li><br/>
 	<li>Folders in which you've organized your &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; playlists aren't transferred</li><br/>
 	<li>Playlists can include only songs available on YouTube Music. If your playlists contains other audio files -- such as podcasts, audio books, or user-uploaded audio files -- they won't be transferred.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
After the transfer process has been completed, playlists from &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; will appear in the Library tab in YouTube Music. If a song is missing, it might not be available on YouTube Music.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/apple-music-youtube-music-playlist-transfer/">Apple Now Lets Users Transfer Apple Music Playlists to YouTube Music</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-lets-users-transfer-apple-music-playlists-to-youtube-music.2434538/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AT&amp;T Hit With &#36;950,000 Fine for 2023 911 Outage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/att-911-outage-fine/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/at-t-hit-with-950-000-fine-for-2023-911-outage.2434537/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 15:32:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/att-911-outage-fine/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AT&amp;amp;T</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AT&T will pay a &#36;950,000 fine for failing to notify 911 call centers about a service outage that occurred in 2023, the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) <a href="https://www.fcc.gov/document/fcc-settles-att-2023-911-outage-violations-950000">said this week</a>. There was an AT&T outage in Illinois, Kansas, Texas, and Wisconsin in August 2023, and AT&T was penalized both for failing to deliver 911 calls and for not notifying call centers in a timely manner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ATT-Banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937556" /><br/>
The outage happened when AT&T was testing its 911 network. A technician accidentally disabled a portion of the network, and AT&T's system did not adjust to accommodate the disabled part of the network. It was not part of planned maintenance, and there was no stringent technical review. During the outage period, which lasted for a little over an hour, there were more than 400 failed 911 calls.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to paying a &#36;950,000 fine, AT&T has implemented a three-year compliance plan to make sure that it does not violate the FCC's 911 and outage notification rules going forward.<br/>
<br/>
Service providers like AT&T are required to let call centers know about an outage right away so that the public can be notified about alternative ways to get emergency assistance.<br/>
<br/>
It's been a bad year for AT&T. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/01/att-data-leak-notifications/">In March</a>, AT&T confirmed that a 2021 data leak included the passcodes and sensitive info from 7.6 million AT&T customers and 65.4 million former AT&T customers. AT&T claimed that the data was obtained without unauthorized access to its systems, but hackers were able to get their hands on names, addresses, birth dates, phone numbers, social security numbers, and more from customers.<br/>
<br/>
In April, the company was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fcc-fines-carriers-customer-data-sharing/">fined over &#36;57 million</a> for illegally sharing customer data with third-party data aggregators, an issue that Verizon and T-Mobile also had to shell out money for.<br/>
<br/>
In July, AT&T <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/12/hackers-steal-att-phone-records/">announced a second major data breach</a>. Hackers were able to get into a cloud platform used by AT&T, and stole the records of "nearly all" of its cellular customers. The stolen data included the phone numbers of cellular and landline customers, as well as records of calls and text messages between May and October 2022.<br/>
<br/>
This week, AT&T is also in mediation with the hope of solving an ongoing Communication Workers strike in the southeast, which <a href="https://www.live5news.com/2024/08/26/att-workers-rally-downtown-amid-ongoing-strike-contract-negotiations/">has impacted service</a> in some areas and involves 17,000 employees.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/att/">AT&amp;T</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/att-911-outage-fine/">AT&amp;T Hit With &#36;950,000 Fine for 2023 911 Outage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/at-t-hit-with-950-000-fine-for-2023-911-outage.2434537/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Debuts New Rocky Point Band for Apple Watch Ultra</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/nomad-apple-watch-ultra-band/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-debuts-new-rocky-point-band-for-apple-watch-ultra.2434535/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 15:09:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/nomad-apple-watch-ultra-band/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nomad today announced the launch of its latest Apple Watch accessory, the <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/collections/rocky-point">Rocky Point Band</a>. The Rocky Point Band was created with the Apple Watch Ultra in mind, and it has a rugged look that matches well with Apple's watch for outdoor enthusiasts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/nomad-rocky-point-apple-watch-band.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962640" /><br/>
According to Nomad, the Rocky Point Band is made from "ultra-touch, compression-molded FKM" fluoroelastomer rubber, and it is equipped with grade 2 lightweight titanium hardware to match the Apple Watch Ultra. The company used metal injection molding titanium to create the components for the band.<br/>
<br/>
The design includes ventilation grooves for breathability, and it is entirely waterproof. While designed for the Apple Watch Ultra and Ultra 2, it is also compatible with all Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad is offering the Rocky Point Band in Storm, Sol, and Atlantic shades, and it can be <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/collections/rocky-point">purchased from the Nomad website</a> for &#36;80.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/nomad-apple-watch-ultra-band/">Nomad Debuts New Rocky Point Band for Apple Watch Ultra</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-debuts-new-rocky-point-band-for-apple-watch-ultra.2434535/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iCloud Mail, iCloud Web Apps, Stocks, Game Center, TestFlight and Apple News Experiencing Outage [Update: Fixed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/icloud-mail-web-apps-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-mail-icloud-web-apps-stocks-game-center-testflight-and-apple-news-experiencing-outage-update-fixed.2434529/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 14:22:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/icloud-mail-web-apps-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Mail service and its &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Web Apps are currently experiencing an outage, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's System Status page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iCloud-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803318" /><br/>
Impacted users are unable to use &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Mail or &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Web Apps, and the services have been down since 4:29 p.m. Eastern Time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that only some users are affected, so not everyone will experience issues. We'll update this article when &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Mail and Apple's &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Web Apps are up and running.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 5:50 p.m. ET:</b> Stocks, Game Center, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a> are also down. <br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 2, 5:52 p.m. ET:</b> Apple has also added TestFlight, and iWork for &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; to the list of services experiencing issues. <br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 3, 6:15 p.m. ET:</b> The outages with &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Mail, &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Web Apps, TestFlight, and Game Center have been resolved. &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; and Stocks are still experiencing issues. <br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 4, 6:30 p.m. ET:</b> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> and Game Center are again listed as having issues. &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; and Stocks are also still down.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 5, 7:30 p.m. ET:</b> Everything is operational except for Game Center. <br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 6, 8:15 p.m. ET:</b> All of Apple's services are back up and running.  <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/icloud-mail-web-apps-outage/">iCloud Mail, iCloud Web Apps, Stocks, Game Center, TestFlight and Apple News Experiencing Outage [Update: Fixed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-mail-icloud-web-apps-stocks-game-center-testflight-and-apple-news-experiencing-outage-update-fixed.2434529/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Now Supports Adding Text and Stickers to Photos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/instagram-text-stickers-photos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-now-supports-adding-text-and-stickers-to-photos.2434527/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 13:58:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/instagram-text-stickers-photos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram <a href="https://creators.instagram.com/blog/new-text-tools-to-help-you-personalize-your-content">today announced</a> support for adding text and additional images to photo and carousel posts, a new feature that will let Instagram users do more with still photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Instagram-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786418" /><br/>
There is a new text button that can be used after selecting a photo to upload, and additional images can be added in sticker form by tapping on the gallery button at the top right of the screen. Stickers can be added in several shapes, including rectangle, square, circle, heart, or star.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/instagram-text-for-photos.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="2000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962586" /><br/>
There are new fonts, animations, and effects that can be used for reels and stories, plus a simplified text tool. Users can open the text tool and tap on the text button to see the new font options. Once a font is chosen, separate animations and effects can be added. The new font options that Instagram is adopting can also be used with photos and carousels.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, Instagram <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/instagram-20-photos-carousel-posts/">added support</a> for putting up to 20 photos and videos in a carousel post, plus it introduced a feature for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/23/instagram-song-on-profile-feature/">adding a song</a> to an Instagram profile.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/instagram-text-stickers-photos/">Instagram Now Supports Adding Text and Stickers to Photos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-now-supports-adding-text-and-stickers-to-photos.2434527/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Mini 7</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-2024-ipad-mini-7.2427857/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:31:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7&#038;post_date=1724797860/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>iPad mini 7</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While Apple refreshed the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> in May 2024, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> is still in need of an update. Apple last introduced a new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; in September 2021, so it's overdue for an overhaul.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-mini-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937844" /><br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple has plans to refresh its smallest tablet later in 2024, and this guide highlights all of the rumors we've heard about the device so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="display_and_design">Display and Design</h2><br/>
We haven't heard rumors of design changes for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, which means it will likely feature the same 8.3-inch size and all-display design. The current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> Power Button, which we're also expecting for the new model.<br/>
<br/>
According to a 2023 rumor, Apple will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">make a small tweak</a> to the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s display in an effort to cut down on "jelly scrolling." The screen assembly will be rotated, which is supposed to reduce the effect when using the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; in portrait orientation.<br/>
<br/>
Jelly scrolling refers to noticeable lag when scrolling vertically through text-based context like a webpage. Each line appears to tilt downward toward the left of the screen as it passes, which makes it look like one side of the display is responding faster. Apple says that this is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">normal behavior</a> for LCD iPads, but the company still wants to make a change to minimize the effect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="a-series_chip">A-Series Chip</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; have M-series chips, but we're not expecting the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; to get a Mac chip this year. Instead, Apple is likely to go with the A17 Pro that was used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, or some other A17 variant that's capable of handling Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
It's also possible that the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will get an A18 chip if it comes after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, as rumors suggest the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have chips in the A18 family.<br/>
<br/>
With an A17 Pro or better, the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; would be on par with or faster than the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, but it won't have the speeds of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_colors">New Colors</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is available in space gray, starlight, pink, and purple right now. Apple often refreshes color options with updates, so new colors are a definite possibility. With the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; often mimics, Apple got rid of pink.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple makes the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; available in the same colors as the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, it could come in space gray, purple, blue, and starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="front_camera">Front Camera</h2><br/>
Apple moved the front-facing camera on the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; to the landscape edge of the device, and it could make the same change for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;. It may make less sense to have a landscape camera on an &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, though, because it's less often used with keyboards.<br/>
<br/>
The camera could get support for HDR 4 and it could have a wider aperture, if it adopts the camera used in the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="connectivity">Connectivity</h2><br/>
Apple has been adding Wi-Fi 6E to each product as it's updated, and it should be the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s turn this year. Wi-Fi 6E will allow the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; to connect to the 6GHz Wi-Fi band on supported routers.<br/>
<br/>
Bluetooth 5.3 is also expected, as that's another update Apple has been making to new devices, and the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; could lose its nano-SIM slot, with Apple opting only for eSIM.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_pencil_pro">Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
The current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; works with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> 2, so the new model will likely support the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro. The &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro has a squeeze gesture, haptic feedback, a gyroscope for barrel roll support, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> integration.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover might also be a new feature, as the current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; does not support it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
Apple will likely release a new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; toward the end of the year, likely in September or October. In some years, Apple holds a special October event for Macs and iPads, and we could get that in 2024. Apple is planning to hold an iPhone-centric event on Monday, September 9, so it's also entirely possible the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will see a debut then.<br/>
<br/>
There are, however, refreshes coming for the MacBook Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, so it would also make sense for Apple to hold a second fall event.<br/>
<br/>
Supplies of the current sixth-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/ipad-mini-stock-dwindling/">starting to dwindle</a> in stores, which could be a sign that a refresh is coming in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="future_ipad_mini_models">Future iPad mini Models</h2><br/>
There are rumors that Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-foldable-2026-could-replace-ipad-mini/">foldable iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/">OLED display technology</a> for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, but neither of these updates are expected in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
An OLED display or a foldable &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; are technologies not expected until 2026, 2027, or even later.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">What to Expect From Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Mini 7</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-2024-ipad-mini-7.2427857/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Max 2: What Rumors Say Ahead of the Apple Event Next Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/airpods-max-2-rumor-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-2-what-rumors-say-ahead-of-the-apple-event-next-month.2434521/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:57:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/airpods-max-2-rumor-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It has been nearly four years since Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, so an update to the over-ear headphones is highly anticipated.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936392" /><br/>
Below, we recap the latest rumors about the AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
As a refresher, Apple released the AirPods Max in December 2020, after announcing them in a press release shared on the Apple Newsroom website. The headphones have not received any hardware upgrades since, leading some customers to hold off on their purchase and hope that Apple will eventually release AirPods Max 2.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, rumors suggest that AirPods Max 2 are not coming any time soon, with only minor revisions expected for the headphones later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman previously reported that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/29/gurman-usb-c-airpods-max-late-2024/">planning to update the AirPods Max in late 2024</a> with a USB-C charging port, instead of the current Lightning port, and he said new color options are also a possibility for the headphones. Beyond that, Gurman said Apple is planning <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1762690933659988326">no other changes</a> for the revised AirPods Max, to the point that he expects the updated headphones to still be considered first-generation AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
If the information shared by Gurman is accurate, that means the AirPods Max would not be updated with the H2 chip that debuted in the second-generation AirPods Pro a few years ago. As a result, the AirPods Max would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/airpods-max-2-could-miss-out-on-adaptive-audio/">miss out on Adaptive Audio features</a>, along with longer battery life afforded by the H2 chip's increased power efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
In the event Apple ever does release AirPods Max 2, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect/">plausible upgrades</a> include the H2 chip, longer battery life, improved active noise cancellation, a U2 chip with support for Precision Finding in the Find My app, Bluetooth 5.3, and a redesigned carrying case.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the AirPods Max would be updated in late 2024, but it is unclear exactly when. Apple recently announced that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">holding a media event on September 9</a>, where it is expected to unveil <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">fourth-generation AirPods</a> alongside new iPhones and Apple Watches, but it is unclear if the revised AirPods Max will also be introduced then.<br/>
<br/>
AirPods Max are regularly &#36;549 in the U.S., but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/airpods-max-hit-399/">Amazon has the headphones on sale for &#36;399</a> in all color options, including Green, Pink, Silver, Sky Blue, and Space Gray.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/airpods-max-2-rumor-recap/">AirPods Max 2: What Rumors Say Ahead of the Apple Event Next Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-2-what-rumors-say-ahead-of-the-apple-event-next-month.2434521/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Massive &#36;770 Discount on Samsung&#039;s 27-Inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-deal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-massive-770-discount-on-samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-s9-5k-monitor.2434518/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:27:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-deal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung's 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor has hit a new record low price on Amazon this week, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2F%3Fth%3D1"><strong>&#36;830.10</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. You can have the monitor delivered by August 29 if you're a Prime member, or by September 2 for everyone else.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/viewfinity-s9-samsung-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958532" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
We typically track deals for the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor at around &#36;899.99, so today's deal beats the previous all-time low by about &#36;70. Right now only Amazon has this deal, so if you're interested be sure to lock it in before it expires.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2F%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;770 OFF</div>Samsung 27-Inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor for &#36;830.10</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This monitor has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4 and AirPlay. Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-deal/">Amazon Introduces Massive &#36;770 Discount on Samsung&#039;s 27-Inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-massive-770-discount-on-samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-s9-5k-monitor.2434518/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac App Store and Apple Books Experiencing Outage [Update: Fixed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/mac-app-store-outage-august/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-app-store-and-apple-books-experiencing-outage-update-fixed.2434512/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 10:27:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/mac-app-store-outage-august/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a> and the Apple Books are both having issues at this time, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's System Status page</a>. There are no specific details on what the outage entails, as Apple only says that some users are experiencing a problem with the services.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Mac-App-Store-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800078" /><br/>
Apple says that the outages started at 12:15 p.m. Eastern Time. Only some users are affected, so not all users will see problems with the &zwnj;Mac App Store&zwnj; or Apple Books.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> Apple says that the outage was fixed as of 2:40 p.m. Eastern Time.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/mac-app-store-outage-august/">Mac App Store and Apple Books Experiencing Outage [Update: Fixed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-app-store-and-apple-books-experiencing-outage-update-fixed.2434512/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
