<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:03:55 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares New &#039;Get Ready&#039; Ad Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-get-ready-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-new-get-ready-ad-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2415813/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:17:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-get-ready-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a new "Get Ready" ad promoting the upcoming launch of the Vision Pro headset. The ad features notable movie and TV show characters putting on masks, glasses, and other similar accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Get Ready Apple Vision Pro" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aqTIB_q40bo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
There are scenes from Star Wars, Fantastic Mr. Fox, Young Frankenstein, Kick-Ass, Up, Iron Man, Ant-Man, Star Trek, Snoopy, SpongeBob SquarePants, and Back to the Future, along with a shot of a woman putting on the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
The video ends with the tagline "Get Ready," as the Vision Pro is set to launch in just a few weeks. Apple will accept pre-orders for the Vision Pro on January 19, with an official launch to follow on February 2.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-get-ready-ad/">Apple Shares New &#039;Get Ready&#039; Ad Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-new-get-ready-ad-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2415813/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Over 150 3D Movies and Spatial Games Coming to Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-movies-games/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/over-150-3d-movies-and-spatial-games-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2415811/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 16:17:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-movies-games/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At launch, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app will have more than 150 3D movie and TV show options for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> users to watch, Apple said today when it announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">the Vision Pro launch date</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-movie-experience.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900262" /><br/>
While the Vision Pro will work with any TV show or movie available through the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app on the device, specific titles have been updated with 3D that will make for an even more immersive experience. TV shows and movies that are not 3D will appear on a screen that "feels 100 feet wide," with the Vision Pro offering the resolution of a 4K TV for each eye, along with HDR support.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has created Apple Immersive Video, a "new entertainment format" that is designed to put users inside action with 180-degree 3D 8K video recordings that have been captured with Spatial Audio, plus there will be interactive experiences like "Encounter Dinosaurs."<br/>
<br/>
As for gaming, the Vision Pro will support more than 250 titles on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, with the content able to be played in 2D using a game controller. There are also select "spatial games" that have been created for the device, including Game Room, What the Golf?, and Super Fruit Ninja. Apple says that these games take advantage of the Vision Pro's capabilities to transform the space around players, providing "unique and engaging gameplay experiences."<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro is set to launch on Friday, February 2, with Apple to begin accepting pre-orders on Friday, January 19. At launch, the Vision Pro will only be available in the United States.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-movies-games/">Over 150 3D Movies and Spatial Games Coming to Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/over-150-3d-movies-and-spatial-games-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2415811/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: This &#039;MagicMirror&#039; Analyzes Facial Blood Flow to Monitor Vital Signs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-anura-magicmirror/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-this-magicmirror-analyzes-facial-blood-flow-to-monitor-vital-signs.2415810/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 15:56:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-anura-magicmirror/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[NuraLogix this week unveiled the <a href="https://www.nuralogix.ai/magic-mirror/">Anura MagicMirror</a>, a new health product that is designed to use a combination of sensors and artificial intelligence to check vital signs and provide disease risk assessments.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="AnuraTM MagicMirrorTM Demo - English" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8QWC9J9sfyA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The 21.5-inch tabletop smart mirror takes a 30 second scan when a person sits in front of it, analyzing facial blood flow to provide a wealth of information. It uses a patented Transdermal Optical Imaging technology to detect a person's face and monitor blood flow. Machine learning algorithms use the data to provide information on more than 100 health parameters.<br/>
<br/>
NuraLogix says that the MagicMirror can provide health information that includes blood pressure, BMI, heart rate variability, pulse rate, breathing rate, and facial skin age. It can provide risk assessments for diabetes, cardiovascular disease, stroke, hypertension, fatty liver disease, and more, plus it offers assessments of mental stress and depression risk.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/anura-magic-mirror.jpg" alt="" width="609" height="587" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929694" /><br/>
More information on the MagicMirror can be <a href="https://www.nuralogix.ai/magic-mirror/">found on the NuraLogix website</a>. The company has not provided a launch date or a price, but the device appears to be aimed at clinic waiting rooms, retirement homes, and other health-related facilities.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-anura-magicmirror/">CES 2024: This &#039;MagicMirror&#039; Analyzes Facial Blood Flow to Monitor Vital Signs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-this-magicmirror-analyzes-facial-blood-flow-to-monitor-vital-signs.2415810/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Invoxia Launches AI Wearable That Monitors Your Pet&#039;s Health</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-invoxia-minitailz/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-invoxia-launches-ai-wearable-that-monitors-your-pets-health.2415808/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 15:42:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-invoxia-minitailz/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://petcare.invoxia.com/">Invoxia</a> at CES unveiled the Minitailz Smart Pet Tracker, an AI wearable that's designed for dogs and cats. The Minitailz is an all-in-one GPS tracker and wellness device for pets, and it is able to measure respiratory rate and heart vitals, alerting owners about possible health issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/invoxia-minitailz.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929690" /><br/>
Invoxia says that the Minitailz is able to watch for anomalies in pet behavior that can be indicative of a problem, and it can differentiate between walking, running, scratching, eating and drinking, barking, and rest.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to collecting heart health information that is said to be 97 to 99 percent accurate, the Minitailz can detect atrial fibrillation in pets. Detailed health reports are provided in the accompanying app.<br/>
<br/>
A built-in SIM with GPS technology allows for tracking of daily activities or locating a pet should it be lost. There are also geofencing features so that a pet owner can be alerted if a pet wanders outside the boundaries of a property.<br/>
<br/>
The Minitailz measures in at 2.32 inches long, 1.18 inches tall, and 0.9 inches thick, and it can be attached to an existing dog or cat collar.<br/>
<br/>
A dog version of the Minitailz is available as of now <a href="https://petcare.invoxia.com/">from the Invoxia website</a>, with the cat model set to launch in March 2024. Both versions are priced at &#36;99, with a subscription fee that starts at &#36;8.30 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-invoxia-minitailz/">CES 2024: Invoxia Launches AI Wearable That Monitors Your Pet&#039;s Health</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-invoxia-launches-ai-wearable-that-monitors-your-pets-health.2415808/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Survives 16,000 Foot Drop After Alaska Airlines Plane Incident</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/iphone-survives-fall-from-plane/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-survives-16-000-foot-drop-after-alaska-airlines-plane-incident.2415799/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:01:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/iphone-survives-fall-from-plane/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that was expelled from the cabin of Alaska Airlines flight 1282 on Friday survived a fall of more than 16,000 feet and was discovered intact.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/recovered-alaska-phone.jpg" alt="" width="1153" height="648" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929685" /><br/>
Vancouver, Washington resident Sean Bates shared images of the device on Sunday after he found it on the side of Barnes Road in Portland, Oregon. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was in full working condition and was in fact still open to an Alaska Airlines email. There were no cracks on the display, though it was protected by a case and presumably landed in a forested area with soft ground cover.<br/>
<br/>
Bates alerted the National Transportation Safety Board, and officials came out to collect the device. The NTSB told Bates that it was the second phone to be found from the flight in the area.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Found an iPhone on the side of the road... Still in airplane mode with half a battery and open to a baggage claim for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AlaskaAirlines?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AlaskaAirlines</a> ASA1282 Survived a 16,000 foot drop perfectly in tact!<br><br>When I called it in, Zoe at <a href="https://twitter.com/NTSB?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@NTSB</a> said it was the SECOND phone to be found. No door yet&#x1f605; <a href="https://t.co/CObMikpuFd">pic.twitter.com/CObMikpuFd</a></p>&mdash; Seanathan Bates (@SeanSafyre) <a href="https://twitter.com/SeanSafyre/status/1744138937239822685?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 7, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was <a href="https://news.alaskaair.com/alaska-airlines/operations/as-1282/?linkId=100000234605102">expelled from Alaska Airlines flight 1282</a> after a portion of the plane blew out shortly after it took off from the Portland International Airport. The aircraft was able to safely land back at the Portland airport, and all passengers and crew members survived.<br/>
<br/>
The sudden depressurization in the cabin of the plane caused items like smartphones to be sucked out, where they fell to the ground below. In 2011, <em>Wired</em> <a href="https://www.wired.com/2011/04/what-is-the-terminal-velocity-of-an-iphone/">wrote a piece</a> on the terminal velocity of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; falling from a plane, which is a good explainer how the device was able to survive. In a nutshell, the low weight and maximum speed of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; leads to a limited amount of force on landing despite the height of the fall, so the end result isn't too much different from dropping it from a lower height.<br/>
<br/>
There were two smartphones found from the plane, along with other debris such as the plug door that may give some insight into what went wrong.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/iphone-survives-fall-from-plane/">iPhone Survives 16,000 Foot Drop After Alaska Airlines Plane Incident</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-survives-16-000-foot-drop-after-alaska-airlines-plane-incident.2415799/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Versions of TestFlight and Xcode With Vision Pro Support, Starts Accepting visionOS Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-releases-vision-pro-updates-testflight-xcode/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-versions-of-testflight-and-xcode-with-vision-pro-support-starts-accepting-visionos-apps.2415797/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:37:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-releases-vision-pro-updates-testflight-xcode/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TestFlight</category>
		<category>Xcode</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released Xcode 15.2 and <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/releases/?id=01082024a">TestFlight version 3.5</a>, both of which have been updated with support for the Vision Pro headset that is set to come out in early February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/testflight-icon.jpg" alt="" width="1117" height="629" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927373" /><br/>
Xcode 15.2 is equipped with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> SDK, and <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/xcode-release-notes/xcode-15_2-release-notes">the release notes</a> suggest that Apple has implemented several fixes for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; into the software. Xcode 15.2 can be used by developers to create &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; apps for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset, and it also includes SDKs for iOS 17.2, iPadOS 17.2, tvOS 17.2, watchOS 10.2, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2.<br/>
<br/>
As for TestFlight, version 3.5 of the app allows for the beta testing of &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; apps for the first time, plus it allows compatible iOS and iPadOS apps to be used on the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; headset.<br/>
<br/>
Apps created for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; can be submitted to the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> starting today. Many <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> apps will work on &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; unmodified, but developers can make device-specific tweaks. Apple plans to publish &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps on the Vision Pro store by default, but developers can opt out through &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Connect.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro headset will launch on Friday, February 2 at retail stores in the United States. Pre-orders for the device will be accepted starting on Friday, January 19 at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/testflight/">TestFlight</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/xcode/">Xcode</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-releases-vision-pro-updates-testflight-xcode/">Apple Releases New Versions of TestFlight and Xcode With Vision Pro Support, Starts Accepting visionOS Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-versions-of-testflight-and-xcode-with-vision-pro-support-starts-accepting-visionos-apps.2415797/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Opening New Store in Korea, Special Wallpaper Available Now</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-store-hongdae-special-wallpaper/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-opening-new-store-in-korea-special-wallpaper-available-now.2415794/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:55:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-store-hongdae-special-wallpaper/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has announced that it will be opening a new retail store in the Hongdae neighborhood of Seoul, South Korea on Saturday, January 20 at 10 a.m. local time. To celebrate the occasion, Apple has released a special wallpaper for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac that can be downloaded for free by <a href="https://www.apple.com/kr/retail/hongdae/">visiting the store's page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Hongdae-Wallpaper.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929661" /><br/>
The wallpaper features an Apple logo in a colorful graffiti style, symbolizing the Hongdae area's artistic and youthful culture. As noted by Michael Steeber <a href="https://michaelsteeber.substack.com/p/a-true-mini-store">in his Tabletops newsletter</a>, the logo has "홍대" (Hongdae) hidden within it.<br/>
<br/>
The store will be located at 140 Yanghwa-ro, near Hongik University, and it will offer Genius Bar appointments and Today at Apple creative sessions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Hongdae.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1390" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929674" /><br/>
January 20 is also the day that Apple will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apples-infinite-loop-store-closing-next-month/">permanently closing its Infinite Loop and Royal Hawaiian stores</a> in the United States.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-store-hongdae-special-wallpaper/">Apple Opening New Store in Korea, Special Wallpaper Available Now</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-opening-new-store-in-korea-special-wallpaper-available-now.2415794/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Second Payment Emails for Refurbished Apple Device Class Action Lawsuit Going Out Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-refurbished-lawsuit-payments-january-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/second-payment-emails-for-refurbished-apple-device-class-action-lawsuit-going-out-tomorrow.2415789/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:27:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-refurbished-lawsuit-payments-january-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>AppleCare</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A second wave of Apple customers eligible for a payment under a &#36;95 million <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/25/apple-class-action-refurbished-lawsuit-payments/">Apple refurbished device lawsuit</a> are today receiving emails letting them know that the funds will be sent out starting tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/applerefurbishedgoodastwo-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2688" height="1512" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834223" /><blockquote>As Settlement Administrator for the matter, we're sending you this courtesy email to inform you that by January 9, 2024, you will receive a payment notification email that contains a link to claim your payment electronically. Once you receive that email, you will have until May 15, 2024, to claim your payment.</blockquote>Back in 2021, Apple agreed to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/10/04/apple-refurbished-lawsuit-settlement/">pay &#36;95 million</a> to settle an AppleCare-related lawsuit that accused the company of violating U.S. law by providing customers with refurbished replacement devices instead of new devices when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> repairs were required.<br/>
<br/>
The settlement was approved in April 2022, and Apple sent out some payments <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/25/apple-class-action-refurbished-lawsuit-payments/">starting in August 2022</a>, but a new wave of emails went out to customers today. The lawsuit covered iPhones and iPads purchased between July 20, 2012 and September, 30, 2021 and replaced with a refurbished device.<br/>
<br/>
A second wave of payments that are being sent out to disburse remaining funds after the first payments were received. Only 31 percent of those eligible claimed the first payment, leaving money for a second payment. <br/>
<br/>
While Apple paid &#36;95 million to settle the lawsuit, the company admitted no wrongdoing and has denied that refurbished devices are inferior to new devices.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-refurbished-lawsuit-payments-january-2024/">Second Payment Emails for Refurbished Apple Device Class Action Lawsuit Going Out Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/second-payment-emails-for-refurbished-apple-device-class-action-lawsuit-going-out-tomorrow.2415789/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Offering Vision Pro Demos Starting on February 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-demos-february-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offering-vision-pro-demos-starting-on-february-2.2415787/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:59:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-demos-february-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to start offering Vision Pro demonstrations at U.S. Apple retail stores on Friday, February 2, Apple said today in emails that are going out to select customers. February 2 is the official launch date of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929475" /><br/>
The demo sessions will be available at Apple retail stores in the United States. Apple says that demo times will be offered through the weekend on a first-come, first-served basis, with signups to take place starting at 8:00 a.m. on February 2.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">New information regarding Apple Vision Pro demos at Apple Stores<br><br>“Be one of the first to get a demo of Apple Vision Pro. Only at the Apple Store. Starting at 8:00 a.m. on Friday, February 2, we invite you to sign up for a demo of Apple Vision Pro at your local Apple Store. Demo… <a href="https://t.co/tPzgBWwcUK">pic.twitter.com/tPzgBWwcUK</a></p>&mdash; M1 (@M1Astra) <a href="https://twitter.com/M1Astra/status/1744429033171951846?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 8, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
It is likely that the available demo spots will fill up quickly, especially in areas with a limited number of Apple Stores, so those interested in testing the headset should plan to sign up early.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to begin accepting pre-orders for the Vision Pro on Friday, January 19, with deliveries on February 2. The headset will be available in all U.S. Apple locations on February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-demos-february-2/">Apple Offering Vision Pro Demos Starting on February 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offering-vision-pro-demos-starting-on-february-2.2415787/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024 Day 1: What&#039;s New From Samsung and CES Unveiled</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-day-1-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-day-1-whats-new-from-samsung-and-ces-unveiled.2415785/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:50:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-day-1-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The annual CES event kicks off this week, and we sent <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera to hunt down cool new products and technologies that are being previewed this year. CES officially starts tomorrow, but Dan attended CES Unveiled last night, and was able to get an early look at devices from Samsung,<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="CES 2024: Insane New Tech from Samsung &amp; CES Unveiled!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x8TuG7Or5y8" width="1673" height="807" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Samsung showed off new OLED TVs with an updated anti-reflective coating that makes them much better in bright rooms and with reflective lights, plus there was a new 8K projector and some very impressive transparent OLED screens.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung had a neat 2D/3D display that uses cameras and eye tracking to display content in 3D without the need for glasses, and Dan was also impressed with a customizable music frame that holds artwork but also serves as a speaker for a subtle surround sound system.<br/>
<br/>
At Unveiled, Dan checked out a pet-focused robot vacuum and mop combo from Narwhal, Belkin's Qi2 wireless chargers and StandDock Pro, a Keurig sort of device for ice cream, and some retro Mac power adapters from Sharge.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch the full video to see the products in action, and stay tuned to <em>MacRumors</em> because we'll be sharing CES videos and articles for the next few days.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-day-1-recap/">CES 2024 Day 1: What&#039;s New From Samsung and CES Unveiled</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-day-1-whats-new-from-samsung-and-ces-unveiled.2415785/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Shazam Shares 2024 Popular Song Predictions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/shazam-shares-2024-popular-song-predictions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/shazam-shares-2024-popular-song-predictions.2415783/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:48:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/shazam-shares-2024-popular-song-predictions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Shazam</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Shazam, Apple's music discovery and identification platform, today shared a <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/shazam-predictions-2024/pl.ecd57f2f9d404ad5a94fbef3a629e247">Shazam Predictions 2024 playlist</a>, available on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>. The playlist provides songs from more than 50 artists that are set to "have a breakthrough year."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/2024-shazam-predictions.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="606" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929615" /><br/>
The predictions playlist is an annual release from Shazam, and the 2024 list includes everything from French pop to contemporary gospel, with content from creators in 21 countries.<blockquote>Have you ever scanned your Shazam history and spotted a big star-someone you discovered months or years before they became a household name? Every day, the app gets millions of requests from users around the world who are curious about the artist behind a song. These Shazams come from all over-TikTok videos, car commercials, coffee shops, overhearing something in the wild-which makes it a powerful tool for predicting tomorrow's heavy hitters. This playlist features 50 emerging artists who, based on Shazam data reviewed by our editors, are poised to have a breakthrough year.</blockquote>Shazam highlighted five artists to keep a close eye on, including Nigerian singer-songwriter Bloody Civilian, hip-hop duo Flyana Boss, South African singer Kenya Grace, indie rock band The Last Dinner Party, and K-pop group RIIZE.<br/>
<br/>
The full playlist can be <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/shazam-predictions-2024/pl.ecd57f2f9d404ad5a94fbef3a629e247">listened to on Apple Music</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shazam/">Shazam</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/shazam-shares-2024-popular-song-predictions/">Shazam Shares 2024 Popular Song Predictions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/shazam-shares-2024-popular-song-predictions.2415783/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Clear&#039; To-Do App Gets Total Design Overhaul and New Feature Set</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/clear-to-do-app-revamp/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/clear-to-do-app-gets-total-design-overhaul-and-new-feature-set.2415775/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 08:56:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/clear-to-do-app-revamp/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Clear is a to-do list app that was first launched in 2012, and while it has received few updates since that time, it has remained popular with users due to its easy-to-use design and simple layout.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_Xw2dVlXzfE" title="Clear: It Had to Be You" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Impending, the team behind Clear, has been working on a major revamp for the last several months, and Clear 2 is launching today. Clear 2 has the same general design and function as the original app, but there are new gestures for more fluid list making, new color themes, an edge-to-edge design, updated fonts, quote packs, sound themes, app icon options, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Creating and managing lists in Clear has not changed. Tap anywhere to add an item to a list, and swipe to either check it off or delete it. A tap at the bottom of the app goes to a list overview, and a second bottom tap leads to personalization options, rewards, the shop, and an archive of completed items.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/clear-app-night-theme.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1200" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929051" /><br/>
Users can have an unlimited number of lists and items on the list, and the simple design of the app puts the focus on what's upcoming. Items on the list can be dragged and dropped between lists, and a swipe and hold to the left allows a time and a date to be added. Screenshotting a list brings up a share sheet so you can share a text or image version of the contents with a friend.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/clear-scene-beach.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="1310" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929052" /><br/>
As with the original version of Clear, using the app unlocks collectibles like unique colors for lists, and just using the app will provide users with new themes and fonts to choose from. There are also haptics and sounds when checking items off, adding new items to the list, and using other app features.<br/>
<br/>
Clear is no longer a paid app and it is free to use, and Impending has a clever monetization strategy. There is an entirely optional store with themes, fonts, sound packs, and app icons that change on a daily basis. The cosmetic options available for purchase do not affect the core functionality of the app, but do offer unique customization options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/clear-scene-ipod.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="1310" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929053" /><br/>
Clear 2 can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for free, and those who have the existing version of Clear will get the update without having to redownload the app. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/clear-todos/id493136154">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/clear-to-do-app-revamp/">&#039;Clear&#039; To-Do App Gets Total Design Overhaul and New Feature Set</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/clear-to-do-app-gets-total-design-overhaul-and-new-feature-set.2415775/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Battery Supports Up to 2.5 Hours of 2D Video Playback</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-battery-life-video-playback/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-battery-supports-up-to-2-5-hours-of-2d-video-playback.2415765/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:51:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-battery-life-video-playback/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Under cover of its Vision Pro headset launch date <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">announcement</a>, Apple has revealed that the external battery supports up to 2.5 hours of 2D video playback, half an hour more than it offers in "general use" on a single charge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-battery-pack.jpg" alt="" width="1640" height="1060" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929544" /><br/>
Apple quietly updated its <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-vision-pro/">product page</a> for the device with the extra detail, qualifying its claim of 2.5 hours of "video playback" based on tests "in conjunction with an Environment, using 2D movie content purchased from the Apple TV app." Environments let users transform the space around them, and Cinema Environments can turn a room into a personal movie theater.<br/>
<br/>
The company defines "general use" as performing tasks that include video playback, internet browsing, spatial video capture, and FaceTime. <br/>
<br/>
This is the first time Apple has said anything about the Vision Pro's external battery pack being optimized to run for longer when watching 2D video content, with Apple previously saying only that the battery lasted two hours on a single charge. Apple also previously said the Vision Pro could be used indefinitely if the battery was itself plugged into an external power source, but that text has been removed from the Vision Pro product page.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says Vision Pro users will be able to watch movies and TV shows from Apple TV+, Disney+, Max, and other services on a screen that feels 100 feet wide with support for HDR content. Elsewhere, within the Apple TV app, users will be able to access more than 150 3D titles.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders of the Vision Pro start on Friday, January 19 and the device goes on sale in the United States on Friday, February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-vision-pro-battery-life-video-playback/">Apple Vision Pro Battery Supports Up to 2.5 Hours of 2D Video Playback</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-battery-supports-up-to-2-5-hours-of-2d-video-playback.2415765/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Hold February 1 Earnings Call Just Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-1-earnings-call/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-hold-february-1-earnings-call-just-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2415764/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:41:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-1-earnings-call/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has announced that its first earnings call of 2024 <a href="https://investor.apple.com/investor-relations/default.aspx">will be held on February 1</a>, one day before the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">Vision Pro launches in the United States</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
On the call, Apple's CEO Tim Cook and CFO Luca Maestri will discuss the company's earnings results for the first quarter of the 2024 fiscal year. The executives will almost certainly provide some additional commentary about the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
A live audio stream of the call will be available on Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">Investor Relations page</a>, and a recording will be available later in the day for replay.<br/>
<br/>
The quarter ran from October 1 through December 30 of 2023. During this period, Apple released new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with the M3 series of chips, updated the iMac with the M3 chip, and debuted a lower-cost Apple Pencil with a USB-C port. Apple also expanded its online store to Chile during the quarter.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not provided formal guidance since early 2020, but analysts expect the company to report quarterly revenue of around &#36;117.8 billion on average, according to <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/AAPL/analysis?p=AAPL">Yahoo Finance</a>. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/02/apple-1q-2023-earnings/">reported &#36;117.2 billion revenue</a> in the year-ago quarter.<br/>
<br/>
AAPL closed at &#36;181.18 on Friday, down from a 52-week high of &#36;199.62.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-1-earnings-call/">Apple to Hold February 1 Earnings Call Just Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-hold-february-1-earnings-call-just-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2415764/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker&#039;s New Year Sale Has Discounts on USB-C Accessories, Portable Batteries, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ankers-new-year-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-new-year-sale-has-discounts-on-usb-c-accessories-portable-batteries-and-more.2415763/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:38:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ankers-new-year-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anker has kicked off its first big sale of the year, and it's happening across <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725533960">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fnew-year-sale%3Fref%3DmasterBanner1">Anker's own website</a>. You'll find low prices on portable batteries, USB-C chargers, and more in this sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/anker-january-image.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929507" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should note that some Amazon deals require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the discounts. At Anker.com, you'll find discount codes are also required, but these should be automatically applied once you add the products to your cart and head to checkout.<br/>
<br/>
On Amazon, the highlight is the 60,000 mAh portable power station for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725533960"><strong>&#36;114.99</strong></a> with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;169.99. If you're looking for a smaller portable battery, there's the 10,000 mAh Nano Power Bank with built-in USB-C cable for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725552056"><strong>&#36;44.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;49.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725533960"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;55 OFF</div>Anker Power Station for &#36;114.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker has a few deals of its own, and some match Amazon's prices. You can get the Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1336-20000mah-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D42691854925974%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023"><strong>&#36;117.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.99. Another notable accessory is the Prime 6-in-1 Charging Station for <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa9128-6-in-1-charging-station%3Fvariant%3D42691854336150%26ref%3Dhappy-new-year-2023"><strong>&#36;89.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;109.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fnew-year-sale%3Fref%3DmasterBanner1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 50% OFF</div>Anker New Year's Sale</div></a></div><h2>Portable Batteries</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XLDLJZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1IAOLW25WS1A7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1IAOLW25WS1A7_1704726043162">Nano Portable Charger with Built-In USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;18.89, down from &#36;22.49</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV5JRCYB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2JZA193S9HC09%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2JZA193S9HC09_1704728017719">Nano Portable Charger with Built-In Lightning Connector</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;22.49</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725913103">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;44.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725956687">Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;114.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;169.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Generator-UltraFast-Optional%2Fdp%2FB0C5C89QKZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;699.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Wall Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Foldable-MacBook%2Fdp%2FB09C5RG6KV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;55.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;44.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;12.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ankers-new-year-sale/">Anker&#039;s New Year Sale Has Discounts on USB-C Accessories, Portable Batteries, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-new-year-sale-has-discounts-on-usb-c-accessories-portable-batteries-and-more.2415763/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro ZEISS Lens Inserts to Start at &#36;99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-zeiss-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99.2415758/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:27:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">announcement</a> of the launch date for its Vision Pro headset earlier today, Apple revealed that the optional optical inserts will begin at &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-lenses.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898584" /><br/>
Because of the way the headset fits against the face, it does not accommodate glasses, but Apple has a solution for those who need reading or prescription lenses. Apple is partnering with ZEISS to offer optical inserts that can be customized to each person's vision requirements. <br/>
<br/>
Apple will offer two versions of the ZEISS Optical Inserts at different price points. "ZEISS Optical Inserts — Readers" will be available for &#36;99, while "ZEISS Optical Inserts — Prescription" will be available for &#36;149. The inserts will attach to the Vision Pro lenses magnetically, allowing for precise viewing and eye tracking.<br/>
<br/>
Glasses wearers will need a valid prescription to get the inserts, and not all prescriptions will be supported, so there will be some limitations that might prevent some people from using the headset.<br/>
<br/>
The inserts are the only optional purchase directly for the Vision Pro headset that Apple has announced so far. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band/">Vision Pro headset comes with</a> a Solo Knit Band, a Dual Loop Band, a Light Seal, two Light Seal Cushions, a cover for the front of the device, a polishing cloth, battery unit, USB-C charging cable, and USB-C power adapter. <br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders of the Vision Pro start on Friday, January 19 and the device goes on sale in the United States on Friday, February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99/">Apple Vision Pro ZEISS Lens Inserts to Start at &#36;99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-zeiss-lens-inserts-to-start-at-99.2415758/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Ships With Dual Loop Band and More, Starts With 256GB of Storage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band-and-more-starts-with-256gb-of-storage.2415755/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:21:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that its Vision Pro headset will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launch in the U.S. on February 2</a>, with pre-orders starting January 19. In its press release, Apple listed some items that will be included with the Vision Pro, including a Dual Loop Band, an Apple Polishing Cloth, an external battery pack, a USB-C power adapter, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929475" /><br/>
Here's everything included with the Vision Pro:<blockquote>Apple Vision Pro comes with a Solo Knit Band and Dual Loop Band — giving users two options for the fit that works best for them. Apple Vision Pro also includes a Light Seal, two Light Seal Cushions, an Apple Vision Pro Cover for the front of the device, Polishing Cloth, Battery, USB-C Charge Cable, and USB-C Power Adapter.</blockquote>On the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro product page</a>, Apple says the Dual Loop Band features "a pair of adjustable upper and lower straps for a personalized fit."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band.jpeg" alt="" width="1640" height="1060" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929483" /><br/>
Apple also confirmed that the Vision Pro starts with 256GB of storage for &#36;3,499, and higher storage capacities will likely be available.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band/">Apple Vision Pro Ships With Dual Loop Band and More, Starts With 256GB of Storage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-ships-with-dual-loop-band-and-more-starts-with-256gb-of-storage.2415755/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces February 2 Launch Date for Vision Pro Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-february-2-launch-date-for-vision-pro-headset.2415753/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:03:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Major News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-vision-pro-available-in-the-us-on-february-2/">announced</a> that the Vision Pro headset will launch in the United States on Friday, February 2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
The headset will be available at all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> locations in the United States, as well as via the online &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj;. Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> today said: <blockquote>The era of spatial computing has arrived. Apple Vision Pro is the most advanced consumer electronics device ever created. Its revolutionary and magical user interface will redefine how we connect, create, and explore.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the Vision Pro is "a revolutionary spatial computer that transforms how people work, collaborate, connect, relive memories, and enjoy entertainment."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="615" height="1093" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/mFvSGXXGn8k" title="Apple Vision Pro Available February 2nd! #visionpro #apple #shorts" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Vision Pro is set to be available starting at &#36;3,499 with 256GB of storage. Pre-orders begin two weeks prior to launch, opening on Friday, January 19 at 5 a.m. PST.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">Apple Announces February 2 Launch Date for Vision Pro Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-february-2-launch-date-for-vision-pro-headset.2415753/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Chipolo Launches &#039;Perfectly Imperfect&#039; Find My Wallet Trackers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-chipolo-card-spot/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-chipolo-launches-perfectly-imperfect-find-my-wallet-trackers.2415752/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-chipolo-card-spot/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Chipolo</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://chipolo.net/en-us/">Chipolo</a> today announced the launch of a series of "Perfectly Imperfect" CARD Spot wallet trackers, which are identical to its standard Chipolo CARD Spot trackers, but with flaws in the plastic casing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/chipolo-card-spot.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1333" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929073" /><br/>
This limited edition series takes advantage of plastic that would otherwise have been discarded and wasted. The item trackers have a blemish on one side and a "Perfectly Imperfect" engraving on the other side.<blockquote>"Chipolo is excited to introduce the 'Perfectly Imperfect' limited series of CARD Spot trackers, as it's another testament to our dedication to create products that make our lives easier -- both physically, through functionality and mentally, by helping to bring people peace of mind", said Primož Zelenšek, Co-founder and CEO at Chipolo. "Through this campaign, we want to inspire a shift in perspective, encouraging people to embrace their imperfections and recognize the real beauty in what makes each of us irreplaceable."</blockquote>The Chipolo CARD Spot is designed to fit inside a wallet, and it works with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> network. The CARD Spot can be tracked right alongside Apple devices and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> in the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
Chipolo plans to donate &#36;1 to a non-profit organization for each of the CARD Spots that are sold, and each one is <a href="https://chipolo.net/en-us/">priced at &#36;35</a>, the same as the standard CARD Spots. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chipolo/">Chipolo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-chipolo-card-spot/">CES 2024: Chipolo Launches &#039;Perfectly Imperfect&#039; Find My Wallet Trackers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-chipolo-launches-perfectly-imperfect-find-my-wallet-trackers.2415752/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Samsung Unveils Refreshed iMac-Style 32-Inch 4K Smart Monitor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/samsung-smart-monitor-4k-refresh/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-samsung-unveils-refreshed-imac-style-32-inch-4k-smart-monitor.2415750/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:23:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/samsung-smart-monitor-4k-refresh/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung at CES has announced its popular Smart Monitor M8 is getting a refresh for 2024, with some extra software features seemingly aimed at deepening the display's support for other devices in the company's ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Samsung-Smart-Monitor-M80D.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929427" /><br/>
The upcoming "M80D" model includes a Multi Control feature that allows images and text to be moved between the display and a Galaxy Book, Tablet, or Phone, while a Galaxy Buds owners will be able to pair their earphones for a spatial audio experience with head tracking.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung says it has also added the ability to pair a Galaxy Watch for those looking to perform guided workouts using the display, and an easier way to control monitor settings with the click of a mouse, where previous models only allowed for adjustments via a remote.<br/>
<br/>
Otherwise, it looks like the iMac-style 4K flat-panel monitor hasn't changed in the hardware department from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/24/samsung-smart-monitor-m8-2023-update/">last year's M8 model</a>, which features 400 nits of brightness, a 60Hz refresh rate (non variable), 99% sRGB, and adaptive picture technology.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, the display retains key features like USB-C charging connectivity, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> 2 support, an integrated webcam, and several smart TV features that enable it to be used when not connected to a PC. <br/>
<br/>
Samsung's M8 doesn't support the P3 color gamut and isn't as bright as Apple's 5K Studio Display, but as a more affordable alternative it is likely remain appealing to some Mac users.<br/>
<br/>
The original M8 comes in 27-inch (~&#36;650) and 32-inch (~&#36;700) sizes, although Samsung only mentioned a 32-inch version of the M80D. Regardless, both sizes have a 11.39mm thick chassis, which is 0.1mm thinner than Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, and include a flat back, thin bezels, and a height and tilt adjustable stand. Expect Samsung's refreshed monitor to arrive in sometime later in the year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/samsung-smart-monitor-4k-refresh/">CES 2024: Samsung Unveils Refreshed iMac-Style 32-Inch 4K Smart Monitor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-samsung-unveils-refreshed-imac-style-32-inch-4k-smart-monitor.2415750/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
