<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 03:02:22 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>22 Tips to Make Your iPhone 16&#039;s Battery Last Longer</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-battery-saving-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/22-tips-to-make-your-iphone-16s-battery-last-longer.2440441/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:28:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-battery-saving-tips&#038;post_date=1729301291/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When Apple releases new iPhones and new operating system updates, there are often complaints about how long the battery lasts. Apple made <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/iphone-16-battery-comparison/">improvements to battery life</a> across the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, and while these iPhones last longer than ever, some people are <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/1fp6cjl/iphone_16_pro_max_not_lasting_long/">still seeing battery issues</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iPhone-16-Battery-Life-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971681" /><br/>
Battery life problems can be caused by new features Apple has added or bugs that have yet to be addressed. Whatever the cause, we've created a list of suggestions for maximizing your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s battery life. There aren't many battery saving options that don't disable key features on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but in situations where every minute counts, it's useful to have options.<br/>
<br/>
You'll need to balance battery drain with the feature set you want enabled, turning things on and off when you need to ensure your battery lasts all day. Not all of these tips are specific to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, but they will help you preserve battery whether you have an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; or an older device.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="1._turn_off_iphone_mirroring">1. Turn Off iPhone Mirroring</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring allows you to control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac, and get your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications on your Mac's display. Since it's on Mac, it seems like it shouldn't be using &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery, but there is a connection there to relay notifications. Notifications still show up when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app is closed on the Mac, so that constant connection might impact battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
<a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-battery-life-thread.2428672/post-33478422">One reader</a> experiencing battery life issues on the <em>MacRumors</em> forums said turning off &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring made a notable difference. If you're not often using this option, it's worth turning it off.<br/>
<br/>
To disable it, go to Settings > General > <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> and Continuity and tap on Edit. From there, delete the Macs that your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; connects to. You can also swipe to delete a Mac from the list.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2._delete_home_screen_and_lock_screen_widgets">2. Delete Home Screen and Lock Screen Widgets</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, Apple made it so you can place app icons and widgets anywhere on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s hidden grid, so you might be using widgets more often than before. If that's the case, it's worth noting that widgets can have an impact on battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-892127" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/iOS-17-Widgets.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
If you're not using a particular widget on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or Lock Screen regularly, it might be best to remove it to preserve battery life. On the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;, you can long press and tap the "-" button to remove a widget.<br/>
<br/>
On the Lock Screen, you can actually set up several different Lock Screen options, so you could create one that has widgets and one that doesn't, using the latter when you're low on battery. To add or edit Lock Screens, long press on the Lock Screen and choose either the "Customize" or the "+" button.<br/>
<br/>
On the <em>MacRumors</em> forums, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-battery-life-thread.2428672/post-33469207">one user said</a> turning off Lock Screen widgets dropped overnight battery usage from 20 percent to 10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="3._use_dark_mode_and_dark_mode_icons">3. Use Dark Mode and Dark Mode Icons</h2><br/>
Turning on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a> has long been a suggested way to preserve battery life, because OLED displays draw less power when displaying darker colored pixels. A <a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3458864.3467682">2021 Purdue study</a> found that using &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; on a sunny day outside can save you up 47 percent battery power, which can make a major difference.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-dark-mode-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956931" /><br/>
Lower levels of brightness in Light Mode use the same battery as higher levels of brightness in &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj;, which explains why &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; can save battery even when screen brightness is turned up. When your screen brightness is lower, such as when you're in a dim room, swapping to &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; doesn't save as much battery life, but it still draws a little less power.<br/>
<br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can set a Dark option for your icons that turns them darker when &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; is enabled (or all the time, if you prefer). Dark icons are easier on the eyes when &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; is on, and it might save just a little extra battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="4._be_mindful_of_control_center_controls">4. Be Mindful of Control Center Controls</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; has a customizable Control Center where you can use the Controls Gallery to choose your controls, including third-party controls. You can change the size of Control Center toggles, and use multiple pages.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-control-center-icon-update.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960815" /><br/>
Some Control Center toggles are animated, and animations can have an effect on battery life. It's probably not a major impact, but worth knowing about. One of the bigger offenders is the full-size Music Control Center toggle, which shows album art and has playback controls.<br/>
<br/>
Home app controls also need to update whenever the Control Center updates, and these controls that refresh might drain some battery.<br/>
<br/>
Customize Control Center by long pressing on the display and tapping the "-" button by any controls you want to remove.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="5._remove_your_lock_screen_controls">5. Remove Your Lock Screen Controls</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can finally swap out or remove the Camera and Flashlight buttons on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. If you've ever accidentally activated one of those buttons while your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s in your pocket, you know that leaving on the Flashlight or the Camera for an extended period can definitely impact battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-lock-screen-buttons.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954622" /><br/>
If you're prone to hitting those buttons, it's worth removing them. You can do so by long pressing on the Lock Screen, tapping on Customize, and then tapping the "-" button next to the icons.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="6._turn_off_promotion_display">6. Turn Off ProMotion Display</h2><br/>
If you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> or another "Pro" &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that supports a 120Hz ProMotion refresh rate, turning it down to 60Hz might extend your battery life. Since Low Power Mode limits the display refresh rate to 60Hz, it's definitely a measure that works to preserve battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iphone-14-pro-120hz-promotion-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1948" height="1090" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816525" /><br/>
Turning on Low Power Mode is one way to disable ProMotion, but there's a more permanent Accessibility setting. Open the Settings app, go to Accessibility, tap on Motion, and then toggle on "Limit Frame Rate."<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="7._disable_live_activities">7. Disable Live Activities</h2><br/>
Live Activities let apps keep an ongoing notification on the Lock Screen or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>. Combined with the Always-On display of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro, 15 Pro, and 16 Pro, Live Activities can drain your battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849710" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/ios-16-live-activities-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Live Activities can be turned off by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Go to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> &amp; Passcode.</li><br/>
 <li>Enter your passcode to unlock the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>Scroll down and toggle off Live Activities.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
This will prevent Live Activities from showing up on the Lock Screen, but you'll want to take this one step further. In the individual app sections in the Settings app, you can disable Live Activities on an app-by-app basis, or avoid using Live Activities features within apps.<br/>
<br/>
You can't fully disable the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;, but you can swipe left on any running animation to dismiss it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="8._turn_off_proximity_airdrop_sharing">8. Turn Off Proximity AirDrop Sharing</h2><br/>
When you hold two iPhones running iOS 17 or later together, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; initiates a proximity-based AirDrop or contact transfer protocol. If you're continually triggering this, it can drain battery. Should you find yourself in a situation where your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is near another &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; often enough that AirDrop continually pops up, you might want to turn it off.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905665" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/airdrop-proximity-sharing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1327" /><br/>
To do so, go to Settings > General > AirDrop and toggle off "Bringing Devices Together."<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="9._take_advantage_of_offline_maps">9. Take Advantage of Offline Maps</h2><br/>
Since iOS 17, you've been able to download <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> for offline usage. It's useful for when you don't have a cellular connection, but it can save battery even if you do. If you're traveling in an area where you have a somewhat spotty connection, downloading a map for that spot and then turning off cellular will preserve your battery life without impacting your ability to get turn-by-turn directions.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899235" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Maps-Offline.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
<br/>
We have a dedicated how-to that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/download-offline-maps-ios-apple-maps/">walks you through downloading a map for offline usage</a>, but it's as simple as searching for a location in Maps, tapping the download button, and then selecting the area of the map to download.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="10._disable_haptic_keyboard_feedback">10. Disable Haptic Keyboard Feedback</h2><br/>
Apple has a keyboard option that gives you haptic feedback when you tap the on-screen keys. It vibrates with each key tap for a more satisfying typing experience, but what you might not know is that it drains battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872406" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/haptic-keyboard-feedback.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1961" /><br/>
Apple has a support document that says keyboard haptics can affect battery life, so it's not something you want to use when you don't have battery to spare. It's not on by default, but if you've enabled it, you can turn it off by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Sounds &amp; Haptics.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Keyboard Feedback.</li><br/>
 <li>Toggle off Haptic.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
<h2 id="11._turn_off_always-on_display">11. Turn Off Always-On Display</h2><br/>
As the name suggests, the Always-On display on some Pro &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models leaves the time, your wallpaper, widgets, and Live Activities visible on the Lock Screen even when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864733" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/turn-off-always-on-display.jpg" alt="settings" width="640" height="408" /><br/>
The display uses a 1Hz refresh rate to preserve battery, and Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/15/apple-details-iphone-14-pro-always-on-display/">has neat tricks</a> like turning off the display when a connected Apple Watch is no longer nearby (signaling that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; owner is out of the room) or the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in a pocket, but Always-On display still drains battery faster than an Always-Off display.<br/>
<br/>
You can turn off the Always-On display by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Display &amp; Brightness.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Always On Display.</li><br/>
 <li>Toggle off Always On Display.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Just how much battery Always-On display drains will depend on your use case, so it may or may not be worth turning off.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="12._use_focus_modes">12. Use Focus Modes</h2><br/>
Using Apple's built-in Focus option can cut down on the number of notifications that you're receiving during the day, and fewer notifications means less opportunity for apps to wake up your display and cause battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-focus-mode-changes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960224" /><br/>
Focus modes let you choose which apps and people can send you notifications and when, so during work hours you can make sure you're only getting work notifications, and during personal time, you can limit your work notifications. Focus filters even let you filter out select emails, messages, calendars, and more.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple Intelligence, Apple is adding a new "Reduce Interruptions" Focus Mode that can intelligently filter out what's not important, while still delivering what you need to see immediately. Toggling this on removes all of the hassle of setting up a Focus mode, but it has all of the benefit.<br/>
<br/>
You can also use the "Intelligent Breakthrough and Silencing" toggle with every Focus mode you make to get the same effect, so you'll never miss something important. Apple Intelligence is coming in iOS 18.1, set to be released in late October.<br/>
<br/>
You'll still get all of your notifications when a Focus mode ends, but all in one alert rather than multiple. Turning off unwanted notifications from apps a great method for saving battery life, and Focus modes are useful for reducing incoming notifications without missing things.<br/>
<br/>
You can find all of the Focus features in the Focus section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="13._use_scheduled_summary">13. Use Scheduled Summary</h2><br/>
Along with Focus modes, you should also make sure that any app that sends non-important notifications is relegated to the Scheduled Summary, which saves up notifications and sends them to you once or twice a day.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-823339" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/ios-15-2-notification-summary.jpg" alt="" width="773" height="768" /><br/>
You can toggle on Scheduled Summary for apps in the Notifications section of the Settings app, where you can specify which apps should have their notifications include in Scheduled Summary and when you want them delivered.<br/>
<br/>
Another option is turning off notifications entirely for apps that are sending you less than useful info like reminders to play games.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="14._limit_when_and_how_often_apps_can_access_location">14. Limit When and How Often Apps Can Access Location</h2><br/>
It's always good to check in on privacy and access settings to make sure apps and services aren't doing things you don't want them to be doing.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872415" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/ios-16-location-services.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1299" /><br/>
Limiting the apps that have access to your location and how often apps can access that data can save battery life.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Choose Privacy & Security.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap Location Services.</li><br/>
 <li>Review the list and edit settings by tapping on the name of each app in the list.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
You have four possible choices for location settings for each app, though not all four choices will always be available for every app depending on what it does. You can select the following: Never, Ask Next Time Or When I Share, While Using the App, and Always.<br/>
<br/>
Never will prevent an app from ever accessing your location, and unless there's a specific need for an app to know where you are, such as a mapping app, setting location access to Never is the best choice.<br/>
<br/>
Ask Next Time Or When I Share will prompt an app to ask you with a pop-up the next time that it wants your location, so you can temporarily approve it. With this setting, location access is off until expressly allowed via the pop-up.<br/>
<br/>
While Using the App allows the app to detect your location only when the app is open and being actively used. If you close the app or switch over to another app, location access ends.<br/>
<br/>
Always lets an app to have access to your location at all times, regardless of whether it's open or closed. This will result in the most battery drain and should be limited to only the apps that you need the most.<br/>
<br/>
A <em>lot</em> of apps will ask for location information that don't really need it to function, so clearing the cruft will save battery life and preserve your privacy.<br/>
<br/>
You can also turn off Location Services all together, but it's not ideal because it can impact crucial apps like Maps.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="15._limit_apps_using_bluetooth">15. Limit Apps Using Bluetooth</h2><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lets you know when apps have requested Bluetooth access, and there are quite a few apps that want Bluetooth access for location tracking, scanning for Chromecast devices, or other not-so-useful reasons.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872416" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/app-bluetooth-permissions.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1961" /><br/>
Checking on the apps using Bluetooth is worthwhile to make sure that you don't have a sneaky app connecting to Bluetooth sources without your permission and draining battery. To get to Bluetooth settings:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Privacy &amp; Security.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap Bluetooth.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Apps like Facebook, MAX, Hulu, and others don't need Bluetooth access for the most part, so toggle off any app that isn't related to some kind of actual Bluetooth accessory. If a feature in an app stops working, you can just turn Bluetooth right back on.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="16._use_low_power_mode">16. Use Low Power Mode</h2><br/>
Using Low Power Mode liberally is an obvious choice for maintaining battery without having to change a lot of settings, and you can toggle it on from Control Center, the Battery section of the Settings app, or using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205234">Low Power Mode</a> cuts down on background activity, turns off your display after inactivity more quickly, limits display refresh rate, limits email fetch, cuts down on visual effects, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-858449" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/ios-16-beta-6-battery-percent-low-power.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Low Power Mode can be set to turn on at a certain battery percentage using Shortcuts, which is a useful way to have it automatically turn on when you need it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="17._use_wi-fi_and_airplane_mode">17. Use Wi-Fi and Airplane Mode</h2><br/>
If you're at home or work, make sure you connect to Wi-Fi instead of cellular. Nothing drains a battery quite like a 5G connection, especially when signal is weak.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872417" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airplane-mode-ios-16.jpg" alt="" width="1954" height="1099" /><br/>
Should you find yourself somewhere with no Wi-Fi and you also have low cellular signal, turning on Airplane Mode or turning off your cellular connection temporarily can save battery because your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; isn't constantly trying to connect to cellular towers.<br/>
<br/>
It's only useful if you don't need a cellular connection, but it can help with battery drain, and most of the time, there's not a lot you can do with super low signal.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="18._manage_apps_draining_battery">18. Manage Apps Draining Battery</h2><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; tells you which apps are using the most battery so you can make sure nothing is secretly draining your battery without your knowledge. You can check your battery usage statistics by opening up the Settings app and tapping on the Battery section.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872418" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/ios-16-battery-settings.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1961" /><br/>
Battery usage charts let you see your battery level over the last 24 hours or for the last 10 days, plus you can see which apps have used the most battery life. If there's an app that you don't need that's draining an excessive amount of battery, delete it. If you do need the app, moderate how often you're using it and what permissions it has like location.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="19._limit_background_activity">19. Limit Background Activity</h2><br/>
Most apps use background refresh to update even when they're not open, and limited background activity and background refresh is a longtime favorite option for cutting down on battery usage.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872419" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/ios-16-background-app-refresh.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1961" /><br/>
You can turn off Background App Refresh all together or choose which apps can refresh in the background.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Select General.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Background App Refresh.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
From there, you can tap on the Background App Refresh option to turn Background App Refresh off altogether or choose to have it activate only when connected to Wi-Fi, which doesn't drain battery as much as downloading over cellular.<br/>
<br/>
You can also choose to turn Background App Refresh on just for your most used apps by tapping on the toggle next to each app in the list.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="20._change_your_mail_settings">20. Change Your Mail Settings</h2><br/>
Along with turning off Background App Refresh, changing when and how often the Mail app checks for new emails can save you some battery.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap Mail.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap Accounts.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap "Fetch New Data" at the bottom. <img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-729024" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/02/mailfetch.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1557" /></li><br/>
</ol><br/>
You can turn off Push (which lets you know right away when a new email message is available) and adjust Fetch settings on a per account basis for accounts that don't support Push (like Gmail accounts).<br/>
<br/>
Adjusting the Fetch settings to have longer intervals before checking for new messages can help save battery life, as can turning off Fetch all together in favor of manual checks that will download new messages only when the Mail app is opened.<br/>
<br/>
You can choose the following settings: Automatically, Manually, Hourly, Every 30 Minutes, and Every 15 Minutes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="21._remove_airtags">21. Remove AirTags</h2><br/>
If you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a>, it's probably pinging your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; regularly, which can impact battery life. If it's not actively in use, consider removing the &zwnj;AirTag&zwnj; from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; until the next time you need it. That also goes for any Find My-connected devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airtag-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957120" /><br/>
AirTags can be managed by opening up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> and navigating to the items tab.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="22._preserve_battery_longevity">22. Preserve Battery Longevity</h2><br/>
With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, you can preserve your battery health with an optimized charging feature that prevents charging up past 80 percent. We tested the 80 percent charging limit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/24/iphone-80-percent-charging-test/">over the course of a year</a>, and while it makes a little bit of a difference, it's not a huge help keeping your maximum battery up over time.<br/>
<br/>
It's not worth turning on if you need full battery for a long day out, but it's possibly worth turning on if you're often using your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at home. There are also settings for limiting your charge to 85, 90, or 95 percent. Anything under 100 percent could have an impact on longterm battery health over several years.<br/>
<br/>
To turn on a charging limit, go to Settings > Battery > Charging and select a limit using the slider.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="a_note_on_apple_intelligence">A Note on Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
Starting with iOS 18.1, Apple is rolling out the first Apple Intelligence features. It will kick off with Writing Tools and a new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; design, but later this year, we'll also get image generation capabilities and ChatGPT integration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-iPhone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964551" /><br/>
AI processing can be GPU intensive, so it's possible that Apple Intelligence will impact battery life, depending on how much you're using it. It's something to keep in mind when Apple Intelligence becomes available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ios_18_battery_drain_complaints">iOS 18 Battery Drain Complaints</h2><br/>
There have been a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/iphone-16-battery-drain-complaints/">lot of recent complaints</a> about battery drain caused by &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, particularly from &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users, so it is entirely possible that there is an underlying bug that will be addressed in a future update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-15-pro-max-battery-test.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968044" /><br/>
In the meantime, some of the tips in this article might help on days when your battery is just draining too fast.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="wrap_up">Wrap Up</h2><br/>
There are a lot of minor changes to make to cut down on battery use, but everything you do on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is going to drain battery. It's important to figure out what works for you, what features you don't need, and where you can compromise to get the most out of your battery.<br/>
<br/>
Do you have a useful battery saving tip that we haven't shared? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-battery-saving-tips/">22 Tips to Make Your iPhone 16&#039;s Battery Last Longer</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/22-tips-to-make-your-iphone-16s-battery-last-longer.2440441/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Bug Causing Random Freezing and Restarts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-16-pro-restart-bug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-bug-causing-random-freezing-and-restarts.2440438/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 14:16:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-16-pro-restart-bug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There appears to be a bug with some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models that is causing random restarts, according to complaints on <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/1fm7uvi/iphone_16_pro_crashing_and_restarting/">Reddit</a>, the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-randomly-restarts.2437509/"><em>MacRumors</em> forums</a>, and the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255772756?sortBy=rank">Apple Support Communities</a>. Affected users are seeing their iPhones freeze unexpectedly and then reboot.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-colors-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964753" /><br/>
Reports about the issue have been ongoing since the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models first launched in September, and have continued to this week. The iOS 18.0.1 and iOS 18.1 updates do not fix the issue, as it has continued to happen to users even after installing the latest software.<br/>
<br/>
The problem seems to pop up randomly. The display will stop responding or will be very slow to respond to touch input, and then the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will do a quick restart. There have also been reports of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; restarting unexpectedly when in StandBy mode.<br/>
<br/>
Some users who contacted Apple shortly after the new iPhones launched were able to get replacement devices, but have had the issue reoccur. Almost all of the complaints are about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> or &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max, so it may only be the Pro models that are impacted.<br/>
<br/>
For most people, the issue is sporadic, but some users have seen 10 to 20 crashes per day. In some cases, doing a fresh install and not reinstalling from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Backup seems to have fixed the problem, so it is possible that this is a bug related to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Let us know in the comments below if you've been experiencing this freezing and crashing issue.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-16-pro-restart-bug/">iPhone 16 Pro Bug Causing Random Freezing and Restarts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-bug-causing-random-freezing-and-restarts.2440438/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Has Display Hardware Changes That Likely Fix Jelly Scrolling</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-jelly-scrolling/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-has-display-hardware-changes-that-likely-fix-jelly-scrolling.2440434/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:45:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-jelly-scrolling/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">the main complaints</a> about the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> 6 was "jelly scrolling" or screen tearing, and it sounds like it's a problem that Apple may have addressed with hardware updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a> display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970887" /><br/>
In the most recent episode of <a href="https://sixcolors.com/">the Six Colors Podcast</a>, Jason Snell and Dan Moren discussed the new &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj;, and shared some information about the display. Snell said that it was his understanding that there have been unspecified adjustments to the display hardware in the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; that should make a difference when it comes to jelly scrolling.<br/>
<br/>
Snell didn't provide a source, but his information likely comes directly from Apple. There is only an "implication" that the changes were to fix jelly scrolling, however, and Snell made it clear that because no one has seen the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; as of yet, there's no concrete information. "My guess is it's different," he said. "And maybe better. And maybe gone."<br/>
<br/>
Jelly scrolling is a display issue that causes text or images on one side of the display to be out of sync with the other side. The result is text or images that can appear to be tilted downward because of a screen refresh rate mismatch, and for some people, once you've noticed the problem, it's hard to ignore.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; 6 owners started <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">noticing jelly scrolling</a> in portrait mode on the device shortly after it launched in 2021. Some users were not bothered by the effect, while others said that it was irritating to look at and could cause eye strain.<br/>
<br/>
Most if not all &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; 6 units seemed to be impacted, but the degree of impact varied from user to user due to different tolerances for screen tearing. The effect likely impacted prior iPads, but it seemed to be more noticeable in the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; 6.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; rumors suggested that Apple would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">rotate the screen assembly</a> in order to cut down on jelly scrolling, so it's possible Apple has done something like that to minimize the issue in the seventh-generation model.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; is available for pre-order and is set to launch on Wednesday, October 23. Once the tablet is available, users will be able to see for themselves whether jelly scrolling has been addressed, and an iFixit teardown will provide insight into any hardware changes. We'll also likely get reviews before the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; models launch, so we could have a more firm answer on the jelly scrolling question in a matter of days.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-jelly-scrolling/">iPad Mini 7 Has Display Hardware Changes That Likely Fix Jelly Scrolling</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-has-display-hardware-changes-that-likely-fix-jelly-scrolling.2440434/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Magic Keyboards Hit Best-Ever Prices, Plus Apple Watch and Anker Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-18-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-magic-keyboards-hit-best-ever-prices-plus-apple-watch-and-anker-sales.2440430/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:14:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-18-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals included record low prices on Apple accessories like the Magic Keyboard for the M4 iPad Pro, as well as discounts on a few Apple Watch models. We're also still tracking great deals on Anker and Jackery accessories as we head into the weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/halloween-hero.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971557" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/magic-keyboard-m4-ipad-pro-halloween.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971556" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Apple's first party accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J63BWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/12/apple-pencil-pro-new-low-price-2/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>11-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;269.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J63BWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>13-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHHJXTC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>2-meter MagSafe Charger for &#36;39.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week we tracked a few deals on Apple's Magic Keyboards for iPad and the new MagSafe Charger. Although some of these have since expired, you can still get all-time low prices on both Magic Keyboards for the M4 iPad Pro, and the 2-meter MagSafe Charger.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/anker-halloween.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971555" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take 20% off Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/14/anker-early-black-friday-deals/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE 20% OFF</div>Anker Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our Anker partnership continued this week, giving our readers an exclusive 20 percent discount on Anker's best chargers, portable batteries, and more. You'll need to enter the code akmacrumors20ch at checkout to see the discount, and can find more information about what accessories work with the code <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/14/anker-early-black-friday-deals/">in our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/samsung-halloween.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971575" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;780 off Samsung monitors</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Streaming-Upscaling-Ergonomic-LS32DM801UNXZA-dp-B0D1DBQRRS%2Fdp%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Ddp_ob_title_ce%3Fth%3D1">Amazon</a></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Streaming-Upscaling-Ergonomic-LS32DM801UNXZA-dp-B0D1DBQRRS%2Fdp%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Ddp_ob_title_ce%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>Samsung 32-inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;780 OFF</div>Samsung 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor for &#36;819.98</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's popular 32-inch Smart Monitor M8 (Model M80D) is down to &#36;399.99 on Amazon, down from &#36;699.99. This is the newest model of the Smart Monitor M8, and this is an overall second-best price, coming just &#36;20 higher when compared to the Prime Day price. Amazon also has a the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor for &#36;819.98, down from &#36;1,599.99, and this one is an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-watch-10-halloween.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971560" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;64 off Apple Watch Ultra 2 and Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHV8NLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/16/apple-watch-ultra-2-series-10-sales/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHV8NLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;27 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;371.28</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3PBKT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;64 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Black) for &#36;734.89</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon hosted a few low prices on the Apple Watch Series 10 this week, with solid markdowns on both the 42mm and 46mm GPS models still available. You can also get the Ultra 2 in Black for a second-best price on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/jackery-halloween.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971559" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Jackery portable power stations</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.IYAIT9VISY5S%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.IYAIT9VISY5S_1729175426364">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/anker-and-jackery-fall-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.IYAIT9VISY5S%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.IYAIT9VISY5S_1729175426364"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;900 OFF</div>Jackery on Amazon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Jackery's best portable power stations and accessories hit low prices on Amazon this week, with up to &#36;900 off select devices. We've compiled the full list of accessories on sale below, and note that you'll only need to clip an on-page coupon for one of the discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.IYAIT9VISY5S%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.IYAIT9VISY5S_1729175426364">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;179.00, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2_1727795997993">Solar Generator with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;269.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QYH6YGJP7QXZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QYH6YGJP7QXZ_1727796039758">Solar Generator 300 Plus</a> - &#36;419.00, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3VHK2OMHTAMBW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3VHK2OMHTAMBW_1729175491070">Explorer 1000 v2 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;459.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2OQFGXBQQGR9Y%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2OQFGXBQQGR9Y_1727796122171">Explorer 500</a> - &#36;502.99, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3DEZ1HJGW9026%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3DEZ1HJGW9026_1727796109673">Explorer 3000 Pro Generator</a> - &#36;1,899.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-18-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Magic Keyboards Hit Best-Ever Prices, Plus Apple Watch and Anker Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-magic-keyboards-hit-best-ever-prices-plus-apple-watch-and-anker-sales.2440430/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Pro Models Again Rumored to Feature 48MP Telephoto Camera, 12GB of RAM, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-pro-rumored-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-models-again-rumored-to-feature-48mp-telephoto-camera-12gb-of-ram-and-more.2440428/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 12:03:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-pro-rumored-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 17 Pro models are still nearly a year away from launching, analyst Jeff Pu has already outlined his expectations for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-design-cameras.jpg" alt="" width="923" height="517" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966096" /><br/>
In a research note with investment bank Haitong International this week, Pu reiterated his previous claim that both the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature a 48-megapixel Telephoto rear camera and a 24-megapixel front camera. Both the Telephoto and front cameras shoot at 12 megapixels on iPhone 16 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
He also expects the iPhone 17 Pro models to be equipped with 12GB of RAM, up from 8GB in iPhone 16 Pro models. This increase in memory would contribute to improved performance for Apple Intelligence and multitasking.<br/>
<br/>
The analyst continues to believe that the iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature a "much narrowed Dynamic Island," as a result of the device adopting a smaller "metalens" for the Face ID system. This would be the first size reduction for the Dynamic Island since it debuted on the iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Pu outlined a few less-surprising details that are apparently planned for the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max, including unchanged 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch display sizes for the devices, respectively. He also expects the devices to have an A19 Pro chip manufactured with TSMC's same 3nm process as used for the A18 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 17 Pro models in September 2025, alongside a regular iPhone 17 and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">all-new, slimmer "iPhone 17 Air."</a><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-pro-rumored-features/">iPhone 17 Pro Models Again Rumored to Feature 48MP Telephoto Camera, 12GB of RAM, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-models-again-rumored-to-feature-48mp-telephoto-camera-12gb-of-ram-and-more.2440428/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All-New &#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Rumored to Feature Single 48MP Rear Camera, 8GB of RAM, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-new-iphone-17-air-rumored-to-feature-single-48mp-rear-camera-8gb-of-ram-and-more.2440425/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:26:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In recent months, several credible sources have claimed that Apple plans to release a redesigned, significantly thinner iPhone 17 model next year. The device's name is not yet known, so we are referring to it as the "iPhone 17 Air" for now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iPhone-17-Slim-Feature-Single-Camera-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960528" /><br/>
There have been conflicting rumors about the design and specifications for the device, but most sources have agreed that it will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">around a 6.6-inch display</a>. In July, Apple supply chain analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">Ming-Chi Kuo said</a> he expects the device to have a standard A19 chip, a Dynamic Island, a single rear camera, and an Apple-designed 5G modem.<br/>
<br/>
In a research note this week with investment bank Haitong International, analyst Jeff Pu agreed that the slim iPhone 17 model will have a 6.6-inch display, and an A19 chip manufactured with TSMC's same 3nm process that is used for the A18 Pro chip. He also expects the device to feature an aluminum frame, Face ID, a single 48-megapixel rear camera, a 24-megapixel front camera, and 8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
Pu expects the slim iPhone 17 model to have a noticeable new design compared to previous iPhone models. He said the device will be a mid-tier iPhone that replaces the Plus model, as he does not expect an iPhone 17 Plus in next year's lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely unveil the "iPhone 17 Air" in September 2025, so the device is still far away from launching, and some features could change over time.<br/>
<br/>
Pu has proven to be a mostly-accurate source of info for upcoming Apple products.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">All-New &#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Rumored to Feature Single 48MP Rear Camera, 8GB of RAM, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-new-iphone-17-air-rumored-to-feature-single-48mp-rear-camera-8gb-of-ram-and-more.2440425/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Lapz App Lets You Watch Formula 1 Races on Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/lapz-formula-1-app-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lapz-app-lets-you-watch-formula-1-races-on-apple-vision-pro.2440420/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:30:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/lapz-formula-1-app-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For Formula 1 fans, there's a <a href="https://www.lapz.io">new app called Lapz</a> that is designed to provide an immersive F1 experience on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset. Users can watch multiple race feeds from different angles, see stats, and view a 3D version of the track that has icons that show where each driver is located in the race.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/lapz-app-f1-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971602" /><br/>
Different windows can be arranged in the virtual space around the Vision Pro wearer for a customizable experience focusing on what's most important to each user.<br/>
<br/>
The app was created in part by John LePore, who created a concept of an interactive experience back in 2018, and won second place in the F1 Innovation Prize contest that year. What was then just a concept is now a functional app that only became possible after Apple launched the Vision Pro. LePore is also known for working with Marvel Studios to create futuristic interfaces and gadgets for movies like Iron Man and Black Panther.<br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/barrycollins/2024/10/02/this-incredible-f1-app-is-the-best-reason-yet-to-buy-a-vision-pro/">Forbes</a></em> highlighted a demonstration video from a Vision Pro user, and called the app "the best reason yet to buy a Vision Pro."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Formula 1 on Apple Vision Pro is Amazing!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1ayHSrhNWoA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Lapz is available as a TestFlight beta right now, and those who want to try out the app can sign up for the TestFlight <a href="https://www.lapz.io">on the Lapz website</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/lapz-formula-1-app-vision-pro/">Lapz App Lets You Watch Formula 1 Races on Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lapz-app-lets-you-watch-formula-1-races-on-apple-vision-pro.2440420/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Sixth Beta of visionOS 2.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-seeds-sixth-beta-of-visionos-2-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-sixth-beta-of-visionos-2-1.2440419/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:14:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-seeds-sixth-beta-of-visionos-2-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the sixth beta of an upcoming visionOS 2.1 update to developers for testing purposes. The sixth beta comes just days after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/14/apple-seeds-fifth-beta-watchos-11-1/">released the fifth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-on-Apple-Vision-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955609" /><br/>
visionOS 2.1 can be installed by going to the Software Update section of the Settings app on the Vision Pro and opting into Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
No major new features have been found in visionOS 2.1, though there are likely minor feature changes and bug fixes that we'll learn about when release notes become available.<br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.1 is expected to see a launch alongside iOS 18.1 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 on Monday, October 28.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-seeds-sixth-beta-of-visionos-2-1/">Apple Seeds Sixth Beta of visionOS 2.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-sixth-beta-of-visionos-2-1.2440419/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iPad Mini 7 Is Here!</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/the-macrumors-show-ipad-mini-7-is-here/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ipad-mini-7-is-here.2440411/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:10:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/the-macrumors-show-ipad-mini-7-is-here/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/apples-shocking-m4-macbook-pro-leak/id1602394741?i=1000672720285">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a>, Apple Intelligence and Genmoji, and the chances of an October Apple event to introduce M4 Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s7c4S9wpviU?si=5cwm43qwXIi7bFre" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple this week announced the seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>. Key upgrades include the A17 Pro chip, Smart HDR 4 and a new True Tone flash, a faster USB-C port, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover support, a 512GB storage option, and support for Apple Intelligence. We discuss our initial thoughts on the product refresh, the significance of the upgrades, and who should consider buying the new device. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-6-vs-7/">iPad Mini 6 vs. iPad Mini 7 Buyer's Guide: 20+ Upgrades Compared</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
With Apple Intelligence being a tentpole feature of the new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, we ponder on whether Genmoji will <em>actually</em> be a popular feature among users when it eventually debuts. Finally, with the first of Apple's October product releases taking place via press release, we appraise whether the next expected products, which include new MacBook Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> models, will follow suit. Until now, reports suggested that there would be an October Apple event to unveil the new devices before their debut in early November. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-pro-first-impressions/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/11/the-macrumors-show-m4-macbook-pro-leak/">unprecedented leak</a> of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/">M4 MacBook Pro</a> models and the company's rumored move to more staggered hardware and software releases.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/the-macrumors-show-ipad-mini-7-is-here/">The MacRumors Show: iPad Mini 7 Is Here!</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ipad-mini-7-is-here.2440411/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Introduces Massive Discounts on M3 MacBook Pro for Members, Get Up to &#36;700 Off</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/best-buy-m3-macbook-pro-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-introduces-massive-discounts-on-m3-macbook-pro-for-members-get-up-to-700-off.2440407/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:34:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/best-buy-m3-macbook-pro-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy today introduced new all-time low prices on a few models of the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro exclusively for members. Non-members can still find solid second-best prices on these computers, but <a href="https://howl.me/cnkfLAjYsvD">My Best Buy Plus/Total</a> members can get an extra &#36;200 off select notebooks this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-bb-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924141" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The highlights of the sale include the 8GB/1TB 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/cnkfNiPUI8E"><strong>&#36;1,299.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,799.00, and the 16GB/1TB model for <a href="https://howl.me/cnkfNA9YGNz"><strong>&#36;1,499.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,999.00. Both of these represent &#36;500 discounts and are new record low prices for each model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Select deals available only to My Best Buy members.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cnkfSyUer2N"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;700 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro Deals at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for the bigger model, the steepest discount at Best Buy is on the 48GB/1TB M3 Max 16-inch MacBook Pro, available for <a href="https://howl.me/cnkfXWgP943"><strong>&#36;3,299.00</strong></a> for members, down from &#36;3,999.00. In addition to this model, Best Buy has every other 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro on sale right now for solid second-best prices.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/best-buy-m3-macbook-pro-2/">Best Buy Introduces Massive Discounts on M3 MacBook Pro for Members, Get Up to &#36;700 Off</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-introduces-massive-discounts-on-m3-macbook-pro-for-members-get-up-to-700-off.2440407/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discontinues Powerbeats Pro, New Model Launching Next Year With These Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-discontinues-powerbeats-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinues-powerbeats-pro-new-model-launching-next-year-with-these-features.2440405/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:06:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-discontinues-powerbeats-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Powerbeats Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple at some point in the past week or so discontinued the Powerbeats Pro, around five and a half years after the wireless earbuds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/03/apple-announces-powerbeats-pro/">launched</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Powerbeats-Pro-Original.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971547" /><br/>
Powerbeats Pro are a sportier, fitness-focused alternative to AirPods Pro with built-in, adjustable ear hooks for a secure fit. Key features of the original Powerbeats Pro include the H1 chip that debuted in the AirPods 2, IPX4-rated sweat and water resistance, up to nine hours of battery life, and silicone ear tips with four size options.<br/>
<br/>
In a short teaser video last month, Apple revealed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/04/beats-teases-powerbeats-pro-2/">it will be launching new Powerbeats Pro 2 next year</a>. The earbuds look similar to the original Powerbeats Pro, but they have a more vertical, slimmer design. <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a> later discovered iOS 18 code revealing that the Powerbeats Pro 2 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/powerbeats-pro-2-heart-rate/">will feature heart rate monitoring</a> during workouts, and gain support for Active Noise Cancellation, Spatial Audio, and Adaptive Audio.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-power-beats-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="2432" height="1368" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964623" /><em>Powerbeats Pro 2 images in iOS 18 code</em></div><br/>
The leaked iOS 18 code also revealed new orange, purple, black, and beige color options for the Powerbeats Pro 2 and their charging case.<br/>
<br/>
Based on other recent Beats headphones, other potential upgrades for the Powerbeats Pro 2 include improved sound quality, longer battery life, a USB-C charging case, and improved cross-platform compatibility with Android features like Find My Device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not reveal a specific release date in 2025 for the Powerbeats Pro 2.<br/>
<br/>
The rumored heart rate monitoring feature has also been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/24/airpods-pro-2-rumored-features/">rumored for the AirPods Pro in the past</a>, so perhaps the feature will extend to the AirPods Pro 3.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/powerbeats-pro/">Powerbeats Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-discontinues-powerbeats-pro/">Apple Discontinues Powerbeats Pro, New Model Launching Next Year With These Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinues-powerbeats-pro-new-model-launching-next-year-with-these-features.2440405/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s When to Expect Apple Intelligence to Launch on the New iPad Mini</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/new-ipad-mini-ships-with-ipados-18-0/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-when-to-expect-apple-intelligence-to-launch-on-the-new-ipad-mini.2440400/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:58:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/new-ipad-mini-ships-with-ipados-18-0/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just like iPhone 16 models, the new iPad mini is likely to launch without Apple Intelligence, but the features should be available on the device soon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970887" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/">Geekbench results</a> for the iPad mini with the A17 Pro chip list the device as running iPadOS 18.0, instead of iPadOS 18.1 with Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, a private account on social media platform X with a proven track record of sharing upcoming iOS versions mentioned a special build of iPadOS 18.0 for the iPad mini 7, and it appears that the device will indeed come preinstalled with iPadOS 18.0 out of the box when it begins arriving to customers on Wednesday, October 23.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, new iPad mini owners shouldn't have to wait too long for Apple Intelligence. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman this week <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1846264631595053353">reiterated his expectation</a> that iPadOS 18.1 will be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/06/apple-to-release-ios-18-1-on-october-28/">on Monday, October 28</a>, so Apple Intelligence should be available on the new iPad mini merely five days after the device launches.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's press release for the new iPad mini had already mentioned that the first Apple Intelligence features would be available on the device starting with an iPadOS 18.1 software update this month, and now the situation is fully clear.<br/>
<br/>
The first Apple Intelligence features include writing tools, notification summaries, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/new-ipad-mini-ships-with-ipados-18-0/">Here&#039;s When to Expect Apple Intelligence to Launch on the New iPad Mini</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-when-to-expect-apple-intelligence-to-launch-on-the-new-ipad-mini.2440400/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Benchmarks Confirm 8GB RAM, 5-Core GPU&#039;s Slower Speeds</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram-5-core-gpus-slower-speeds.2440393/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 05:20:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Geekbench</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> has now appeared on Geekbench, confirming that it has 8GB of memory and revealing how the 5-core GPU version of the A17 Pro chip performs. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-apple-intelligence-a17-pro-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-970909" /><br/>
The new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, identified as <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/search?q=iPad16%2C2">iPad 16,2 on the Geekbench database</a>, includes the same A17 Pro SoC first introduced in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro series last year. The six-core chip is clocked at 3.78 GHz, which matches the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> version, but with a key distinctiona five-core GPU, which is one core less than the version found in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. This suggests that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a>'s A17 Pro chip is likely a "binned" version.<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s Geekbench scores reveal a range between 2,710 and 2,840 in single-core performance and 6,274 to 6,982 in multi-core performance, positioning it slightly below the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro in both metrics. For comparison, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro's A17 Pro typically scores around 2,888 in single-core and 7,169 in multi-core tests. <br/>
<br/>
Nonetheless, the benchmarks confirm that the new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; offers a substantial performance upgrade over its predecessor. The sixth-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; from 2021 achieved approximate single-core scores of 2,121 and multi-core scores of 5,367. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <th></th><br/>
    <th>Chip</th><br/>
    <th>GPU cores</th><br/>
    <th>Memory</th><br/>
    <th>Single-Core CPU Score</th><br/>
    <th>Multi-Core CPU Score</th><br/>
  <th>Metal GPU Score</th><br/>
  </tr><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <th>&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; 6 (2021)</th><br/>
    <td>A15 Bionic</td><br/>
    <td>5</td><br/>
    <td>4GB</td><br/>
    <td>2,121</td><br/>
    <td>5,367</td><br/>
    <td>19,486</td><br/>
  </tr><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <th>&zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; (2024) </th><br/>
    <td>A17 Pro</td><br/>
    <td>5</td><br/>
    <td>8GB</td><br/>
    <td>2,840</td><br/>
    <td>6,982</td><br/>
<td>25,895</td><br/>
  </tr><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro (2023)</th><br/>
    <td>A17 Pro</td><br/>
    <td>6</td><br/>
    <td>8GB</td><br/>
    <td>2,888</td><br/>
    <td>7,169</td><br/>
  <td>27,144</td><br/>
  </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The Geekbench listings also confirm the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s adoption of 8GB of memory. While this was expected due to Apple Intelligence's 8GB memory, it was not actually known until now. The previous-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; featured just 4GB of memory, marking a substantial upgrade on the latest device.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/geekbench/">Geekbench</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/">iPad Mini 7 Benchmarks Confirm 8GB RAM, 5-Core GPU&#039;s Slower Speeds</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram-5-core-gpus-slower-speeds.2440393/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Users Complain About Excessive iOS 18 Battery Drain</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/iphone-16-battery-drain-complaints/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-users-complain-about-excessive-ios-18-battery-drain.2440363/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:06:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/iphone-16-battery-drain-complaints/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> users have been experiencing excessive and unexplainable battery drain, according to complaints on <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/1fp6cjl/iphone_16_pro_max_not_lasting_long/">Reddit</a>, the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255761370?page=1&amp;sortBy=newest_first">Apple Support Communities</a>, and the <em>MacRumors</em> forums. While many of the reports are from &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users, older iPhones running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> may also be experiencing battery life issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-max.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964692" /><br/>
There is a long-running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-battery-life-thread.2428672/">battery life complaint thread</a> on <em>MacRumors</em> that was started while the update was still in beta, but there have been a fresh wave of complaints following &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;'s launch and the debut of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
Affected &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; owners have seen significant battery drain even when the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is not in use. From <em>MacRumors</em> reader <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-battery-life-thread.2428672/post-33454611">T1aaj</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>Yes I own the 16 pro and battery life goes down to almost 60% from 100% halfway through the day, through no heavy use. Definitely needs to be fixed, should've kept my 15 pro!</blockquote><br/>
From <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-battery-life-thread.2428672/post-33474865">JulianL</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>I'm getting horrible battery life with my new 16 Pro Max. I upgraded from a 15 Pro Max - upgraded to iOS 18 and with battery health of 99% when I sold it. With Apple quoting better battery life spec for the 16 I was excited to see how much more run time I would get. The answer? I now get 50 to 60% of time between charges vs what I got with my 1 year old 15 Pro Max. Really disappointing. All Settings the same including background refresh globally disabled, screen max refresh set to 60Hz and data locked to 4G (because for my use I see absolutely no difference in how my phone functions when I set all those settings so I might as well set them for optimal battery life). I got my 16PM on launch day so it's 19 days old now; any early days indexing and other background setup stuff should be well and truly over by now.</blockquote><br/>
In some cases, much of the battery drain happens in standby mode when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; isn't in use, suggesting a background activity could be causing problems for some users. Using the phone seems to cut the battery drain in these instances.<br/>
<br/>
From <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/goto/post?id=33469688">huanbrother</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>The 16 Pro has horrible standby battery life when sleeping (it is not connected to my Apple Watch), and as you can see from the graph, it runs background activities like crazy. But, guess what, I turned off AOD(but this shouldn't be the case when in sleep mode it was off anyways) and turned on frame limit in accessibility (not low power mode) to turn off ProMotion, boom, the background craze disappeared! However, the battery drain wasn't fixed, 4hours and 20minutes it drained 11%, from 70% to 59%.</blockquote><br/>
From <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-battery-life-thread.2428672/post-33483020">kirbysmartdawg</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>Clearly, something isn't right on Apple's end. The idle battery drain is excessive. This morning, I unplugged my phone at 9 a.m., and it held at 95% (my charging limit) for only 20 minutes before starting to drop rapidly. Every five minutes, I lost a percentage until I finally picked it up to use it. Now it seems to have stabilized a bit, but I'm really puzzled by this behavior.</blockquote><br/>
There are similar complaints about the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models and older iPhones running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; on Reddit, and while we always see reports of battery life issues when a new version of iOS comes out, there seems to be a definite uptick in the number of people having problems.<br/>
<br/>
From Reddit user <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/applehelp/comments/1fq8xw4/iphone_16_pro_battery_issue/">Ok-Interest-6561</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>I upgraded from my iPhone 12 and got new 16 Pro. I upgraded mostly because of battery and speaker issues but I observed that even though 16 has "better battery" and more battery life, it drains around 10-15% overnight doing nothing just laying on my bedside table.</blockquote><br/>
<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/1fp6cjl/iphone_16_pro_max_not_lasting_long/lqzcjy6/">On Reddit</a>, one user did an experiment with an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro, and claimed to have used both in the same way. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; dropped to 58 percent battery life within 36 hours, while the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro was at 85 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Battery drainage issues are difficult to diagnose because &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; usage habits vary so much from person to person and from day to day. Impacted users have tried turning off ProMotion, disabling the Always On display, turning off background app refresh, removing widgets, turning off cellular, and entirely resetting their iPhones. Some people have seen improvement with some of these methods, but not all have, and the battery life issues persist for many despite troubleshooting.<br/>
<br/>
Some users reported improvement with iOS 18.0.1 and the iOS 18.1 beta, but software updates have not worked for everyone. It is not clear exactly what's going on to impact battery, but it's sounding like there is an underlying bug that Apple will need to fix in a future &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/iphone-16-battery-drain-complaints/">iPhone 16 Users Complain About Excessive iOS 18 Battery Drain</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-users-complain-about-excessive-ios-18-battery-drain.2440363/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing to Add ChatGPT Integration to Siri</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-siri-chatgpt-integration/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-to-add-chatgpt-integration-to-siri.2440354/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:59:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-siri-chatgpt-integration/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working behind the scenes to get ready to add new Apple Intelligence features to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and macOS 15. We'll get the first set in the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS 15.1 updates, but Apple is preparing for the next batch, too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/chatgpt-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2585" height="1454" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971405" /><br/>
In backend code, <em>MacRumors</em> has discovered new references to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>'s ChatGPT integration as Apple prepares to implement ChatGPT support. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; code mentions options for ChatGPT-generated text and ChatGPT-generated images, two features that Apple plans to implement soon.<br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT integration with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; was announced as part of the Apple Intelligence feature set highlighted at the Worldwide Developers Conference, and it is functionality that Apple plans to introduce before the end of the year. ChatGPT integration is not in the current software that Apple is testing, but we are expecting it to come in iOS 18.2, iPadOS 18.2, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.2.<br/>
<br/>
Mentions of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; with ChatGPT integration first surfaced <a href="https://x.com/aaronp613/status/1845268988609114391">earlier in October</a>, and we've also seen references to Visual Intelligence, another AI feature that Apple is working on. The separate mentions of images and text are new today, and it's clear that Apple is continuing behind-the-scenes work to get these features ready for launch.<br/>
<br/>
With ChatGPT integration, when users ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; a complicated question that the personal assistant is unable to handle, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will suggest handing the query off to ChatGPT. ChatGPT will provide relevant information, which will be relayed through &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT will be able to generate both text and images, and while Apple Intelligence includes some of this functionality, ChatGPT is more advanced. Apple's Writing Tools, for example, can offer spelling and grammar assistance or change the tone of something that's already written, while ChatGPT will be able to generate text from scratch with a simple prompt.<br/>
<br/>
Image Playground and Genmoji will allow for the creation of cartoon-like images and custom emoji, but ChatGPT's image generation features will be able to be used for more realistic images. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will reference the latest GPT-4o model, and ChatGPT integration will be free with no account creation required. Apple and OpenAI will not store ChatGPT requests made from Apple devices, and IP addresses will be hidden.<br/>
<br/>
As for Visual Intelligence, it is an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> feature that uses the Camera Control button. &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users will be able to point their camera at objects or locations around them, with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> providing information about what's being viewed when the Camera Control button is pressed and held.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 are expected to see a release on Monday, October 28, and we'll likely get the first betas of iOS 18.2, iPadOS 18.2, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.2 shortly after. If testing follows other .2 updates, the software will be released at some point in December.<br/>
<br/>
Along with ChatGPT integration and Visual Intelligence, iOS 18.2 could bring support for the Image Playground image generation feature, Genmoji, and Image Wand, a Notes app feature for generating images from text or basic drawings.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-siri-chatgpt-integration/">Apple Preparing to Add ChatGPT Integration to Siri</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-to-add-chatgpt-integration-to-siri.2440354/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ to Offer Behind-the-Scenes Coverage of 2024 World Series</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-tv-plus-2024-world-series-documentary/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-to-offer-behind-the-scenes-coverage-of-2024-world-series.2440350/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:58:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-tv-plus-2024-world-series-documentary/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple TV+ today <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/10/apple-tv-announces-new-major-league-baseball-documentary-event-offering-fans-an-immersive-all-access-view-on-the-2024-world-series/">announced</a> it has partnered with Major League Baseball and Imagine Documentaries on a three-part documentary that will offer "behind-the-scenes coverage" of the upcoming 2024 World Series. Production on the currently-untitled docuseries is already underway, but a release date has yet to be disclosed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/2024-World-Series-MLB.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971444" /><br/>
Apple said the docuseries will explore the "dramatic, high-stakes world" of the World Series and each team's battle to win the championship, and offer interviews with players and their family members, coaches, fans, and journalists. New York Yankees legend and five-time World Series champion Derek Jeter will serve as an executive producer.<br/>
<br/>
The 2024 World Series is expected to begin in late October, but the two teams who will compete for the championship have yet to be determined. In the American League Championship Series, the New York Yankees have a 2-0 lead over the Cleveland Guardians in the best-of-seven series. In the National League Championship Series, the Los Angeles Dodgers have a 2-1 advantage over the New York Mets in that best-of-seven series. The winning teams in those series will face each other in the World Series.<br/>
<br/>
Apple TV+ has been the home of MLB's "Friday Night Baseball" for three consecutive seasons, and the service has also offered documentaries about the NFL's New England Patriots, NBA star Stephen Curry, Argentinian soccer star Lionel Messi, and more.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-tv-plus-2024-world-series-documentary/">Apple TV+ to Offer Behind-the-Scenes Coverage of 2024 World Series</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-to-offer-behind-the-scenes-coverage-of-2024-world-series.2440350/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Chief Suggests Digital Car Keys Could Expand to Rentals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/digital-car-keys-rental-cars/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-chief-suggests-digital-car-keys-could-expand-to-rentals.2440347/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:30:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/digital-car-keys-rental-cars/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Car Keys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As Apple celebrates the 10th anniversary of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; and Apple Wallet chief Jennifer Bailey today did an interview with <em><a href="https://thepointsguy.com/news/apple-pay-anniversary-new-features/">The Points Guy</a></em>, providing some insight into current and future Apple Pay-related features like car key and ID integration in the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/bmw-car-key-photo.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-778616" /><br/>
&zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; wasn't an immediate hit with consumers, but Bailey said that Apple "worked really hard" to establish a "great customer experience" over the last decade. As mobile payments via &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; have become widely available and more well-known, Apple and Bailey are focusing on expanding the capabilities of the Wallet app to make it more useful.<br/>
<br/>
Back in 2020, Apple introduced support for car key, an implementation of the Digital Key standard that uses NFC. The feature is designed to allow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch users to store a key for a compatible vehicle in the Wallet app, and multiple manufacturers have implemented support. Apple is working with more than 30 car manufacturers on car keys.<br/>
<br/>
As support for car keys expands, Bailey sees a future where digital keys are available for rentals.<br/>
<blockquote>Being able to book a car rental, confirm your authentication and identity ... you can imagine that a car rental company is going to issue you a digital key, and that key could be used to unlock and use a car.</blockquote><br/>
Some hotel chains have already implemented support for accessing a hotel room with a key stored in Wallet, so it's not hard to imagine this kind of functionality also expanding to cars at some point.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;'s transit usage is "just fantastic," according to Bailey, and "people absolutely love it." Apple in 2022 launched Wallet support for Digital IDs and driver's licenses, and while that's taken some time to take off, Bailey is confident adoption will pick up because the option for a digital ID is "really profound."<br/>
<blockquote>It'll be a long-term journey like we had with Apple Pay. It's helping states understand how our approach is privacy-protected and highly secure, how we don't have the data, and how we don't keep any association with where you're presenting your ID.</blockquote><br/>
Bailey told <em>The Points Guy</em> that Apple is only at the beginning of its "long-term vision to replace the wallet," but the core &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; technology that kicked off the effort "is perfect."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/carkey/">Car Keys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/digital-car-keys-rental-cars/">Apple Pay Chief Suggests Digital Car Keys Could Expand to Rentals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-chief-suggests-digital-car-keys-could-expand-to-rentals.2440347/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Developers Now Required to Share Phone Number and Address on EU App Store to Meet &#039;Trader&#039; Requirement</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/developers-eu-app-store-trader-requirements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-now-required-to-share-phone-number-and-address-on-eu-app-store-to-meet-trader-requirement.2440339/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:26:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/developers-eu-app-store-trader-requirements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=yfacfeal">today reminded developers</a> that the EU trader requirement in the European Union is now being enforced. Developers who distribute apps in the EU will now need to share information that includes address, phone number, and email address on the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961762" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/app-store-trader-requirement-dsa.jpg" alt="" width="1538" height="865" /><br/>
Submitting updates for apps on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the European Union now requires trader information that's added via &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Connect, with those details shared on each developer's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; page. App updates can no longer be submitted without trader information, and starting on February 17, 2025, apps that do not have a trader status set will be removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the EU until trader status is provided and verified.<br/>
<br/>
The Digital Services Act (DSA) in the European Union requires Apple to verify and display trader contact information for all "traders" who are distributing apps on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the European Union. Developers who make money from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; through either an upfront purchase price or through in-app purchases are considered traders, regardless of size.<br/>
<br/>
Contact information for each developer that is considered a trader will be publicly available, and there will undoubtedly be some developers that are unhappy with the requirement. Independent developers and small companies may not have dedicated business addresses and phone numbers to provide, and will likely be reluctant to provide their personal contact information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/app-store-trader-requirement-eu-october/">warned developers</a> about the upcoming trader status requirement earlier this year. As of now, trader information has to be provided before an app can be submitted for review.<br/>
<br/>
Displaying trader status is a Digital Services Act requirement in the European Union, which means Apple has to implement the feature. Developer contact information will be displayed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; product page when an app is distributed in any of the 27 territories in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
More information on determining who is a trader and who needs to provide contact details can be <a href="https://developer.apple.com/help/app-store-connect/manage-compliance-information/manage-european-union-digital-services-act-trader-requirements/">found on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/developers-eu-app-store-trader-requirements/">Developers Now Required to Share Phone Number and Address on EU App Store to Meet &#039;Trader&#039; Requirement</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-now-required-to-share-phone-number-and-address-on-eu-app-store-to-meet-trader-requirement.2440339/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Now Lets Artists Create Playlists Based on Concert Set Lists</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-music-concert-set-list-playlists/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-now-lets-artists-create-playlists-based-on-concert-set-lists.2440336/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:05:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-music-concert-set-list-playlists/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://artists.apple.com/support/5466-promote-shows-set-lists">introduced</a> a new feature that allows all artists to create Apple Music playlists based on their concert set lists. The playlists will appear on the artist's page in Apple Music, on their concert page in Shazam, and in Spotlight Search on iOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-Music-Playlists-Concert-Sets-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971394" /><br/>
The feature is built into the Apple Music for Artists tool.<br/>
<br/>
"Turn a set list from your latest show into a playlist on Apple Music for Artists on the web," said Apple, in a blog post explaining how artists can use the feature. "Share your Set List playlist with fans on Apple Music and social media to promote upcoming tour dates, let fans relive your concerts, and connect with listeners."<br/>
<br/>
Apple Music has already featured more than 450 set lists for popular artists like Taylor Swift, Beyonc, Sabrina Carpenter, and Post Malone since last year, and now all artists can create set list playlists to promote their past or upcoming concerts.<br/>
<br/>
More details are available <a href="https://artists.apple.com/support/5466-promote-shows-set-lists">on the Apple Music for Artists website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-music-concert-set-list-playlists/">Apple Music Now Lets Artists Create Playlists Based on Concert Set Lists</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-now-lets-artists-create-playlists-based-on-concert-set-lists.2440336/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Finally Begins Selling Refurbished 2022 iPad Pro and iPad Air Models in More Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/refurbished-2022-ipads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-finally-begins-selling-refurbished-2022-ipad-pro-and-ipad-air-models-in-more-countries.2440320/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 08:38:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/refurbished-2022-ipads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week began selling certified refurbished 2022 iPad Pro and iPad Air models through its online store in additional countries, including <a href="https://www.apple.com/fr/shop/refurbished/ipad/">France</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/de/shop/refurbished/ipad/">Germany</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/shop/refurbished/ipad/">Japan</a>, and the <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/shop/refurbished/ipad/">UK</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/13/refurbished-2022-ipad-pro-and-ipad-air-models/">Availability in the U.S.</a> and Canada began last month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/11/ipad-pro-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870798" /><br/>
The fourth-generation 11-inch iPad Pro with the M2 chip, sixth-generation 12.9-inch iPad Pro with the M2 chip, and fifth-generation iPad Air with the M1 chip are each available in a variety of storage capacities and color options. The refurbished models are discounted by approximately 15% compared to the original pricing of these iPads.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first introduced this particular iPad Air model in March 2022, and the iPad Pro models followed in October of that year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says its refurbished iPads include a new battery and outer shell, a new white box, and all manuals and accessories, including a USB-C charging cable and power adapter. Apple says it puts refurbished devices through a "thorough cleaning process and inspection," and it performs full functionality testing to ensure there are no defective units.<br/>
<br/>
All refurbished iPads are covered by Apple's one-year limited warranty and 14-day return policy, and eligible for AppleCare+ coverage.<br/>
<br/>
While some savings can be had here, these are obviously two-year-old iPad models with fewer remaining years of iPadOS support. There are often <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-deals/">better deals available for newer-generation iPads on Amazon</a> that are brand new in the box.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/refurbished-2022-ipads/">Apple Finally Begins Selling Refurbished 2022 iPad Pro and iPad Air Models in More Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-finally-begins-selling-refurbished-2022-ipad-pro-and-ipad-air-models-in-more-countries.2440320/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
