<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 08:03:06 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are All the iPhone Changes Coming to EU Users by March 6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users-by-march-6.2417492/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 04:30:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Thursday seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 software updates to developers, and the betas revealed a panoply of changes that will impact users in the European Union in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act (DMA).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
Apple implemented several major changes to the way the App Store and apps operate in the EU in order to comply with the DMA. These changes are included in iOS 17.4, but are generally limited to countries that are in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is working towards a March 6 deadline to make the changes live for users who update to iOS 17.4. Below, we've summarized what will change for affected users and the reasons that Apple has offered for said changes, along with some related news.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Alternative App Stores</strong>: App developers in the EU can opt to offer alternative app stores or install their apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">through alternative stores</a>, and Apple has a new fee structure as part of the change. Any developer can create an app marketplace, so long as they meet Apple's criteria for customer experience, fraud prevention, customer support, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Alternative Payment Options</strong>: Apple is allowing apps to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">alternative payment options</a>, and there is no longer a requirement to use in-app purchases. Developers can integrate these into their app, or developers can link out to their websites where users can make a purchase.</li><br/>
<li><strong>App Store Notarization</strong>: Apple has outlined how Apps that are distributed through alternative app stores in EU countries will need to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-notarization-process/">submit to a notarization process</a> that's similar to the notarization process for Mac apps. </li><br/>
<li><strong>Screen Time and Refund Limitations:</strong>: Apple says apps distributed through alternative app stores <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/features-unavailable-with-alternative-app-stores/">won't work with some long-standing features</a> like Screen Time, refunds, and in-app purchases, as they do for standard App Store apps.<br/>
<li><strong>NFC Third-Party Access</strong>: NFC payments will be available directly in apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-nfc-third-party-apps-eu/">without the need for Apple Pay or the Wallet app</a>, allowing third-party payment services and banks to offer their own tap-to-pay solutions on Apple devices in the European Economic Area.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Default Browser Options</strong>: Users in the EU will be allowed to choose a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/third-party-default-browsers-eu-ios-17-4/">new default browser</a> from a list of the most downloaded browsers on iOS devices. Some of the options include Firefox, Opera, Chrome, Brave, and Microsoft Edge.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Hardware and Software Developer Access</strong>: Apple will allows developers of iOS apps distributed in the EU to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-interoperability-request-form/">request additional interoperability</a> with iPhone hardware and software features. Apple says it will evaluate interoperability requests on a case-by-case basis.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Expanded Analytics Availability</strong>: As part of the App Store changes in the EU, Apple is providing all developers worldwide with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-developer-analytics-expansion/">updated analytics information</a>. More than 50 new reports will be available through the App Store Connect API to help developers analyze their app performance.<br/>
<li><strong>Apple's Reasons for Limiting Changes to EU</strong>: In a support document, Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-eu-risks/">explained</a> why alternative app stores, alternative payment options, and other updates are being limited to the EU, highlighting risks like fraud, scams, and other privacy threats.</li></ul>As a direct or indirect consequence of the announced changes coming in iOS 17.4, there have also been some other significant developments overnight. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's new EU terms include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-eu-fees-could-bankrupt-app-developers/">Core Technology Fee</a> that some developers have warned could completely bankrupt freemium apps that go viral by charging them astronomical fees. Apple does not charge for the first one million "first annual installs" per iOS account each year, but after that, developers will begin racking up charges. Apple's Core Technology Fee could also be prohibitively expensive for apps like Spotify that have millions of users.<br/>
<br/>
Epic Games says it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/fortnite-returning-to-ios-in-europe/">plans to bring its Epic Games Store to the iPhone and the iPad</a> under Apple's new alternative app store policy in the EU. The Epic Games Store will include popular game Fortnite, which means iPhone and iPad users will be able to install and play the title without having to use a cloud gaming service. Fortnite has been banned from the iOS App Store for the last several years due to the legal dispute between Apple and Epic Games.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-allows-game-streaming-apps-on-app-store/">announced</a> that it will allow streaming game apps on the App Store worldwide. This will mean services like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW will be available as standalone iPhone and iPad apps, whereas previously they were only accessible via the web.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BAzqrT_hZwA?si=oMxgS8QR78TTEEhW" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Technology companies need to adhere to the EU's DMA regulations by March 6, 2024. iOS 17.4 is currently available as a beta update, and it is set to see a public release in March. Given Apple's concerns over user privacy and security, the company is unlikely to implement similar changes worldwide without being forced to by similar legislation from other countries.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">Here Are All the iPhone Changes Coming to EU Users by March 6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users-by-march-6.2417492/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Confirms Next-Generation CarPlay Launching in 2024, Reveals New Features in iOS 17.4 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-next-generation-carplay-launching-in-2024-reveals-new-features-in-ios-17-4-beta.2417478/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:19:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/carplay/">updated its website</a> to confirm that the first U.S. vehicle models with next-generation CarPlay support will debut in 2024, but it did not provide a more specific timeframe, or indicate when availability will begin in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><br/>
In a next-generation CarPlay section of its website, Apple replaced "Vehicle announcements coming in late 2023" with "First models arrive in 2024."<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1/">first beta of iOS 17.4</a> released today references eight new CarPlay apps, as discovered by <em>MacRumors</em> contributors <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1750666693251051812">Aaron Perris</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/stevemoser">Steve Moser</a>:<ul><li><strong>Auto Settings:</strong> This app will let you manage paired iPhones and adjust vehicle settings.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Car Camera:</strong> This app will display the vehicle's rear-view camera feed.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Charge:</strong> For electric vehicles, this app will display battery level, charging status, time remaining until the battery is fully charged, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Climate:</strong> This app will provide access to a vehicle's climate controls within CarPlay, allowing you to adjust the temperature of the A/C or heating system, fan speed, heated seats, heated steering wheel, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Closures:</strong> This app will display if any of the vehicle's doors are opened, and it might also display vehicle warning symbols.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Media:</strong> This app will provide access to FM and AM radio station controls within CarPlay, along with other media options like SiriusXM. It is unclear if SiriusXM will offer satellite connectivity, or remain limited to internet streaming. Users will be able to select from a list of music genres, such as Top 40 and Rock.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Tire Pressure:</strong> This app will display air pressure for each of the vehicle's tires, and provide low pressure, high pressure, and flat tire warnings.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Trips:</strong> This app will provide a variety of driving-related data, including the vehicle's average speed, fuel efficiency or energy efficiency, the total time elapsed and distance traveled on a trip, and more.</li></ul>An image uncovered in the iOS 17.4 beta reveals that next-generation CarPlay will likely display a "Goodbye" screen after the driver shuts off the vehicle:<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Goodbye.jpg" alt="" width="1374" height="484" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932992" /><br/>
As previously announced by Apple, additional images in the iOS 17.4 beta confirm that users will be able to adjust the theme and color scheme of next-generation CarPlay, including the appearance of the instrument cluster:<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Cluster-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="987" height="186" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932994" /><br/>
Apple first previewed next-generation CarPlay in June 2022. The interface can be tailored to a specific vehicle model and automaker's brand identity, as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed by Aston Martin and Porsche</a> in late December. Aston Martin said it would release its first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay in 2024, including a new model of its high-end DB12 sports car. Porsche did not provide a timeframe or specific details about its own plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Aston-Martin.jpeg" alt="" width="980" height="551" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927535" /><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1540" height="854" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927564" /><br/>
When first announcing next-generation CarPlay, Apple said committed automakers included Acura, Audi, Ford, Honda, Infiniti, Jaguar, Land Rover, Lincoln, Mercedes-Benz, Nissan, Polestar, Porsche, Renault, and Volvo. Beyond the addition of Aston Martin, it is unclear if this list has changed since that initial announcement.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not indicated if any next-generation CarPlay features will be made available in existing vehicles with classic CarPlay support. Apple said iOS 17.4 will be released in March, so perhaps additional details will be shared around then.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">Apple Confirms Next-Generation CarPlay Launching in 2024, Reveals New Features in iOS 17.4 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-next-generation-carplay-launching-in-2024-reveals-new-features-in-ios-17-4-beta.2417478/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Beta: All the New Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-all-the-new-changes.2417467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:23:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced the first betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to developers, bringing some radical updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in Europe. Most of the big changes will only impact EU users, but there are also updates in the operating system that are available worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932462" /><br/>
In this article, we've rounded up everything new in iOS 17.4 beta 1. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>EU Changes</h2><br/>
Apple implemented several major changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps operate in the European Union in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act. These changes are included in iOS 17.4, but are generally limited to countries that are in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833990" /><br/>
<h3>Alternative App Stores and New App Store Terms</h3><br/>
App developers in the EU can opt to offer alternative app stores or install their apps through alternative stores, and Apple has a whole new fee structure that goes along with this change. There's a new business structure that developers can opt in to, which applies to both apps distributed in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and apps that are distributed through alternative means.<br/>
<br/>
App developers using the new system will need to pay a standard fee of 0.50 euros per user per year, with the first million installs offered for free. Apps distributed through alternative app stores will have no commission. Apps distributed through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will pay a reduced 17 percent commission, or 10 percent for those in the small business program or for user subscriptions older than a year.<br/>
<br/>
Developers can choose not to opt in to the new system and can use the existing system with the same 15/30 percent commission that's available elsewhere in the world. Apple has a fee calculator to help developers determine what they'll pay with the existing setup, with the new setup, with the new setup using alternative app stores, and with the new setup using the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Users are able to set their preferred alternative app store as the default app store on their device if desired. EU users will see an option for this in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
There are a huge number of behind-the-scene changes that are enabling this feature in the EU, with updates to all kinds of system messaging. Users in the EU will, for example, get a pop up warning when an app from an alternative app store contains malware, and there are new screens for verifying the information from an alternative app.<br/>
<br/>
A Screen Time setting will allow parents to decide whether their children's devices are able to install apps from alternative app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Alternative Payment Options</h2><br/>
Apple is also allowing apps to use alternative payment options in their apps, and there is no longer a requirement to use in-app purchase. Developers who distribute apps through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and use an alternative payment option will see a three percent discount in their &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; fees.<br/>
<br/>
Developers who distribute through alternative apps and also use an alternative payment option will pay Apple no fees beyond the set 0.50 euro fee per user.<br/>
<br/>
With alternative payments, purchases for digital goods and services can be made directly in an app or a developer can choose to link to their website to have a user make a payment. Apple is requiring developers to use a known, secure payment provider.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Third-Party Browser Updates</h3><br/>
After updating to iOS 17.4, EU users that open Safari will see a pop up that allows them to choose a new default browser option from a list of the most popular browsers on iOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also allowing alternative browser engines, and will not limit browsers like Chrome to the WebKit engine.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>NFC Access</h3><br/>
Third-party payment apps and banks have access to the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in iOS 17.4, and can offer contactless payments directly on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; without using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> or the Wallet app in the European Economic Area. Users can set a default contactless payment provider that activates at tap-to-pay terminals or when the Side button on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is pressed twice.<br/>
<br/>
The option for setting a default contactless payment provider is available in the Settings app in the EU, and this section will also provide details on all apps that have requested and been granted contactless payment access.<br/>
<br/>
EU users can also change the default Wallet app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Gaming App Changes</h2><br/>
Streaming game apps are now allowed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; worldwide, which means services like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW can be offered as standalone &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously only allowed cloud gaming services to be offered via the web, but dedicated apps that let users stream games from servers are now permitted.<br/>
<br/>
Mini-app, mini-games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Emoji</h2><br/>
The iOS 17.4 beta adds new emoji characters that include lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-New-Emoji-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1077" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932812" /><br/>
These emoji are part of the Unicode 15.1 update that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ios-17-future-emoji/">approved in September 2023</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Messaging with Siri</h2><br/>
The Automatically Send Messages setting under <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> & Search has been renamed "Messaging with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;," and there is an option to set &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to read incoming messages in a specific language like Spanish, French, German, Chinese, and many more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-messaging-with-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932819" /><br/>
The change does not update the primary language that &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; listens in and responds to, but is limited to message playback.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Podcasts and Music</h2><br/>
The "Listen Now" tabs in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and Podcasts have been renamed to "Home."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-music-home.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932818" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Podcast Transcripts</h2><br/>
The Podcasts app now offers transcripts, similar to how lyrics work in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/podcast-app-transcript.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932875" /><br/>
<h2>Safari</h2><br/>
The URL/search bar in Safari is now wider than it was before.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-wider-safari-url-bar.jpg" alt="" width="2807" height="1579" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932817" /><br/>
<h2>Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
In the Stolen Device Protection section of the Settings app, there is now an option to require a security delay always or only when away from familiar locations. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932874" /><br/>
<h2>More Features</h2><br/>
Know of something new in iOS 17.4 that we left out? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1-changes/">iOS 17.4 Beta: All the New Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-all-the-new-changes.2417467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s EU Core Technology Fee Could Bankrupt Freemium App Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-eu-fees-could-bankrupt-app-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-eu-core-technology-fee-could-bankrupt-freemium-app-developers.2417464/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:52:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-eu-fees-could-bankrupt-app-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[App developers in the European Union who choose to opt in to Apple's new business terms must pay an €0.50 "<a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/core-technology-fee/">Core Technology Fee</a>" or CTF for every app install over one million installs, a model that has the potential to bankrupt free or freemium app developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/app-store-fees-eu.jpg" alt="" width="2856" height="1607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932868" /><br/>
Apple does not charge for the first one million "first annual installs" per iOS account each year, but after that, developers will begin racking up charges. A free or freemium app that goes "viral" and is downloaded more than one million times could be forced to pay astronomical fees, as <a href="https://mastodon.social/@stroughtonsmith/111818345294643786">demonstrated in estimates</a> shared by developer Steve Troughton-Smith.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe src="https://mastodon.social/@stroughtonsmith/111818345294643786/embed" class="mastodon-embed" style="max-width: 100%; border: 0" width="400" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><script src="https://mastodon.social/embed.js" async="async"></script></div><br/>
Under Apple's new business terms, a free or freemium app that gets two million annual "first installs" would need to pay an estimated &#36;45,290 in fees per month according to <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/fee-calculator-for-apps-in-the-eu/">Apple's fee calculator</a>, or more than half a million dollars per year, even if no money is earned.<br/>
<br/>
That's an unsustainable model for free apps, and freemium apps would need to be earning at least €0.50 per user to break even with the fee. A freemium app with thousands of installs from non-paying users could end up owing far more than is made. Developers will likely need to charge up front to ensure their apps make enough money to pay the CTF, as offering a free-to-download app could be risky if downloads exceed 1 million.<br/>
<br/>
Free and freemium app developers can, however, choose to stick with Apple's current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> business terms instead of opting for the new terms. In that situation, nothing would change, and app developers would continue to pay a 15 to 30 percent commission to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
The €0.50 CTF applies to apps distributed both through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and through alternative app stores if developers choose the new business terms. With the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, developers are charged the €0.50 fee and must pay a 10 to 17 percent commission to Apple. With an alternative app store, there is no commission. Fees can be estimated for the existing terms and the new terms <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/fee-calculator-for-apps-in-the-eu/">through a dedicated calculator</a> that Apple has provided to developers. <br/>
<br/>
Here's a breakdown of the available options:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Current App Store Agreement</strong> - Developers pay Apple a 15 to 30 percent commission. Under one million in revenue is a 15 percent commission through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Small Business Program, over &#36;1 million results in a 30 percent commission. Subscriptions require a 30 percent commission for the first year, and a 15 percent commission for the second year and beyond.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>New terms, App Store distribution</strong> - Commission drops to 17 percent from 30 percent, and 10 percent from 15 percent. There is an additional fee of 3 percent for using Apple's payment system, so the commission would be between 13 and 20 percent for a developer that opts for the new rules and uses in-app purchases. The 3 percent fee does not apply for developers who use alternative payment systems. Developers must also pay €0.50 per app install per user each year after 1 million app installs.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>New terms, alternative app store distribution</strong> - No commission, but developers must pay €0.50 per app install per user annually after 1 million app installs.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
According to Apple, the CTF is applied for the first annual install, which is the first time an app is installed by an account in the EU in a 12-month period. After the first annual install, the app can be installed any number of times by the same account for the next 12 months with no charge.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is waiving the fee for nonprofit organizations, accredited educational institutions, and government entities that are approved for a fee waiver.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Core Technology Fee could also be prohibitively expensive for apps like Spotify that have millions of users. An app that makes &#36;10 million in sales through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; with 10 million "first installs" (aka, a 0.99 price) will need to pay Apple over &#36;500k per month.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Under the App Store&#39;s new fee structure for Europe, if you make &#36;10 million in sales, Apple&#39;s cut is &#36;6.2 million annually.<br><br>Assuming you have no operating costs or salaries, your take home amount: <br>&#36;2 million after tax—or 20% of your sales<br><br>I will never launch an app in Europe. <a href="https://t.co/MUCxVHcHOo">pic.twitter.com/MUCxVHcHOo</a></p>&mdash; Nikita Bier (@nikitabier) <a href="https://twitter.com/nikitabier/status/1750592825060921353?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The EU app ecosystem changes are included in iOS 17.4, and developers who opt for Apple's new system will need to start paying fees starting in March when the update launches to the public.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-eu-fees-could-bankrupt-app-developers/">Apple&#039;s EU Core Technology Fee Could Bankrupt Freemium App Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-eu-core-technology-fee-could-bankrupt-freemium-app-developers.2417464/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expands Analytics Available to Developers as Part of App Store Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-developer-analytics-expansion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-analytics-available-to-developers-as-part-of-app-store-changes.2417459/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:51:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-developer-analytics-expansion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> changes being enabled in Europe, Apple is providing all developers worldwide with updated analytics information.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-developer-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="572" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757303" /><br/>
More than 50 new reports are available through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Connect API to help developers analyze their app performance. Some of the new metrics:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Engagement</strong> - Apple is offering additional insight into the number of users on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; that interact with a developer's app or share it with other people.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Commerce</strong> - Developers can get more information on downloads, sales and proceeds, pre-orders, and transactions made with the In-App Purchase system.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Usage</strong> - Apple now provides more information on crashes, active devices, installs, app deletions, and more.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Frameworks Usage</strong> - Developers can get info on their app's interaction with iOS features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, and PhotoPicker.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
As it does with current reports, Apple will anonymize the data that is used in the new report options. Developers will be able to grant third-party access to their performance reports.<br/>
<br/>
More information about report details and access will be provided to developers in March.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-developer-analytics-expansion/">Apple Expands Analytics Available to Developers as Part of App Store Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-analytics-available-to-developers-as-part-of-app-store-changes.2417459/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>This is How Notarization Will Work for iOS Apps Distributed Through Alternative App Stores</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-notarization-process/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/this-is-how-notarization-will-work-for-ios-apps-distributed-through-alternative-app-stores.2417454/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:22:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-notarization-process/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apps that are distributed through alternative app stores in EU countries will need to <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/dma-and-apps-in-the-eu#ios-app-eu">submit to a notarization process</a> that's similar to the notarization process for Mac apps. According to Apple, Notarization applies to all apps, and it is a process focused on privacy, security, and maintaining device integrity.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-app-store-notarization-eu.jpg" alt="" width="2124" height="1195" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932861" /><br/>
Apple is aiming to ensure that apps do not have viruses, malware, or other security threats, and that they function as promised without exposing users to "egregious fraud."<br/>
<br/>
Notarization will check for the following:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Accuracy</strong> - Apps are required to accurately represent the developer, capabilities, and costs to users.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Functionality</strong> - Binaries must be reviewable, free of serious bugs or crashes, and compatible with the current version of iOS. Software or hardware cannot be manipulated in ways that negatively impact the user experience.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Safety</strong> - Apps cannot promote physical harm of the user or public.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Security</strong> - Apps cannot enable distribution of malware, or suspicious or unwanted software. They also cannot download executable code, read outside of the container, or direct users to lower the security on their system or device. Apps also must provide transparency and allow user consent to enable access to the system or device, or to reconfigure the system or other software.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Privacy</strong> - Apps cannot collect or transmit private, sensitive data without a user's knowledge or in a manner contrary to the stated purpose of the software.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The malware and virus portion of the notarization process will be automatic, but there will also be a human review to make sure that apps are functioning as advertised.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to encrypt and sign all iOS apps intended for alternative distribution to ensure that users are getting apps from known parties and to protect developers' intellectual property.<br/>
<br/>
Notarized apps will be double checked during installation to ensure that they have not been tampered with and that installation was initiated through an authorized web browser. An iOS app that is found to have known malware after it's been installed will be prevented from launching on a user's device and new installations will be revoked.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> review process, Notarization will not check apps for quality or content. Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules do not allow for content that is "offensive, insensitive, upsetting, intended to disgust, in exceptionally poor taste, or just plain creepy," and this content guideline will not apply to apps installed through alternative stores.<br/>
<br/>
Information from Notarization will be used for app installation sheets that will be presented to end users. Apple will offer at-a-glance information about apps and their functionality that users can review before deciding to install an app through an alternate app store.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the Notarization system is aimed at providing "basic protections" that will reduce "some of the new risks" that are created by alternative app distribution. Apple says that it will not set the "same high bar for privacy and security" as the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; review process.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-notarization-process/">This is How Notarization Will Work for iOS Apps Distributed Through Alternative App Stores</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/this-is-how-notarization-will-work-for-ios-apps-distributed-through-alternative-app-stores.2417454/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Allows Developers to Request Access to Additional iPhone Hardware and Software Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-interoperability-request-form/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-allows-developers-to-request-access-to-additional-iphone-hardware-and-software-features.2417451/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 13:47:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-interoperability-request-form/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[To comply with the EU's Digital Markets Act, Apple has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/ios-interoperability/">introduced</a> a new <a href="https://developer.apple.com/contact/request/interoperability/">request form</a> that allows developers of iOS apps distributed in the EU to request additional interoperability with iPhone hardware and software features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912514" /><br/>
Apple already offers developers more than 250,000 APIs, enabling them to access iPhone features and frameworks such as cameras, microphones, Bluetooth, HealthKit, SiriKit, and much more. Now, developers can request access to additional iPhone features and technologies for use in their apps in the EU, as they see fit.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says it will evaluate interoperability requests on a case-by-case basis, and release additional APIs in future iOS versions as necessary. Apple says requests must be technically feasible and adhere to the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear how many of these requests Apple will approve, if any.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is already making the NFC chip in iPhones <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-nfc-third-party-apps-eu/">accessible to third-party payment and wallet apps</a> in the EU, along with Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway, which will provide users with alternatives to Apple Pay and the Apple Wallet. This change was introduced with iOS 17.4, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">available in beta now</a> and will be released in March.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://developer.apple.com/contact/request/interoperability/">request form</a> and <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/ios-interoperability/">additional details</a> can be found on Apple's website.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-interoperability-request-form/">Apple Now Allows Developers to Request Access to Additional iPhone Hardware and Software Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-allows-developers-to-request-access-to-additional-iphone-hardware-and-software-features.2417451/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Are the Countries Where You Can Install Apps Outside of the iOS App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/eu-countries-alternative-app-stores-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-the-countries-where-you-can-install-apps-outside-of-the-ios-app-store.2417447/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 13:30:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/eu-countries-alternative-app-stores-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">completely overhauled its app system</a>, introducing changes that allow developers to distribute their apps through alternative app stores and use alternative methods of payment in iOS 17.4. Unfortunately, these changes are limited to countries that are in the European Union, and they won't be implemented worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
There are 27 EU countries: Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Republic of Cyprus, Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Romania, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, and Sweden.<br/>
<br/>
Options to install apps through alternative app stores will only be available in the countries listed above, and elsewhere in the world, there will be no changes to how apps are installed and distributed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said that it is limiting these changes to the EU because the company is concerned about how alternative app stores and payment methods will impact user privacy and security. Apple claims that users are now at risk for being exposed to malware, illicit and questionable app content, pirated software, scams, and fraud.<br/>
<br/>
The updates to the iOS app ecosystem were mandated by Europe's Digital Markets Act, which Apple must comply with by March 6, 2024. If Apple did not change its app rules, it could have faced significant fines levied by the European Commission.<br/>
<br/>
Given Apple's concerns over user privacy and security, the company is unlikely to implement similar changes worldwide without being forced to by similar legislation from other countries. Note that these features are tied to the iOS 17.4 beta that was released today. Apple plans to release iOS 17.4 in March.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/eu-countries-alternative-app-stores-available/">These Are the Countries Where You Can Install Apps Outside of the iOS App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-the-countries-where-you-can-install-apps-outside-of-the-ios-app-store.2417447/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fortnite to Return to iOS in Europe Following App Store Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/fortnite-returning-to-ios-in-europe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-to-return-to-ios-in-europe-following-app-store-changes.2417444/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:57:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/fortnite-returning-to-ios-in-europe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> plans to bring its &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> under Apple's new alternative app store policy in the European Union, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; announced today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite_apple_featured.jpg" alt="" width="2140" height="1204" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-754674" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store will include popular game Fortnite, which means &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users will be able to install and play the title without having to use a cloud gaming service. Fortnite has been banned from the iOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for the last several years due to the legal dispute between Apple and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Fortnite will return to iOS in Europe in 2024, distributed by the upcoming <a href="https://twitter.com/EpicGames?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@EpicGames</a> Store for iOS. Stay tuned for details as we figure out the regulatory timeline. We&#39;ll continue to argue to the courts and regulators that Apple is breaking the law. <a href="https://t.co/MHh6EGVinC">https://t.co/MHh6EGVinC</a></p>&mdash; Epic Games Newsroom (@EpicNewsroom) <a href="https://twitter.com/EpicNewsroom/status/1750616436957933711?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Even as Epic is planning for an &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; app store on iOS, Epic CEO Tim Sweeney has been criticizing Apple's planned changes. Sweeney said that Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes are a "devious new instance of malicious compliance" and are aimed at thwarting the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple&#39;s plan to thwart Europe&#39;s new Digital Markets Act law is a devious new instance of Malicious Compliance.<br><br>They are forcing developers to choose between App Store exclusivity and the store terms, which will be illegal under DMA, or accept a new also-illegal anticompetitive…</p>&mdash; Tim Sweeney (@TimSweeneyEpic) <a href="https://twitter.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1750589570880516402?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple is charging an 0.50 euro fee per user per year for apps installed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; (and in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; for developers who opt in to the new terms and also still choose to use Apple's system), but there are no &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; commissions or in-app fees. While Apple is waiving fees for the first one million installs, the 0.50 per user fee will cost app developers like &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; a notable amount of money. Sweeney called Apple's payment "junk fees."<br/>
<br/>
Sweeney also criticizes Apple for the notarization process that will potentially allow it to reject alternative app stores from iOS. He claims that Apple could block Epic from launching an &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store and distributing Fortnite through it, but there have been no signs that Apple would do so.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is "determined" to launch on iOS and compete with the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, said Sweeney, and while &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is planning for a store on iOS, the company says it will continue to "argue to the courts and regulators that Apple is breaking the law."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/fortnite-returning-to-ios-in-europe/">Fortnite to Return to iOS in Europe Following App Store Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-to-return-to-ios-in-europe-following-app-store-changes.2417444/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Upcoming iPad Pro Could Feature Landscape Face ID Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/upcoming-ipad-pro-could-feature-landscape-face-id-camera.2417442/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:45:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> is likely to include a landscape <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> camera, according to code in iOS 17.4 discovered by <a href="https://twitter.com/stevemoser?lang=en"><em>MacRumors</em> contributor Steve Moser</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/ipad-pro-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870696" /><br/>
"During &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; setup, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> needs to be in landscape with the camera at the top of the screen," reads the code.<br/>
<br/>
With the 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Apple relocated the front-facing camera to the side of the device so that it would be usable in landscape mode rather than portrait mode, and it appears that Apple is making this change with future iPads as well.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is the only &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; model that has &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; at the current time, so the code suggests that Apple is relocating the front-facing camera from the top of the device to the side. Apple could, however, be adding &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, so it is also possible that this change applies to that device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has long positioned the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; as an alternative to the Mac, and as a Mac replacement, it is often used in a horizontal orientation rather than a vertical orientation, so relocating the camera makes sense.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple will introduce new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models as soon as April.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/">Upcoming iPad Pro Could Feature Landscape Face ID Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/upcoming-ipad-pro-could-feature-landscape-face-id-camera.2417442/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Limiting Alternative App Stores and Payments to EU Due to Malware, Fraud and Scam Risks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-eu-risks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-limiting-alternative-app-stores-and-payments-to-eu-due-to-malware-fraud-and-scam-risks.2417436/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:52:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-eu-risks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/dma-and-apps-in-the-eu/">developer documentation</a> outlining systemwide changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> in the European Union, Apple explains why alternative app stores, alternative payment options, and other updates are being limited to the EU.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/07/iPhone-Security-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2844" height="1600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-751214" /><br/>
Apple claims that these changes are introducing notable risks for users and developers, introducing "new avenues for malware, fraud and scams, illicit and harmful content, and other privacy and security threats."<br/>
<br/>
Further, Apple says that the updates compromise its ability to "detect, prevent, and take action" against malicious apps, and also to support users impacted by issues with apps that are downloaded outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
"We're limiting these changes to the European Union because we're concerned about their impacts on the privacy and security of our users' experience - which remains our North Star," Apple writes.<br/>
<br/>
To limit risk, Apple is requiring alternative app stores to undergo a notarization process that will check for malware and viruses, but Apple will not evaluate an app's content. Though notarization will add safeguards, Apple says there is risk involved with the alternate app store system.<br/>
<blockquote>If not properly managed, alternative distribution poses increased privacy, safety, and security risks for users and developers. This includes risks from installing software from unknown developers that are not subject to the Apple Developer Program requirements, installing software that compromises system integrity with malware or other malicious code, the distribution of pirated software, exposure to illicit, objectionable, and harmful content due to lower content and moderation standards, and increased risks of scams, fraud, and abuse. Apple has less ability to address these risks, and to support and refund customers regarding these issues. Even with safeguards, many of these risks remain.</blockquote><br/>
Going forward, Apple plans to engage with the European Union, developer community, and EU users about the impacts of alternative app stores.<br/>
<br/>
Outside of the EU, app developers must continue to use the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and in-app purchase system as usual.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/alternative-app-store-eu-risks/">Apple Limiting Alternative App Stores and Payments to EU Due to Malware, Fraud and Scam Risks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-limiting-alternative-app-stores-and-payments-to-eu-due-to-malware-fraud-and-scam-risks.2417436/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Warns That Some Screen Time and Sharing Features Won&#039;t Work With Alternative App Distribution in the EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/features-unavailable-with-alternative-app-stores/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-warns-that-some-screen-time-and-sharing-features-wont-work-with-alternative-app-distribution-in-the-eu.2417433/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:29:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/features-unavailable-with-alternative-app-stores/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in iOS 17.4 will begin allowing apps in the European Union to be distributed through alternative app stores rather than the iOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, but the Cupertino company warns that this means certain features users have come to rely on will not work as they do for standard &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; apps.  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Clorange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833988" /><br/>
Restrictions on In-App Purchases in Screen Time will not be available, for example, nor will Family Purchase Sharing for apps and subscriptions that are made outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Ask to Buy is not a supported feature, and universal purchase, a feature that allows apps to work across all of a user's devices, is not offered. <br/>
<br/>
Apple will not be able to offer these features because it will not be facilitating purchases of apps distributed through alternative app stores. <br/>
<br/>
Screen Time, parental controls, and Spotlight will continue to function, according to Apple, but parents will need to adjust to not having access to purchasing restrictions for apps installed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
Apple also warns that it will not be able to assist users with refunds, purchase history, subscription management and cancelation, violations of user data privacy, abuse, or fraud and manipulations. <br/>
<br/>
Developers or the alternative app marketplace an app was downloaded from will need to handle issues like refunds and subscription cancelations. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users will be able to choose not to install apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, of course, and these changes are limited to users in the European Union. <br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/features-unavailable-with-alternative-app-stores/">Apple Warns That Some Screen Time and Sharing Features Won&#039;t Work With Alternative App Distribution in the EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-warns-that-some-screen-time-and-sharing-features-wont-work-with-alternative-app-distribution-in-the-eu.2417433/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Beta Adds New Emoji: Shaking Head, Lime, Phoenix, Brown Mushroom and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-adds-new-emoji-shaking-head-lime-phoenix-brown-mushroom-and-more.2417425/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 10:42:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iOS 17.4 beta that was released today introduces new emoji characters, which include lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/emojipedia-15-1-emoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903229" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Mockup of new emoji <a href="https://blog.emojipedia.org/whats-new-in-unicode-15-1-and-emoji-15-1/">via Emojipedia</a></div></em><br/>
These characters are part of the Unicode 15.1 update that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ios-17-future-emoji/">approved in September 2023</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There are also four new family emoji combinations, along with updates to six people emoji that now have direction specifications such as facing right or facing left. The direction options can be used with person walking, person running, person kneeling, person with white cane, person in manual wheelchair, and person in motorized wheelchair.<br/>
<br/>
This is a smaller update than we typically get, with fewer emoji characters, but that is because it is a .1 Unicode Consortium update rather than a major point update.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 is limited to developers at the current time, but it should soon be coming to public beta testers. It will see an official launch sometime in March.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/">iOS 17.4 Beta Adds New Emoji: Shaking Head, Lime, Phoenix, Brown Mushroom and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-adds-new-emoji-shaking-head-lime-phoenix-brown-mushroom-and-more.2417425/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Opens Up NFC to Third-Party Apps in EU, Allowing New Tap-to-Pay Options</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-nfc-third-party-apps-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-opens-up-nfc-to-third-party-apps-in-eu-allowing-new-tap-to-pay-options.2417424/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 10:38:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-nfc-third-party-apps-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of major changes being made to the app ecosystem in the EU in iOS 17.4, Apple is allowing apps to access and use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s NFC chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
Going forward, NFC payments will be available directly in apps without the need for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> or the Wallet app, paving the way for third-party payment services and banks to offer their own tap-to-pay solutions on Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users can set a default app that will be activated when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is near an NFC terminal or when the side button on the device is double clicked, which means native support for tap-to-pay payments that are not &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; is now available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will require apps using NFC for payments to confirm to industry security standards, such as having valid agreements with an authorized Payment Service Provider.<br/>
<br/>
This access to NFC technology is limited to banking and wallet apps that are in the European Economic Area, which includes the 27 European Union countries plus Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-nfc-third-party-apps-eu/">Apple Opens Up NFC to Third-Party Apps in EU, Allowing New Tap-to-Pay Options</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-opens-up-nfc-to-third-party-apps-in-eu-allowing-new-tap-to-pay-options.2417424/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Allowing Non-WebKit Engines in EU, Offering More Options for Changing Default Browser</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/third-party-default-browsers-eu-ios-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-allowing-non-webkit-engines-in-eu-offering-more-options-for-changing-default-browser.2417423/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 10:26:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/third-party-default-browsers-eu-ios-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the iOS 17.4 update, Apple is making sweeping changes to iOS in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act in the European Union. Apple is opening up the browser engine, and giving users more choice over what apps and services they use as the defaults on their devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
Users in the EU who update to iOS 17.4 will be presented with a splash screen upon opening Safari that allows them to choose a new default browser. Apple is not providing just the standard browsers that have been options on iOS in the past, but a list of the most downloaded browsers on iOS devices. Some of the options include Firefox, Opera, Chrome, Brave, and Microsoft Edge. <br/>
<br/>
Browser apps can also now use browser engines other than WebKit, both for browser apps and in-app browsing experiences within apps. At the current time, Apple requires all browsers on iOS to use the WebKit engine, including popular options like Chrome and Firefox. Going forward, Chrome will be able to use Blink, for example.<br/>
<br/>
Users will also be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">choose a default app marketplace</a>, thanks to support for alternative marketplaces, and they will be able to select a default contactless app for contactless payments. These changes are limited to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users in the European Union, and they are being implemented as part of iOS 17.4, which is available to developers as a beta as of today.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/third-party-default-browsers-eu-ios-17-4/">Apple Now Allowing Non-WebKit Engines in EU, Offering More Options for Changing Default Browser</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-allowing-non-webkit-engines-in-eu-offering-more-options-for-changing-default-browser.2417423/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Allows Game Streaming Apps on App Store Worldwide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-allows-game-streaming-apps-on-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-allows-game-streaming-apps-on-app-store-worldwide.2417422/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 10:21:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-allows-game-streaming-apps-on-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=f1v8pyay">announced</a> that it now allows streaming game apps on the App Store worldwide, in response to feedback from developers. This will pave the way for services like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW to be available as standalone iPhone and iPad apps, whereas they were previously only accessible via the web.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/App-Store-and-XCloud.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-758525" /><br/>
These cloud gaming apps will allow iPhone and iPad users to stream games from servers, with the entire selection of games available within a single app.<br/>
<br/>
"Developers can now submit a single app with the capability to stream all of the games offered in their catalog," reads Apple's announcement.<br/>
<br/>
Streaming game apps will need to maintain an age rating of the highest age-rated content included in the app, and the apps will of course also need to respect all of the latest App Store Review Guidelines, according to Apple.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-allows-game-streaming-apps-on-app-store/">Apple Now Allows Game Streaming Apps on App Store Worldwide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-allows-game-streaming-apps-on-app-store-worldwide.2417422/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Introduces Alternative App Marketplaces With No Commission in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-introduces-alternative-app-marketplaces-with-no-commission-in-eu.2417417/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 10:00:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced major changes to its app ecosystem in the European Union, implementing updates that will allow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users to download and install apps outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> through alternative app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BAzqrT_hZwA?si=qxN6_mCoQBlHyxPH" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Alternative app marketplaces will function as an iOS app that is able to install other iOS apps on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. Any developer can create an app marketplace, so long as they meet Apple's criteria for customer experience, fraud prevention, customer support, and more. Apple is creating new APIs to build marketplaces on iOS to distribute apps to users. <br/>
<br/>
In the EU, when an app developer submits an app to Apple for distribution, they can choose the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; or any alternative app marketplaces. This includes distribution through multiple alternative app marketplaces or through both the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and an app marketplace. <br/>
<br/>
Apps installed through alternative app stores will need to go through a notarization process that includes safety and security checks, which is how Mac apps work. <br/>
<br/>
Apple will not charge a commission on apps installed through alternative marketplaces, nor will it charge commission for alternative payment systems, which are also allowed under the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; updates in the European Union. Developers can integrate an alternative payment processor into their app that allows a user to make a purchase and check out entirely in an app, or developers can link out to their websites where users can make a purchase. <br/>
<br/>
While there are no commissions for alternative app marketplaces and alternative payment systems, there is a Core Technology Fee that is .50 euros per install per account on an annual basis. The first 1 million installs are free for all developers, but after 1 million installs, the fee comes into play.<br/>
<br/>
App developers who choose to continue to distribute under the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will pay Apple reduced commission with the new terms. Apple is dropping the 30 percent commission to 17 percent, and the 15 percent commission paid for subscriptions over a year old or by small businesses will drop to 10 percent. Apple says the vast majority of apps will qualify for the 10 percent rate. <br/>
<br/>
Developers have a choice between opting into the new business terms in the EU or sticking with the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; terms as they are today. Developers who choose to maintain the status quo will pay the fees they pay now -- 15 to 30 percent commission.<br/>
<br/>
Developers who opt for the updated business terms will pay the reduced commissions, will have access to alternative app stores, and will also be subject to the Core Technology Fee. There is an also optional 3 percent payment processing fee for those who choose to continue to use Apple's integrated payment system rather than an alternative payment system under the new terms. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's Core Technology Fee will be paid annually, and Apple says that the fee reflects the value that developers get from Apple's tools and platform. Apps distributed by government agencies, non-profits, and educational institutions will be exempt from the Core Technology Fee. To help developers decide between the existing policies and the new system, Apple is providing a fee calculator and analytics report for the first annual install metric. <br/>
<br/>
Apple believes that allowing for alternative app installations will bring a major risk to platform integrity, but the measures that it is taking with notarization are aimed at reducing the risk of malware and other issues as much as possible. Apple's automated notarization checks will scan for known viruses and malware, plus there will be a baseline human review to ensure an app meets platform policies for security and privacy.<br/>
<br/>
Unlike &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; review, notarization will not enforce quality or content standards.There will be a system sheet for a notarized app that displays the app's name, screenshots, and more so that a user can verify an app's information before choosing to install it. <br/>
<br/>
Users will be able to install multiple app marketplace apps, and they will need to give permission before an app marketplace can install apps on a device. There is a management system in the Settings app that allows users to revoke permissions for app marketplaces and also, set a default app marketplace on their device.<br/>
<br/>
There are other changes coming as well. Users in the European Union will have an option to choose a default browser after updating to iOS 17.4, with Apple providing a list of the most downloaded browsers. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is giving app developers in the EU access to NFC and allowing for alternative browser engines, so WebKit will not be required for third-party browser apps. Apps will be able to offer NFC payments without using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> or the Wallet app through Host Card Emulation. Apps can also access field detect, and a default app can be set to activate when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is placed near a terminal.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules around <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> gaming are being updated globally to make it easier for users to download and enjoy games. <br/>
<br/>
Developers worldwide have access to expanded analytics, with more than 50 new reports on commerce, user engagement, and more. Data is still anonymized, but developers will have more information to work with.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is making these changes to comply with the European Union's Digital Markets Act, which tech companies need to adhere to by March 6, 2024. iOS 17.4 is coming out as a beta update today, and it is set to see a public release in March.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">iOS 17.4 Introduces Alternative App Marketplaces With No Commission in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-introduces-alternative-app-marketplaces-with-no-commission-in-eu.2417417/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers.2417420/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:59:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 betas to developers for testing purposes, with the updates coming a day after the launches of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/">iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932463" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has a March 6 deadline to introduce app sideloading in the European Union in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act (DMA), and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">iOS 17.4 will add support for this</a>. Sideloading will allow Apple users in Europe to download apps outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, but the change will be limited to the EU and won't impact customers in other parts of the world. <br/>
<br/>
There's no word yet on what else is included in iOS 17.4, but Apple's updates around this time often introduce new emoji characters. If there are indeed new emoji in the update, we can expect to see the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ios-17-future-emoji/">Unicode 15.1 additions</a>, which include phoenix, lime, an edible mushroom, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake), and broken chain.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers.2417420/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Beta of tvOS 17.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/tvos-17-4-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-17-4-to-developers.2417421/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:58:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/tvos-17-4-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.4 to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a day after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-tvos-17-3/">release of tvOS 17.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.4 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.4.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/tvos-17-4-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Beta of tvOS 17.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-17-4-to-developers.2417421/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some Macs Auto-Updating to macOS Sonoma Without User Permission</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/some-macs-auto-updating-to-macos-sonoma/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-macs-auto-updating-to-macos-sonoma-without-user-permission.2417410/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:14:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/some-macs-auto-updating-to-macos-sonoma/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Ventura</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks, some Mac users have complained that their computer automatically upgraded itself from macOS Ventura to the latest macOS Sonoma release, even with the automatic updates setting turned off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" /><br/>
There are widespread complaints about this issue across the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255413533">Apple Support Community</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ventura-magically-updated-to-sonoma.2416284/">MacRumors Forums</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/MacOS/comments/193tmio/macos_monterey_automatically_updated_to_sonoma/">Reddit</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/macz_music/status/1748747516839936403">X</a>, and <a href="https://www.askwoody.com/forums/topic/forced-upgrade-to-macos-sonoma/">other</a> <a href="https://talk.tidbits.com/t/apple-just-force-upgraded-me-to-sonoma/26342">websites</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In most cases, it appears that affected users received a desktop notification alerting them that macOS Sonoma was an available software update. However, despite dismissing the notification and having automatic updates turned off, affected users said their Mac proceeded to install macOS Sonoma regardless. Apple began showing the notification to users on January 10, according to <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The underlying cause of the issue is unclear, and an Apple spokesperson did not immediately respond to a request for comment.<br/>
<br/>
It is possible to downgrade a Mac to an older macOS version by using a bootable installer to erase and install the older version and then restoring your data from a Time Machine backup. Always make sure to back up your data before downgrading a Mac.<br/>
<br/>
To review your Mac's update settings, open the System Settings app, click General → Software Update, and click the info symbol next to Automatic Updates.<br/>
<br/>
We will update this report if new information becomes available.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-ventura.239">macOS Ventura</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/some-macs-auto-updating-to-macos-sonoma/">Some Macs Auto-Updating to macOS Sonoma Without User Permission</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-macs-auto-updating-to-macos-sonoma-without-user-permission.2417410/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
