<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:10:28 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Experimenting With New Generative AI Features for YouTube</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/generative-ai-tools-youtube/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-experimenting-with-new-generative-ai-features-for-youtube.2410105/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:00:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/generative-ai-tools-youtube/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google <a href="https://support.google.com/youtube/thread/242690316/testing-new-experimental-generative-ai-features">today announced</a> that it is testing two new generative AI features designed to improve the YouTube viewing experience. A select number of YouTube users will have access to these new additions during Google's testing period.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/google-ai-youtube.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921299" /><br/>
For YouTube videos with long comment threads, YouTube will use artificial intelligence to organize them into themes or comment topics to facilitate conversation. Google says that creators can use these comment summaries to jump into comment discussions or draw inspiration for new content.<br/>
<br/>
Topics are pulled from published comments, and will not be created from comments held for review or that include blocked words. The comment test is being done on mobile, so users who have access will see a star topic on a small number of videos in English.<br/>
<br/>
YouTube is also gaining a conversational AI tool that is able to provide answers to questions about the video that you're watching. It can provide background information, offer up suggestions for related content, and more, without interrupting playback. For academic videos, the AI is able to provide quizzes and responses that Google says "encourage deeper understanding."<br/>
<br/>
Conversational AI is available to a small number of people on a subset of videos, and those who have access will see a star icon.<br/>
<br/>
While some users have access to these options for test purposes, YouTube Premium subscribers <a href="https://www.youtube.com/new">can opt in to these new features</a> as the YouTube Premium subscription includes access to experimental features. Comment topics are available to premium members today, while the conversational AI option will be available in the coming weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Google says that the AI features are experimental and that the company "may not always get it right," which is why these tests are available to a limited number of customers as Google collects feedback.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/generative-ai-tools-youtube/">Google Experimenting With New Generative AI Features for YouTube</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-experimenting-with-new-generative-ai-features-for-youtube.2410105/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Final Cut Pro Gaining New Features on Mac and iPad Later This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/final-cut-pro-gaining-new-features-on-mac-and-ipad-later-this-month.2410097/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:17:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/final-cut-pro-for-mac-and-ipad-get-powerful-updates/">today announced upcoming updates</a> for Final Cut Pro, with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Mac apps set to gain new features that Apple says will streamline workflows.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/final-cut-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921303" /><br/>
Final Cut Pro on the Mac will be updated with organizational refinements like automatic timeline scrolling. Users will be able to keep their clips in view during playback, with the view able to be adjusted using keyboard shortcuts or the Zoom option.<br/>
<br/>
The organization of the timeline will be viewable at a glance, and it will be easier to differentiate clips by assigned role using distinct colors. Apple is also adding tools for cleaning up complex timeline sections and fine tuning edits by combining overlapping connected clips into a single connected storyline.<br/>
<br/>
On Apple silicon Macs, exporting projects in H.264 and HEVC will be faster than before as Final Cut Pro is able to send video segments to available media engines for simultaneous processing.<br/>
<br/>
On the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, the updated version of Final Cut Pro will include voiceover capabilities that will let creators record narration and audio directly into the timeline with the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. In pro camera mode, stabilization will now improve shaky footage for smoother video, and there are new options for combining connected clips.<br/>
<br/>
Editing is being sped up through new keyboard shortcuts for voiceover and grouping clips, plus there are new color-grading presets and titles.<br/>
<br/>
The new versions of Final Cut Pro will be coming to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> later this month and they will be free to existing users. Final Cut Pro for Mac is priced at &#36;300, and Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is priced at &#36;4.99 per month or &#36;49 per year.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-new-features/">Final Cut Pro Gaining New Features on Mac and iPad Later This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/final-cut-pro-gaining-new-features-on-mac-and-ipad-later-this-month.2410097/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First M3 MacBook Pro and iMac Orders Begin Arriving to Customers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/first-m3-mac-orders-australia-nz/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-orders-begin-arriving-to-customers.2410091/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 13:42:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/first-m3-mac-orders-australia-nz/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When new products launch, Apple fans in Australia and New Zealand are always the first to get their hands on updated devices because of their time zone. It is Tuesday, November 7 in those two countries, which means customers who ordered a new M3 MacBook Pro or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> are now beginning to receive their shipments.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919851" /><br/>
Apple customers will soon be sharing photos and first impressions of the New Macs on Instagram, Twitter, Reddit, and the <em>MacRumors</em> forums. If you've received a new Mac, make sure to let us know your thoughts in the comments below!<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the new Macs at its "Scary Fast" event on October 30, which was the first nighttime event that Apple has held. Apple debuted the M3-series chips, and it also marked the first time that standard, Pro, and Max Apple silicon chips have been introduced at the same time.<br/>
<br/>
The 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models can be purchased with the M3, M3 Pro, or M3 Max chip, while the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; has the M3. Today's orders will feature the M3 and M3 Pro machines, as the MacBook Pro models with M3 Max had delivery dates ranging from November 9 to November 13 when Apple first began accepting orders. We won't see customers with the initial M3 Max MacBook Pro orders until later this week.<br/>
<br/>
Apple made no design updates to the MacBook Pro or the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; when it refreshed the chips inside. The MacBook Pro models also received a minor display update to increase the SDR brightness by 100 nits, while the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; also got support for Wi-Fi 6E, more maximum memory, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
Built on 3-nanometer technology, the M3 chips have a next-generation GPU with support for hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading, along with Dynamic Caching for improved GPU utilization. According to Apple, the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips are up to 50 percent faster than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>, &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro, and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
New Zealand does not have any Apple retail stores, so customers in Australia will be the first to be able to pick up one of the new Macs in an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>. We are not expecting supply shortages, and the updated machines should be readily available for those who want one. Note that Apple Stores offer stock configurations, so customers who want to upgrade the memory, SSD, or chip will need to order a custom machine online.<br/>
<br/>
Following New Zealand and Australia, sales and deliveries of the new Macs will kick off in Asia, the Middle East, Europe, Africa, and finally, North and South America. Make sure to stay tuned to <em>MacRumors</em> because we'll have a hands-on and unboxing tomorrow, as well as deeper looks at the performance of the new machines.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/first-m3-mac-orders-australia-nz/">First M3 MacBook Pro and iMac Orders Begin Arriving to Customers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-orders-begin-arriving-to-customers.2410091/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Likely to Release iOS 17.1.1 This Week With iPhone Bug Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/ios-17-1-1-likely-to-be-released-this-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-to-release-ios-17-1-1-this-week-with-iphone-bug-fixes.2410080/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:16:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/ios-17-1-1-likely-to-be-released-this-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A minor iOS 17.1.1 update is likely to be released for the iPhone this week, as a protected account with a proven track record shared the build number 21B91 for the update today on X, formerly known as Twitter. The account typically shares build numbers for upcoming iOS updates less than a week before they are released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-17.1.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920500" /><br/>
Last week, we were first to report that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/ios-17-1-1-is-coming/">internally testing iOS 17.1.1</a>, based on evidence of the software version in our website's analytics logs. The update will almost certainly be focused on bug fixes and security patches.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear exactly which bugs will be addressed in iOS 17.1.1. The update might include the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/ios-17-2-beta-addresses-wifi-issues/">fix for Wi-Fi connectivity issues</a> that Apple rolled out in the iOS 17.2 beta, and it could resolve an issue where <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/ios-17-1-shutdown-bug-no-fix/">some iPhones temporarily shut off overnight</a> for users still experiencing that. Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-to-fix-iphone-15-bmw-charging-issue/">promised to fix a BMW wireless charging issue</a> affecting the iPhone 15 lineup in an unspecified update coming later this year.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 remains in beta testing, and it is expected to be released in December. That update includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">many new features and changes</a>, including Apple's promised Journal app, the ability for Apple Music subscribers to collaborate on playlists, a Translate option for the Action button on iPhone 15 Pro models, an iMessage Contact Key Verification security option, additional Weather and Clock widgets, and more.<br/>
<br/>
We also reported that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/watchos-update-to-fix-battery-drain-issue/">preparing to release a watchOS update soon</a> with a fix for excessive Apple Watch battery drain. It's likely that update will be watchOS 10.1.1, but it could be watchOS 10.2 if Apple needs more time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/ios-17-1-1-likely-to-be-released-this-week/">Apple Likely to Release iOS 17.1.1 This Week With iPhone Bug Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-to-release-ios-17-1-1-this-week-with-iphone-bug-fixes.2410080/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the New USB-C Apple Pencil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/usb-c-apple-pencil-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-usb-c-apple-pencil.2410075/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:46:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/usb-c-apple-pencil-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last week began shipping out the new USB-C <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, so we thought we'd check it out for <em>MacRumors</em> readers who might be interested in purchasing one. The USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is compatible with all iPads that have a USB-C port and that are running iOS 17.1 or later. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MbuXDZ_VKRA" title="New Apple Pencil (USB-C) - Unboxing &amp; Hands-On!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
When it comes to design and feel, the USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is much like the second-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, featuring a matte finish and a flat side where it can attach to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, but it's worth noting that it's shorter. Unlike the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2, it is not able to pair with an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; automatically, and you'll need a USB-C cable for pairing purposes. <br/>
<br/>
If you pull on the bottom of the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, you'll reveal a USB-C port, but Apple does not include a cable so you will need to use your own. Pairing can be done by attaching a USB-C to USB-C cable to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and the USB-C port. <br/>
<br/>
Though the USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; can be placed on the top of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; thanks to the magnetic connection, it is not able to charge magnetically like the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2. As with pairing, charging is done via USB-C. <br/>
<br/>
The USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is the most affordable &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; option at &#36;79, but it lacks Double Tap for swapping tools, and there is no pressure sensitivity for varying line thickness. It does support tilt functionality and the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Hover gesture that's available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models. <br/>
<br/>
What do you think of the USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;? Let us know in the comments. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/usb-c-apple-pencil-hands-on/">Hands-On With the New USB-C Apple Pencil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-usb-c-apple-pencil.2410075/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Developing Custom Batteries for Launch in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/apple-developing-custom-batteries-for-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-developing-custom-batteries-for-launch-in-2025.2410051/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:58:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/apple-developing-custom-batteries-for-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is developing custom batteries with significantly improved performance that it aims to bring to its devices starting in 2025, <a href="https://m.etnews.com/20231106000233"><em>ETNews</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macbook-air-spacegray-purple-battery.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913843" /><br/>
Apple's custom battery technology has reportedly been in the works since 2018, with the company actively seeking patents and hiring new personnel related to the project. The company is reportedly seeking to create an "all-new" kind of battery with significantly improved performance by becoming directly involved in its use of materials.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is apparently curating the battery's cathode materials to determine its performance, energy density, output, and stability. The battery apparently uses a completely different composition from those that currently exist on the market, adopting a new composition of nickel, cobalt, manganese, and aluminum. <br/>
<br/>
The company is considering the use of carbon nanotubes to improve the conductivity of battery materials, delivering better performance from lesser-used battery materials. Apple is also looking to increase its battery's silicon content, replacing graphite to increase capacity, and shorten charging and discharging times.<br/>
<br/>
The result is expected to be an innovative battery type that has not yet been commercialized. A source familiar with Apple's plans suggested to <em>ETNews</em> that the Vision Pro headset has dramatically increased the company's need for high-performance batteries. The headset features just two hours of battery life. Other devices such as the Apple Watch and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> have been left with the same "all-day" battery life since their introduction.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's custom battery project was reportedly co-developed with the company's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">electric vehicle project</a>, but the mobile applications are now the main target for the technology. It is expected to begin being added to Apple devices starting in 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/apple-developing-custom-batteries-for-2025/">Report: Apple Developing Custom Batteries for Launch in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-developing-custom-batteries-for-launch-in-2025.2410051/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker Black Friday Early Access Sale Has Sitewide Savings on USB-C Accessories, MagSafe Chargers, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/anker-black-friday-early-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-black-friday-early-access-sale-has-sitewide-savings-on-usb-c-accessories-magsafe-chargers-and-more.2410050/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:52:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/anker-black-friday-early-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anker is back with another pre-Black Friday discount event on its website, which it's calling the "<a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu">Black Friday Early Access Sale</a>." When you purchase two or more Anker items, you'll get 25 percent off your order. Additionally, there are numerous straight cash discounts on dozens of Anker accessories during the event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/anker-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921182" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
There are plenty of great accessories that you can buy to take advantage of the bundle savings, including the new MagSafe-compatible <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/y1811?ref=black-friday-sale">Anker 3-in-1 Charging Cube</a> (&#36;149.95). This device has space to simultaneously charge an iPhone, Apple Watch, and AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
There's also the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1336-20000mah-power-bank?ref=black-friday-sale&amp;variant=42691854925974">Anker Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> (&#36;129.99). Although this one is on sale at &#36;110.49 without the bundle deal, if you buy this and the 3-in-1 Cube together, you'll net a bigger discount. The Power Bank will be knocked down to &#36;97.50 and the 3-in-1 Cube will go down to &#36;112.46 thanks to the 25 percent savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">25% OFF</div>Anker Black Friday Early Access</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you scroll down on the main sale page, you'll find Anker's suggestions for the Black Friday Early Access event. This includes dozens of products that are being discounted without needing to be bundled if you're only looking for one specific device.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Wall Chargers</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2668?variant=41974350315670">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;37.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2669-3-port-wall-charger">67W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;59.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469063005">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2340?variant=41974288777366">150W 4-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;87.99, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2342-240w-gan-charger?variant=42691851550870">Prime 240W 4-Port Desktop Charger</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Portable Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1653-usb-c-portable-charger-5000mah">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.50, down from &#36;29.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK77HJ">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1268">PowerCore 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;36.52, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1651">PowerCore 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1289">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/b1291">PowerCore 26,000 mAh</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1336-20000mah-power-bank">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;110.49, down from &#36;129.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469007512">Amazon</a>]</li></ul> <br/>
<strong>Portable Power Stations</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1751">PowerHouse 535</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1761">SOLIX C1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;749.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1770111">PowerHouse 757</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1780">PowerHouse 767</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul> We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/anker-black-friday-early-sale/">Anker Black Friday Early Access Sale Has Sitewide Savings on USB-C Accessories, MagSafe Chargers, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-black-friday-early-access-sale-has-sitewide-savings-on-usb-c-accessories-magsafe-chargers-and-more.2410050/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Logic Pro for Mac and iPad Updated With New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/logic-pro-for-mac-updated/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logic-pro-for-mac-and-ipad-updated-with-new-features.2410047/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:11:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/logic-pro-for-mac-updated/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Logic Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/apple-supercharges-logic-pro-for-mac-and-ipad/">announced</a> it has updated its professional music creation app Logic Pro for the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/logic-pro/id634148309">Mac</a> and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/logic-pro-for-ipad/id1615087040">iPad</a> with new features and enhancements, including support for Split View and Stage Manager on the iPad. The updates are available now on the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/MacBook-Pro-Logic-Pro-2023.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921238" /><br/>
The release notes for Logic Pro version 10.8 for the Mac:<blockquote>• Deliver a release-ready mix with Mastering Assistant and its professional palette of intuitive sound-shaping tools<br/>
• Transform any audio sample into a malleable sound that you can perform using Sample Alchemy<br/>
• Radically reshape and reshuffle audio with Beat Breaker, a sophisticated time and pitch morphing plug-in<br/>
• New Slip and Rotate tools allow for the contents inside a region to be moved independent of its position on the timeline<br/>
• Ability to record in 32-bit float now available when using supported audio devices<br/>
• Free "Hybrid Textures" Sample Alchemy pack includes a collection of 70 patches and over 80 loops built from found sounds flipped into creative playable instruments</blockquote>The release notes for Logic Pro version 1.1 for the iPad:<blockquote>• Deliver a release-ready mix with Mastering Assistant and its professional palette of intuitive sound-shaping tools<br/>
• Record live into Quick Sampler to create instruments and drum kits using the built-in microphone or any connected audio device<br/>
• Interact seamlessly between apps like Voice Memos with added support for Split View and Stage Manager<br/>
• Select and drag multiple files at once from the Files app to quickly build drum kits or add stems to a project<br/>
• Instantly audition samples, loops or instruments in the Browser by sliding your finger up or down<br/>
• Free "Hybrid Textures" Sample Alchemy pack includes a collection of 70 patches and over 80 loops built from found sounds flipped into creative playable instruments</blockquote>Logic Pro costs &#36;199.99 for the Mac and &#36;4.99 per month for the iPad. More details about the new features can be found in <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/apple-supercharges-logic-pro-for-mac-and-ipad/">Apple's press release</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Logic Pro companion app MainStage and GarageBand for the Mac were also both updated with stability improvements and bug fixes.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/logic-pro/">Logic Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/logic-pro-for-mac-updated/">Logic Pro for Mac and iPad Updated With New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logic-pro-for-mac-and-ipad-updated-with-new-features.2410047/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New MacBook Pro Reviews: Scary Fast, But M3 Pro Chip Has a Catch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-pro-reviews-scary-fast-but-m3-pro-chip-has-a-catch.2410039/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:24:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-pro&#038;post_date=1699295092/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last week, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-m3-macbook-pros/">updated the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models</a> with M3 Pro and M3 Max chips for faster performance. There is also an entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the standard M3 chip. Other new features include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">Space Black finish</a> for M3 Pro and M3 Max configurations, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/new-macbook-pros-20-percent-brighter-displays/">20% brighter displays</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
The new MacBook Pro models will begin arriving to customers and launch in stores on Tuesday, November 7, although M3 Max configurations do not launch until a few days later. Ahead of time, the first reviews of the laptops have been shared by select media outlets and YouTube channels, and we have rounded up some of them below.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Written Reviews</h2><br/>
Geekbench 6 benchmark results for the new MacBook Pro models already leaked last week. The results showed that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-chip-benchmark-results/">M3 chip is up to 20% faster than the M2 chip</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/m3-pro-chip-benchmark-result/">M3 Pro is up to 6% faster than the M2 Pro</a>, and the M3 Max is up to 50% faster than the M2 Max and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-max-chip-benchmark-results/">roughly on par with the M2 Ultra chip</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/computing/apple-macbook-pro-16-late-2023-review-max-power-for-creators/"><em>CNET</em>'s Lori Grunin</a> on M3 vs. M3 Max performance:<blockquote>For a sense of practical scale within the M3 line, the MacBook Pro 14 with the base processor took just under 20 minutes to import (with lens corrections on import) and simultaneously create full-resolution previews of around 1,000 raw+JPEG photos and videos; the MacBook 16 Pro took just over 8.5 minutes. Lightroom import and thumbnail generation is CPU and memory-bound, which explains much of the difference.</blockquote>Both the M2 Pro and M3 Pro are equipped with up to a 12-core CPU, but the M3 Pro has two fewer high-performance CPU cores. So while the M3 Pro is manufactured with TSMC's improved 3nm process, compared to 5nm for the M2 Pro, the chip's resulting performance gains are diminished due to this change. Apple says the M3 Pro also has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/apple-m3-pro-less-memory-bandwidth/">25% less memory bandwidth</a> and one fewer GPU core compared to the M2 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
M3 series chips offer not only performance and power efficiency improvements over M2 series chips, but they also have an upgraded GPU with support for hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for improved graphics rendering in games.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/11/review-apples-16-inch-m3-max-macbook-pro-crams-ultra-level-speed-into-a-laptop/"><em>Ars Technica</em>'s Andrew Cunningham</a> on M3 Max graphics performance:<blockquote>Graphics performance also sees a solid boost, more than you'd expect from just a pair of extra GPU cores. The M3 Max benchmarks around 50 percent faster than the M1 Max—and playing Baldur's Gate 3 on it with all the settings turned up was actually by-and-large a pleasant experience. The Mac still isn't a viable AAA game platform for most people, but Apple does seem to be trying, and if it ever succeeds, the M3 Max will be up for it.</blockquote>Apple says the new Space Black finish features an "anodization seal" to "greatly reduce fingerprints," presumably compared to the MacBook Air's dark Midnight finish. Based on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">hands-on videos shared following Apple's event</a>, the new anti-fingerprint seal does appear to be an improvement compared to the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/extras/indybest/gadgets-tech/laptops-tablets/apple-macbook-pro-m3-review-b2442362.html"><em>The Independent</em>'s David Phelan</a> on the Space Black finish and fingerprints:<blockquote>When Apple announced the new space black version, it made a big deal out of one aspect: although it's a matte finish, it doesn't collect fingerprints. Apple says this is down to what it calls "breakthrough chemistry" – there's an anodization seal that reduces fingerprint marks. Whatever the science, it really works. Marks may not vanish completely but they are very hard to spot.</blockquote><a href="https://mobilesyrup.com/2023/11/06/apple-m3-max-macbook-pro-imac-benchmarks/"><em>MobileSyrup</em>'s Patrick O'Rourke</a>:<blockquote>What's most notable about Space Black is the anodization seal that prevents most grease and smudges from getting on the laptop. When Apple mentioned this during its keynote, I assumed it was just marketing, but to my surprise, it was tough to get grease to appear on the Space Black M3 MacBook Pro I've been using for the last few days. If your hands are exceptionally grimy, it's still possible and isn't entirely as perfect as I initially thought, but it happens so infrequently it's shocking.</blockquote>Apple's tech specs indicate that all of the new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models provide up to 600 nits of peak brightness for standard/SDR content, which is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/new-macbook-pros-20-percent-brighter-displays/">20% increase</a> over the 500 nits maximum on the previous models. This means the laptops now have the same peak brightness as Apple's Studio Display.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.tomshardware.com/laptops/apple-16-inch-macbook-pro-late-2023"><em>Tom's Hardware</em>'s Brandon Hill</a> on the brighter display:<blockquote>In SDR content, brightness maxed out at 563 nits, which confirms Apple's assertion of a 20 percent boost compared to the previous generation. Switching to HDR content, we hit a maximum of 1539 nits with 40 percent coverage, compared to 1,470 nits for the older model.</blockquote><h2>Video Reviews</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/My32TaofRkI?si=wLleafqtibQUJ28G" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/18xMsdrdKuM?si=TddvIsDFenqRCIGV" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qie7cfjnLAY?si=9OleH2R9fEAM7mTg" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6BYFofUbeDk?si=HoqAwslwKK9lXODi" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/P0sVCUWJ6VU?si=JFeh_Usj2FIIbkrP" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-macbook-pro/">New MacBook Pro Reviews: Scary Fast, But M3 Pro Chip Has a Catch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-pro-reviews-scary-fast-but-m3-pro-chip-has-a-catch.2410039/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 iMac Reviews: Impressive Chip Performance but Lightning Accessories Disappoint</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-imac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-imac-reviews-impressive-chip-performance-but-lightning-accessories-disappoint.2410028/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:26:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-imac&#038;post_date=1699291566/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last week, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-m3-macbook-pros/">updated the 24-inch iMac</a>, with the headline upgrade being the M3 chip for significantly improved performance. Other new features include Wi-Fi 6E, Bluetooth 5.3, and up to 24GB of unified memory.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iMac-M3-Blue-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-917291" /><br/>
<br/>
The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> can be purchased from the Apple's online store, with prices starting at &#36;1,299. Apple began accepting orders on October 30, and new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; will begin arriving to customers and launch in stores on Tuesday, November 7.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-vs-m3-imac/">M1 vs. M3 iMac Buyer's Guide: 15+ Differences Compared</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Ahead of time, the first reviews of the laptops have been shared by select media outlets and YouTube channels, and we have rounded up some of them below.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Written Reviews</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.techradar.com/computing/macs/apple-imac-24-inch-m3-review"><em>TechRadar</em></a>'s Matt Hanson pointed out the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/magic-accessories-still-feature-lightning/">continued use of Lightning ports</a> on its Magic Keyboard, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Mouse:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Sticking to the same design also brings back some old frustrations, such as the charging port on the bottom of the Magic Mouse, which means you can't use it while it's charging, plus a reliance on the increasingly obsolete Lightning connection for charging all of the peripherals, rather than getting with the times and using USB-C. </blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/11/06/apple-imac-m3-review/"><em>TechCrunch</em></a>'s Brian Heater downplayed the significance of the continued use of the Lightning port, but emphasised that it was time for Apple to move on:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Apple's desktop accessories are one of the few remaining vestiges of a connector that's past its prime. It largely won't bother you. There's less daily wear, as most people don't plug and unplug their keyboards and trackpads at the same rate they do their phones. Also, you're probably not going to get pocket lint jammed in there. Still, it's time for to Apple rip off the Band-Aid off, once and for all.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Early Geekbench 6 benchmark results indicated that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-chip-benchmark-results/">M3 chip is up to 40% faster than the M1</a> used in the previous &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; from 2021.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.digitaltrends.com/computing/apple-imac-m3-review/"><em>Digital Trends</em></a>'s Luke Larsen on the performance improvements delivered by the M3 chip:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Moving from the M1 to the M3 is a big jump. Even if you think the performance changes between each individual generation aren't too exciting, skipping one adds up to a noticeable difference.<br/>
<br/>
When you look at Cinebench R23 scores, the M3 is a whopping 20% faster in both single-core and multi-core. That's massive. It means no matter what the strenuous task is, the M3 iMac will be at least 20% faster. A good example is a simple video encoding test in Handbrake. The M3 iMac encoded the same video to H.265 27% faster than the M1 iMac.<br/>
<br/>
It shows how far Apple has taken these chips in just a few generations, especially on the GPU front. I was sent the 10-core GPU model, and with the inclusion of Dynamic Caching, this little iMac is a pretty solid little engine for graphics. In the Cinebench 2024 GPU test, it was 35% faster than the M1 Pro in a 14-inch MacBook Pro despite having six less GPU cores. Meanwhile, the M3 iMac beats the M2 Pro in the Mac mini by 20% in this same graphics test. Again, I think you can credit Dynamic Caching for doing a lot of the heavy lifting in that comparison.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip is among Apple's first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> chips. The M3 chip features eight CPU cores like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip, but it now offers an eight- or 10-core GPU, rather than the seven- or eight-core GPU of the &zwnj;M1&zwnj;. It also features a 4.05 GHz CPU clock speed, up from 3.20 GHz on the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip, more memory bandwidth, support for AV1 decode, and a new GPU architecture with Dynamic Caching, hardware-accelerated ray tracing, and hardware-accelerated mesh shading.<br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://www.tomshardware.com/desktops/apple-imac-2023">Tom's Hardware</a></em>'s Brandon Hill on the 2023 &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; as a whole:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>The iMac has always been a reasonably economical system for Mac users who want "just the basics" in an everyday computer. The screen is large, bright, and colorful. The minimalist design blends in with just about any décor (and you can choose from various colors to match), and the new Apple M3 chip provides a big jump in performance compared to the M1 model that debuted in 2021.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, there are quite a few "gotchas" here. While the &#36;1,299 starting price is enticing, you're saddled with just 8GB of unified memory and a 256GB SSD. That's hardly enough to futureproof the iMac. A simple upgrade to 16GB of memory costs a staggering &#36;200, while storage upgrades are equally pricey.<br/>
<br/>
If you want Gigabit Ethernet, that's a &#36;30 upcharge, and you only get two Thunderbolt 4 ports on base systems. You must spend at least &#36;1,499 to get two Thunderbolt 4 ports and two USB 3 ports.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's iMac is an excellent all-in-one macOS machine, though it's in need of a rethink when it comes to its pricing and available configurations.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Video Reviews</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BfmclAxSPKQ?si=csK1CRYxGOBnCuwp" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kBZ6kW8G8Y8?si=MY40OqmYiTN0qkna" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/w6HwaSwfYbc?si=Zt9MZvH_mfKdPbt_" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/m3-imac/">M3 iMac Reviews: Impressive Chip Performance but Lightning Accessories Disappoint</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-imac-reviews-impressive-chip-performance-but-lightning-accessories-disappoint.2410028/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says There Won&#039;t Be a 27-Inch iMac With Apple Silicon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/no-27-inch-with-apple-silicon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-there-wont-be-a-27-inch-imac-with-apple-silicon.2410027/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:05:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/no-27-inch-with-apple-silicon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac Pro</category>
		<category>2025 iMac Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/6/23947196/apple-no-27-inch-apple-silicon-imac">confirmed to <em>The Verge</em></a> and some other publications that it has no plans to release a new 27-inch iMac with Apple silicon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iMac-Pro-2022-27-and-24-iMac.jpg" alt="" width="1626" height="914" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833952" /><br/>
Apple discontinued both the Intel-based 27-inch iMac and iMac Pro over the past two years, and it has yet to launch a larger-screen iMac with an Apple silicon chip as a replacement, leaving the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-imac-with-m3-chip/">recently-updated 24-inch iMac</a> with the M3 chip as its only all-in-one desktop computer. For customers who want a larger or higher-end desktop, Apple recommends pairing the 27-inch Studio Display with a Mac Studio or Mac mini.<br/>
<br/>
From the report:<blockquote>Apple will not be making an Apple Silicon version of the 27-inch iMac to replace the Intel-equipped model that it discontinued in 2022. The company is instead focusing the iMac line around the 24-inch model that was first released in early 2021 and just updated with the new M3 processor this fall.<br/>
<br/>
Apple PR representative Starlayne Meza confirmed the company's plans to The Verge. The company encourages those who have been holding out hope for a larger iMac to consider the Studio Display and Mac Studio or Mac mini.</blockquote>Apple has only ruled out a new 27-inch iMac, so a larger-screened iMac is still possible. Last month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said Apple was still <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/new-32-inch-imac-pro-expected-2024-or-2025/">developing an iMac Pro with a 32-inch display</a> for release in late 2024 or in 2025. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">also expects</a> a 32-inch iMac with mini-LED display backlighting to launch in 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-imac-pro/">2025 iMac Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/no-27-inch-with-apple-silicon/">Apple Says There Won&#039;t Be a 27-Inch iMac With Apple Silicon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-there-wont-be-a-27-inch-imac-with-apple-silicon.2410027/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expected to Update Entire iPad Lineup Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/all-ipads-expected-to-be-updated-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expected-to-update-entire-ipad-lineup-next-year.2409944/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 08:41:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/all-ipads-expected-to-be-updated-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to update its entire iPad lineup throughout 2024, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-11-05/apple-vision-pro-plan-includes-launching-initially-just-at-apple-stores-in-2024"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. This means new models of the iPad Pro, iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad can be expected to launch next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
Gurman touched on the lack of new iPads and AirPods heading into the holiday shopping season in the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-11-05/apple-vision-pro-plan-includes-launching-initially-just-at-apple-stores-in-2024"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a>:<blockquote>Apple could have tried to rush out more new products, but revamped iPads and AirPods aren’t yet ready. The company plans to update its entire iPad lineup during 2024. New low-end AirPods are coming next year as well, with a refreshed Pro model following in 2025.</blockquote>2023 is expected to be the first year without any new iPads released since Apple first unveiled the device in 2010, so updates to all models next year sounds likely.<br/>
<br/>
When each iPad model was last updated:<ul><li><strong>iPad Pro:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPad:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPad Air:</strong> March 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPad mini:</strong> September 2021</li></ul>Gurman previously reported that the low-end to mid-range iPads <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-march-2024-launch/">could be updated as early as March 2024</a>, while he expects new 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro models with the M3 chip and OLED displays to launch in the first half of 2024. The next iPad Air and iPad mini are likely to be equipped with M2 and A16 Bionic chips, respectively.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/all-ipads-expected-to-be-updated-in-2024/">Apple Expected to Update Entire iPad Lineup Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expected-to-update-entire-ipad-lineup-next-year.2409944/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 Pro Chip Barely Faster Than M2 Pro in Unverified Benchmark Result</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/m3-pro-chip-benchmark-result/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-pro-chip-barely-faster-than-m2-pro-in-unverified-benchmark-result.2409903/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 22:05:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/m3-pro-chip-benchmark-result/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Geekbench</category>
		<category>Benchmarks</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new M3 Pro chip with a 12-core CPU offers only marginally faster CPU performance compared to the M2 Pro chip with a 12-core CPU, according to a <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/v6/cpu/3390128">Geekbench 6 result</a> spotted today by <a href="https://twitter.com/VadimYuryev/status/1720982471062491428">Vadim Yuryev</a>, co-host of the YouTube channel <a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/maxtechofficial">Max Tech</a>. This is only a single benchmark result, so further results are needed to ensure accuracy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Pro-Chip-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1405" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-921224" /><br/>
Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-m3-macbook-pros/">new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models</a> with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips on Monday. This benchmark result <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1719775450963095885">appears to be</a> for the 14-inch model, based on the "Mac15,6" model identifier listed.<br/>
<br/>
The result shows the M3 Pro has a single-core score of 3,035 and a multi-core score of 15,173. If these scores are accurate, the M3 Pro is up to 14% faster than the M2 Pro in terms of single-core performance, but only up to 6% faster <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/macs/macbook-pro-14-inch-2023-m2-pro-12c-cpu">in terms of multi-core performance</a> for the most demanding tasks and workflows.<br/>
<br/>
Both the M2 Pro and M3 Pro are equipped with up to a 12-core CPU, but the M3 Pro has only six high-performance cores and six efficiency cores, while the M2 Pro has eight high-performance cores and four efficiency cores. So while the M3 Pro is manufactured with TSMC's 3nm process, compared to 5nm for the M2 Pro, the chip's resulting performance gains are diminished due to it having two fewer performance cores. The M3 Pro also has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/apple-m3-pro-less-memory-bandwidth/">25% less memory bandwidth</a> and one fewer GPU core compared to the M2 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
By limiting the M3 Pro's number of high-performance cores, Apple has created more differentiation between the M3 Pro and the M3 Max, which has up to 12 high-performance cores. However, as a result, the M3 Pro is only marginally faster than the M2 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Geekbench 6 results from earlier this week showed that the M3 Max is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-max-chip-benchmark-results/">up to 45% faster than the M2 Max</a>, while the standard M3 chip is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-chip-benchmark-results/">up to 20% faster than the standard M2 chip</a>, so the M3 Pro is by far the least improved chip of the series. Of course, the M3 Pro is still a significant upgrade for those coming from an Intel-based Mac. M3 Pro is also up to 20% faster than the M1 Pro chip, which is a decent improvement.<br/>
<br/>
As always, benchmarks provide a useful reference point, but real-world performance can vary.<br/>
<br/>
The new MacBook Pro models are available to order now, and M3 and M3 Pro configurations will begin arriving to customers and launch in stores on Tuesday, November 7. M3 Max configurations will launch a few days later.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/geekbench/">Geekbench</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/benchmarks/">Benchmarks</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/m3-pro-chip-benchmark-result/">M3 Pro Chip Barely Faster Than M2 Pro in Unverified Benchmark Result</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-pro-chip-barely-faster-than-m2-pro-in-unverified-benchmark-result.2409903/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS Update Coming Soon With Fix for Apple Watch Battery Drain</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/watchos-update-to-fix-battery-drain-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-update-coming-soon-with-fix-for-apple-watch-battery-drain.2409877/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 14:36:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/watchos-update-to-fix-battery-drain-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing a fix for an issue causing some Apple Watches to experience excessive battery drain after being updated to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-watchos-10-1/">watchOS 10.1</a>, the company said today in an internal memo shared with Apple Authorized Service Providers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/watchOS-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890854" /><br/>
In the memo, which <em>MacRumors</em> obtained from multiple sources, Apple said the issue will be fixed in a watchOS update that is "coming soon." Apple did not provide any additional details in the memo, so it is unclear what the underlying cause of the issue is, how many customers are affected, and if every Apple Watch model is impacted.<br/>
<br/>
There have been complaints about this issue from customers across the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-with-double-tap-namedrop-and-more.2408650/post-32666614">MacRumors Forums</a>, <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255241541">Apple Support Community</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/watchos/comments/17gpob9/101_battery_drain/">Reddit</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/Martin_J_Cooper/status/1720728159681704166">X</a> since watchOS 10.1 was released in late October. The issue seems to affect a variety of Apple Watches, ranging from older models like the Apple Watch Series 5 to the latest Apple Watch Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
"WatchOS 10.1 is killing the battery on my Apple Watch," wrote customer Martin Cooper on X. "100% to 50% in less than 60 mins."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's developer release notes for iOS 17.1 <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/ios-ipados-release-notes/ios-ipados-17_1-release-notes#Power">said</a> that update fixed an issue where "increased power consumption might occur" when an Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 is paired with an iPhone running iOS 17, but evidently the Apple Watch battery drain issue has not been completely fixed, so a watchOS update will be necessary.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> recently reported that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/ios-17-1-1-is-coming/">preparing to release iOS 17.1.1</a> for the iPhone, and it is likely that the Apple Watch battery drain issue will be fixed in a watchOS 10.1.1 update. However, it is possible that the fix might not arrive until watchOS 10.2, which is currently in beta testing and is expected to be released in December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/watchos-update-to-fix-battery-drain-issue/">watchOS Update Coming Soon With Fix for Apple Watch Battery Drain</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-update-coming-soon-with-fix-for-apple-watch-battery-drain.2409877/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Black Friday iPhone Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-iphone-deals.2409875/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 14:23:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals&#038;post_date=1699140182/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We've begun tracking early Black Friday deals for major Apple products <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">like AirPods</a>, and now we're focusing on iPhone. Specifically, in this guide we'll share the best early Black Friday deals on iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-early-black-friday-iphone-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920873" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there is a chance that we could see better deals on iPhone arrive as Black Friday gets closer. This is a risk anyone has to take while shopping during the holidays, so with that in mind, many of the deals shared below are currently their best prices ever seen. More information on these sales can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_iphone_and_accessory_deals">Best iPhone and Accessory Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html"><strong>iPhone 15 Pro/Pro Max</strong></a> for up to &#36;1,000 off at AT&T</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F"><strong>iPhone 15 Pro</strong></a> with free Apple TV 4K and Apple One six month subscription at Verizon</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-MX542AM-A-AirTag-Pack%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp"><strong>AirTag 4-Pack</strong></a> for &#36;86.88 at Amazon, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</strong></a> for &#36;44.25 at Amazon, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_4"><strong>MagSafe Duo Charger</strong></a> for &#36;94.99 at Woot, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2 id="best_black_friday_deals">Best Black Friday Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</strong></a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday AirPods Deals</strong></a></li></ul><br/>
<h2 id="att">AT&T</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fdeals%2F">AT&T</a> has offers across Apple's brand new iPhone 15 lineup, starting at up to &#36;1,000 off the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro-max.html">iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> with an eligible smartphone trade-in. You'll also need to purchase the new smartphone on a qualifying installment agreement. If you select models with lower storage capacities, you can get these new iPhones at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-15-colors-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920875" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Pro at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get up to &#36;830 off the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15.html">iPhone 15</a> or <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-plus.html">iPhone 15 Plus</a> as well, with the same stipulations as the Pro devices. Both offers will be delivered via monthly bill credits, starting within three bills after trade-in is completed. It'll be applied in equal amounts over the term of your installment agreement.<br/>
<br/>
For the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max offer, you'll need to trade in a device with a value of &#36;230 or higher to get the full &#36;1,000 off markdown. You'll get up to &#36;830 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;130 to &#36;229 and up to &#36;350 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;35 to &#36;129.<br/>
<br/>
For older iPhone models, AT&T is offering the 128GB <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-14.html">iPhone 14 at &#36;10.99/month</a> with no trade-in required. Similarly, the iPhone 14 Pro is available at &#36;15/month with no trade-in required. For these, all you'll need is to purchase the smartphones on an installment plan and pick or upgrade to an eligible unlimited plan.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, AT&T is offering a chance to get <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fwearables%2F">&#36;300 off any Apple Watch</a> when you buy two. You'll need to buy any two Apple Watch models on an installment plan, add at least one new line and activate both watches on your wireless plan, and then you'll get up to &#36;300 in bill credits over 36 months.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="verizon">Verizon</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a> has a special bundle offer for anyone interested in purchasing the new iPhone 15 Pro this season. When you purchase the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F">128GB iPhone 15 Pro</a> with a new smartphone line on an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan, you'll get an Apple TV 4K (64GB) and six months of Apple One. All of this will be covered by Verizon with no cost to you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-15-green-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920876" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">FREE APPLE TV 4K</div>iPhone 15 Pro at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, you can purchase <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple%2F">higher storage iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max models</a>, but at that point you'll be paying a little extra. The Apple TV 4K promotion requires a smarpthone purchase on an eligible plan and ends on November 15, while the Apple One six month promotion requires a line subscribed to an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan.<br/>
<br/>
For last year's models, you can <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-14-plus%2F">get four iPhone 14 Plus devices for free</a> along with four lines on Unlimited Welcome at &#36;120/month. A new line on any 5G Unlimited plan is required per smartphone. You can also stack this with Verizon's current tablet and smartwatch promotions, which offer up to &#36;279.99 off these devices.<br/>
<br/>
Verizon is also a great place to buy stocking stuffers for techies during the holiday season with its abundant <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14048362?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fdeals%2Fproducts%2F">accessory sales</a>. Right now it has up to &#36;50 off Anker speakers, 30% off Nimble chargers, 20% off Apple Watch bands, and 20% off Mophie chargers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="visible">Visible</h2><br/>
The Verizon-owned <a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909">Visible</a> brand is offering its premium Visible+ service at &#36;35/month (&#36;10 off) with the promo code 35FOR6 at checkout. This promo lasts for six months, then it will return to its regular &#36;45/month price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF/MONTH</div>Visible+ Cellular Plan</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Visible offers all of the latest smartphones, including iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models. When you join Visible, you'll save up to &#36;240 via monthly bill credits on your account. You'll need to join Visible on a new line of service, purchase a new device, and select the Visible+ plan.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="t-mobile">T-Mobile</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519">T-Mobile</a> is offering up to &#36;1,000 off the new iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Pro when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Next plan. You can get up to &#36;830 off these devices when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Plus plan.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The carrier also has a wide variety of previous generation iPhones at a discount. This includes the iPhone 13 and iPhone SE at no extra cost when purchased on select cellular plans and trading in eligible devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
To cap things off, we're pointing out some great iPhone accessories that you can find on sale at Amazon and <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">Woot</a>. This sale included the MagSafe Charger at a low price of &#36;29.99, but that has since expired. If it returns, we'll be sure to update this page.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-MX542AM-A-AirTag-Pack%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">AirTag 4-Pack</a> - &#36;86.88, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;44.25, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9FJTK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;46.73, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_4">MagSafe Duo Charger</a> - &#36;94.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-plus-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_5">iPhone 14 Plus Leather Case</a> - &#36;24.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-mptc3fe-a-iphone-14-plus-silicone-case-w-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_5">iPhone 14 Plus Silicone Case</a> - &#36;24.99, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-pro-max-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">iPhone 14 Pro Max Leather Case</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;59.00</li></ul> We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday iPhone Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-iphone-deals.2409875/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Argued Safari Is Three Different Browsers to Avoid Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/apple-argued-safari-is-three-different-browsers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-argued-safari-is-three-different-browsers-to-avoid-regulation.2409850/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:44:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/apple-argued-safari-is-three-different-browsers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Safari</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Europe</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/competition/digital_markets_act/cases/202344/DMA_100027_197.pdf">recently claimed</a> that Safari is three different browsers in effort to avoid regulation in the European Union (via <a href="https://www.theregister.com/2023/11/02/apple_safari_browser/"><em>The Register</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/safari-icon-blue-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833485" /><br/>
The claim came as part of a <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/competition/digital_markets_act/cases/202344/DMA_100027_197.pdf">response</a> to the European Union in August, just before the European Commission designated many of Apple's iOS, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and Safari as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/app-store-safari-and-ios-designated-gatekeepers/">gatekeeper platforms</a>. This classification means that Apple now has to ensure that these platforms fall in line with the Digital Markets Act's requirements, such as allowing browser engines other than WebKit and the installation of third-party app stores.<br/>
<br/>
It has now emerged that after being informed that Safari was likely to fall under the DMA's regulations, Apple filed formal a response to the European Union claiming that Safari is, in fact, "three distinct web browsers." The company's claim is based on the argument that Safari for iOS, iPadOS, and macOS are entirely different and serve different purposes.<br/>
<br/>
On example cited by Apple is Safari's sidebar feature on iPadOS and macOS, allowing users to see opened tabs, tab groups, bookmarks, and browsing history. Since this feature is unavailable in the version of Safari for iOS, Apple claimed that it is a distinctly different browser. The company added that each version of Safari serves different purposes for users depending on the device upon which it is accessed.<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission went on to point out that Safari's functionality and underlying technologies are near-identical across platforms. The Commission even highlights Apple's own marketing materials for its Continuity feature, which appear to contradict the company's claims, touting the tag line "Same Safari. Different device." As a result, the Commission rejected Apple's claim and insists that "Safari qualifies as a single web browser, irrespective of the device through which that service is accessed."<br/>
<br/>
Apple is now obliged to ensure that Safari adheres to the DMA's requirements, such as by allowing non-WebKit-based browsers on iOS and iPadOS. Companies that do not adhere to the new regulations risk facing EU investigations, substantial fines, and the imposition of "behavioral or structural remedies." The fines can amount to 10 percent of a company's global turnover, with a 20 percent penalty for repeat violations. Questions remain about whether Apple's argument about Safari being three different browsers violates the DMA's Anti-Circumvention provision that forbids subdividing a platform's market share to avoid regulation. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/europe/">Europe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/apple-argued-safari-is-three-different-browsers/">Apple Argued Safari Is Three Different Browsers to Avoid Regulation</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-argued-safari-is-three-different-browsers-to-avoid-regulation.2409850/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Event Delivers MacBook Pro and iMac Updates</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/top-stories-scary-fast-event-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-delivers-macbook-pro-and-imac-updates.2409839/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/top-stories-scary-fast-event-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's "Scary Fast" event this week went off about as expected, with Apple showing off its next-generation Mac chips in a couple of product lines during a fast-paced 30-minute presentation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/top-stories-4nov2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920863" /><br/>
Our biggest stories this week unsurprisingly delved into Apple's announcements including some early tidbits on the updated MacBook Pro and iMac, a goodbye to the Touch Bar, and more, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything Apple Announced During the 'Scary Fast' Event</h2><br/>
Trick or treat! Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">held its "Scary Fast" event</a>, focused entirely on the Mac. During the brief presentation, Apple announced new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips, and an updated iMac with the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Everything-Announced-at-Scary-Fast-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919534" /><br/>
We've <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">recapped everything that Apple announced during the event</a> for those who missed it or want to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces New 14-Inch and 16-Inch MacBook Pro Models With M3 Series Chips</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-m3-macbook-pros/">new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models are equipped with M3 Pro and M3 Max chips</a>, and there is now an entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro available with the standard M3 chip as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
The new MacBook Pro models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">available in a Space Black finish</a> when configured with the M3 Pro or M3 Max chip, and they are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/new-macbook-pros-20-percent-brighter-displays/">equipped with 20% brighter displays</a> compared to the previous generation.<br/>
<br/>
The new MacBook Pro models are available to order now, and most configurations will launch on Tuesday, November 7.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces New iMac With M3 Chip</h2><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-imac-with-m3-chip/">updated the 24-inch iMac with the M3 chip</a> for up to 35% faster performance compared to the previous model with the M1 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-imac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="902" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919460" /><br/>
The all-in-one desktop computer features the same design and color options as the 2021 model. There are only a few other changes with the new iMac, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/imac-max-memory-wi-fi-6e/">Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 support</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Contrary to rumors, the Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad accessories <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/magic-accessories-still-feature-lightning/">still have Lightning instead of USB-C</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Discontinues 13-Inch MacBook Pro With Touch Bar</h2><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-discontinues-13-inch-macbook-pro/">discontinued the 13-inch MacBook Pro following the event</a>, meaning that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/touch-bar-discontinued/">Touch Bar has now been completely phased out</a> after seven years.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/13-inch-macbook-pro-2022-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1100" height="619" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850662" /><br/>
The first MacBook Pro models with the Touch Bar were released in October 2016, as part of a controversial redesign that also included a defective butterfly keyboard and the removal of many connectivity options, including an SD card slot, HDMI port, and MagSafe.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>First Benchmark Results Surface for M3 Chip in New Macs</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-chip-benchmark-results/">first benchmark results for the standard M3 chip</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-max-chip-benchmark-results/">high-end M3 Max chip</a> surfaced in the Geekbench 6 database after Apple's event, providing a closer look at CPU performance improvements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Chip-Apple-Event-Slide.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920110" /><br/>
The results show the M3 chip is around 20% faster than the M2 chip, while the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/m3-max-chip-benchmark-results/">M3 Max chip is around as fast as the M2 Ultra chip</a> that debuted in the Mac Pro and Mac Studio desktop computers earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2023 MacBook Pro Buyer's Guide: 20+ Differences Compared</h2><br/>
Are you considering purchasing one of the new 14-inch or 16-inch MacBook Pro models? If so, make sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-pro-upgraders-buyers-guide/">check out our in-depth 2023 MacBook Pro buyer's guide</a> that compares over 20 features and differences between MacBook Pro generations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/MacBook-Pro-2021-2023-and-2023-Buyers-Guide-Feature-1.875.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920052" /><br/>
We also shared a buyer's guide <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-vs-m3-imac/">comparing the new iMac with the M3 chip to the 2021 model with the M1 chip</a> for those who are interested in that computer.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/nov-2-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/top-stories-scary-fast-event-recap/">Top Stories: Apple Event Delivers MacBook Pro and iMac Updates</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-delivers-macbook-pro-and-imac-updates.2409839/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Coming Later This Year With These 10 New Features for iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/10-new-features-in-ios-17-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-coming-later-this-year-with-these-10-new-features-for-iphone.2409791/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 14:23:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/10-new-features-in-ios-17-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple made the first beta of iOS 17.2 available to developers and public beta testers last week, and the software update includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">many new features and changes for iPhones</a>. Below, we have highlighted 10 of these new features and changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/10-New-Features-With-iOS-17.2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919093" /><br/>
iOS 17.2 is expected to be released to the public in December. Once available, the update can be installed in the Settings app under General → Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Journal App</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Journal-App-iOS-17-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1469" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918878" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app-hands-on/">Apple's new Journal app</a> allows iPhone users to reflect on their day and memories, complete with text, photos, music, audio recordings, and more. The app provides personalized suggestions based on recent on-device activity.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Translate Option for Action Button</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Action-Button-Translate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911022" /><br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are equipped with a customizable Action button that replaces the traditional mute switch on previous iPhones. By default, the button is set to toggle between Ring and Silent modes, but it can also be assigned to a different action for quick access to the camera, flashlight, Voice Memos, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Starting with iOS 17.2, the Action button can now be assigned to the Translate app for quick access to language translation in the Dynamic Island.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Widgets</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/weather-app-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918889" /><br/>
There are new Home Screen and Lock Screen widget options for the Weather and Clock apps on iOS 17.2. The new Weather options include, Daily Forecast, and Sunrise and Sunset, while the Clock app now offers a digital clock widget. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music: Collaborative Playlists</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-music-collaborative-playlist.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898803" /><br/>
A new Collaborative Playlists feature for Apple Music allows multiple people to add, reorder, and remove songs in a shared playlist.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music: Favorite Songs Playlist</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-favorite-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918891" /><br/>
In the Music app on iOS 17.1 and later, you can favorite songs by tapping the star icon to receive improved recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
Starting with iOS 17.2, favorited songs are also added to a new Favorite Songs playlist.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music: Listening History Focus Filter</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-focus-filters.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918906" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-music-listening-history-focus-filter/">Tired of your kids or someone else messing up your Apple Music recommendations</a> while they are borrowing your iPhone to listen to music? iOS 17.2 includes a new Focus filter for Apple Music‌ listening history that addresses this problem. When this filter is toggled on, the other person's song choices won't affect your recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMessage: Contact Key Verification</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-iMessage-Contact-Key-Verification_screen-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876653" /><br/>
iMessage Contact Key Verification allow users who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials, to further verify that they are messaging only with the people they intend. In conversations between users who have enabled iMessage Contact Key Verification, users are alerted if a state-sponsored attacker or other malicious actor were ever to succeed breaching cloud servers and inserting their own device to eavesdrop on the conversation.<br/>
<br/>
As an additional layer of security, iMessage Contact Key Verification users are able to compare a Contact Verification Code in person, on FaceTime, or through another secure call to further verify they are communicating only with whom they intend.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previewed iMessage Contact Key Verification in December 2022, and it is finally launching as part of iOS 17.2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMessage: Sticker Reactions via Tapback Menu</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tapback-reply-sticker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918892" /><br/>
iOS 17.2 allows you to more quickly react to a message with any sticker by tapping "Add Sticker" in the Tapback menu in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Memoji: New Customization Options</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-memoji-body.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918895" /><br/>
Apple added a "Body" section for Memoji, allowing users to customize their Memoji character's waist, bust, shoulders, and arms.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Contact Posters: Rainbow Text</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-contact-poster-rainbow.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918893" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 17.2, there is a rainbow-colored text option for your name when setting up a Contact Poster in the Contacts app.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/10-new-features-in-ios-17-2/">iOS 17.2 Coming Later This Year With These 10 New Features for iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-coming-later-this-year-with-these-10-new-features-for-iphone.2409791/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Black Friday AirPods Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-airpods-deals.2409779/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:11:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals&#038;post_date=1699045904/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yesterday we shared the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">overall best early Black Friday deals</a> you can get three weeks ahead of the big shopping holiday on Friday, November 24. Today, we're focusing in on Apple's AirPods lineup and sharing the best early Black Friday deals you can get on AirPods, AirPods Pro, and AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/new-airpods-early-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920764" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there is a chance that we could see better deals on AirPods arrive as Black Friday gets closer. This is a risk anyone has to take while shopping during the holidays, so with that in mind, many of the deals shared below are currently their best prices ever seen. More information on these sales can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_airpods_deals">Best AirPods Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>AirPods 2</strong></a> for &#36;99.00 at Amazon (&#36;30 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>AirPods 3</strong></a> for &#36;149.99 at Amazon (&#36;19 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C)</strong></a> for &#36;199.99 at Amazon (&#36;49 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>AirPods Max</strong></a> for &#36;479.99 at Amazon (&#36;69 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_black_friday_deals">Best Black Friday Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</strong></a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday iPhone Deals</strong></a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the cheapest AirPods model, the AirPods 2 are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a> on Amazon right now, down from &#36;129.00. As the oldest AirPods model in the lineup (from 2019), these may not be perfect for the audiophile on your list, but anyone wanting a simple and convenient pair of wireless earbuds will be happy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirPods 3 with Lightning Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;149.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00. These are upgraded in a few ways from the AirPods 2, with spatial audio, Adaptive EQ, force sensor controls, sweat and water resistance, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the Pro lineup, Amazon has the AirPods Pro 2 with Lightning/MagSafe Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHWDR12%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> and the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case is <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a>. For the USB-C model, this is a second-best price and we expect a return of the &#36;189 price tag before the end of the month. <br/>
<br/>
The USB-C model was just released a few weeks ago and this is still a great price for the newest AirPods model. Because of this, as long as the two models are around the same price, we recommend going with the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C over Lightning.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the high-end AirPods Max are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;479.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;549.00. Discounts on the AirPods Max have been rare over the past few months, so this one is a second-best price on the over-ear headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;479.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday AirPods Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-airpods-deals.2409779/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Are the M3 MacBook Pro and iMac Worth the Wait?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-are-the-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-worth-the-wait.2409767/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:13:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/be/podcast/is-the-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-worth-the-wait-episode-77/id1602394741?i=1000633607216">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">"Scary Fast" event</a> and the new Macs it introduced.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/N0mmnrebzBc?si=pyW2Z2qZPHhz0w70" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We talk through our candid feelings about the unusual Apple event and the way in which the company presented its latest devices. We look at the all-new M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips, and weigh up the new MacBook Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, who should consider upgrading to the next-generation machines, and more. Let us know what you think of Apple's new Macs in the comments.<br/>
<br/>
The podcast is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so head over and subscribe to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/the-macrumors-show-scary-fast-event-expectations/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about what we were expecting to see at Apple's event to see what we got right and wrong.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is now on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@macrumorsshow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/the-macrumors-show-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac/">The MacRumors Show: Are the M3 MacBook Pro and iMac Worth the Wait?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-are-the-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-worth-the-wait.2409767/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
