<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 03:01:06 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>15+ New Features Coming to the iOS 18 Messages App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-messages/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/15-new-features-coming-to-the-ios-18-messages-app.2432803/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:17:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-messages&#038;post_date=1722647827/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Major changes are coming to the Messages app with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, with Apple adding several fun Apple Intelligence features, new formatting, updated effects, satellite support, better texting with green bubble people, and tons more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Messages-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955693" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything that's new in the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="send_later">Send Later</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; adds the option to schedule an iMessage to be sent to someone at a later time or date. If you know someone's birthday is coming up, for example, you can schedule a happy birthday text to them ahead of the date so it's ready to go.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-send-later.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960705" /><br/>
Scheduling a message can be only be done in conversations with other iMessage users, and it is not an option when texting with an Android user. It works in both individual and group chats, as long as all participants have an Apple device and access to iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
To schedule a message, follow these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up a conversation in the Messages app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the "+" button on the left side of the text box.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on More.</li><br/>
 <li>Choose Send Later.</li><br/>
 <li>Type in your Message.</li><br/>
 <li>To change the send time, tap on the blue bubble that defaults to Tomorrow 9:00 am. From there, you will have a slider that lets you input a date and a time.</li><br/>
 <li>With your time selected and your message typed in, tap on the blue arrow to schedule it.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Messages can be scheduled up to 14 days in advance, so if it's August 1, for example, you can schedule up to August 15. Messages are sent even if your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is offline without a Wi-Fi or cellular connection.<br/>
<br/>
Scheduled messages are displayed at the bottom of a conversation. If you want to change the time of a message or cancel it, tap on the "Edit" button. You will have options to edit the time, delete the message, or send it immediately.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="tapback_reactions">Tapback Reactions</h2><br/>
Tapbacks are those little characters you can use to respond to a message by long pressing on it, so you don't need to type out a whole response to something that can be answered with a thumbs up or a heart. &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; has two key updates for Tapbacks.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="updated_design">Updated Design</h3><br/>
The six standard Tapback icons now feature color and more detail. You can see the new look when long pressing on a text to respond, and in the Tapbacks that you receive.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-tapback-colors.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960707" /><br/>
When you tap on a Tapback you've received on a message, you can now see who sent what, which is useful if you are in a group chat and get multiple Tapback responses.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-tapback-info.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960708" /><br/>
<h3 id="emoji_support">Emoji Support</h3><br/>
Along with the six classic Tapback responses, you can now choose any emoji character when using Tapback. After long pressing to respond to a message, swipe to the left to see common emoji responses or tap on the generic emoji icon thought bubble to bring up the emoji picker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-tapback-emoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960706" /><br/>
You can choose any emoji, but you can also select from your stickers or your Memoji. Tap on the Memoji icon at the bottom left to get to Memoji, or the sticker icon to see your sticker selections. To add one as a Tapback, just tap on your selection.<br/>
<br/>
Stickers can be hard to see at the small size of a Tapback, but most emoji characters and Memoji work well.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rcs">RCS</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>, or Rich Communication Services, is a new text message protocol replacing SMS and MMS. You'll see it when texting people who don't have iMessage, such as Android users. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; has nothing to do with iMessage conversations, aka the conversations you have with other Apple device owners (blue bubbles), but it does improve texts with green bubble Android users.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-rcs-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2776" height="1562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923042" /><br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; is a more modern technology than SMS, and it allows for more feature parity in &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to Android text message conversations. Many of the frustrations you might have encountered when texting someone with an Android device are resolved with &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, such as errors sending photos and videos.<br/>
<br/>
Here's what you'll get with &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Support for higher resolution photos and videos.</li><br/>
 <li>Support for larger file sizes and file sharing.</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages.</li><br/>
 <li>Cross-platform emoji reactions.</li><br/>
 <li>Real-time typing indicators.</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts.</li><br/>
 <li>Ability to send messages over cellular or Wi-Fi (SMS is cellular only). There is no cost to send an &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; message over Wi-Fi.</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Again, &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; only comes into play when you're texting someone who has an Android device. iMessage is still the default for conversations between Apple device owners, and blue bubbles and green bubbles are not changing.<br/>
<br/>
We <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">have a full guide on RCS</a> if you want to know more about what to expect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_via_satellite">Messages via Satellite</h2><br/>
Messages via satellite is a new feature that lets you send texts even when you don't have a Wi-Fi or cellular connection, leveraging the satellites that Apple uses for the Emergency SOS via satellite feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-via-satellite.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960711" /><br/>
Messages via satellite is available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> or later, and you can send and receive both iMessage and SMS messages, so you're not limited to texting with just &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, Messages via satellite is free, just like Emergency SOS via satellite. Apple offers two free years of satellite access with an &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; or later, but the company has expanded free access for the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; until November 2025. Apple has not provided any insight into how much it will eventually charge for satellite access.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="smart_replies_apple_intelligence">Smart Replies (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
Using Apple Intelligence, your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can analyze the content in a message that you've received, suggesting Smart Reply options that you can tap for a quick response.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-messages-smart-reply.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960223" /><br/>
If someone asks a question like "Do you want to go to the movies?" Messages will suggest responses like "Sure!" or "Sorry, busy tomorrow." Smart Replies aren't an option for every message that you receive, but Apple often has a suggestion.<br/>
<br/>
Smart Replies show up at the top of the keyboard, where suggestions have been in prior versions of iOS. Smart Replies are similar to suggestions, but are more intelligent and are often complete phrases and responses rather than word suggestions that pop up as you type.<br/>
<br/>
To use a Smart Reply, just tap it and it'll populate the text box so you can send it. If you don't care for the suggestion, just ignore it, and type in your own response. You'll still see suggestions once you disregard a Smart Reply.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="writing_tools_apple_intelligence">Writing Tools (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
Writing Tools aren't specific to the Messages app, but are a systemwide option anywhere you can input text. In Messages, you can write out a text and then select it with a tap and drag gesture to bring up the Writing Tools interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-writing-tools.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960712" /><br/>
Here's what Writing Tools can do for a text message:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Proofread what you've written for spelling and grammar errors, including word choice and sentence structure.</li><br/>
 <li>Rewrite with a different tone, with options that include Friendly, Professional, and Concise.</li><br/>
 <li>Summarize what you've written. You can get a quick summary, pull out key points, create a list of topics, or make a table.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can tap on the various options to use the Writing Tools, and you can preview changes and decide not to use them or swap them in for what you've written.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-writing-tools-rewrite.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960713" /><br/>
<h2 id="notification_summaries_apple_intelligence">Notification Summaries (Apple Intelligence)</h2><br/>
If you have multiple notifications from the Messages app, Apple Intelligence will summarize them for you so you can catch up at a glance and see what's most important without having to read through everything.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-summary.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960714" /><br/>
This works for both individual conversations and group conversations, and you can see the summaries on the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="emoji_design_updates">Emoji Design Updates</h2><br/>
When you send a single emoji to someone in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, the emoji now appears much larger than before so the detail is easier to see. Emojis in other quantities are still displayed at the same size.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Messages-Emoji.jpg" alt="" width="1179" height="921" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955798" /><br/>
Apple has also updated the emoji picker. Emoji are displayed larger and with more space between them, plus the Sticker and Memoji interfaces have been integrated into the emoji window.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping on the two icons on the bottom left of the emoji picker will take you to Memoji and Stickers, respectively. You can create Memoji and make new stickers directly from the two sections that are in the emoji picker. For stickers, select the sticker section and tap on the blank sticker icon. For Memoji, tap into the Memoji section, tap the three dots, and then choose New, Edit, or Duplicate.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stickers_and_memoji_as_emoji">Stickers and Memoji as Emoji</h2><br/>
Stickers and Memoji have new dedicated sections in the emoji picker because you can now use a sticker or a Memoji just like an emoji. If you add a sticker when typing a text, for example, it is added to the end of your text rather than sent as a separate image.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-emoji-stickers-memoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957882" /><br/>
You can still send a full-size sticker as long as you send it separate from text.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-sticker-emoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960709" /><br/>
Stickers and Memoji sent as emoji only display as emoji on devices running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>. On earlier versions of iOS, stickers are sent as separate images as before.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="text_formatting">Text Formatting</h2><br/>
You can enhance your text messages with new formatting options. After typing something, tap on the "A" icon above the keyboard. What you've typed is selected, and you can add bold, italic, underline, or strikethrough formatting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-formatting.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960715" /><br/>
To add formatting to just one word, double tap on the word to select it and then tap on the "A" icon. You can also use the Text Effects option from the popup menu. Formatting can be used with emoji, but the bold and italic options don't do anything.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="text_effects">Text Effects</h2><br/>
Along with the bold, italic, underline, and strikethrough formatting, there are new animated text effects that can be applied to your entire message, a single word, a phrase, or even an emoji or sticker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-text-effects-messages.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960710" /><br/>
Just select the text that you want to add an effect to with a double tap and then tap on the "A" icon to get to the text effects interface.<br/>
<br/>
Options include Big, Small, Shake, Nod, Explode, Ripple, Bloom, and Jitter.<br/>
<br/>
In a conversation with someone running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; or one of its sister updates, the text or emoji that has an effect applied to it will continually animate when viewed. These effects do not work on earlier versions of Apple's operating systems and simply don't show up.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="math_notes">Math Notes</h2><br/>
The systemwide Math Notes feature that lets your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; solve equations for you works in Messages. To see it in action, type in an equation and you'll get an immediate answer when you add in an equals sign.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-math-notes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960716" /><br/>
Math Notes also works for conversions in the Messages app, including currency conversions, temperature conversions, measurement conversions, and more. You can use it by typing in your conversion, such as "20 euros to dollars" and then adding in an equals sign to get the result.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="link_card_update">Link Card Update</h2><br/>
Apple tweaked the design of link cards in the Messages app, and the cards now have colorful backgrounds that match the color of the main image in the link, if available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-Link-Cards.jpg" alt="" width="2358" height="1323" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955800" /><br/>
You can see link card previews before a link is sent, and if you long press, you can get customization options. Link cards can be converted to a simpler card style or transformed into a text link that only shows the hyperlink with no preview at all.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="image_playground_coming_later_this_year">Image Playground (Coming Later This Year)</h2><br/>
Image Playground is an upcoming Apple Intelligence feature that is designed to let you create images using text-based prompts, much like you can do with other AI image generation platforms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960704" /><br/>
Apple is integrating Image Playground into the Messages app, so you can create and send images without having to swap over to another app. Apple Intelligence can glean the gist of your conversation from the Messages app and come up with suggestions for images that you might want to send.<br/>
<br/>
Image Playground can even incorporate images of your friends and family, so if you're chatting with a friend, you can create a silly image that uses the friend's contact photo. Apple adds a style to each image, so there is no option to generate something that could be mistaken for a real photo.<br/>
<br/>
You can choose from Animation, Illustration, and Sketch styles, and all image generation is done on-device.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="genmoji_coming_later_this_year">Genmoji (Coming Later This Year)</h2><br/>
Based on Image Playground, Genmoji lets you create custom emoji with a text prompt. Have you always wanted an emoji of a mint chocolate chip ice cream cone? It can be made with Genmoji.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-genmoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960703" /><br/>
Need a cat made from pizza, or a flower that's not a rose or a sunflower? Genmoji will make it possible. With the Genmoji interface, you can describe a Genmoji and Apple Intelligence will generate several options for you to choose from.<br/>
<br/>
You can even create an emoji based on the contact image of a friend or family member, similar to Image Playground.<br/>
<br/>
Genmoji behave just like emoji and can be used in place of emoji.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
Additional information on new features that Apple has added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">can be found in our iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-messages/">15+ New Features Coming to the iOS 18 Messages App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/15-new-features-coming-to-the-ios-18-messages-app.2432803/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Sued by United States Justice Department for Violating Child Privacy Laws</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/tiktok-sued-us-justice-department/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-sued-by-united-states-justice-department-for-violating-child-privacy-laws.2432795/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:35:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/tiktok-sued-us-justice-department/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-sues-tiktok-and-parent-company-bytedance-widespread-violations-childrens">today sued TikTok</a> and its parent company ByteDance for violating the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). COPPA makes it illegal for websites to collect, use, and disclose data from children under the age of 13 without parental consent.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-752609" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/tiktok-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The lawsuit [<a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/media/1362606/dl?inline">PDF</a>] alleges that from 2019 on, TikTok has knowingly allowed children to create TikTok accounts and to create, view, and share videos and messages with adults and others on the TikTok platform. TikTok is accused of collecting and retaining personal information from children without consent from their parents. Data was collected even from accounts created in Kids Mode.<br/>
<br/>
Millions of children under 13 have used the regular TikTok app, which the DoJ says has subjected them to "extensive data collection" and allowed them to "interact with adult users and access adult content." TikTok is also accused of making it difficult for parents to get their child's account and data deleted.<br/>
<br/>
The Department of Justice is seeking civil penalties for every COPPA violation and injunctive relief that would prevent TikTok from continuing to collect data from children.<br/>
<br/>
TikTok is already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/08/tiktok-sues-us-government/">embroiled in a lawsuit</a> with the U.S. government over a bill that requires the social network to be sold off to a non-Chinese company or face a ban in the United States. TikTok parent company ByteDance has until January 19, 2025 to find a buyer for TikTok, but a sale is unlikely because the Chinese government would need to approve the divestiture, and it has said that it would "firmly oppose" any effort to sell TikTok.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/tiktok-sued-us-justice-department/">TikTok Sued by United States Justice Department for Violating Child Privacy Laws</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-sued-by-united-states-justice-department-for-violating-child-privacy-laws.2432795/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With Dyson&#039;s OnTrac Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/hands-on-dyson-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-dysons-ontrac-headphones.2432790/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:47:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/hands-on-dyson-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Dyson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Dyson recently announced <a href="https://www.dyson.com/headphones/ontrac">new OnTrac over-ear headphones</a> with ANC, and at &#36;500, OnTrac is a direct competitor for Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>. Dyson smartly did away with the unpopular air purifying mask design that it used for its prior-generation headphones, and the new model boasts a more traditional look with exceptional battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-W6AnA1fdt0" title="Dyson Made Headphones Again...but these are GOOD!? | Dyson OnTrac Review" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Dyson's OnTrac headphones come in four metallic colorways, including CNC Aluminium, Copper, Ceramic Cinnabar (with a ceramic-feel painted finish), and Black Nickel, plus there are interchangeable ear caps and cushions in a range of colors for customization.<br/>
<br/>
The headphones have "high-grade foam cushions" covered in microsuede, and multi-pivot gimbal arms that are meant to relieve ear pressure. There's also a headband with a battery inside, which Dyson says evenly distributes weight. With the metal build and the multiple batteries that Dyson has included, the headphones weigh 451 grams, making them heavier than the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; (385 grams).<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are too heavy for some users, and weight has been a complaint. With the OnTrac, weight is indeed well distributed and not all in the ear cups like the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;, but we found that they still get uncomfortable over time, so for many people, they likely won't be ideal for all-day use. For comparison, Sonos recently came out with the Ace headphones that weigh 312 grams, and they're more comfortable than both the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; and the OnTrac.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of design, these are not subtle headphones, and you're going to stand out when wearing them. The OnTrac headphones are huge, but well-built and sturdy. The left ear cup has a power button and USB-C charging port, while the right ear cup has a joystick for music playback and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> activation when used with an Apple device.<br/>
<br/>
Dyson focused on battery life with the OnTrac. With Active Noise Cancellation turned on, the headphones last for up to 55 hours, more than double the battery life of the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; (20 hours with ANC). Dyson could have cut some weight with less battery capacity, but if you're off grid and need headphones that are going to last for a good three days with heavy listening, the OnTrac has you covered.<br/>
<br/>
Dyson says the headphones have 40mm, 16-ohm neodymium speaker drivers and advanced audio signal processing with sub-bass you can feel. While the sound quality was good, the OnTrac is not notably better than the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; or the Sonos Ace. Active Noise Cancellation and transparency are both solid, and the OnTrac does a good job cutting out ambient noise. Dyson says they can reduce noise by up to 40 decibels.<br/>
<br/>
You can adjust the ANC and sound through the app, so there is some customizability, but you are limited to three EQ levels, enhanced, bass boost, and neutral. On-ear detection is available for pausing music when removing the OnTrac, but these are Bluetooth headphones and don't work as seamlessly as the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; with Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
Dyson plans to start selling the OnTrac headphones on August 12, and they will be <a href="https://www.dyson.com/headphones/ontrac">available from the Dyson website</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dyson/">Dyson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/hands-on-dyson-headphones/">Hands-On With Dyson&#039;s OnTrac Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-dysons-ontrac-headphones.2432790/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pulls Latest Ad After Criticism Over Depiction of Thailand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pulls-latest-underdogs-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-latest-ad-after-criticism-over-depiction-of-thailand.2432788/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:15:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pulls-latest-underdogs-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Thailand</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today issued an apology to Thailand for the way the country was portrayed in a July "The Underdogs" short film, and the video has also been removed from Apple's YouTube channel. In the ad that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/">released on July 18</a>, the underdogs design team traveled to Bangkok and Rayong, Thailand for a project and were depicted traveling in a tuk-tuk and staying in a rundown hotel.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/underdogs-video.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959216" /><br/>
Thai residents found the depiction of Thailand offensive, and took to social media to criticize Apple for portraying the country with outdated stereotypes. The video made Thailand look "low-tech and underdeveloped" due to the faded, sepia tone and focus on dilapidated architecture, according to the Bangkok Post.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple’s latest short film commercial &#39;The Underdogs: OOO (Out Of Office)&#39; that aims to represent its gadgets filmed in Thailand has sparked criticism among Thai people as the commercial portrays Thailand in a low-tech and underdeveloped mood and tone, using a warm colour in… <a href="https://t.co/yYgAXCDFUd">pic.twitter.com/yYgAXCDFUd</a></p>&mdash; Bangkok Post (@BangkokPostNews) <a href="https://twitter.com/BangkokPostNews/status/1816768894218260808?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 26, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Thai House of Representatives Committee on Tourism spokesperson Sattra Sripan called for a boycott on Apple over the video. "Thai people are deeply unhappy with the advertisement," he said. "I encourage Thai people to stop using Apple products and change to other brands." He said that the tourism committee planned to invite Apple representatives and state agencies to discuss the ad.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in a statement to <em><a href="https://www.bangkokpost.com/life/tech/2840337/apple-apologises-and-removes-controversial-ad">Bangkok Post</a></em> this morning said that it was sorry that Thailand was inaccurately portrayed, and confirmed that the ad had been taken down.<br/>
<blockquote>Our intent was to celebrate the country's optimism and culture, and we apologize for not fully capturing the vibrancy of Thailand today.</blockquote><br/>
Apple worked with Thailand-based film production studio Indochina Productions on the video, and it was shot entirely in Thailand. Since 2019, Apple has released several videos that star the underdogs as part of an "Apple at Work" ad campaign.<br/>
<br/>
This is the second ad that Apple has pulled this year. When the M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models came out in May, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/apple-crush-ad-apology/">showed a video</a> of a hydraulic press crushing an array of creative tools, which was not well received by creatives. Apple pulled the video, apologized, and said that it had "missed the mark" with the ad.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/thailand/">Thailand</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pulls-latest-underdogs-ad/">Apple Pulls Latest Ad After Criticism Over Depiction of Thailand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-latest-ad-after-criticism-over-depiction-of-thailand.2432788/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Prices Hit Nearly Every MacBook Air and MacBook Pro, Plus AirPods Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-2-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-prices-hit-nearly-every-macbook-air-and-macbook-pro-plus-airpods-sales.2432781/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:12:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-2-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week we saw a huge collection of discounts hit both the MacBook Air and MacBook Pro, with as much as &#36;500 off select models of these computers. We're also still tracking record low prices on the M4 iPad Pro as we head into the weekend, as well as a few AirPods deals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0013.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848004" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airpods-pro-2-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939073" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;69 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/airpods-2-hit-all-time-low/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;69.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
AirPods deals were in abundance earlier this week, and they're all still available today. You can get the AirPods 2, AirPods 3, and AirPods Pro 2 all for solid second-best prices on Amazon right now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m4-ipad-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952117" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;150 off M4 iPad Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmMFPxxvE8h">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFPxxvE8h"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>11-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFUSaNsv1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy is hosting a massive sale on the M4 iPad Pro this week, including record low prices on both Wi-Fi and cellular tablets. You can find a bigger list of all the iPad Pro models on sale <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/">in our original post</a>, and note that most of these require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership to see the final deal price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;250 off MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmLOPci9HbR">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/best-buy-macbook-air-back-to-school/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmLOPci9HbR"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmLOKv5uRMs"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmLONCkWAwU"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
MacBook Air discounts this week include all-time low prices on the M2 MacBook Air and the M3 MacBook Air, starting at just &#36;799.00 for the former model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956595" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;500 off M3 MacBook Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;500 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Best Buy and Amazon have notable markdowns on Apple's 14-inch and 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro this week, with up to &#36;500 off select models.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-2-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Prices Hit Nearly Every MacBook Air and MacBook Pro, Plus AirPods Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-prices-hit-nearly-every-macbook-air-and-macbook-pro-plus-airpods-sales.2432781/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says iOS 18&#039;s ChatGPT Integration on Track for Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/ios-18-chatgpt-later-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-ios-18s-chatgpt-integration-on-track-for-later-this-year.2432780/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:32:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/ios-18-chatgpt-later-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO Tim Cook on Thursday said that ChatGPT will be integrated across iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia "by the end of the calendar year." He shared this timeframe during <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-q3-2024-earnings-takeaways/">Apple's quarterly earnings call</a> with analysts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-ChatGPT.jpg" alt="" width="1825" height="1027" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960667" /><br/>
Apple first said that ChatGPT integration was coming to the iPhone, iPad, and Mac later this year during its WWDC keynote in June, and Cook's comment indicates that this timeframe remains on track as of the first week of August.<br/>
<br/>
"ChatGPT is integrated by the end of the calendar year," said Cook, in response to a question about the timing of Apple Intelligence features.<br/>
<br/>
With user permission, Siri will be able to show ChatGPT answers directly in response to questions and other prompts. ChatGPT will also be an option for Apple's system-wide Writing Tools feature, allowing users to generate text and images. Apple said ChatGPT will be powered by OpenAI's latest GPT-4o model on its platforms.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone, iPad, and Mac users will be able to use ChatGPT for free, without creating an account, and ChatGPT Plus subscribers will be able to connect their accounts to access paid features on these devices. Apple said OpenAI will not store ChatGPT requests made from its devices, and  it said users' IP addresses will be obscured.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features started rolling out to developers for testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">in the iOS 18.1 beta</a> earlier this week, but ChatGPT integration is not available yet.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features require an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max, or a Mac or iPad equipped with an M1 chip or newer. The device's language must be set to U.S. English, with support for additional languages to roll out over the next year. <br/>
<br/>
The full suite of Apple Intelligence features is expected to be available <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-powered-siri/">by time iOS 18.4 is released</a> to the public around March 2025. These features will enable users to summarize text, prioritize notifications and emails, generate custom emoji and images, and more. The technology will also power a smarter version of Siri with richer language understanding, deeper per-app controls, on-screen awareness, and personalized context.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/ios-18-chatgpt-later-this-year/">Apple Says iOS 18&#039;s ChatGPT Integration on Track for Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-ios-18s-chatgpt-integration-on-track-for-later-this-year.2432780/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple Intelligence Beta is Here</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-beta-is-here.2432776/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:53:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/apple-intelligence-beta-is-here/id1602394741?i=1000664139205">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's unusual iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 betas that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">introduce Apple Intelligence</a> for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6Ha8HZAVkNU?si=kMFfyntryyFlid0-" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
The beta versions currently available are exclusive to developers, providing them with a first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/apple-intelligence-hands-on/">hands-on look at Apple Intelligence</a>. Apple continues to beta test <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15 separately.<br/>
<br/>
One of the most prominent aspects of Apple Intelligence is its Writing Tools, which allow users to proofread text for spelling and grammar errors and rewrite content to change its tone. Users can also summarize any text, creating paragraphs, lists, or tables, which are accessible anywhere text input is possible across the operating system.<br/>
<br/>
The revamped version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is another key feature of Apple Intelligence. The voice assistant now boasts a new design with a glowing edge around the display when activated, indicating when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is listening. There is also a Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; option, which allows users to interact with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; via text instead of voice commands. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has been enhanced to maintain context between requests and follow along if the user stumbles over words. Additionally, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can now answer a wide range of questions about Apple devices, leveraging Apple's extensive product knowledge and support database.<br/>
<br/>
Several other features included in the beta release are designed to improve communication and media management. For example, users can record, transcribe, and summarize phone calls, which are then stored in the Notes app. The Mail and Messages applications now feature Smart Replies, offering quick, context-based responses. In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, the new Memory Maker feature allows users to create memory movies from photo collections using natural language descriptions. This feature automatically selects relevant photos and music, although users can customize their creations further.<br/>
<br/>
Some features have been postponed to later releases. The Image Playground app, which offers image creation tools, is not yet available. Genmoji, a tool for creating custom emojis, and the Image Wand feature, which inserts contextually relevant images into Notes, are also missing from the current beta. Additionally, Priority Notifications, which prioritize important alerts, and advanced Mail categories for sorting incoming messages are not yet implemented. Other postponed features include the ability to remove unwanted objects from photos with a single tap, enhanced &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; capabilities such as on-screen awareness, and ChatGPT integration, which should significantly expand &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s conversational abilities.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has indicated that these additional features will be rolled out progressively throughout 2024 and 2025. The current Apple Intelligence beta is limited to U.S. English and is not accessible to developers in the European Union or China. Apple Intelligence is supported by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, all Apple silicon iPads, and all Apple silicon Macs. The public will have access to the first Apple Intelligence features upon the official release of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/26/the-macrumors-show-talking-weird-iphone-17-slim-rumors/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion on all of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">latest rumors</a> about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> "Slim" – a whole new kind of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> coming next year.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-beta/">The MacRumors Show: Apple Intelligence Beta is Here</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-beta-is-here.2432776/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All iPhone 17 Models Again Rumored to Feature 24MP Front Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphone-17-models-again-rumored-to-feature-24mp-front-camera.2432762/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:56:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[All four iPhone 17 models expected to launch next year will feature an upgraded 24-megapixel front-facing camera, according to Apple analyst Jeff Pu.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iPhone-17-Slim-Feature-Single-Camera-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960528" /><br/>
In a research note today for investment bank Haitong, obtained by <em>MacRumors</em>, Pu shared a chart indicating that the iPhone 17, the tentatively-named <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">iPhone 17 Slim</a>, the iPhone 17 Pro, and the iPhone 17 Pro Max will each be equipped with a 24-megapixel front camera with six plastic lens elements. By comparison, all iPhone 15 models are equipped with a 12-megapixel front camera with five plastic lens elements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo also claimed that at least one iPhone 17 model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/">would be equipped with a 24-megapixel front camera</a> with a six-piece lens back in January, so this upgrade has now been rumored by multiple sources, making it more likely. Kuo said these changes will "significantly improve the image quality."<br/>
<br/>
With a higher 24-megapixel resolution, photos can maintain their quality even when cropped to a greater degree, providing more flexibility in post-processing. A six-piece lens would also slightly enhance image quality, as each element is designed to correct for various aberrations and distortions, leading to clearer, more accurate photos.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 17 models are expected to launch in September 2025, so they are still over a year away. Rumors about the two-generations-away iPhones always begin quite early, as Apple develops and prototypes products well before they are released.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-rumor/">All iPhone 17 Models Again Rumored to Feature 24MP Front Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphone-17-models-again-rumored-to-feature-24mp-front-camera.2432762/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s First Foldable iPad Could Face Delays Into 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-foldable-ipad-delays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-foldable-ipad-could-face-delays-into-2026.2432754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 05:04:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-foldable-ipad-delays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		<category>Foldable iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's first foldable device may not hit its previously expected 2025 schedule for mass production, based on new comments made by Haitong analyst Jeff Pu.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1458" height="820" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-797663" /><br/>
In a note to investors seen by <em>MacRumors</em>, Pu said that he continued to expect enhanced Apple product power driven by the likes of the iPhone 17 and Apple Intelligence, but this came despite some "pushouts" seen for Apple's foldable iPad.<br/>
<br/>
When investors or analysts use the term "pushout" in relation to product releases, they typically mean the expected release date has been moved further into the future, either because there's a delay in the development or manufacturing process, or the company has decided to postpone the launch for other reasons.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/first-apple-foldable-coming-in-2025/">May report</a>, Pu said Apple's first foldable devices would reach mass production in 2025 and 2026, following increasing evidence of foldable devices in Apple's supply chain. At the time, the analyst said Apple would likely release a large-screen foldable iPad or MacBook in that timeframe before launching a higher-volume foldable iPhone in late 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Pu had said one Apple foldable with a 20.3-inch display would start production in late 2025, which was sooner than previously expected. However, Pu now thinks Apple will join the foldable market in the second quarter of 2026 due to "display durability issues."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-ipad/">Foldable iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-foldable-ipad-delays/">Apple&#039;s First Foldable iPad Could Face Delays Into 2026</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-foldable-ipad-could-face-delays-into-2026.2432754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pressures ByteDance and Tencent Over App Fee Loopholes in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pressures-bytedance-tencent-app-fees/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pressures-bytedance-and-tencent-over-app-fee-loopholes-in-china.2432751/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 04:35:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pressures-bytedance-tencent-app-fees/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is putting pressure on Tencent and ByteDance to make significant changes to two of China's most popular apps in order to remove loopholes that circumvent Apple's typical 30% commission, <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-02/apple-pressures-tencent-and-bytedance-over-app-fees-in-china">Bloomberg</a></em> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/App-Store-Blue-Banner-Chinese-Flag-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917631" /><br/>
The loopholes are linked to mini-apps that allow users of Tencent's social-messaging app WeChat and ByteDance's short-video app Douyin to play games, hail taxis, and make online purchases without leaving the app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple reportedly told both companies they need to prevent mini-app creators from including links to outside payment systems that circumvent its commission system. Apple said it would not approve future updates to WeChat or Douyin until the companies complied. <br/>
<br/>
Apple also has asked Tencent to disable in-game chats between developers and users, because they can also be used to send links, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>. Tencent has reportedly pushed back against the idea due to the negative impact it would have on the game experience.<br/>
<br/>
The report characterized the moves by Apple as "unusually aggressive" in China, suggesting they may inflame tensions at a time when its business practices are under scrutiny by antitrust regulators around the world. <br/>
<br/>
An Apple spokesperson who contacted <em>Bloomberg</em> cited its guidelines that the sale of all digital goods must go through its system, and that its review team may reject app submissions that violate that policy.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pressures-bytedance-tencent-app-fees/">Apple Pressures ByteDance and Tencent Over App Fee Loopholes in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pressures-bytedance-and-tencent-over-app-fee-loopholes-in-china.2432751/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Wallet App Support for Apple Account Cards Now Live in Australia and Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-account-cards-canada-australia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wallet-app-support-for-apple-account-cards-now-live-in-australia-and-canada.2432748/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 03:37:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-account-cards-canada-australia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Australia</category>
		<category>Canada</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Support for Apple Account Cards in the Wallet app has gone live in Canada and Australia, over two years since it first launched in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/apple-account-card-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-846914" /><br/>
The change means users can use the Wallet app to add an Apple Account Card, which displays the Apple credit balance associated with an Apple ID. If you receive an App Store or Apple Store gift card, for example, it is added to an Apple Account that was previously visible in the ‌App Store‌ and ‌Apple Store‌ apps. <br/>
<br/>
Support for the feature in Canada and Australia requires iPhone users updating to iOS 17.6, as spotted by <a href="https://x.com/nicolas09f9/status/1819173249973997699?s=46">Nicolás Álvarez</a>. Prior to today, support for the feature was thought to be limited to Japan and the US.<br/>
<br/>
To add an Apple Account Card, open up the Wallet app and under "Available Cards," tap on "Add Apple Account." As long as you have an Apple Account balance, you'll be able to add the card.<br/>
<br/>
Once added, you can view your Apple Account balance right from the Wallet app and use it to purchase Apple products, apps, games, and music. It works in the same way as any other card in the Wallet app when at an ‌Apple Store‌. The Apple Account Card replaces the iTunes Pass that used to be available a long time ago.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/australia/">Australia</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/canada/">Canada</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-account-cards-canada-australia/">Wallet App Support for Apple Account Cards Now Live in Australia and Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wallet-app-support-for-apple-account-cards-now-live-in-australia-and-canada.2432748/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Model to Get Biggest Battery Capacity Jump</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-16-pro-battery-capacities/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-model-to-get-biggest-battery-capacity-jump.2432744/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 03:18:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-16-pro-battery-capacities/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are rumored to feature bigger battery capacities compared to previous-generation models, but it looks like the smaller iPhone 16 Pro device could see the biggest improvement, according to new details.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Update-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953750" /><br/>
Chinese Weibo-based leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/Oqjg7Flks">Instant Digital</a> today posted the mAh (milliampere-hours) figures for the iPhone 16 Pro (3,577 mAh) and iPhone 16 Pro Max (4,676 mAh), with only the larger model capacity lining up with previous leaked figures.<br/>
<br/>
The mAh is a measure of battery capacity, or the amount of electric charge that a battery can store. The higher the mAh rating of a battery, the more charge it can hold, and the longer it can power a device. The following table shows the battery capacity comparison between the iPhone 15 Pro models and iPhone 16 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>iPhone 15 Pros (2023)</th><br/>
 <th>iPhone 16 Pros (2024)</th><br/>
 <th>% Change</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <td>3,274 mAh</td><br/>
 <td>3,577 mAh</td><br/>
 <td>+9.25%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <td>4,422 mAh</td><br/>
 <td>4,676 mAh</td><br/>
 <td>+5.74%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div>The change in capacity of the iPhone 16 Pro over the previous Pro model shows the most marked difference, with an over 9% increase (303 mAh). Meanwhile, the iPhone 16 Pro Max, while not as dramatic as its smaller sibling, gets an over 5% increase (254 mAh). Combined with efficiency improvements, the increases should see both devices offer more sustained real-world usage on a single charge.<br/>
<br/>
According to one <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223409700148&navType=by">rumor</a>, this year's ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max will boast a 30-hour-plus battery life (compared to 29 hours for the iPhone 15 Pro Max). Not only that, the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are expected to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/iphone-15-could-feature-stacked-battery-technology/">stacked battery technology</a> for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/iphone-16-pro-max-biggest-rumored-features/">5 Biggest Changes Rumored for iPhone 16 Pro Max</a></li></ul><br/>
Both devices are also rumored to support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/iphone-16-pro-40w-fast-charging-20w-magsafe/">40W wired fast charging and 20W MagSafe charging</a>. For comparison, iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models are capable of up to 27W peak charging speeds with an appropriate USB-C power adapter, while official MagSafe chargers from Apple and authorized third parties can wirelessly charge the iPhone 15 models at up to 15W. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-16-pro-battery-capacities/">iPhone 16 Pro Model to Get Biggest Battery Capacity Jump</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-model-to-get-biggest-battery-capacity-jump.2432744/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Q3 2024 Earnings Call Takeaways</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-q3-2024-earnings-takeaways/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-q3-2024-earnings-call-takeaways.2432715/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:24:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-q3-2024-earnings-takeaways/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today held an earnings call for the third fiscal quarter of 2024 (second calendar quarter), with Apple reporting its best June quarter to date, with revenue higher than expected. Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and Apple CFO Luca Maestri provided some insight into Apple's performance, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> sales, services growth, AI plans, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834994" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/Apple-Logo-Cash-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2676" height="1504" /><br/>
We've highlighted the most interesting tidbits from the Q3 2024 earnings call.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone Performance</h2><br/>
Apple CEO &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; said that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models did better than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models. The install base hit an all-time high during the June quarter.<br/>
<br/>
As for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, Apple CEO &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; said that the company is "very excited" about Apple Intelligence and the level of value that Apple will provide to users. Cook said that Apple Intelligence presents "another reason for a compelling upgrade."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
On Apple Intelligence, Cook said that Apple can't wait to see what kind of amazing things developers do with Apple Intelligence. Cook expects that developers will adopt Apple Intelligence in their apps on a broad basis, with features that are applicable to many types of apps.<br/>
<br/>
He confirmed that Apple is planning a staggered rollout of the Apple Intelligence features. There are some functions that will come over the course of the year, and languages beyond U.S. English will not be available at launch.<br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT integration with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is expected before the end of the calendar year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is investing more in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning, with plans to increase that on a yearly basis.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Sales</h2><br/>
Apple saw a sharp increase in &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; sales thanks to the launch of the M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> during the quarter. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue was at &#36;7.2 billion, up 24 percent from &#36;5.8 billion in the year-ago quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Services Revenue</h2><br/>
Apple saw a steep increase in services revenue at &#36;24.2 billion, up from &#36;21.2 billion a year ago and a new all-time revenue record. Paid subscriptions hit an all-time high, and Apple has more than one billion paid subscriptions across services. Apple set new records in advertising, cloud, and payment services.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CFO Luca Maestri said that Apple is seeing continued growth in the level of engagement that customers have with its ecosystem. Maestri also said that Apple is doing a "very good job" improving the quality of its services and improving the amount of content available. Apple plans to continue to add new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> content.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Other Product Revenue</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> revenue dropped one percent (&#36;39.3B), Mac revenue was up two percent (&#36;7B), and Home, Accessories, and Wearables fell two percent (&#36;8.1B).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Digital Markets Act</h2><br/>
Maestri said that Apple is continuing to discuss its DMA compliance with the European Commission. Apple has seen "a good level of adoption" from developers on the changes, and in general, results for the services business and for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> have been "pretty good until now."<br/>
<br/>
Maestri once again reiterated that the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; is responsible for seven percent of the total revenue that Apple earns in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
Cook said that Apple is working to understand the regulatory requirements it is subject to before introducing Apple Intelligence in the European Union. Apple Intelligence features will not be available in the EU when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> launch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>September Quarter</h2><br/>
Apple said that it expects September quarter revenue to grow year over year at a rate similar to the June quarter. Services revenue is expected to grow double digits, similar to the rest of this year. Gross margin is expected to be 45.5 and 46.6 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Mac will have a challenging compare from a year ago, according to Maestri, as there was the full quarter impact of the 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> in fall 2023. There have been rumors that we could see refreshed M4 MacBook Pros before the end of the year, but if Apple is expecting Mac revenue to fall, that may not happen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-q3-2024-earnings-takeaways/">Apple&#039;s Q3 2024 Earnings Call Takeaways</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-q3-2024-earnings-call-takeaways.2432715/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reports 3Q 2024 Results: &#36;21.4B Profit on &#36;85.8B Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-3q-2024-earnings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reports-3q-2024-results-21-4b-profit-on-85-8b-revenue.2432709/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:37:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-3q-2024-earnings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Jordan Golson</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-reports-third-quarter-results/">announced</a> financial results for its third fiscal quarter of 2024, which corresponds to the second calendar quarter of the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/aapl-3q24-line.jpg" alt="" width="1720" height="792" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960550" /><br/>
For the quarter, Apple posted revenue of &#36;85.8 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;21.4 billion, or &#36;1.40 per diluted share, compared to revenue of &#36;81.8 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;19.9 billion, or &#36;1.26 per diluted share, in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/03/apple-3q-2023-results/">year-ago quarter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple set new June quarter records for both revenue and earnings per share, while the Services category set an all-time revenue record. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> category also saw a notable increase in revenue thanks to the introduction of new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
Gross margin for the quarter was 46.3 percent, compared to 44.5 percent in the year-ago quarter. Apple also declared a quarterly dividend payment of &#36;0.25 per share, payable on August 15 to shareholders of record as of August 12.<blockquote>"Today Apple is reporting a new June quarter revenue record of &#36;85.8 billion, up 5 percent from a year ago," said Tim Cook, Apple's CEO. "During the quarter, we were excited to announce incredible updates to our software platforms at our Worldwide Developers Conference, including Apple Intelligence, a breakthrough personal intelligence system that puts powerful, private generative AI models at the core of iPhone, iPad, and Mac. We very much look forward to sharing these tools with our users, and we continue to invest significantly in the innovations that will enrich our customers' lives, while leading with the values that drive our work."</blockquote>As has been the case for over four years now, Apple is once again not issuing guidance for the current quarter ending in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/aapl-3q24-pie.jpg" alt="" width="2090" height="1172" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960551" /><br/>
Apple will <a href="http://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">provide live streaming</a> of its fiscal Q3 2024 financial results conference call at 2:00 p.m. Pacific, and <em>MacRumors</em> will update this story with coverage of the conference call highlights.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Conference call recap ahead...</b><br/>
<!--more--><br/>
<b>1:41 pm</b>: After declining over 1.5% in regular trading today, Apple's stock is currently up over 1% in after-hours trading following the earnings release.<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:45 pm</b>: Apple CEO Luca Maestri notes that Apple generated nearly &#36;29 billion in operating cash flow and returned over &#36;32 billion to shareholders during the quarter, while the company's installed base of active devices hit all-time highs in all geographic segments.<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:47 pm</b>: On a year-over-year basis, Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> revenue was down 1.0%, Mac revenue was up 2.5%, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue was up 23.7%, Wearables revenue was down 2.3%, and Services revenue was up 14.1%<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:56 pm</b>: Apple's quarterly earnings call with analysts should begin at the top of the hour. Expected on the call are CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and CFO Luca Maestri.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:01 pm</b>: The call is beginning with the usual warning about forward-looking financial statements. Tim and Luca are indeed on the call, beginning with opening statements.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:02 pm</b>: "Apple assumes no obligation to update any forward looking statements, which speak only as of the date they are made."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:02 pm</b>: Tim is on.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:02 pm</b>: Apple reports a June quarter revenue record of &#36;85.8 billion, up 5% from a year ago, and better than Apple had expected. EPS grew double-digits to &#36;1.40, a record for the June quarter. Set quarterly revenue records in more than two dozen countries and regions, including Canada, Mexico, France, Germany, the UK, India. Indonesia, the Philippines and Thailand.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:03 pm</b>: Services revenue set a new all-time record, up 14%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:03 pm</b>: Tim is going over the announcements from WWDC, in particular Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:04 pm</b>: "We are very excited about Apple, intelligence, and we remain incredibly optimistic about the extraordinary possibilities of AI, and its ability to enrich customers lives."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:05 pm</b>: Now he's talking up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, noting 2,500 native spatial apps and new immersive content coming to Vision Pro. "And we've seen great interest for Vision Pro in the enterprise where it can empower companies large and small to pursue their best ideas like never before."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:06 pm</b>: Now &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, revenue was &#36;39.3 billion, down 1% year over year. On a constant currency basis, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales grew compared to 2023.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:07 pm</b>: Moving to Mac, revenue was &#36;7 billion, up 2%  from a year ago. He's mentioning the M3-powered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>'s as the best computer for students and others. In particular, he notes Apple Intelligence running on M3, in particular safety and privacy.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:08 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue was &#36;7.2 billion, 20% higher year over year, on the back of the new 11- and 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, as well as the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:08 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models, powered by the M series of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, will be able to use Apple Intelligence, he notes.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:09 pm</b>: In Wearables, Home and Accessories, revenue was &#36;8.1 billion, down 2% from last year. This category includes Apple Watch, AirPods, HomePods and the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:09 pm</b>: In Services, Apple set an all-time revenue record of &#36;24.2 billion, with paid subs rising to an all-time high. Set new records in advertising, cloud, and payment services.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:11 pm</b>: Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; expanded to more markets, including Canada, Italy, and more. New updates to Services are coming this fall, including National Park hikes to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:13 pm</b>: Tim is talking up Apple's focus on privacy, security, accessibility, and more. "We are determined to keep users in control of their data. And we are just as dedicated to ensuring the security of our user's data."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:13 pm</b>: All of Apple's data centers, including those using cloud compuete, operate on 100% renewable energy.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:14 pm</b>: Now Luca is on to discuss the financials in more detail.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:16 pm</b>: There was a new record of &#36;85.8 billion, up 5% year over year, despite 230 basis points of negative foreign exchange impact. Products revenue was &#36;61.6 billion, up 2% year over year. The install base of active devices reached an all-time high across all products and geographic segments.<br/>
<br/>
Services revenue reached a new record, with an all-time record in developed markets and a June quarter record in emerging markets. Gross margin was 46.3%, at the high end of its guidance range. Products gross margin was 35.3%, down 130 basis points. Services gross margin was 74%, down 60 basis points from last quarter.<br/>
<br/>
OpEx of &#36;14.3 billion, up 7% year over year. Net income was &#36;21.4 billion, diluted EPS of &#36;1.40 (up 11% and a June quarter record). Operating cash flow was &#36;28.9 billion, also a June quarter record.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:16 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; revenue was &#36;39.3 billion, down 1% YoY, but growing on a constant currency basis. "We set June quarter records across several countries, including the UK, Spain and In Poland, Mexico, Indonesia and the Philippines, and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; active install base to a new all time high. In total, and in every geographic segment."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:17 pm</b>: "According to a survey from Cantar &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was the top selling model. In the US, urban China, the UK, Germany, Australia and Japan. Customer satisfaction on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> family continues to be extremely high, with 451 Research measuring it at 98% in percent in the US in their latest reports."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:18 pm</b>: "The Mac installed base reached an all time high, with half of &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; customers in the quarter new to Mac. Customer satisfaction for Mac was recently reported at 96% In the US."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:19 pm</b>: Almost two thirds of customers buying an Apple Watch in the quarter were new to the product. Customer sat of 97% for Watch in the US.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:20 pm</b>: The growth of the install base of active devices "sets a strong foundation for the future expansion of our ecosystem." Transacting and paid accounts continue to show strong double digit growth. There are more than 1 billion paid subscriptions across the platforms, more than double that of four years ago.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:21 pm</b>: "We continue to see businesses leveraging our entire suite of products to drive productivity and creativity for their teams and customers. USAA, a leading insurance and financial services company, recently expanded beyond their existing &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; deployments to provide their employees the latest &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and American Express has continued to add to their fleet of over 10,000 Macs to enhance their employees' productivity."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:22 pm</b>: Apple entered the quarter with &#36;153 billion in cash and marketable securities. It repaid &#36;4.3 billion in maturing debt and increased commercial paper by &#36;1 billion, leaving total debt of &#36;101 billion. Net cash was &#36;52 billion after returning &#36;32 billion to shareholders between dividends and open market repurchases of &#36;26 billion across 139 million AAPL shares.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:23 pm</b>: Foreign exchange will continue being a headwind, affecting 1.5 percentage points year over ear. September quarter revenue is expected to grow at a rate similar to June, with Services revenue growing double digits at a similar rate to the first three quarters of the year. Gross margin between 45.5 and 46.5%, OpEx between &#36;14.2 and &#36;14.4 billion, and a tax rate of around 16.5%. The board declared a cash dividend of &#36;0.25/share later in August.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:23 pm</b>: The Q&A session is beginning.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:25 pm</b>: Q: Can you help us understand where you see &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; replacement cycles today, where you think the size of the base of iPhones that are aged and likely to upgrade are and what that translates to, and potential pent up demand as we enter a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; cycle?<br/>
<br/>
A: The install base hit an all time high during the quarter, and so we were very happy about that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in general, it grew in constant currency. And the 15, as you point out, if you look at the same number of weeks of the 15 from launch and compare that to the 14, the 15 is doing better than the 14. And so that's kind of a state of of where we currently are.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of upgrade rates, it's very difficult mid cycle to call upgrade rates. With Apple intelligence, we're very excited and about the level of value that we're going to provide to users and we believe that that presents another reason for a compelling upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:28 pm</b>: Q: Can you dig into China dynamics a bit, sales down 6% this quarter, 3% in content currency, an improvement from last quarter on a tougher compare. You know that came on the back of some &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; discounting. So can you share color on the China market as a whole? How much do you believe promotions helped in the quarter, how sustainable this improvement is, and if this performance really changes any of your approach to the China market, as we look forward?<br/>
<br/>
A: This quarter was an improvement from the first half of the year. If you look at &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, in particular, for Greater China, the install base set a record. We also, in mainland China, set a June quarter record for upgraders. And so, that that's a very strong signal. iPhones were the top three models in Urban China.<br/>
<br/>
One of the things we look at is the 15 family compared to the 14 family for the same number of weeks from launch. So this goes all the way back to the September of '23 if you if you look at that, the 15 is outperforming the 14. In addition, one of the things that we're very focused on is the level of new customers buying the our products. And so if you look at this on the Mac and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in mainland China, the majority of customers are buying for the first time. We're very confident in the long term.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:29 pm</b>: Q: Now that you've launched Apple Intelligence, will it accelerate Services and augment it, maybe folks need to buy more storage, how is it a catalyst for Services in the next year?<br/>
<br/>
A: We started the rollout of Apple Intelligence this week. Some of the features are out there as of Monday. We couldn't be more excited about getting them out there. This will enable developers to take their apps to the next level, we're taking this first step in getting the beta out there and we're excited to see what they do with it.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:32 pm</b>: Q: Have you seen a shift in demand for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and Pro Max models that could potentially foreshadow consumer demand for Apple Intelligence-enabled phones?<br/>
<br/>
A: We just announced the requirements for the system and the Silicon level in June, and we had limited time in the quarter so it's really too early to tell.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:33 pm</b>: Q: With the focus on upgrader potential for the next few years, what are you expecting for the US promotional environment from your channel partners given the importance of device sales for those partners during an upgrade cycle?<br/>
<br/>
A: We are very excited about Apple Intelligence and what it brings and it's another compelling reason for an upgrade. I think the promotional questions are for the carriers themselves to answer, but I think it will be a key time for a compelling upgrade cycle.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:35 pm</b>: Q: Is the intent to launch Apple Intelligence at the same time to consumers or will it get staggered? How could it affect how consumers buy during the rollout?<br/>
<br/>
A: We started with some features this week, but not the complete suite. There are some languages beyond US English that will happen over the course of the year, and other features. ChatGPT will be integrated by the end of the calendar year. It is a staggered launch.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:37 pm</b>: Q: Services growth rate has been extremely impressive for several quarters. How much is coming from installed base growth versus better monetization of the existing base? How do you see that going forward?<br/>
<br/>
A: Combination of a number of factors, install base growth is very important, because we have more customers. We are seeing this consistently for many quarters, we see continued growth in the level of engagement that our customers have with our ecosystem, we have more transacting accounts every quarter, more people using the ecosystem, both free and paid elements. We see paid accounts growing double digits for many quarters now. Our paid subscriptions on our platform are growing strong double digits as well. Obviously, the growing level of engagement helps us both from an ARPU standpoint and a volume standpoint. <br/>
<br/>
As you've seen over the last several years, we launch new services and we've launched many new services fairly recently. Payments, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, Fitness+, we're providing more opportunities for customers to interact with the ecosystem. And we've done a good job improving the quality of these services. Launching new shows and new games all the time and I think you will continue to see that going forward. Very happy with the 14% growth that we had this quarter.<br/>
<br/>
If you look at performance of Services a year ago, it got a little more challenging in the second half of the fiscal year, but in spite of that we delivered a level of growth better than we were expecting.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:39 pm</b>: Q: You announced Apple Intelligence but also announced partnerships with OpenAI and other partners down the road. How should we think about monetization of models like these and these partnerships? The CapEx investments are being made by these potential partners, but you're leveraging  your distribution. Do you see the Services growth from Apple Intelligence being the larger contributor or these partnerships over time?<br/>
<br/>
A: The way I look at it, Apple Intelligence is the on-device processing and private cloud compute. A lot of that will be things with a personal context, and then for world knowledge, we are integrating with ChatGPT initially and that will be focused on world knowledge. The monetization model, I don't want to get into the terms of the commercial agreements because they're confidential, but I see both aspects as being very important. People want both.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:42 pm</b>: Q: You had margin growth over the last several years and a bit more flat. Are there other headwinds besides FX that are limiting upside perhaps?<br/>
<br/>
A: Foreign exchange is incremental on a year over year basis and is outside our control, we try to hedge but it is what it is. When the dollar is strong our margins are affected. Within the products business, our products have different margin profiles and depending on their relative success in the marketplace, our product gross margin tends to move. The mix of our products has an impact on gross margin. We just launched an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; so that's one of the factors. We want all our products to be successful, so we always look at gross margin dollars as first priority and percentage follows from that.<br/>
<br/>
Also we have the state of the commodity markets and this tends to go in cycles, so we'll see how that plays out over time. We feel good about the level of gross margin we have for our products business. We feel in a good position there.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:44 pm</b>: Q: We keep hearing about this increase in silicon content for AI edge devices, Luca you talk about increasing commodity costs, how should we think about margins for new AI devices, and do any Apple Intelligence features need more hardware than we have today?<br/>
<br/>
A: In terms of the requirements to run Apple Intelligence, there are system requirements and there are silicon requirements, so from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; point of view, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max will run Apple Intelligence and the successor products. If you look at the Mac, it starts with the M-series of silicon that started in 2020, and the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is the same. The M series of silicon. There are system requirements and silicon requirements that go with each of those.<br/>
<br/>
From a gross margin standpoint, we don't provide any color for the quarter, 45.5-46.5, essentially broadly in line with what we recorded for the June quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:45 pm</b>: Q: On China, was the weakness macro related or related to Apple or domestic competitors?<br/>
<br/>
A: The competitive environment is the most competitive in the world and that remains the case. The macro economic factors have been in the press too, I'm not an expert on those, I can only tell you what we're seeing. We were pleased that the business showed improvement from the first half of the year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:47 pm</b>: Q: Developers are just getting their hands on Apple Intelligence, are these going to be iterative applications, is there some category that lends itself more naturally to Apple Intelligence, games, more creative, trying to get a sense...<br/>
<br/>
A: If you look at how we've deployed Apple Intelligence, we've thought about it as all of the apps you use every day. Notes, Mail, Messages and all the rest. There's been a deep level of thinking about how it affects those apps. That's going to surface Apple Intelligence in a way that is natural to the user and in a way that will get them very excited about it.<br/>
<br/>
Similarly, I think the developers will do that on a broad basis with their apps as well. I think it's profound, and we'll see what the developers do. We're excited to get the initial seed out there this week and see what they do. I think it will be amazing.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:49 pm</b>: Q: It sounds like, with Services being strong and FX easing, you're saying product revenue might be flat with the quarter next year. What are the puts and takes in that outlook with Apple Intelligence stoking demand going forward?<br/>
<br/>
A: We have provided... we think we'll be growing company revenue at a state that is similar to what we reported. 5%, in spite of the fact that we'll have 150 bp of FX headwinds in the December quarter. We said that we'll grow Services double digits at a rate similar to the first three quarters of the fiscal year. We are not going into the other categories, there's a lot of good math that you can do from what we've given you. Keep in mind, on Mac we'll have a challenging compare from a year ago given that we had a full-quarter impact of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; 15-inch a year ago, and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; we had the benefit from the launch of the new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; this past quarter so keep that in mind on a sequential basis.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:50 pm</b>: Q: You mentioned a staggered launch of Apple Intelligence, are all of these going to be a part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> or will some potentially be part of iOS 19 next year?<br/>
<br/>
A: We'll start with US English this fall and add more functionality, features, and languages and regions coverage over the next year. We gave a time frame and we're tracking to that.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:52 pm</b>: Q: Are you seeing any impact from changes made to the European app store rules?<br/>
<br/>
A: We have seen a good level of adoption from developers on those changes, we are in ongoing discussions with the European Commission on how to ensure full compliance with the DMA. In general, our results for the Services business and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> have been pretty good. To provide a frame of reference, the percentage of revenue we get from the EU on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; is about 7% of the total.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:53 pm</b>: Q: Re Apple Intelligence, how do you think about the regulatory process in the EU and China, thinking about the rollout, are you embedding the regulartory aspect in it and how should we think about timing?<br/>
<br/>
A: We are engaging with the regulatory bodies and we're moving as fast as we can. Our objective is always to get features out there for everyone. We have to understand the regulatory requirements before we can commit to doing that but we're engaged with both.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:54 pm</b>: Q: On Wearables, it's been lagging there for the last couple of quarters. Any comment on that?<br/>
<br/>
A: When you look at Wearables, Home and Accessories, we have a difficult launch compare. Last year we had the continued benefit of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, the Watch SE, and the first Watch Ultra. It's important to keep that in mind. If you take a step back and look at the business across the trailing 12 months, the Wearables business has grown to almost &#36;40 billion, double what it was five years ago.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:56 pm</b>: Q: You referenced the investment in innovation, R&D to sales ratio reached a record even before launching Apple Intelligence. How should we think about CapEx for cloud compute capacity and is it possible to forecast services usage as these things roll out?<br/>
<br/>
A: We've increased R&D over time, we've been investing in AI and ML for years. We've redeployed certain skills onto AI and ML, and the growth is sort of embedded in our numbers that we've shared. On CapEx, remember that we employ a hybrid approach where we do things internally and we have partners that we do business with externally where the CapEx would appear in their respective businesses. Yes, you can expect that we will continue to invest and increase it year on year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:58 pm</b>: Q: When we look at the free cash flow margins for the first nine months, they're up materially. What, in the services mix or cost controls, what is driving structural higher free cash flow margins across the business?<br/>
<br/>
A: I'm glad you noticed that. We're pretty pleased with that fact. We also increased our return to shareholders, a record quarter for us. An improvement in the topline helps, margin expansion that we've had over the last several years and quarters has helped. That is driving better operating cash flow. On the CapEx front, as Tim said, we employ a hybrid model. Some investments show up on our balance sheet, other investments show up somewhere else and we pay as we go. In general, we try to run the company efficiently. We think capital efficiency is a good thing. We're pleased that our free cash flow is doing well this year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:59 pm</b>: The call has completed. Expect the next quarterly earnings call in late October.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-3q-2024-earnings/">Apple Reports 3Q 2024 Results: &#36;21.4B Profit on &#36;85.8B Revenue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reports-3q-2024-results-21-4b-profit-on-85-8b-revenue.2432709/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates App Store Guidelines for PC Emulator Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/app-store-review-guidelines-pc-emulator-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-app-store-guidelines-for-pc-emulator-apps.2432705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:44:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/app-store-review-guidelines-pc-emulator-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>App Store Review Guidelines</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today refreshed its <a href="https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/">App Store Guidelines</a> created for developers, modifying the emulator rules to include express permission for PC emulators to download games.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
Guideline 4.7 has been updated to state that PC emulator apps can offer to download games. The guideline previously said that console emulator apps could include the option to download games, but it did not explicitly cover PC emulators.<br/>
<br/>
The rule change comes following Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> approval of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-approves-first-retro-pc-emulator-ios/">PC emulator UTM SE</a>, which lets users emulate old versions of Windows, macOS, and Linux to use classic software and games.<br/>
<br/>
Apple initially rejected UTM SE in June, even though it started <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">allowing retro game emulators</a> back in April. Apple told the app's developers at the time that it violated the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; guidelines because a "PC is not a console." The developers behind UTM SE were able to make some technical changes, and Apple ultimately approved the app.<br/>
<br/>
UTM SE was the first PC emulator app to be allowed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but the guideline changes today will streamline the approval process for similar apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also updated its separate guidelines for app notarization, which applies to third-party apps that are submitted for distribution outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the European Union. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; guidelines 4.7, 4.7.2, and 4.7.3 are now applicable to the notarization process.<br/>
<br/>
The 4.7 guideline allows for mini apps, mini games, streaming games, chatbots, plug-ins, and game emulators. 4.7.2 prevents apps from extending or exposing native platform APIs to the software without Apple's permission, and 4.7.3 says that apps may not share data or privacy permissions to any individual software offered within an app without user consent. Prior to today's update, these guidelines were not part of the EU notarization review process.<br/>
<br/>
Apps distributed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; are not subject to all of Apple's rules, but to receive notarization from Apple, third-party apps do have to adhere to some guidelines. Apple created the notarization process for EU apps distributed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and an app must have Apple approval to run on an Apple device.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store-review-guidelines/">App Store Review Guidelines</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/app-store-review-guidelines-pc-emulator-apps/">Apple Updates App Store Guidelines for PC Emulator Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-app-store-guidelines-for-pc-emulator-apps.2432705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Files Motion to Dismiss Department of Justice Antitrust Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-doj-motion-to-dismiss/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-files-motion-to-dismiss-department-of-justice-antitrust-lawsuit.2432699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:11:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-doj-motion-to-dismiss/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>DOJ</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Apple vs. DoJ</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today filed a motion to dismiss its ongoing lawsuit with the United States Department of Justice, a standard step in the litigation process. In its motion to dismiss, Apple argues that the government's complaint has not demonstrated anticompetitive conduct, anticompetitive effect that harms consumers, or that Apple is a monopoly power in the U.S. smartphone market. The government needs to prove all three of these claims for a successful antitrust lawsuit.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-vs-DOJ-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943221" /><br/>
For the anticompetitive allegation, the DoJ lawsuit focused on third-party access to Apple services and features, but Apple argues that there is longstanding Supreme Court precedent that companies can set the terms and conditions of their third-party dealings. Apple claims that the DoJ is attempting to force it to spend money to develop tools for big business competitors, which could have a "chilling" effect on innovation. The DoJ suggested, for example, that Apple should have developed an iMessage app for Android.<br/>
<blockquote>iMessage is Apple's proprietary, innovative messaging service that Apple created to competitively differentiate iPhone. Under the Government's view, companies like Apple should face antitrust liability for not expending the resources, cost, and time to develop versions of proprietary products and services for competitors' devices.</blockquote><br/>
Apple points out that the DoJ's complaint does not explain how Apple's alleged limiting of "super apps," cloud streaming apps, digital wallets, messaging apps, and competing smartwatches has harmed consumers or impacted consumer choice about which smartphone to purchase. For a successful antitrust lawsuit, the DoJ needs to prove that Apple's actions hurt consumers and stifle competition, and the DoJ argues that Apple has "locked" customers into its ecosystem.<br/>
<blockquote>It is implausible to claim, as the Government does, that Apple has deterred any customers from switching to Google or Samsung because of its policies with respect to "super apps," cloud gaming, smartwatches, or anything else. The opposite is much more plausible: Users unhappy with Apple's reasonable policies on third-party access can and do switch away to competitors' devices, where those limits do not exist.</blockquote><br/>
Apple argues that it is not a monopolist because it faces competition from companies like Google and Samsung, preventing the government from establishing the "typical hallmarks of monopoly power." Apple does not have enough U.S. smartphone marketshare to make the monopoly claim easy for the government to establish. The DoJ has compared Apple to Microsoft, but Microsoft had a 95 percent share of the operating system market when it faced an antitrust lawsuit, while Apple's is closer to 65 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Apple further suggests that the DoJ is aiming to have the court establish a "new theory of antitrust liability" that no prior court has recognized and that would provide "unprecedented authority to control Apple design choices." Apple says that the DoJ is targeting the very features that distinguish iPhones from competing devices, and if the DoJ ultimately wins the case, courts would need to "oversee product-design and policy choices," which they are not equipped to do.<br/>
<br/>
A motion to dismiss limits the information that Apple can provide to dispute the DoJ's claims, and rulings often favor plaintiffs. The allegations that the DoJ made are assumed to be true at this stage, and Apple needs to prove that the claims fail as a matter of law. For this reason, the lawsuit is likely to progress, though claims could be narrowed and there is a chance for dismissal.<br/>
<br/>
If the court rules in the Department of Justice's favor on the dismissal, there will be many future chances for Apple to sway the court because this is a legal battle that will span years.<br/>
<br/>
After Apple's motion to dismiss, the government has until September 12 to file an opposition brief. From there, Apple will file a reply brief on October 10, and there could be a possible hearing after that. A ruling on the motion to dismiss is expected in late 2024 or early 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Should the government win, Apple will file an answer to the initial complaint, leading to a discovery period where both parties provide documents, expert testimony, and depositions, which can last for over a year. A summary judgment will follow, which is where Apple can make a stronger case, and that might not happen until 2027. Should the case ultimately go to trial, a trial could take place sometime in 2028, or even later.<br/>
<br/>
For a refresher on the DoJ's antitrust claims against Apple, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">we have a dedicated guide</a> that highlights everything you need to know about the U.S. vs. Apple legal fight.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/doj/">DOJ</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">Apple vs. DoJ</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-doj-motion-to-dismiss/">Apple Files Motion to Dismiss Department of Justice Antitrust Lawsuit</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-files-motion-to-dismiss-department-of-justice-antitrust-lawsuit.2432699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Adds AI-Powered Google Lens and Tab Compare to Chrome for Desktop</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-lens-ai-chrome-desktop/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-adds-ai-powered-google-lens-and-tab-compare-to-chrome-for-desktop.2432693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-lens-ai-chrome-desktop/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today announced three new AI features that are coming to its Chrome browser, with Google taking advantage of the latest Google AI and Gemini models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
Google Lens is now available for the Chrome desktop browser, allowing users to search for what they see on the browser screen with a quick drag and search gesture. Google says that Chrome users can select anything on the page to search for visual matches, including text and images.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Introducing the new Google Lens in Chrome desktop" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/43YUCNEHBHU" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Searches can be refined by color, brand, and other details, and follow up questions are available for a deeper dive into a topic.<br/>
<br/>
Tab compare is a new feature that is designed to let users see an AI-generated overview of products from across multiple tabs in one spot. Google says that this is useful for comparing reviews, prices, and other elements of multiple products when deciding what to purchase.<br/>
<br/>
Google is also introducing a natural language search option for Chrome browsing history, allowing Chrome users to quickly find a site that they visited in the past with a phrase like "What was that ice cream shop I looked at last week?" Conversational search is optional, and can be turned on or off in the Chrome settings. It will not include data from incognito mode.<br/>
<br/>
The AI-powered Google Lens feature will be available with the latest Chrome update that's rolling out over the next few days, while the other two features will be available in the next few weeks. Tab compare and the browser search option will both be rolled out in the U.S. to begin with.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-lens-ai-chrome-desktop/">Google Adds AI-Powered Google Lens and Tab Compare to Chrome for Desktop</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-adds-ai-powered-google-lens-and-tab-compare-to-chrome-for-desktop.2432693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;500 Off M3 MacBook Pro With Amazon and Best Buy&#039;s New Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-m3-macbook-pro-with-amazon-and-best-buys-new-sales.2432691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:31:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">Best Buy</a> today have introduced major discounts on the 14-inch and 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro, providing up to &#36;500 off select models of the 2023 computer. In regards to Best Buy's prices, these deals are available to all members and do not require a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-blue-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935646" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's and Amazon's deals include all-time low prices on the 14-inch and 16-inch models, and the best discounts will be found on the larger screen computers. The 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro is currently discounted by &#36;500 on Amazon and Best Buy, which are solid second-best prices. You'll also find up to &#36;300 off the 14-inch computers at both retailers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;500 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for the MacBook Air, we're also tracking a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/best-buy-macbook-air-back-to-school/">massive collection of discounts on the M2 and M3 MacBook Air models</a> this week. The M2 MacBook Air is available for just &#36;799.00, while the M3 models start at &#36;849.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,399.99 (&#36;199 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KB9M3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,999.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5L3PPZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,399.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5MKMD4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,999.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5K7BCR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;3,499.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/">Get Up to &#36;500 Off M3 MacBook Pro With Amazon and Best Buy&#039;s New Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-m3-macbook-pro-with-amazon-and-best-buys-new-sales.2432691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Enable Apple Intelligence If You&#039;re Outside the US</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-enable-apple-intelligence-if-youre-outside-the-us.2432686/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:47:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us&#038;post_date=1722530854/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is introducing a set of AI features in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 under the banner "Apple Intelligence." These features are officially only currently available in beta to developers in the US, but it's actually pretty easy to get it up and running on iPhones and iPads in most other locations with the exception of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-intelligence-europe-delay/">European Union</a> and China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
The main reason Apple has limited region access to Apple Intelligence is that it only supports US English at this time, but if you can work with that – and you have a compatible device – then there's no technical reason why you can't start exploring the new AI features. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Supported Devices</h2><br/>
Apple Intelligence encompasses a range of capabilities, including composing text and emails, automating actions across various apps, generating images, summarizing documents and texts, and more. However, these features require a lot of on-device computing power, so before you do anything, it's worth checking if your device is compatible. iPhone users need either an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max to run Apple Intelligence, while only iPads powered by M1 or later Apple silicon processors are compatible. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Install Beta Software</h2><br/>
If your device is supported, the first thing you need to do is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-18-developer-beta-iphone/">install the developer beta for your device</a>. Once you've followed the instructions provided in the linked article and your device is up and running with the latest beta, follow these steps on your iPhone or iPad.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open <strong>Settings</strong>, then tap through to <strong>General ➝ Language & Region</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Add Language..</strong> and choose <strong>English (US)</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Region</strong> and choose <strong>United States</strong>. (Note that this won't affect your App Store regions or purchases.)<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/settings-region.jpg" alt="settings" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960491" /><br/>
  <li>Return to the main <strong>Settings</strong> menu and tap <strong>Apple Intelligence & Siri</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Language</strong> and choose <strong>English (United States)</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>You will now be able to join the Apple Intelligence waitlist, which in most cases gets accepted in just a few minutes. Under the Apple Intelligence header text, tap <strong>Join Waitlist</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-intelligence-join-waitlist.jpg" alt="" width="1391" height="807" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960498" /><br/>
<li>After what should hopefully be a short wait, the message will change to <strong>Turn On Apple Intelligence</strong>. Tap it, and a welcome message should appear, indicating you have sucessfully enabled the AI features on your device. </li></ol><br/>
<br/>
You can learn more <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">here</a> about all of the Apple Intelligence features available in the iOS 18.1 developer beta. Note that some of the Apple Intelligence additions <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">won't be coming until later</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us/">How to Enable Apple Intelligence If You&#039;re Outside the US</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-enable-apple-intelligence-if-youre-outside-the-us.2432686/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade Frustrations Persist for Game Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-game-developers.2432682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:17:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some developers continue to be unhappy working with Apple's subscription-based mobile gaming service <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, <a href="https://mobilegamer.biz/inside-apple-arcade-again-late-payments-stonewalled-studios-terrible-tech-support-and-vision-pro-woes/"><em>mobilegamer.biz</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/apple-arcade-orange-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-748620" /><br/>
Talking to the website, some developers said that studios have to wait up to six months to receive payments from &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;. They also pointed out difficulties getting responses to routine emails, unsatisfactory technical support, and poor discoverability. One developer said:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>We were able to sign a good deal for our titles which covered our whole development budget. Things have changed since the early times, it's a very difficult and long process to sign a deal with Apple these days. The lack of vision and clear focus of the platform is frustrating and if there is any goal, it keeps changing every year or so. Also technical support is pretty miserable.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Most developers pointed out that &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; pays well, particularly during its first few years:<blockquote>Whatever anyone else says, the advances were fantastic. They were off the charts compared to what we're used to being paid. And you got royalties on top of that.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
While initially developers benefited from prompt monthly payments from the Bonus Pool of ongoing royalty payments, there is now a five month backlog. One developer claims to have almost gone out of business as a result of the slow payments, while others have had to chase for payments for months.<br/>
<br/>
Developers also pointed out general communication issues, and when they do receive a response, the results are often disappointing. One developer shared:<blockquote>We can go weeks without hearing from Apple at all and their general response time to emails is three weeks, if they reply at all. We're supposed to be able to ask product, technical and commercial questions, but often half the Apple team won't turn up and when they do they have no idea what's going on and can't answer our questions, either because they don't have any knowledge on how to answer it, or are not able to share that info for confidentiality reasons.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
There are also apparently significant issues with developing &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games for the Vision Pro headset. Developers expressed their frustration with Apple's technical support for the  Vision Pro, which they described as inadequate and unhelpful. One developer said:<blockquote>The technical support is awful – the worst I have seen anywhere. They are unable to offer any insights into how the hardware and the software it runs on works, or how essential middleware is meant to work with it.<br/>
<br/>
Developing for Vision Pro is like going back in time 10 years because despite the advertised power – and the cost – it is not a machine built for gaming. Getting any complex games working on the platform is difficult.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Other sources told mobilegamer.biz that while they had been approached by Apple to make a game for the Vision Pro, they were offered no financial incentives and no guarantees of promotion. This contrasts with competitors like Meta, which offers generous financial incentives and marketing guarantees to developers creating content for its platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Developers also pointed out issues with quality assurance and updates, claiming that a prolonged discussion with Apple over a single update cost their team two months of work. "Submitting updates is so painful our developers started trying to avoid it," they said. Likewise, there are apparently issues with discoverability. Other developers shared their frustration, stating:<blockquote>It feels like the game's been in a morgue for the last two years. It doesn't matter what we put in the game, Apple won't feature us, it's like we don't exist. So as a developer you think, well, they've given us this money for exclusivity… I don't want to give them the money back, but I do want people to play my game. It's like we're invisible.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
One developer concluded with a broader critique of &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;'s strategic direction:<blockquote>Arcade has no clear strategy and feels like a bolt-on to the Apple company ecosystem rather than like it is truly supported inside the company. Apple 100% does not understand gamers – they have little to no info on who plays their games that they can share with developers, or how they interact with games on the platform already.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
I believe Apple Arcade is a good idea in general, but they need a clear goal for where it should go and what it is for. That's a question they need to answer and then act accordingly.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Another developer offered a slightly more positive perspective:<blockquote>I think Arcade knows who its audience is much more today than at the outset. If that doesn't turn out to be high concept artful indie games, that's not Apple's fault. If they can build a business on family games, good for them and good for the devs who can chase that opportunity.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; launched in September 2019, giving users access to a large library of games for a monthly fee of &#36;6.99. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is also available as part of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription bundle, which combines multiple Apple services into a single monthly plan. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-developers/">Apple Arcade Frustrations Persist for Game Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-game-developers.2432682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
