<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:03:21 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Urgently Addressing iPhone 15 Pro Max Production Challenges to Boost Supply</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/kuo-apple-improving-iphone-15-pro-max-production/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-urgently-addressing-iphone-15-pro-max-production-challenges-to-boost-supply.2403015/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 08:50:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/kuo-apple-improving-iphone-15-pro-max-production/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has urgently addressed production challenges related to the iPhone 15 Pro Max's upgraded Telephoto lens in order to boost supply of the device, according to <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/iphone-15-pro-max%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%A4%E4%BB%98%E6%99%82%E9%96%93%E5%AE%8C%E5%85%A8%E5%8F%96%E6%B1%BA%E6%96%BC%E5%A4%A7%E7%AB%8B%E5%85%89%E7%8D%A8%E5%AE%B6%E4%BE%9B%E6%87%89%E4%B9%8B%E5%9B%9B%E9%87%8D%E5%8F%8D%E5%B0%84%E7%A8%9C%E9%8F%A1-%E6%BD%9B%E6%9C%9B%E9%8F%A1-%E9%8F%A1%E9%A0%AD%E4%B9%8B%E5%87%BA%E8%B2%A8%E9%87%8F-%E5%9B%9B%E9%87%8D%E5%8F%8D%E5%B0%84%E7%A8%9C%E9%8F%A1%E9%8F%A1%E9%A0%AD%E5%96%AE%E5%83%B9%E9%A1%AF%E8%91%97%E6%8F%90%E5%8D%8720-%E4%BB%A5%E4%B8%8A-iphone-15-pro-max-55a8711abb17">research shared today</a> by supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/f-4d62f49966d4af93a651379f09657fba6cc3c770.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910268" /><br/>
Kuo said the iPhone 15 Pro Max's tetraprism lens <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/">with up to 5x optical zoom</a> has been the most significant supply bottleneck for the device. In response, he said that Apple supplier Largan Precision has expanded its production lines for the tetraprism lens in order to meet strong demand for the iPhone 15 Pro Max, which is already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/">facing November shipping estimates</a> for some configurations on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro Max shipping estimates range from 3-4 weeks for some configurations to 6-7 weeks for others. Yesterday, Kuo said iPhone 15 Pro Max demand had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/">outpaced iPhone 14 Pro Max demand</a> during the same period last year.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the camera-related bottleneck, Kuo previously said that the iPhone 15 Pro Max entered mass production later than the other devices in the iPhone 15 series, which has presumably contributed to the device's lengthy shipping delays. In the U.S., the iPhone 15 Pro Max starts at &#36;1,199 with 256GB of storage.<br/>
<br/>
All of the iPhone 15 models are now available to order and launch this Friday.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/kuo-apple-improving-iphone-15-pro-max-production/">Kuo: Apple Urgently Addressing iPhone 15 Pro Max Production Challenges to Boost Supply</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-urgently-addressing-iphone-15-pro-max-production-challenges-to-boost-supply.2403015/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Color Options: Which Did You Choose?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-color-options/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-color-options-which-did-you-choose.2403006/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 08:12:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-color-options&#038;post_date=1695060736/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models are available in a range of color options, with entirely new hues available on both sets of devices, as well as some popular classics. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> lineups have different colors to choose from, so if you have your heart set on a particular shade, you may not be able to get your preferred model in that color. This guide focuses on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models, but for more information about the color options of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-color-options/">check out our other color options guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Colors-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911673" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus are available in a total of five colors, two of which are entirely new for this year's lineup. Although previous standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> color options have tended to be bolder and brighter, in 2023, Apple chose to offer a much more muted color palette due to its color-infused frosted glass back. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus's color options are as follows:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Black</li><br/>
<li>Blue</li><br/>
<li>Green</li><br/>
<li>Yellow</li><br/>
<li>Pink</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Previous years' "Midnight" is now simply "Black" once again. This returns as the standard model's darkest color option, differing from Midnight since it no longer has a slight hint of navy blue. "Starlight," which replaced "White" several years ago, is no longer available, and there is no equivalent to either of these light, neutral color options in the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-and-15-Plus-Newsroom.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910395" /><br/>
All of the other new colors, Blue, Green, Yellow, and Pink, are pale, muted pastel shades, toning down some of the options available with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>. While they are quite understated colors, the overall look is very distinctive to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s more refined design.<br/>
<br/>
Unlike previous &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineups, there is no PRODUCT(RED) &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. Apple usually releases a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; color option in the spring, so a PRODUCT(RED) &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; could potentially be in the pipeline for early 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="how_to_decide_on_a_color">How to Decide on a Color</h3><br/>
If you use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a case, you may wish to consider which device color will best complement your case. You may prefer a more neutral tone such as Black and use a more colorful case. Alternatively, you could choose a more striking device color like Green or Pink and use a more neutral case. A case is definitely a good option for a bolder look, especially since the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s color options are generally so muted and pale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-finewoven-cases.jpg" alt="" width="2984" height="1198" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910345" /><br/>
Black may age better over time as new devices are released since it is a neutral, monochrome shade, and has effectively been offered across multiple &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; generations. If you do not use a case at all, you may wish to take advantage of a more eye-catching color option such as Yellow.<br/>
<br/>
If you want an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in a brand new color for this year, Pink and Green are the best options. These colors are the most noticeably new and clearly indicate that you have the latest-generation device.<br/>
<br/>
Your choice of color may also be dependent on how often you upgrade your ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌. If you upgrade every year, you may be more confident in buying a more striking new color. If you upgrade more often, it can be a good idea to get a different color every time. A new finish can certainly add some novelty to purchasing a new ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ and make it feel more different from your previous device. Alternatively, if you tend to keep your ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ for many years and upgrade less often, it may be wiser to consider a color that is more similar to one you have enjoyed previously.<br/>
<br/>
Customers with multiple Apple devices may also want to get an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; color that complements their other devices. For example, if you have a Pink <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, it will be best complemented by the Pink &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. Likewise, if you already have a Space Gray MacBook Pro, it will likely be best accompanied by a Black &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-color-options/">iPhone 15 Color Options: Which Did You Choose?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-color-options-which-did-you-choose.2403006/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro With USB-C Reviews: Few Hardware Changes, But Useful iOS 17 Software Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/airpods-pro-usb-c/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-with-usb-c-reviews-few-hardware-changes-but-useful-ios-17-software-features.2403005/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 08:04:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/airpods-pro-usb-c&#038;post_date=1695060272/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At its iPhone 15 event last week, Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">updated second-generation AirPods Pro</a> with a USB-C charging case, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/new-airpods-pro-features/">additional dust resistance</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/apple-vision-pro-lossless-new-airpods-pro-2-only/">support for lossless audio with Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset</a>. Apple still classifies these as second-generation AirPods Pro, and it does not sell the USB-C case separately.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-USB-C-Port-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911678" /><br/>
The updated AirPods Pro have been available to order since last week, and will begin arriving to customers and launch in stores on Friday. Ahead of time, select media outlets and YouTube channels have shared first impressions of the updated earbuds.<br/>
<br/>
There is minimal commentary about the hardware changes, with most reviews agreeing that there is little reason for existing second-generation AirPods Pro users to upgrade. USB-C is a convenient addition, additional dust resistance is welcomed, and lossless audio support cannot be tested until the Vision Pro launches in the U.S. in early 2024.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17 adds several features to all second-generation AirPods Pro, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-airpods/">Adaptive Audio, Conversation Awareness, and Personalized Volume</a>. Keep in mind that these software features are also available on the original second-generation AirPods Pro released in September 2022, so there is no need to update to the USB-C model to use them.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.theverge.com/23878402/apple-airpods-pro-usb-c-adaptive-audio-conversation-awareness-test-review"><em>The Verge</em>'s Chris Welch</a> on Adaptive Audio:<blockquote>Adaptive Audio is meant to be a set-it-and-forget-it mode that blends active noise cancellation and transparency, canceling loud distractions where needed while also helping you stay present in your environment. In my experience so far, this feature rarely cancels my surroundings to the same degree as the full noise cancellation mode (I wouldn’t use it on a plane), but it reduces outside sound enough to not take away from my music — even at lower volumes. To my ears so far, it’s basically an even smarter version of the adaptive transparency that Apple debuted with last year’s AirPods Pro.</blockquote><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/09/18/airpods-pro-get-usb-c-and-a-few-new-tricks/"><em>TechCrunch</em>'s Brian Heater</a> on Conversation Awareness:<blockquote>Conversational Awareness is a nice addition. It uses a combination of different sensors to determine when you’re talking. That includes obvious things like built-in mics, coupled with more surprising elements like the accelerometer, which detects vibration to determine that you are, in fact, the one who is talking, without having to resort to something like voice recognition. When that's triggered, the audio begins to lower, effectively getting out of your way when talking.<br/>
<br/>
I was impressed by the detection. It didn't trigger when I, say, coughed, yawned or cleared my throat. When I started talking, however, the music began to lower. It doesn't stay down for any specific set amount of time. The company says it relies on an algorithm to determine such things. Factors include the length of time you're talking, so it doesn't mistake a break in conversation for the end of one.</blockquote><a href="https://www.thestreet.com/deals/apple-airpods-pro-usb-c-review-adaptive-audio#adaptive-mode-is-a-smart-combination-of-transparency-and-noise-cancellation"><em>TheStreet</em>'s Jacob Krol</a> on both Adaptive Audio and Conversation Awareness:<blockquote>It feels almost magical as it works as intended. For instance, sitting in a bustling hotel lobby, you'll encounter background noise and chatter from other patrons nearby; once I engaged Adaptive, it lowers the brunt of the noise, and with music playing, it all becomes very faint. If a louder noise appears, like a cart being pushed through the space, it will process it in real time and lower it specifically.<br/>
<br/>
Let's take a more likely or commonly occurring scenario—I'm walking around my apartment with AirPods Pro, listening to some music with Adaptive on. It lowers the brunt of my HVAC system, similar to how the ANC performs, but I can hear a faint knock on my door as I'm expecting a package from FedEx. I open the door, and thanks to Conversation Awareness turned on, I can start talking, and AirPods Pro automatically switches to Transparency mode.<br/>
</blockquote><a href="https://www.inverse.com/tech/airpods-pro-2nd-gen-usb-c-review"><em>Inverse</em>'s Raymond Wong</a> on Personalized Volume:<blockquote>Personalized Volume uses machine learning to automatically adjust the volume just for your ears. Apple says Personalized Volume is determined by "environmental conditions and volume selections" over time. I didn't notice any meaningful volume adjustments over a week of testing so I turned it off.</blockquote><h2>Videos</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eT3CFyuCdU8?si=ws_dpGyDsipUI00K" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bbfRJCfnjUE?si=aoVutFMk0jTlbXgz" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B1THpjzy-gs?si=vmiF81LKHNLUVduW" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JBQvu6l-3e4?si=uFtmzippNLpGRmTQ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GbzLugBp_t0?si=InmArzTiOdwT3yA7" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/airpods-pro-usb-c/">AirPods Pro With USB-C Reviews: Few Hardware Changes, But Useful iOS 17 Software Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-with-usb-c-reviews-few-hardware-changes-but-useful-ios-17-software-features.2403005/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Take Up to &#36;89 Off Apple&#039;s 9th and 10th Gen iPad With Record Low Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/deals-9th-10th-gen-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-take-up-to-89-off-apples-9th-and-10th-gen-ipad-with-record-low-prices.2402993/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:31:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/deals-9th-10th-gen-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a collection of deals on Apple's iPad, including the 9th and 10th generation models. Both sales include matches of all-time low prices on these tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
Starting with Apple's 10th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad, this model is available at the all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.00. The soonest the iPad can be delivered is around September 20, but some colors are seeing dates extend into October.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Deals-399-2.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893587" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Three colors are on sale, including Yellow, Blue, and Pink. You won't need any coupon code in order to get these record low prices, as they have been applied automatically by Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Only the 64GB Wi-Fi is getting a best-ever discount right now on Amazon, but there are a few solid second-best prices to check out. The 256GB Wi-Fi iPad is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;549.00</strong></a> in every color (&#36;50 off). You can also get &#36;50 off both <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJMCHC91%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">cellular versions</a> of the tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
There's also a solid discount on the previous-generation 9th generation iPad this week on Amazon. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;269.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. This is just about &#36;20 higher than the previous all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/yellow-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-844762" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;269.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The 256GB Wi-Fi iPad is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;389.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;479.00 on Amazon. This is a match of the record low price on this version of the tablet, and right now only Amazon has the sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;89 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;389.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/deals-9th-10th-gen-ipad/">Deals: Take Up to &#36;89 Off Apple&#039;s 9th and 10th Gen iPad With Record Low Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-take-up-to-89-off-apples-9th-and-10th-gen-ipad-with-record-low-prices.2402993/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17: How to Set and Label Multiple Timers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-label-multiple-timers-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-how-to-set-and-label-multiple-timers.2402991/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:18:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-label-multiple-timers-ios&#038;post_date=1695057487/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's taken this long, but in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, Apple has added support for multiple timers, and has also made it easy to manage several timers on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with the introduction of labels. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/set-multiple-timers-ios.jpg" alt="timers" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912030" /><br/>
That's right. Believe it or not, iPhones have not included the ability to set multiple ongoing timers until now. In &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, the Clock app finally enables several timers to be set that will run down at the same time, allowing you to keep track of more than one thing, which is handy when cooking a meal that includes several dishes, for example.<br/>
<br/>
Not only can you have several timers counting down at the same time, you can also label timers, which helps you identify each one in your timer list. That way, you'll always know which timer relates to what, and you can save custom timers without having to remember what they were set up for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/siri-suggestion-set-a-timer.jpg" alt="siri" width="1339" height="725" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912032" /><br/>
To quickly set a timer on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, swipe down on the Home screen, search "timer," and tap the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> Suggestion, or to set a timer with a name, say "&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, set a timer called [name] for [duration]." Alternatively, open the Clock app and tap the Timers tab. In the timer setup options, select a duration, then tap the Label field and type in what you want to call it. <br/>
<br/>
Choose a distinct alert for the timer if it helps you recognize it. Note that in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, you also have the option of selecting one of several preset durations in the setup screen. When a timer is set, it will be added to your editable list of timers. For added convenience, the list will also include any recently completed timers that you used. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/set-multiple-timers.jpg" alt="" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912029" /><br/>
If your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, the last timer you set will appear inside it when you are doing other things on your device. The most recently set timer will also appear as a Live Activity on the Lock Screen, and you can tap to expand it and see any other timers that are running concurrently. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-label-multiple-timers-ios/">iOS 17: How to Set and Label Multiple Timers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-how-to-set-and-label-multiple-timers.2402991/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 vs. Ultra 2 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 25 Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-ultra-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-vs-ultra-2-buyers-guide-25-differences-compared.2402984/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 06:33:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-ultra-2&#038;post_date=1695054834/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At its "Wonderlust" event in 2023, alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, Apple announced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>. The Apple Watch Ultra is a relatively new kind of smartwatch from Apple with a focus on withstanding extreme environments, a high level of durability, extended battery life, and additional features to aid activities like diving and exploration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9-vs-Ultra-2-Buyers-Guide.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911647" /><br/>
Both the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; feature the S9 chip, a second-generation Ultra Wideband chip, an Always-On Retina display, IP6X dust resistance, and more, but there are significant differences between the two devices.<br/>
<br/>
With as little as &#36;50 between the 45mm stainless steel &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and the Apple Watch Ultra, some prospective customers will be weighing up whether it is worth spending a little extra to get the 49mm Ultra model. While there is a &#36;400 difference between the 41mm aluminum &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and the Apple Watch Ultra, the high-end model offers a set of features to address specific challenges, so it may even be worth it for some of these buyers.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch Ultra (second-generation)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Aluminum casing</td><br/>
 <td>Aerospace-grade titanium casing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Front crystal curves at edges onto shaped aluminum casing</td><br/>
 <td>Lighter, corrosion resistant case with raised edges to protect the flat sapphire front crystal</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Digital Crown with haptic feedback and side button</td><br/>
 <td>Digital Crown with haptic feedback, side button, and customizable Action button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>45mm or 41 mm case size (vertical)</td><br/>
 <td>49mm casing size (vertical)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>10.7mm thickness</td><br/>
 <td>14.4mm thickness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 31.9 grams to 51.5 grams</td><br/>
 <td>Weighs 61.4 grams</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ion-X front glass (aluminum) or sapphire crystal (stainless steel)</td><br/>
 <td>Sapphire crystal front glass</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Curved display with refractive edge</td><br/>
 <td>Flat display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>904 sq mm (41mm) or 1,143 sq mm (45mm) display area</td><br/>
 <td>1164 sq mm display area</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>352 by 430 pixels (41mm) or 396 by 484 pixels (45mm)</td><br/>
 <td>410 by 502 pixels</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 2,000 nits brightness</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 3,000 nits brightness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Exclusive Wayfinder and Modular Ultra faces</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/night-mode/">Night Mode</a> for low-visibility conditions</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single speaker</td><br/>
 <td>Dual speakers</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Triple-microphone array with beamforming and wind noise mitigation</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>GPS (L1)</td><br/>
 <td>Precision dual-frequency GPS (L1 and L5)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>86-decibel Siren to attract attention</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Water resistant to 50m</td><br/>
 <td>Water resistant to 100m</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Swimproof</td><br/>
 <td>Swimproof and recreational dive to 40m</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Tested to MIL-STD 810H</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>EN13319 certification</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Water temperature sensor, depth gauge, and dive computer app</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 18-hour battery life, up to 36 hours in Low Power Mode</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 36-hour battery life, up to 72 hours in Low Power Mode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Midnight, Starlight, Silver, Pink, and PRODUCT(RED) (aluminum) or Silver, Graphite, or Gold (stainless steel)</td><br/>
 <td>Natural titanium finish only</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;399 (aluminum) and &#36;699 (stainless steel)</td><br/>
 <td>Priced at &#36;799</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra offers specific capabilities to address the requirements of those who need their Apple Watch to provide assistance in challenging environments. If you need a more durable Apple Watch with features like a brighter display, louder speakers, a more reliable GPS, better water resistance, and more, the Apple Watch Ultra is undoubtedly the best choice. <br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra is also the largest and most feature-rich Apple Watch option available, not to mention that it offers the first true redesign of the device since its introduction in 2015. For technology enthusiasts, Apple Watch Ultra represents a way to get a new Apple Watch experience with the top specifications. Features like longer battery life and a larger, brighter display are also highly accessible, and will be beneficial to all users. As such, some customers may still be inclined to choose the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; over the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj;, even if they do not need it for use in challenging environments.<br/>
<br/>
As the largest Apple Watch model to date, the size of the Apple Watch Ultra will not be for everyone. If you already prefer the 41mm Apple Watch casing size, the Apple Watch Ultra may be far too large for you. If in doubt, it may be worth heading to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> and trying on the Apple Watch Ultra in person to get to grips with the size and determine if it is too big and bulky for you. <br/>
<br/>
Similarly, the Apple Watch Ultra's look may not appeal to some buyers. If you prefer the stainless steel Apple Watch and are looking for a more fashion-focused smartwatch that pairs well with premium bands, the more aggressive, rugged design of the Apple Watch Ultra may not be for you. <br/>
<br/>
If the Apple Watch Ultra is out of your price range but you still want to use your Apple Watch in challenging environments, it is worth bearing in mind that the Series 9 still offers a durable design with a strong front crystal, water resistance, and many of the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj;'s software features like waypoint marking.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; has a lot to offer, especially for the subset of users who can take advantage of all of its capabilities, so it is certainly worth considering when purchasing a new model, but the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; is still a compelling all-around option that comes in at a lower price point with a subtler design.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-ultra-2/">Apple Watch Series 9 vs. Ultra 2 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 25 Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-vs-ultra-2-buyers-guide-25-differences-compared.2402984/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says 128GB iPhone 15 Pro Limited to 1080p ProRes Video Recording Unless External Storage Connected</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-15-pro-128gb-prores-1080p-only/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-128gb-iphone-15-pro-limited-to-1080p-prores-video-recording-unless-external-storage-connected.2402975/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:54:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-15-pro-128gb-prores-1080p-only/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[ProRes video recording remains limited to 1080p quality at 30 frames per second on the 128GB model of the iPhone 15 Pro, unless the device is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-external-storage-prores/">recording directly to a connected external storage drive</a>, according to Apple. On the 256GB and higher iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max, ProRes video recording is supported in up to 4K quality at 60 frames per second to both internal storage and external storage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
Apple does not mention this information on the iPhone 15 Pro's tech specs page on its website, but the limitation is listed when comparing the iPhone 15 Pro to another iPhone model in the Apple Store app, as seen in the screenshot below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-128GB-ProRes.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912008" /><br/>
The same limitation applied to iPhone 13 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro models with 128GB of storage, but those devices cannot record ProRes video to external storage, so at least iPhone 15 Pro users have that option this time around. The limitation does not apply to the iPhone 15 Pro Max, as that model starts with 256GB of storage.<br/>
<br/>
ProRes video files are very large. Apple says a one-minute 10-bit ProRes video is approximately 1.7GB in 1080p and 6GB in 4K. Apple likely feels that offering 4K ProRes video recording to internal storage on the 128GB model would be a subpar user experience. With recording to an external storage now an option, it is less of an issue.<br/>
<br/>
Introduced on the iPhone 13 Pro models, ProRes refers to a family of codecs from Apple that can compress videos into smaller file sizes with "impressive image quality preservation." Apple says ProRes is designed as a final delivery format for high-quality videos like commercials, feature films, and broadcasts.<br/>
<br/>
ProRes video recording is still not supported at all on the standard iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-15-pro-128gb-prores-1080p-only/">Apple Says 128GB iPhone 15 Pro Limited to 1080p ProRes Video Recording Unless External Storage Connected</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-128gb-iphone-15-pro-limited-to-1080p-prores-video-recording-unless-external-storage-connected.2402975/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 15 Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 35+ Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-15-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-15-pro-buyers-guide-35-differences-compared.2402964/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:41:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-15-pro&#038;post_date=1695048092/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> are among Apple's newest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models and follow last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Pro</a>, but how different are the two latest 6.1-inch &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, and what exactly does a "Pro" device give you?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-vs-15-Pro-Buyers-Guide.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911649" /><br/>
Last year, the biggest new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-14-pro/">differences between the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Pro</a> were always-on functionality, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, three hours of battery life, and rear cameras with different apertures. With &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, both devices share new features like the USB-C port, second-generation Ultra Wideband chip, and next-generation portraits, but Apple's "Pro" and non-Pro &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models are more different than ever.<br/>
<br/>
Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models is best for you, and serves as a way to clearly see what additional features and upgrades the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; brings to the table.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Aluminum and glass design</td><br/>
 <td>Titanium and glass design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Slightly smaller due to slimmer borders around the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 171g or 201g</td><br/>
 <td>Weighs 187g or 221g</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>ProMotion with adaptive refresh rates up to 120Hz</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Always-on display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A16 Bionic chip (5nm)</td><br/>
 <td>A17 Pro chip (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a>)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU (up to 10% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>6-core GPU with with hardware-accelerated ray tracing (up to 20% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine (up to 2x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated AV1 decoder</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Advanced" dual-camera system</td><br/>
 <td>"Pro" triple camera system</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Main camera with ƒ/1.6 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel Main camera with ƒ/1.78 aperture and larger sensor</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera with ƒ/2.4 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel Ultra Wide camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel Telephoto camera with ƒ/2.8 aperture (unit with larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module on Pro Max model only)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, and 2x optical zoom</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, 3x, and 5x optical zoom (5x on Pro Max only)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Sensor-shift optical image stabilization</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation sensor-shift optical image stabilization</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>True Tone flash</td><br/>
 <td>Adaptive True Tone flash</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>LiDAR scanner</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Macro photography</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Apple ProRAW</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Shoot and instantly transfer 48-megapixel ProRAW images to Mac via USB 3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record video directly to an external drive</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 30 fps (60 fps with external recording)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Macro video recording, including slo‑mo and time‑lapse</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Log video recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Academy Color Encoding System</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record spatial video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>USB 2 transfer speeds (up to 480Mb/s)</td><br/>
 <td>USB 3 transfer speeds (up to 10Gb/s, 20x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>DisplayPort support for up to 4K HDR video output</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6E connectivity </td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thread networking technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>20- or 26-hour battery life</td><br/>
 <td>23- or 29-hour battery life</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, and 512GB storage options</td><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB storage options (no 128GB on Pro Max)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Yellow, Blue, Pink, Green, and Black color options</td><br/>
 <td>Natural Titanium, Blue Titanium, White Titanium, and Black Titanium color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;799</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;999</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; offers a large number of upgrades over the standard &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. With just &#36;200 difference to obtain a display with ProMotion and always-on functionality, the Action Button, and longer battery life, many customers will be able to justify getting the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; over the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. Other differences, such as the A17 Pro chip and 2GB additional memory are notable, but most significant are perhaps the devices' fundamentally different rear camera setups. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; unlocks 10 additional camera features and offers four additional or different pieces of camera hardware. Due to the scale and breadth of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s improvements and features, most customers will be happy to choose the high-end model.<br/>
<br/>
The standard &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; still offers many of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s most compelling capabilities, such as USB-C, &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;, and a 48-megapixel main camera, at a lower price point. It will only be worth getting the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; over the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; if you want a lighter device, do not care for the "Pro" rear camera setup or features like ProMotion and the always-on display, or cannot justify the &#36;200 to upgrade to the high-end model. In this instance, you will still benefit from the device's generous roster of advanced features. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; is still a very well designed and balanced device, especially for average customers and those coming from a much older model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 15 Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 35+ Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-15-pro-buyers-guide-35-differences-compared.2402964/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook Watched Entire Third Season of &#039;Ted Lasso&#039; on Apple Vision Pro, Which Remains on Track for Early 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/tim-cook-watched-ted-lasso-apple-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-watched-entire-third-season-of-ted-lasso-on-apple-vision-pro-which-remains-on-track-for-early-2024.2402826/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 03:23:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/tim-cook-watched-ted-lasso-apple-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		<category>CBS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO Tim Cook confirmed in an interview with <em>CBS Sunday Morning</em>'s John Dickerson that the company's Vision Pro headset remains on schedule for release in early 2024, and revealed that he's already using it on a regular basis. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M-FBYmIhRoo?si=Xf7CJ11sifs_ojXP" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
When asked how he uses the upcoming headset, Cook said he watched "the entire third season of 'Ted Lasso' on the Vision Pro," and admitted there are "some things I have access to that other people don't have access to, so I'm doing that, but that I can't talk to you about."<br/>
<br/>
Cook went on to say that the challenges Apple has faced creating the headset are "more complex" than making something like the iPhone, so it requires "more innovation, not only in the development but also in the manufacturing." However, the Apple chief batted away any suggestion that the company was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/03/apple-vision-pro-drastic-production-cuts/">facing production issues</a> with the Vision Pro, saying the device was "on track" for a launch early next year.<br/>
<br/>
In the course of the interview, Cook also touched on other topics including Apple's environmental initiatives (he hopes other companies "rip it off"), whether Apple should be advertising on X, formerly known as Twitter, when its owner Elon Musk has been accused of promoting anti-Semitism on the platform ("It's something we constantly ask ourselves"), and the post-pandemic return to working in the office. <br/>
<br/>
In between a walk-and-talk around Apple's Austin, Texas campus, Cook was also filmed taking a sales call with a surprised customer. "The caller wanted to upgrade their iPhone," Cook later explained to Dickerson. When asked if he told her to hold out for the iPhone 15, Cook laughed. "I didn't exactly say that."   <br/>
<br/>
You can watch the full interview above or view it on YouTube <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M-FBYmIhRoo">here</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cbs/">CBS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/tim-cook-watched-ted-lasso-apple-vision-pro/">Tim Cook Watched Entire Third Season of &#039;Ted Lasso&#039; on Apple Vision Pro, Which Remains on Track for Early 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-watched-entire-third-season-of-ted-lasso-on-apple-vision-pro-which-remains-on-track-for-early-2024.2402826/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Find Your Apple TV Siri Remote Using Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/find-apple-siri-remote-with-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-find-your-apple-tv-siri-remote-using-your-iphone.2402756/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:26:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/find-apple-siri-remote-with-iphone&#038;post_date=1695040015/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 17 and tvOS 17, Apple has added a feature that lets Apple TV users locate a misplaced Siri Remote using their iPhone. Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/find-siri-remote-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911918" /><br/>
Prior to the launch of the latest ‌Apple TV‌ 4K, there were rumors that Apple would build ‌Find My‌ functionality into the ‌Siri‌ Remote. That didn't happen, but in its latest major software updates, Apple has introduced a new iPhone option that does essentially the same thing. <br/>
<br/>
In early September, Apple quietly released new firmware for its second and third-generation Siri Remotes. With the new firmware, tvOS 17, and iOS 17, if a ‌Siri‌ Remote becomes lost, the ‌Apple TV‌ remote control available in the Control Center on an ‌iPhone‌ can be used to locate the missing remote.<br/>
<br/>
When enabled, users will see a Find My-like interface on their iPhone that guides them toward the remote, with an onscreen circle that changes in size to guide movement in the right direction. <br/>
<br/>
Note that Find My for the ‌Siri‌ Remote is available on the second and third-generation ‌Siri‌ Remotes, and the feature is limited to the ‌Apple TV‌ 4K models released in 2021 and 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Also, bear in mind that the updated firmware is necessary, and there is no established method for getting the ‌Siri‌ Remote to update. The ‌Apple TV‌ will need to be up to date, on, and connected to the ‌Siri‌ Remote to initiate, but there is no way to force the new firmware to download.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Find Your Siri Remote With Your iPhone</h2><br/>
<ol><li>Bring up the Control Center from your iPhone by swiping down from the upper right corner of the screen (on an ‌iPhone‌ with a Home button, swipe up from the bottom of the screen).</li><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>Apple TV Remote</strong> button (if it's not there, you can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/customize-control-center-ios-11/#customize">manually add it to Control Center</a>).</li><br/>
<li>Tap the chevron next to the name of the connected Siri Remote.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/find-apple-tv-remote-with-iphone1.jpg" alt="control center" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911920" /><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>Find</strong> button next to the misplaced Siri Remote.</li><br/>
<li>Use the onscreen Find My-like interface to locate the remote. The size of the circle increases to guide movement in the correct direction. When your iPhone is right next to the remote, the screen shows a solid white orb.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>X</strong> button to close the location interface.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/find-apple-tv-remote-with-iphone2.jpg" alt="remote" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911921" /></ol>In our experience, the proximity accuracy of the feature is equivalent to locating an AirTag with Find My, so it's really helpful for locating your Siri Remote even if it's just hidden between the sofa cushions.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/find-apple-siri-remote-with-iphone/">How to Find Your Apple TV Siri Remote Using Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-find-your-apple-tv-siri-remote-using-your-iphone.2402756/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17 Launching Today for iPhones With These 10 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-feature-list/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-launching-today-for-iphones-with-these-10-new-features.2402541/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 12:35:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-feature-list/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In June, Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> with a wide range of new features and changes for the iPhone. Following over three months of beta testing, the free software update will be released this Monday, September 18 for the iPhone XS and newer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-and-iPhones-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1372" height="773" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898529" /><br/>
Below, we have recapped 10 key features coming to the iPhone with iOS 17, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-features-coming-later-this-year/">additional features coming later this year</a>. The update should be released to users around 10 a.m. Pacific Time / 1 p.m. Eastern Time today, and once it is available, it can be installed from the Settings app under General → Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>StandBy</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/StandBy-iOS-17.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898860" /><br/>
StandBy is a new full-screen view that provides glanceable information designed to be viewed from a distance when an iPhone is on its side and charging, according to Apple. The customizable interface can show a clock in various styles, a calendar, favorite photos, the weather forecast, music playback controls, widgets, and more.  <br/>
<br/>
StandBy is designed for an iPhone charging on a nightstand, kitchen counter, or desk, and it supports Live Activities, Siri, incoming calls, and larger notifications. The feature also works with the iPhone 14 Pro's always-on display.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Contact Posters</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Contact-Posters-iOS-17.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1828" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898862" /><br/>
iOS 17 lets users create a personalized Contact Poster that appears during an incoming phone call on another person's iPhone. The poster can include a photo or Memoji, and the font and background color can also be customized. The feature is available in the built-in Phone app and will also be available for third-party calling apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>NameDrop</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/namedrop.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898310" /><br/>
NameDrop allows users to easily share contact information by bringing their iPhones close together. Both individuals can choose the specific phone numbers or email addresses they would like to share, and can also share their Contact Posters.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Live Voicemail</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Live-Voicemail-iOS-17.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="793" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898863" /><br/>
Live Voicemail provides real-time transcription on the screen as someone leaves a voicemail. If the user considers the voicemail to be important, they can pick up the call while the caller is leaving their message. Apple says calls identified as spam by carriers are not transcribed and will instead be instantly declined.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Swipe to Reply in iMessage</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iMessage-Swipe-to-Reply.jpg" alt="" width="1330" height="794" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898868" /><br/>
In the Messages app, users can now swipe to the right on any message to send an inline reply.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Interactive Widgets</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Interactive-Widgets.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898611" /><br/>
Interactive widgets are now available on the iPhone across the Home Screen, Lock Screen, and the new StandBy view. Apple gave some examples of what interactive widgets can be used for, including marking a reminder as completed, playing or pausing a song or podcast, and controlling accessories in the Home app, and there will be many more possibilities as third-party apps are updated with support in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
Home Screen widgets offered limited functionality until now, as Apple did not allow developers to include scrolling, buttons, or animations.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Improved Autocorrect</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Autocorrect-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="638" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898562" /><br/>
Apple says iOS 17 includes a state-of-the-art language model for word prediction that will greatly improve autocorrection on the iPhone. When typing, on-device machine learning will intelligently correct mistakes with greater accuracy than ever before. In addition, users will now receive predictive text recommendations inline as they type, allowing for words or complete sentences to be added by tapping the space bar.<br/>
<br/>
Autocorrection has an updated design on iOS 17 that briefly underlines an autocorrected word. Tapping on an underlined word reveals the original word typed, making it easy to quickly revert the change. The system will also learn the user's typing habits over time and avoid some corrections, which Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi said is designed for "those moments where you just want to type a ducking word."<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple Maps Offline</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Maps-Offline.jpg" alt="" width="1324" height="956" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898866" /><br/>
Apple Maps is catching up on a key Google Maps feature on iOS 17 with the ability to download maps for offline use. Apple says users can download a specific map area and access turn-by-turn navigation, view their estimated time of arrival, find places, and more when an iPhone is not connected to a cellular or Wi-Fi network.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Stickers Drawer</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Sticker-Drawer.jpg" alt="" width="2770" height="1628" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898869" /><br/>
A new stickers drawer on iOS 17 provides access to all stickers, including Live Stickers, emoji, Memoji, and iMessage sticker packs in one place. Live Stickers can be created by touching and holding an object in a photo, such as a cat or a dog.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>"Hey Siri" Shortened to Siri</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Hey-Siri-vs-Siri.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898361" /><br/>
Apple has simplified the voice command to invoke Siri on the iPhone and other Apple devices, including the iPad, Mac, HomePod, and newest AirPods Pro. Instead of "Hey Siri," users are now simply able to say "Siri" to activate the voice assistant, and can issue multiple commands in succession without having to say "Siri" again.<br/>
<br/>
For more features, read our in-depth <strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17 roundup</a></strong>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-feature-list/">iOS 17 Launching Today for iPhones With These 10 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-launching-today-for-iphones-with-these-10-new-features.2402541/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Significantly Lowers Repair Fees for iPhone 15 Pro Models With Cracked Back Glass</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-significantly-lowers-repair-fees-for-iphone-15-pro-models-with-cracked-back-glass.2402536/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 11:51:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we reported last week, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-models-more-repairable/">more repairable internal design</a>, with a redesigned frame that allows for the back glass panel to be easily removed from the devices. This change was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/19/ifixit-iphone-14-teardown/">first made to the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus</a> last year, and now it extends to the Pro models this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature-White.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911430" /><br/>
At the time, we said that the removable back glass would likely result in significantly lower repair fees for iPhone 15 Pro models with cracked back glass for customers without AppleCare+ coverage, and this is now confirmed. As noted <a href="https://twitter.com/ianzelbo/status/1703439723400667246">by Ian Zelbo</a>, Apple has <a href="https://support.apple.com/iphone/repair">updated its U.S. website</a> with iPhone 15 repair fees, revealing that it will charge &#36;169 or &#36;199 to repair the iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max with back glass damage. By comparison, these fees are set at &#36;499 or &#36;549 for the iPhone 14 Pro or iPhone 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
The lower fees were also reported <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/09/17/replacing-back-glass-iphone-15-pro/">by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>. For customers with AppleCare+ coverage for their iPhone, back glass damage can be repaired for &#36;29.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple's battery replacement fee is set at &#36;99 for all four iPhone 15 models, which is unchanged from the iPhone 14 series. For additional iPhone 15 repair fees, such as for the rear camera or other damage, visit <a href="https://support.apple.com/iphone/repair">Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/">Apple Significantly Lowers Repair Fees for iPhone 15 Pro Models With Cracked Back Glass</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-significantly-lowers-repair-fees-for-iphone-15-pro-models-with-cracked-back-glass.2402536/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Models Reportedly Max Out at 27W Charging Speeds Despite 35W Rumor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-27w-max-charging-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-models-reportedly-max-out-at-27w-charging-speeds-despite-35w-rumor.2402528/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:57:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-27w-max-charging-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Mac Otakara</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models are capable of up to 27W peak charging speeds with an appropriate USB-C power adapter, according to <a href="https://www.macotakara.jp/iphone/entry-45309.html">Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em></a>. It is unclear where the website sourced this information from, but it seems to confirm that the iPhone 15 Pro models have the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/18/iphone-14-and-14-pro-charging-speeds/">same maximum charging speeds as the iPhone 14 Pro models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
In August, <em>9to5Mac</em> reported that at least some iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/17/iphone-15-faster-charging-speeds/">could support up to 35W charging speeds</a>, but this rumor appears to be incorrect.<br/>
<br/>
Just like the iPhone 14 models, Apple says all four iPhone 15 models can charge up to 50% in around 30 minutes with a 20W or higher power adapter.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, the website ChargerLAB determined that Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MY1W2AM/A/30w-usb-c-power-adapter">30W USB-C power adapter</a> was the company's lowest-priced charger that could charge the iPhone 14 Pro models at their maximum charging speeds of up to 27W, and this will likely remain the case for the iPhone 15 Pro models. In the U.S., the adapter is priced at &#36;39 on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
Real-world tests still need to be completed, but for now it appears the 35W rumor was wrong.<br/>
<br/>
All of the new iPhone 15 models launch on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-27w-max-charging-report/">iPhone 15 Pro Models Reportedly Max Out at 27W Charging Speeds Despite 35W Rumor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-models-reportedly-max-out-at-27w-charging-speeds-despite-35w-rumor.2402528/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max Seeing &#039;Robust&#039; Demand, Shipping Estimates Extending Into November</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-seeing-robust-demand-shipping-estimates-extending-into-november.2402511/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:12:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There has been "robust" demand for the iPhone 15 Pro Max since the device became <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/">available to pre-order</a> on Friday, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/iphone-15%E9%A6%96%E9%80%B1%E6%9C%AB%E9%A0%90%E8%B3%BC%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F-thoughts-on-the-iphone-15-first-weekend-pre-order-436f33668ad6">post on Medium</a> today, Kuo said iPhone 15 Pro Max demand has outpaced iPhone 14 Pro Max demand during the equivalent period last year. However, he said demand for the iPhone 15 Pro is weaker than it was for the iPhone 14 Pro so far, which he believes could be the result of more customers choosing to buy the Pro Max model this year.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro Max exclusively features an upgraded Telephoto lens with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/">up to 5x optical zoom</a>, compared to up to 3x on the iPhone 15 Pro. In the U.S., pricing for the iPhone 15 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-pricing/">starts at &#36;1,199 for 256GB of storage</a>, with Apple no longer offering the Pro Max with 128GB of storage for &#36;1,099 like it did in years past.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo reiterated that the iPhone 15 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/30/kuo-iphone-15-colors-and-more/">entered mass production later</a> than the other devices in the iPhone 15 series, which has contributed to the device's lengthy shipping delays. In the U.S., some configurations of the iPhone 15 Pro Max are currently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/">estimated for delivery in November</a> on Apple's online store. He said the Pro Max continues to face production challenges that are "more pronounced" than they are for the other models.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes that demand for the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus has been "roughly on par" with the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus after the same amount of time.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models will launch on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/">Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max Seeing &#039;Robust&#039; Demand, Shipping Estimates Extending Into November</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-seeing-robust-demand-shipping-estimates-extending-into-november.2402511/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: When to Expect USB-C AirPods Max, Magic Mouse, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-magic-mouse-and-more.2402498/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 06:58:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While all four iPhone 15 models are equipped with a USB-C port, Apple continues to sell a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/remaining-apple-products-with-lightning/">handful of products with Lightning</a>. In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-09-17/apple-s-watch-series-9-iphone-15-will-hold-it-over-until-vision-pro-ai-in-2024-lmngtodu">"Power On" newsletter today</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman outlined when some of these products will move to USB-C.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Dark-Red-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877636" /><br/>
First, Gurman said he expects USB-C versions of the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard to be released alongside the next iMac.<br/>
<br/>
Second, he said the standard AirPods should be updated with a USB-C charging case <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/usb-c-airpods-and-airpods-max-2024/">in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Third, he said the next AirPods Max will be equipped with a USB-C port, but he did not provide a release timeframe for the over-ear headphones. He previously reported that the AirPods Max could be updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/usb-c-airpods-and-airpods-max-2024/">as early as next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Last, he said that he expects the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger accessories to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/">return with USB-C ports eventually</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more/">Gurman: When to Expect USB-C AirPods Max, Magic Mouse, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-magic-mouse-and-more.2402498/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger Ever Return With USB-C Ports?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-magsafe-battery-pack-and-magsafe-duo-charger-ever-return-with-usb-c-ports.2402494/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 06:28:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>MagSafe Battery Pack</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple quietly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo/">discontinued the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger</a> immediately after unveiling four new iPhone 15 models with a USB-C port last week. Both accessories were equipped with a Lightning connector.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/magsafe-battery-pack-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2820" height="1587" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-807695" /><br/>
Apple has not commented on why the MagSafe accessories were removed from sale, but the move was not surprising given the company is transitioning away from Lightning. The big question is, will they ever return with USB-C ports?<br/>
<br/>
As noted <a href="https://daringfireball.net/linked/2023/09/16/magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo-charger">by <em>Daring Fireball</em>'s John Gruber</a>, Apple has often released battery packs months after new iPhones. Apple released Smart Battery Cases for the iPhone 6s, iPhone XR, and iPhone 11 between two and four months after each of those devices launched, while the MagSafe Battery Pack launched nine months after the iPhone 12.<br/>
<br/>
"So, maybe Apple is simply done selling the MagSafe Battery Pack," said Gruber. "But, even if they have a new USB-C version in the works, I'm not at all surprised that it wasn't released last week. Let's wait for November."<br/>
<br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-09-17/apple-s-watch-series-9-iphone-15-will-hold-it-over-until-vision-pro-ai-in-2024-lmngtodu">"Power On" newsletter today</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said he still expects USB-C versions of the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger to return "eventually." However, he said "don't hold your breath."<br/>
<br/>
In May 2022, prior to the MagSafe Battery Pack being discontinued, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said a USB-C version of the accessory would be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/15/kuo-usb-c-apple-accessories/">in the "foreseeable future,"</a> but it's unclear if he still expects this to happen.<br/>
<br/>
Released in July 2021, the ‌MagSafe Battery Pack‌ was priced at &#36;99 and attaches magnetically to the back of the iPhone 12 and newer, providing hours of additional battery life. The battery pack can be recharged with a Lightning cable.<br/>
<br/>
Released in December 2020, the MagSafe Duo was a &#36;129 foldable charging mat with a MagSafe charger for iPhones and an Apple Watch charging puck.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/">Will the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger Ever Return With USB-C Ports?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-magsafe-battery-pack-and-magsafe-duo-charger-ever-return-with-usb-c-ports.2402494/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Likely Feels Even Lighter Than It Really Is Due to Inertia Change</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-lighter-than-it-really/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-even-lighter-than-it-really-is-due-to-inertia-change.2402485/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 05:19:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-lighter-than-it-really/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> likely feels considerably lighter than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a>, not just due to the switch from stainless steel to titanium, but also a change to the device's moment of inertia, according to calculations by Dr. Drang's <a href="https://leancrew.com/all-this/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-facts-and-estimates/"><em>LeanCrew</em> blog</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Internal-Chassis.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910920" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; weighs 187g, a 9% reduction of the &zwnj;iPhone 14 Pro&zwnj;'s 206g weight. During its announcement, Apple highlighted that the new lightweight feel is facilitated by switching from a stainless steel frame to titanium. Those who have already spent some time with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, including <em>MacRumors</em>' Dan Barbera, have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">noted</a> just how much lighter the device feels in the hand. Yet new analysis suggests that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; likely feels even lighter than its actual weight reduction due to a change of its moment of inertia. <br/>
<br/>
The moment of inertia, a fundamental concept in physics, measures an object's resistance to rotational motion. Its value is determined by both the amount of mass an object has and how that mass is distributed. Crucially, the further away mass is positioned from an object's axis of rotation, the greater the moment of inertia. Thus, for commonly handled objects like smartphones, this resistance to rotation plays a significant role in how weighty or light they feel during daily use.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's shift from stainless steel to titanium for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s outer band is pivotal in this change since a substantial portion of the phone's weight reduction is localized at its outer edges. Dr. Drang's analysis suggests that by minimizing mass predominantly at the perimeter, Apple achieved a reduction in the phone's moment of inertia that is more significant than would be expected from the sheer weight decrease alone.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>This reduction, which is more than the mass reduction, would make the iPhone 15 Pro easier to turn, and that may add to the impression that it's significantly lighter than the 14 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
Reducing the mass at the perimeter, which the change from stainless steel to titanium has done, has definitely reduced the moment of inertia more than a uniform reduction in mass would have. And that will make the 15 Pro easier to manipulate and will contribute—at least somewhat—to the impression of lightness.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Based on an analysis of the new phones' dimensions and assuming the mass reduction is mostly around the phone's perimeter, the moment of inertia for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is estimated to be reduced by 14–15%. Overall this means that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; doesn't just weigh less; its design ensures that its mass is distributed in a manner that makes it resist rotational motion less strongly. This results in a device that feels more agile and nimble, giving an amplified impression of lightness.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-lighter-than-it-really/">iPhone 15 Pro Likely Feels Even Lighter Than It Really Is Due to Inertia Change</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-even-lighter-than-it-really-is-due-to-inertia-change.2402485/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Unlike Apple Watch, Google Will Not Repair Broken Pixel Watches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/google-will-not-repair-pixel-watches/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unlike-apple-watch-google-will-not-repair-broken-pixel-watches.2402480/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 04:03:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/google-will-not-repair-pixel-watches/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Google Pixel</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google currently offers no official repair procedure for the Pixel Watch, meaning that broken devices simply become e-waste (via <a href="https://www.theverge.com/23874281/google-pixel-watch-cracks-no-repairs-warranty"><em>The Verge</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/pixel-watch-vs-apple-watch-4.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-868839" /><br/>
This information was recently confirmed by Google spokesperson Bridget Starkey to <em>The Verge</em>. Starkey stated, "At this moment, we don't have any repair option for the Google Pixel Watch. If your watch is damaged, you can contact the Google Pixel Watch Customer Support Team to check your replacement options." Google Support chats add that the company "doesn't have any repair centers or service centers" for the Pixel Watch.<br/>
<br/>
The device's lack of repair options stands in contrast to Google's approach with its Pixel phones, where it partners with iFixit to ensure that spare parts and repair guides are accessible for consumers looking to mend their handsets. An independent <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/Guide/Google+Pixel+Watch+Screen+Replacement/160350">iFixit guide</a> details how to replace the Pixel Watch screen, proving that it is possible to do so. Yet users who wish to undertake such a repair are faced with the challenge of finding a replacement part. Given the Pixel Watch's limited sales compared to mainstream rivals like the Apple Watch, obtaining damaged "donor hardware" with the required intact part remains a difficult proposition.<br/>
<br/>
By comparison, Apple offers repair solutions for the Apple Watch, albeit at different costs depending on the availability of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+. For Apple Watch owners without &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+, the company cites a flat &#36;299 estimate for an Apple Watch Series 8 and &#36;499 for an Apple Watch Ultra. With &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+, this drops to &#36;69 for the Apple Watch Series 8 and &#36;79 for the Apple Watch Ultra, not including the cost of &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj; itself.<br/>
<br/>
The Pixel Watch's screen is particularly vulnerable due to its design, featuring a large glass hemisphere that can easily crack upon impact. Google's hardware warranty does not cover damage resulting from accidents, such as drops or impacts, leaving users without many options other than to simply replace the entire device with a new one. The Pixel Watch 2 is rumored to feature almost exactly the same design.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-pixel/">Google Pixel</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/google-will-not-repair-pixel-watches/">Unlike Apple Watch, Google Will Not Repair Broken Pixel Watches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unlike-apple-watch-google-will-not-repair-broken-pixel-watches.2402480/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15&#039;s USB-C Port: 4.5W Charging for Accessories, USB 3.2 Gen 2 for Pro Models, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15s-usb-c-port-4-5w-charging-for-accessories-usb-3-2-gen-2-for-pro-models-and-more.2402440/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 20:17:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213839">support document</a> published on Friday, Apple provided some additional details about the USB-C port found on all iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
First, Apple said all iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-usb-c-port-apple-watch-airpods-charging/">can charge an Apple Watch, AirPods case</a>, or other small accessories connected to the USB-C port at up to 4.5W. Apple already announced this capability, but it had not provided the wattage information.<br/>
<br/>
Second, the document reveals that the iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max support USB 3.2 Gen 2 for data transfer speeds up to 10 Gbps. Apple had already revealed that the devices support USB 3, but the exact specification is now confirmed. The USB-C cable included with iPhone 15 Pro models supports USB 2 speeds, so a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MU883AM/A/thunderbolt-4-usb%E2%80%91c-pro-cable-1-m">higher-spec cable</a> is needed for faster speeds. <br/>
<br/>
As we previously reported, the document indicates that all iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/">support DisplayPort</a> for up to 4K HDR video mirroring to an external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable, or an adapter. However, unlike select iPad models with Stage Manager, the iPhone lacks an extended display mode.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro models also support recording ProRes video <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-external-storage-prores/">directly to an external storage device</a>, at up to 4K and 60 frames per second.<br/>
<br/>
To connect an iPhone 15 to a vehicle with a USB-A port for wired CarPlay usage, Apple says customers can use a USB-C to USB-A cable.<br/>
<br/>
Additional information is outlined in the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213839">support document</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/">iPhone 15&#039;s USB-C Port: 4.5W Charging for Accessories, USB 3.2 Gen 2 for Pro Models, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15s-usb-c-port-4-5w-charging-for-accessories-usb-3-2-gen-2-for-pro-models-and-more.2402440/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Event Recap With iPhone 15, New Apple Watches, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/top-stories-iphone-15-event-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-recap-with-iphone-15-new-apple-watches-and-more.2402352/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/top-stories-iphone-15-event-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[What a week! Things are finally beginning to settle down after a flurry of announcements at Tuesday's event involving the usual suspects of iPhone and Apple Watch. All of the new hardware is now available to order, with launches happening next Friday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/top-stories-16sep2023-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911682" /><br/>
Don't forget about Apple's software updates, with iOS 17, watchOS 10, and tvOS 17 all coming on Monday and macOS Sonoma debuting on September 26. Read on below for all the details on the biggest announcements from this week's event!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything Announced at Apple's Event in Six Minutes</h2><br/>
Apple hosted its annual iPhone event this week, and it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">packed with announcements as usual</a>. New products unveiled include the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, Apple Watch Series 9, Apple Watch Ultra 2, and USB-C AirPods Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Everything-Announced-at-Apples-Wonderlust-Event-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910543" /><br/>
There are also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/every-iphone-15-case/">new iPhone cases</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/every-apple-watch-band-2023/">Apple Watch bands</a> with a "FineWoven" material instead of leather, wired EarPods with a USB-C connector, and several other new accessories, so be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">check out our recap of everything announced at Apple's event</a> to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces iPhone 15 Pro With Titanium Design, Action Button, A17 Pro Chip, and More</h2><br/>
As widely expected, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro models</a> are equipped with a USB-C port instead of Lightning, providing users with a more universal charging standard and faster data transfer speeds up to 10 Gbps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
Other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">new features for the Pro models</a> include a lightweight titanium frame, the A17 Pro chip, a customizable Action button, slimmer bezels around the screen, Wi-Fi 6E support, increased RAM, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus With USB-C Port, Dynamic Island, and More</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">lower-end iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a> models also feature a USB-C port, and the Dynamic Island first added to iPhone 14 Pro models last year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Colors-pink.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911680" /><br/>
Other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">new features for the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a> include an upgraded 48-megapixel main camera lens with a new 2x Telephoto zoom option, the A16 Bionic chip, a frosted glass back, brighter displays, a second-generation Ultra Wideband chip, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9 Unveiled With S9 Chip, 'Double Tap' Gesture, and More</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-unveiled/">next-generation Apple Watch Series 9 is official</a>, with new features including a faster S9 chip, a "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watch without touching the screen, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-64gb-storage/">increased 64GB of storage</a>, a pink color option for the aluminum case, a brighter display, faster on-device Siri, Precision Finding for iPhone, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
For the first time, Apple said customers can choose a carbon-neutral variant of any Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Features Faster S9 Chip, Brighter Display, and More</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-apple-watch-ultra-2/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 is here</a>, with a handful of new features added, including the same S9 chip and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-double-tap/">Double Tap gesture</a> from the Series 9, a brighter display with peak brightness of 3,000 nits, expanded altitude range, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
Unfortunately, the rumor that the Apple Watch Ultra 2 would be available in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/01/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-titanium-rumor/">new Black Titanium finish</a> was incorrect, with only Natural Titanium offered.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Introduces Updated AirPods Pro and EarPods With USB-C and More</h2><br/>
In addition to the iPhone 15 models getting a USB-C port, Apple announced that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">second-generation AirPods Pro are now available to order with a USB-C charging case</a> for &#36;249, and the wired EarPods headphones now come in a USB-C version as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-USB-C-Port-Purple-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911676" /><br/>
On an accessory-related note, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo/">Apple discontinued the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger</a>, both of which used Lightning, following the iPhone 15 event.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/sep-14-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/top-stories-iphone-15-event-recap/">Top Stories: Apple Event Recap With iPhone 15, New Apple Watches, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-recap-with-iphone-15-new-apple-watches-and-more.2402352/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
