<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:03:18 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro: All the Rumors and Known Features So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/iphone-16-pro-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-all-the-rumors-and-known-features-so-far.2412568/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:53:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/iphone-16-pro-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</a> are still around 10 months away from launching, there are already several rumors about the devices. Below, we have recapped new features and changes expected for the devices so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
These are some of the key changes rumored for the iPhone 16 Pro models as of December 2023:<ul><li><strong>Larger displays:</strong> The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be equipped with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>, respectively, according to Ross Young, CEO of Display Supply Chain Consultants. The devices are expected to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/iphone-16-pro-to-feature-taller-aspect-ratio/">taller aspect ratios</a> as part of this change. By comparison, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max have 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch displays, respectively.</li><br/>
<li><strong>More power-efficient displays:</strong> iPhone 16 Pro models could have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/iphone-16-more-efficient-oled-display/">more power-efficient OLED displays supplied by Samsung</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>"Capture" button:</strong> Apple is rumored to be planning a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">new "Capture button"</a> for all iPhone 16 models. The button would be located below the power button, which would require the mmWave 5G antenna window to be relocated on U.S. models. The button's purpose is unknown, but it has been speculated that it could be a dedicated shutter or spatial video recording button for the camera. The button might have a solid-state design, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/03/will-iphone-16-feature-taptic-buttons/">rumors are conflicting</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens:</strong> The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">upgraded 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera lens</a> for higher-resolution photos with more detail when shooting in 0.5× mode, according to Jeff Pu, a tech analyst at Hong Kong investment firm Haitong International Securities.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Wi-Fi 7 support:</strong> The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">support Wi-Fi 7</a>, according to Pu. This would enable the devices to send and receive data over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously, resulting in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. Wi-Fi 7 is expected to offer peak data transfer speeds of over 40 Gbps, a 4× increase over Wi-Fi 6E.</li><br/>
<li><strong>A18 Pro chip:</strong> Apple's next-generation A18 Pro chip is expected to be manufactured with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, known as N3E</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Improved thermal design:</strong> iPhone 16 Pro models are rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/">new thermal design</a> for improved heat dissipation. Similar to recent Apple Watch models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">battery might have a metal casing</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>5G Advanced:</strong> iPhone 16 Pro models will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">equipped with Qualcomm's Snapdragon X75 modem</a> for faster and more power efficient 5G connectivity, according to Pu. The modem supports the "5G Advanced" standard, which has been described as "the next phase of 5G" and an "evolution towards 6G."</li><br/>
<li><strong>5× optical zoom for iPhone 16 Pro:</strong> The iPhone 15 Pro Max's tetraprism Telephoto lens system with 5× optical zoom will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">expand to the regular iPhone 16 Pro</a>, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.</li><br/>
<li><strong>More than 5× optical zoom for iPhone 16 Pro Max:</strong> It has been rumored that the iPhone 16 Pro Max will feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/18/iphone-16-pro-max-super-telephoto-camera/">additional upgrades to the Telephoto lens</a> that might allow for more than 5× optical zoom.</li></ul>Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 Pro models in September 2024. Additional details about the devices should surface over the coming months, so be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/"><strong>keep tabs on our iPhone 16 Pro roundup</strong></a> for the latest information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/iphone-16-pro-rumors/">iPhone 16 Pro: All the Rumors and Known Features So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-all-the-rumors-and-known-features-so-far.2412568/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air and M3 MacBook Pro for Record Low Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/deals-m2-macbook-air-m3-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-apples-m2-macbook-air-and-m3-macbook-pro-for-record-low-prices.2412564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 06:59:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/deals-m2-macbook-air-m3-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is discounting a collection of MacBook Air and MacBook Pro models to all-time low prices today. We're tracking these deals below in addition to great discounts on the Apple Pencil 2 and Apple Watch Ultra 1.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/m2-macbook-air-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923162" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, Best Buy has the 256GB model for <a href="https://howl.me/ck7p7awq1GP"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> in Starlight, down from &#36;1,099.00. This is a match of the best price we've ever seen on this model, and right now it's only available in one color.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck7p7awq1GP"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For more storage, you can get the 512GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/ck7qae2R7IE"><strong>&#36;1,179.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,399.00. This is just about &#36;30 away from the all-time low price, and it's available in all four colors on Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qae2R7IE"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;220 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,179.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the 15-inch models, Best Buy has the 256GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/ck7qeeWg6LN"><strong>&#36;1,099.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. All four colors are available at this price, which is a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qeeWg6LN"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally for MacBook Airs, the 512GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air is down to <a href="https://howl.me/ck7qgg7UzpG"><strong>&#36;1,299.00</strong></a>, from &#36;1,499.00. Both this model and the 256GB MacBook Air are just about &#36;50 off from their all-time low prices and still solid second-best options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qgg7UzpG"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,299.00</div></a></div><h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/14in-macbook-pro-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923159" /><br/>
<br/>
There's only one MacBook Pro model on sale right now at an all-time low price: the 1TB 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro. This model is on sale for &#36;1,599.00 on <a href="https://howl.me/ck7qihHFl41">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LZWJ1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a>, down from &#36;1,799.00. If you have My Best Buy Plus/Total, you can get an additional &#36;50 off and knock the notebook down to &#36;1,549.00, a new record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qihHFl41"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch M3 MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;1,599.00</div></a></div><h2>Apple Watch Ultra 1</h2><br/>
In another sale, Best Buy is discounting nearly every model of the first generation Apple Watch Ultra. You can get many of these wearables for <a href="https://howl.me/ck7qldLGUDG"><strong>&#36;639.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00, while a few other models are on sale for a slightly higher price of &#36;659.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qldLGUDG"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;160 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 1 for &#36;639.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This beats the best sale seen on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 by about &#36;100, so if you're willing to adopt a previous generation model it's the best way to save the most amount of money. You'll find Trail Loop, Alpine Loop, and Ocean Band models all on sale right now.<br/>
<h2>Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qqeErcVP">Apple Pencil 1 with USB-C</a> - &#36;79.00, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qopd4J5g">Apple Pencil 2</a> - &#36;79.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qoXKtwfc">AirTag 1 Pack</a> - &#36;23.00, down from &#36;29.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck7qpoNZ3CD">AirTag 4 Pack</a> - &#36;80.00, down from &#36;99.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">also at Amazon</a>]</li></ul> Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/deals-m2-macbook-air-m3-macbook-pro/">Get Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air and M3 MacBook Pro for Record Low Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-apples-m2-macbook-air-and-m3-macbook-pro-for-record-low-prices.2412564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Steam to End Support for macOS Mojave and 32-Bit Games</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/steam-drops-macos-support-for-32-bit-games/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steam-to-end-support-for-macos-mojave-and-32-bit-games.2412556/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 05:21:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/steam-drops-macos-support-for-32-bit-games/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Valve</category>
		<category>Steam</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Valve's Steam gaming store will drop support for macOS High Sierra and macOS Mojave early next year, effectively ending support for the last versions of macOS that could run 32-bit games.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/steam-apple-logo.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-784620" /><br/>
After the change comes into effect on February 15, 2024, Valve said existing Steam Client installations on these operating systems will no longer receive updates of any kind from Steam, including security updates, and technical support for issues related to macOS 10.13 (High Sierra) and 10.14 (Mojave) will not be offered. <br/>
<br/>
Valve announced the change in a <a href="https://help.steampowered.com/en/faqs/view/743F-2E0E-C9A5-C375">Steam support post</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>Unfortunately, macOS 10.14 was the last version to support running 32-bit games on macOS. Apple chose to drop support for 32-bit applications in macOS 10.15 (released 2019), and since many developers have not updated their games to support 64-bit executables, some games will effectively stop functioning on macOS.</blockquote>As a result, Valve said the Steam store will stop considering games that offer only 32-bit macOS binaries to be Mac compatible at the end of 2023. <br/>
<br/>
On the plus side, the change won't affect the majority of Mac users, since 98%+ of Steam customers on Mac are already running macOS 10.15 or newer. As Valve points out, "this means 32-bit only games and applications no longer run on your current operating system." <br/>
<br/>
Valve's decision to end support was not independent. As <em><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/11/steam-drops-macos-mojave-support-effectively-ending-life-for-many-32-bit-games/">ArsTechnica</a></em> notes, it is in fact related to Google's ending of macOS 10.13 and 10.14 support in Chrome, several parts of which the Steam UI relies on. <br/>
<br/>
Apple ended security updates and technical support for macOS 10.13 in December 2020 and for macOS 10.14 in October 2021. Future versions of Steam will require macOS features and security updates only present in macOS 10.15 and above. Despite this, however, Valve says it says it still expects "the Steam client and games on these older operating systems to continue running for some time."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/valve/">Valve</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/steam/">Steam</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/steam-drops-macos-support-for-32-bit-games/">Steam to End Support for macOS Mojave and 32-Bit Games</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steam-to-end-support-for-macos-mojave-and-32-bit-games.2412556/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights Partnership With (RED) For World AIDS Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/apple-partnership-red-world-aids-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-partnership-with-red-for-world-aids-day.2412554/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 04:52:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/apple-partnership-red-world-aids-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>World AIDS Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For World AIDS Day today, Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/12/apple-marks-world-aids-day-with-red/">highlighted</a> its long-standing partnership with (RED), which has raised more than a quarter of a billion dollars since 2006, and is promoting  (PRODUCT)RED versions of a range of products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-RED-World-AIDS-Day-family.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1120" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924838" /><br/>
PRODUCT(RED) products include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, and accessories, including the Silicone Case with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> for the entire &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; lineups. A portion of the proceeds from every (PRODUCT)RED purchase goes to the Global Fund to combat AIDS and COVID-19. <br/>
<br/>
This year, Apple is also donating all proceeds from in-app purchases for three games — MONOPOLY GO!, Gardenscapes, and EA Sports FC Mobile — to the Global Fund, including playful avatars, cool shields, and star soccer players. From the press release:<br/>
<blockquote>Today through December 4, all proceeds from exclusive in‑app purchases in three popular games on the App Store will be donated to the Global Fund. Order Apple Watch Series 9 (PRODUCT)RED by December 21 to gift in time for the holidays.</blockquote>Additionally, now through December 8, Apple says it will donate &#36;1 for every purchase made using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> on apple.com, through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> app, or at an &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; location. <br/>
<br/>
To raise visibility for World AIDS Day and the ongoing effort to eradicate HIV and AIDS, hundreds of ‌&zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj;‌ retail locations are marking the day with new window and product displays. The company is also spotlighting ways for customers to learn about AIDS in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, Apple Books, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/world-aids-day/">World AIDS Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/apple-partnership-red-world-aids-day/">Apple Highlights Partnership With (RED) For World AIDS Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-partnership-with-red-for-world-aids-day.2412554/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple and Paramount Considering Discounted TV+ Streaming Bundle</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/apple-paramount-bundled-tv-services/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-and-paramount-considering-discounted-tv-streaming-bundle.2412552/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 04:40:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/apple-paramount-bundled-tv-services/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Paramount have discussed bundling their TV streaming services at a discount, according to a new report by <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/business/media/apple-and-paramount-discuss-bundling-their-streaming-services-226972d1">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/paramount-plus-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850456" /><br/>
The companies have talked about offering a combination of Paramount+ and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> that would cost less than subscribing to both services separately, according to people familiar with the discussions. The discussions are in their early stages, and it is unclear what shape a bundle could take, they said.<br/>
<br/>
The report notes that the discussions between Apple and Paramount come at a time when competitive pressures have seen services increase their prices to bring them to profitability, while also having to deal with customers increasingly canceling subscriptions or switching services.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in October <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">announced</a> that it was increasing the prices of some of its subscription-based services, including &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, which went from &#36;6.99 per month to &#36;9.99 per month, a &#36;3 rise. For those who subscribe to &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; on an annual basis, the price has increased from &#36;69 per year to &#36;99 per year accordingly.<br/>
<br/>
The rationale behind offering multiple services as part of one package is that it is thought to reduce the likelihood that subscribers will cancel on any given month. The strategy has already been put in place by Netflix and Max, which are being bundled together as part of a deal with Verizon.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/apple-paramount-bundled-tv-services/">Apple and Paramount Considering Discounted TV+ Streaming Bundle</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-and-paramount-considering-discounted-tv-streaming-bundle.2412552/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Both iPhone 16 Pro Models to Feature Tetraprism Zoom Lens</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/both-iphone-16-pro-models-tetraprism-zoom-lens/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/both-iphone-16-pro-models-to-feature-tetraprism-zoom-lens.2412551/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 04:26:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/both-iphone-16-pro-models-tetraprism-zoom-lens/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to bring tetraprism camera technology to both iPhone 16 Pro models next year, enabling at least <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/">5x optical zoom and 25x digital zoom</a> on the Telephoto lens. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Pro-Mock-Header-Updated.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924442" /><br/>
According to a new report by <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=24491">The Elec</a></em>, Apple will add LG Innotek as another supplier of the folded zoom module used in the technology, in an attempt to secure production yields for the increased number of units required.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro has a 12-megapixel Telephoto camera that offers 3x zoom, but the iPhone 15 Pro Max is using an upgraded Telephoto system that allows for 5x zoom. The iPhone 15 Pro Max has a folded glass structure below the lens, which Apple refers to as tetraprism technology. It reflects light four times over, allowing for a longer focal length of 120mm.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> has repeatedly said he expects the tetraprism lens with up to 5x optical zoom to expand to both the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max next year. It has been rumored that the iPhone 16 Pro will feature a larger 6.3-inch display, compared to the 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro. This change would increase the overall size of the device, which would provide additional internal space for a tetraprism lens.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/01/both-iphone-16-pro-models-tetraprism-zoom-lens/">Both iPhone 16 Pro Models to Feature Tetraprism Zoom Lens</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/both-iphone-16-pro-models-to-feature-tetraprism-zoom-lens.2412551/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 to Include Action Button Across Entire Lineup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-include-action-button-across-entire-lineup.2412512/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:08:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Action Button</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and Pro Max saw the introduction of an entirely new user-configurable button known as the Action button, and now, <em>MacRumors</em> has seen extensive evidence confirming Apple is planning to include the Action button on the entire <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> range.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-Updated-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922680" /><br/>
Designs and plans for the Action button date back to at least 2021, as the button was intended for release alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/">haptic volume and power buttons on the iPhone 15 Pro</a>. While the haptic volume and power buttons were abruptly canceled due to unresolved technical issues, the Action button remained, eventually making its way onto final mass production units of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
On the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max, the Action button replaces the mute switch previously found on all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. Unlike the mute switch, which only served a singular purpose, the Action button provides &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users with a variety of uses. It can be configured to perform a range of functions, such as:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Silent Mode</strong>: Toggle silent mode, which mutes/unmutes the ringer and alerts much like the Ringer switch on older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Flashlight</strong>: Turn the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s flashlight function on or off.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Camera</strong>: Launch the Camera app to your choice of photo, selfie, video, portrait, or portrait selfie mode.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Shortcuts</strong>: Open a shortcut from the Shortcuts app, allowing for a range of powerful functions.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Voice Memo</strong>: Start or stop recording a voice memo.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Focus</strong>: Enable or disable a specific Focus mode.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Accessibility features</strong>: Enable or disable any of a variety of accessibility features and settings for users with impaired vision or hearing.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Magnifier</strong>: Use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s camera as a magnifying glass through the Magnfier app.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Translate</strong> (coming in iOS 17.2): Quickly translate speech between two languages.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, Apple plans to add even more functionality to the Action button by changing the button from mechanical to a capacitive-type button. The revamped Action button, developed under the codename Atlas, is expected to function similarly to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> Home button on older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, or the Force Touch trackpad on found on more recent MacBooks.<br/>
<br/>
According to internal documentation, the updated Action button will feature a force sensor, which detects changes in pressure, as well as "tact-switching functionality," although exactly what the latter entails is currently unclear. The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">"Capture" button</a> planned for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is also set to include the same functionality as the improved Action button.<br/>
<br/>
As with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, even the earliest known designs and prototypes of the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; featured an Action button. The presence of the Action button has remained constant across different development stages and even different hardware configurations.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also experimented with different sizes for the Action button, with certain hardware configurations featuring an Action button larger than the one currently found on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, and more closely resembling the volume buttons in size. The Action button has been seen on multiple &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; prototype units, and has also appeared in internal documentation related to the new devices.<br/>
<br/>
The Action button is also set to appear on the next iteration of the budget-oriented <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/">iPhone SE fourth-generation</a> reportedly planned for a 2025 launch, thereby effectively eliminating the dedicated mute switch from all future iPhones currently in development. <br/>
<br/>
While it remains unlikely that Apple's plans will change, it is important to consider that the information presented here is pre-production information, and may not necessarily reflect what eventually ships on mass production units as we are still many months away from finalized hardware designs.<br/>
<br/>
For more details on what to expect, check out our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> roundups.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/action-button/">Action Button</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">iPhone 16 to Include Action Button Across Entire Lineup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-include-action-button-across-entire-lineup.2412512/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Adds New Features to Final Cut Pro, iMovie, Motion, Compressor, and Logic Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-final-cut-pro-imovie-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-new-features-to-final-cut-pro-imovie-motion-compressor-and-logic-pro.2412493/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:49:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-final-cut-pro-imovie-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Final Cut Pro</category>
		<category>iMovie</category>
		<category>Motion</category>
		<category>Compressor</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released updates for its Final Cut Pro, iMovie, Motion, Compressor, and Logic Pro software, introducing new features and optimizations. Apple announced the Final Cut Pro updates for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Mac <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/final-cut-pro-mac-ipad-new-features/">earlier this month</a> and has now launched them. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921303" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/final-cut-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" /><br/>
Final Cut Pro on the Mac has been updated with organizational refinements like automatic timeline scrolling. Users will be able to keep their clips in view during playback, with the view able to be adjusted using keyboard shortcuts or the Zoom option.<br/>
<br/>
The organization of the timeline is viewable at a glance, and it is easier to differentiate clips by assigned role using distinct colors. Apple also added tools for cleaning up complex timeline sections and fine tuning edits by combining overlapping connected clips into a single connected storyline.<br/>
<br/>
On Apple silicon Macs, exporting projects in H.264 and HEVC is faster than before as Final Cut Pro is able to send video segments to available media engines for simultaneous processing.<br/>
<br/>
On the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, the updated version of Final Cut Pro includes voiceover capabilities that let creators record narration and audio directly into the timeline with the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. In pro camera mode, stabilization now improves shaky footage for smoother video, and there are new options for combining connected clips. Editing is being sped up through new keyboard shortcuts for voiceover and grouping clips, plus there are new color-grading presets and titles.<br/>
<br/>
iMovie and Compressor include the same file exporting optimizations on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-max/">M1 Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-ultra/">M1 Ultra</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Max, &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra, and M3 Max machines. iMovie also includes new options for creating stereoscopic packages for the iTunes Store, and support for JSON and XML when batch exporting submissions using the command line.<br/>
<br/>
Motion has improvements to the Object Tracker on Macs with Apple silicon, and for Logic Pro, Apple has added bug fixes.<br/>
<br/>
Final Cut Pro for Mac is priced at &#36;300, and Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is priced at &#36;4.99 per month or &#36;49 per year. Compressor and Motion for Mac are priced at &#36;50 each, Logic Pro is &#36;200, and iMovie is free.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imovie/">iMovie</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/motion/">Motion</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/compressor/">Compressor</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-final-cut-pro-imovie-update/">Apple Adds New Features to Final Cut Pro, iMovie, Motion, Compressor, and Logic Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-new-features-to-final-cut-pro-imovie-motion-compressor-and-logic-pro.2412493/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.1.2 With Security Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-releases-ios-17-1-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-1-2-with-security-fixes.2412491/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:12:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-releases-ios-17-1-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2, small updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> operating systems that Apple introduced in September. iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2 come a few weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/">release of iOS 17.1.1</a>, another bug fix update.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923208" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-17.1.2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
iOS 17.1.2 and iPadOS 17.1.2 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, iOS 17.1.2 includes important security fixes. Specifically, the update addresses vulnerabilities that may have been exploited in earlier versions of iOS.<blockquote> Processing web content may disclose sensitive information. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.1.<br/>
<br/>
Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.1.</blockquote>Apple is already working on a major iOS 17.2 update that is set to come out in December. iOS 17.2 includes the Journal app, changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, new Weather widgets, and more, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">full details available in our iOS 17.2 guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-releases-ios-17-1-2/">Apple Releases iOS 17.1.2 With Security Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-1-2-with-security-fixes.2412491/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.1.2 With Bug Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-2-with-bug-fixes.2412490/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:11:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.1.2, a minor update to the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that came out in September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1.2 comes three weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-1/">release of macOS Sonoma 14.1,1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898568" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-feature-purple-green.jpg" alt="" width="2585" height="1454" /><br/>
The ‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1‌.2 update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings.<br/>
<br/>
Today's update includes bug fixes and security updates according to Apple.<blockquote>This update provides important bug fixes and security updates and is recommended for all users.<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices. For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222">https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</a></blockquote><br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's security support page, the update fixes two vulnerabilities that Apple says were exploited on versions of iOS earlier than iOS 16.7.1.<blockquote> Processing web content may disclose sensitive information. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.1.<br/>
<br/>
Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.1.</blockquote>More information on the features in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">found in our macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-2/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.1.2 With Bug Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-2-with-bug-fixes.2412490/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>UK Revives Antitrust Probe Into Apple&#039;s Browser and Cloud Gaming Restrictions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/uk-revives-antitrust-probe-into-apple-restrictions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-revives-antitrust-probe-into-apples-browser-and-cloud-gaming-restrictions.2412483/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:07:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/uk-revives-antitrust-probe-into-apple-restrictions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple faces a renewed comprehensive investigation into its dominance in mobile browsers and cloud gaming following a ruling by London's Court of Appeal (via <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-30/apple-loses-fight-to-thwart-uk-antitrust-watchdog-s-mobile-probe?">Bloomberg</a></em>). The court's decision effectively reverses a previous verdict that had halted the probe, reinforcing the authority of the UK's Competition and Markets Authority (CMA).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/app-store-blue-banner-uk-fixed.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-804521" /><br/>
In November 2022, the CMA <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/22/uk-cma-market-probe-apple-google/">launched an investigation</a> into the cloud gaming and mobile browser restrictions put in place by both Apple and Google, suggesting that the two companies were holding back innovation and increasing costs for web developers, cloud gaming service providers, and browser vendors. This decision was initially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/31/uk-apple-browser-probe-shut-down/">overturned</a> by the Competition Appeal Tribunal (CAT), which agreed with Apple that the CMA <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/31/uk-apple-browser-probe-shut-down/">took too long to open an investigation</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Court of Appeal's latest judgment clarified that the CMA acted within its legal bounds, rejecting Apple's argument regarding time limits. The ruling emphasized that such restrictions apply only to consultation processes within a market study and do not limit the CMA's broader investigative powers.<br/>
<br/>
The court highlighted the CMA's role in promoting competition and safeguarding consumer interests, pointing out the potential "serious consequences" of restricting these powers. The CMA's investigation, which remains paused pending Apple's option of a Supreme Court appeal, is set to resume efforts to scrutinize the company's influence in the mobile browser market and its approach to cloud gaming on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/uk-revives-antitrust-probe-into-apple-restrictions/">UK Revives Antitrust Probe Into Apple&#039;s Browser and Cloud Gaming Restrictions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-revives-antitrust-probe-into-apples-browser-and-cloud-gaming-restrictions.2412483/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Holiday Sales Continue With Special Prices for My Best Buy Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/best-buy-holiday-sales-members/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-holiday-sales-continue-with-special-prices-for-my-best-buy-members.2412478/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:39:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/best-buy-holiday-sales-members/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy continues to expand its <a href="https://howl.me/ck61q61zroJ">ongoing Holiday Deals sale</a>, with discounts on video games, notebooks, smartphones, TVs, major appliances, and much more. Throughout all of these sales, <a href="https://howl.me/ck6ZZa9kiGv"><strong>My Best Buy Plus and My Best Buy Total members</strong></a> have a chance to save even more money through exclusive offers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-new-blue-holiday-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-924820" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
There are three tiers of the <a href="https://howl.me/ck6ZZa9kiGv">My Best Buy membership program</a>, including a free option that offers free standard shipping for all members. If you want to start getting access to more interesting benefits and discounts, you'll need to look at the My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total tiers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck6ZZa9kiGv"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE SAVINGS</div>My Best Buy Plus/Total Memberships</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Starting with <a href="https://howl.me/ck6ZYEFKSVF"><strong>My Best Buy Plus</strong></a>, for &#36;49.99 per year you'll get free two-day shipping, exclusive discounts, and exclusive access to certain sales, events, and products. There's also an extended 60-day return window on most products.<br/>
<br/>
There's also the <a href="https://howl.me/ck6Z4pdQsmT"><strong>My Best Buy Total</strong></a> tier, priced at &#36;179.99 per year and including the most robust benefits for members. It has all of the benefits of My Best Buy Plus, with the addition of protection plans (including AppleCare+), 24/7 tech support, VIP member support, and 20 percent off repairs.<br/>
<br/>
In regards to the AppleCare+ benefit, My Best Buy Total members will get up to 24 months of AppleCare+ for most new Apple products purchased at Best Buy while their membership is active. This includes Apple's most popular products, like MacBook Pro, iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, AirPods, HomePod, Apple TV, Studio Display, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Deals Exclusive to My Best Buy Plus/Total Members</h2><br/>
Best Buy has a <a href="https://howl.me/ck61OoXRVNW">page full of exclusive member deals</a>, but we've rounded up some of the best in the list below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61PV9oWri">Nest x Yale Smart Lock</a> - Save &#36;50</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61Q9TzG8O">Logitech Keyboard + iPad bundles</a> - Save 25%</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61GY6s0ys">Bose Wireless Noise Canceling Headphones</a> - &#36;259.00, down from &#36;379.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61S0pbEJY">Google Nest Cam 3-Pack</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;449.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61I0yXb6W">LG 86-inch Class UR7800 Series LED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,249.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61FA0dofO">Samsung Galaxy Book3 15-inch Laptop</a> - &#36;949.99, down from &#36;1,549.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61EQJ9alV">Dell XPS 13-inch Laptop</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck61O1sEVDa">Dyson hair care</a> - Save 20% on select products</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Other Best Buy Deals</h2><br/>
<h3>Computers</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924749" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6Z7bCtHli">13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> - &#36;949.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6Z7AEUD30">13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB)</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60altlKHs">Chromebook Plus Laptops</a> - Save up to &#36;320 on select models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6bWIIqm2n">Lenovo Ideapad 15-inch Touch Laptop</a> - &#36;329.99, down from &#36;629.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6bYP1njgS">Windows Laptops</a> - Save up to &#36;600 on select models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6bZRy8xZg">Gaming Laptops and PCs</a> - Save up to &#36;600 on select models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6b0xcZS29">PC Storage and Accessories</a> - Save up to 40 percent</li></ul><br/>
<h3>TVs</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924748" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60eNSogjg">Hisense 40-inch LED Google TV</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0EZNrRGkg">TCL 40-inch S-Class 1080p Smart TV with Fire TV</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60dRACozA">Hisense 50-inch LED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;239.99, down from &#36;269.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60f2BMtL7">Hisense 65-inch LED 4K UHD Google TV</a> - &#36;349.99, down from &#36;399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BnaSOPqN">LG 65-inch LED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E0KC17zf">LG 48-inch Class A2 Series OLED Smart TV</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E1y2bnRl">Samsung 75-inch Class TU690T Crystal 4K Smart Tizen TV</a> - &#36;579.99, down from &#36;749.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E2vxgpnW">LG 86-inch Class UR7800 Series LED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,249.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BoaZNrLh">Samsung 65-inch OLED 4K UHD TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E3qCGZKD">Samsung 77-inch Class S89C OLED 4K UHD Smart Tizen TV</a> - &#36;2,299.99, down from &#36;3,599.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Video Games</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ps5-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924747" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60nl664HJ">Nintendo Switch + Mario Kart 8 Deluxe + 3 Months Switch Online</a> - &#36;299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60kUoqEaX">Nintendo Switch + Super Smash Bros. Ultimate + 3 Months Switch Online</a> - &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BODf5yvN">Xbox Series X 1TB Console</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E9SazKdl">PlayStation 5 Console Marvel's Spider-Man 2 Bundle</a> - &#36;499.99 (full game download of Marvel's Spider-Man 2 included)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Smartphones</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-galaxy-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924746" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60qE56v2c">Samsung Galaxy Z Fold4</a> - Save &#36;750</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60rfIsJiR">Samsung Galaxy Z Flip4</a> - Save &#36;700</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60rRfy5QJ">Samsung Galaxy A53 5G</a> - Save &#36;400</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60ssxNsqK">Samsung Galaxy S22 Ultra</a> - Save &#36;700</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60s1y27Yi">Samsung Galaxy S22</a> - Save &#36;250</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60tZnlmRe">And more including up to &#36;1,000 off Galaxy S23</a></li></ul><br/>
<h3>Appliances</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/fridge-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924750" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60welCshg">LG</a> - Save up to 30 percent on select microwaves, washers, dryers, dishwashers, and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60w64RDLd">LG washer and dryer pairs</a> - Save an extra &#36;100</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60zewHS64">LG appliance packages</a> - Save up to an extra &#36;500 when buying multiple appliances at once</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60x2g4GGE">French door refrigerators</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck60AjLWWTj">And more Black Friday deals still available on major appliances</a></li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/best-buy-holiday-sales-members/">Best Buy Holiday Sales Continue With Special Prices for My Best Buy Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-holiday-sales-continue-with-special-prices-for-my-best-buy-members.2412478/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights iPhone Feature That Lets You Preserve Your Own Voice</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-ad-for-personal-voice-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-iphone-feature-that-lets-you-preserve-your-own-voice.2412472/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:28:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-ad-for-personal-voice-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ra9I0HScTDw">heartwarming ad</a> for its new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/ios-17-personal-voice/">Personal Voice accessibility feature</a>, available on the iPhone, iPad, and Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Personal-Voice-iPhone-Feature.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896144" /><br/>
Introduced with iOS 17, iPadOS 17, and macOS Sonoma, Personal Voice allows those at risk of losing their ability to speak to create a synthesized voice that sounds similar to their actual voice, so they can continue to communicate with others.<br/>
<br/>
Personal Voice integrates with another accessibility feature called Live Speech, which lets users type what they want to say to have it be spoken aloud during in-person conversations, phone calls, and FaceTime video calls.<br/>
<br/>
In the video, called "The Lost Voice," physician and disability advocate Tristram Ingham uses Personal Voice and Live Speech to read aloud a bedtime story to a young girl. More details about Ingham's life can be found in an <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/a-disability-advocate-preserves-his-voice-with-iphone/">Apple Stories article</a> shared today.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ra9I0HScTDw?si=9iP1J0kg2nYprZjw" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
To create a Personal Voice, users read aloud a randomized set of text prompts until 15 minutes of audio has been recorded. The feature can be found in the Settings app under Accessibility → Personal Voice, and it is currently available for English only. Apple says the feature uses on-device machine learning for privacy and security.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-ad-for-personal-voice-feature/">Apple Highlights iPhone Feature That Lets You Preserve Your Own Voice</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-iphone-feature-that-lets-you-preserve-your-own-voice.2412472/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some Apple Silicon Chips Will Soon Be Produced and Packaged in U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-amkor-chip-packaging-new-arizona-facility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-silicon-chips-will-soon-be-produced-and-packaged-in-u-s.2412465/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:30:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-amkor-chip-packaging-new-arizona-facility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of its efforts to expand its U.S. manufacturing, Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/apple-announces-expanded-partnership-with-amkor-for-silicon-packaging/">announced</a> that Amkor will package some Apple silicon chips at its new facility being built in Peoria, Arizona. The chips will be produced at a nearby TSMC factory, and then Amkor will handle packaging, a final step that protects the chip from physical damage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-silicon-1-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1422" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924673" /><br/>
Amkor will invest approximately &#36;2 billion in the facility, which will employ more than 2,000 people once it is completed, according to the announcement.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple is deeply committed to the future of American manufacturing, and we'll continue to expand our investment here in the United States," said Apple's operating chief Jeff Williams, in a press release today. "Apple silicon has unlocked new levels of performance for our users, enabling them to do things they could never do before, and we are thrilled that Apple silicon will soon be produced and packaged in Arizona."<br/>
<br/>
In its own press release today, Amkor <a href="https://ir.amkor.com/news-releases/news-release-details/amkor-announces-us-advanced-packaging-and-test-facility">announced</a> that it plans to begin limited production at the facility within the next two to three years. The company said it applied for <a href="https://www.nist.gov/chips">CHIPS funding</a> from the U.S. federal government to help fund the project. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says Amkor has packaged chips used in all of its products for more than a decade. Apple silicon chips are found in iPhones, iPads, Macs, and other devices, but it's unclear exactly which chips will be packaged  at the new facility in Arizona.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/apple-amkor-chip-packaging-new-arizona-facility/">Some Apple Silicon Chips Will Soon Be Produced and Packaged in U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-silicon-chips-will-soon-be-produced-and-packaged-in-u-s.2412465/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Drop Back Down to Black Friday Price at &#36;189.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/airpods-pro-2-usb-c-black-friday-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-drop-back-down-to-black-friday-price-at-189-99.2412464/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:23:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/airpods-pro-2-usb-c-black-friday-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C have returned to their all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. We last saw this deal during Black Friday and Cyber Monday deals, and Amazon has been one of the only retailers to offer the sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airpods-pro-2-holiday-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-872479" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple launched these earbuds in September and their headlining new feature is the addition of a USB-C port on the MagSafe Charging Case, replacing the Lightning port. There are a few minor changes to the AirPods Pro 2 besides the addition of USB-C, including additional dust resistance and support for lossless audio with the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't sell the USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case separately, so if you want USB-C support you'll have to purchase a full new set of earbuds. Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/airpods-pro-2-usb-c-black-friday-price/">AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Drop Back Down to Black Friday Price at &#36;189.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-drop-back-down-to-black-friday-price-at-189-99.2412464/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Latest Chrome Browser Update Fixes Critical Security Flaw</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/chrome-browser-update-zero-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/latest-chrome-browser-update-fixes-critical-security-flaw.2412455/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:35:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/chrome-browser-update-zero-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google has issued a critical security update for Chrome on macOS, Windows, and Linux that fixes a zero-day vulnerability in the browser. On Tuesday, Google in a Chrome <a href="https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2023/11/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_28.html">stable channel update</a> said it "is aware that an exploit for <a href="https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-6345">CVE-2023-6345</a> exists in the wild."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
Google has not provided further details about the CVE-2023-6345 exploit, which was discovered last week by security researchers in Google's Threat Analysis Group (TAG). However, it is believed to be related to Skia, the open-source 2D graphics library in the Chrome graphics engine. <br/>
<br/>
According to the notes for the macOS update 119.0.6045.199, the exploit allowed at least one attacker to "potentially perform a sandbox escape via a malicious file," which could theoretically result in arbitrary code execution and data theft.<br/>
<br/>
Users who have Chrome browser set up to automatically update should not need to do anything. Anyone else is advised to manually update immediately (version 119.0.6045.199 on macOS) to avoid the risk posed by the zero-day exploit. In Chrome settings, click the About Chrome tab, and click Update Google Chrome. If there is no option to update, you are already on the latest version. <br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://www.androidcentral.com/apps-software/google-updates-chrome-browser-sixth-zero-day-vulnerability-of-2023">Android Central</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/chrome-browser-update-zero-day/">Latest Chrome Browser Update Fixes Critical Security Flaw</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/latest-chrome-browser-update-fixes-critical-security-flaw.2412455/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Is Coming to the EU in December</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/threads-to-launch-eu-in-december/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-is-coming-to-the-eu-in-december.2412453/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:07:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/threads-to-launch-eu-in-december/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Meta intends to launch Threads in the European Union next month, according to a report by <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/meta-threads-europe-launch-98448df5">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
The social media network debuted in most markets in July, but did not launch in the EU because Meta was unsure whether it would be able to adhere to the bloc's stringent regulations for online services. Threads can import data from Instagram, including behavioral and advertising information.<br/>
<br/>
According to sources who spoke to <em>WSJ</em>, Meta will comply with the regulations by giving EU users a choice of using Threads purely for consumption, without a profile that allows them to make their own posts.<br/>
<br/>
The change coincides with recent comments by Adam Mosseri, head of Instagram, who said the platform was rolling out a way to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/delete-threads-profile-keep-instagram-account/">delete or deactivate a Threads profile separately</a> while leaving the associated Instagram account intact.<br/>
<br/>
The large market expansion should see Threads' user numbers take a jump. Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg said on a company earnings call last month that Threads now has "just under" 100 million monthly users. Since its launch earlier this year it has gained a web app, an ability to search for posts, and a post editing feature.   <br/>
<br/>
The expansion comes after several major advertisers, including Apple and Disney, suspended ad spending on Threads rival X (formerly Twitter) after Elon Musk posted controversial comments from his account. Musk on Wednesday said the post in question was a "mistake," and anyone trying to "blackmail" him over advertising money could "go f–yourself," while also admitting the loss of ad revenue could end the social media platform.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/delete-threads-profile-keep-instagram-account/">Delete Your Threads Profile and Stay on Instagram - Here's How</a></li></ul><br/>
As mentioned above, Threads integrates with Instagram, so it continues to have a strong user base for such a new app. <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors"><em>MacRumors</em> is on Threads</a>, and all of our content is posted there for those who would like to follow us outside of Twitter and Facebook.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/threads-to-launch-eu-in-december/">Threads Is Coming to the EU in December</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-is-coming-to-the-eu-in-december.2412453/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces 2023 App Store Award Winners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/29/2023-app-store-award-winners/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-2023-app-store-award-winners.2412425/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/29/2023-app-store-award-winners/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/apple-unveils-app-store-award-winners-the-best-apps-and-games-of-2023/">chose its 2023 App Store Award winners</a>, highlighting the best apps and games on the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and more. Apple is recognizing 14 apps and games in total, with the winners picked by the global App Store Editorial team.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/app-store-awards-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876046" /><br/>
According to Apple, the 2023 App Store Award Winners provided users "with meaningful experiences" and inspired cultural change. The picks "empowered users to unleash their creativity, discover a world of new adventures, and have fun with family and friends."<br/>
<blockquote>"It's inspiring to see the ways developers continue to build incredible apps and games that are redefining the world around us," said Tim Cook, Apple's CEO. "This year's winners represent the limitless potential of developers to bring their visions to life, creating apps and games with remarkable ingenuity, exceptional quality, and purpose-driven missions."</blockquote><br/>
Apple selected App of the Year winners for each of its products, and Game of the Year winners for iPhone, iPad, and Mac.<br/>
<h2>Apps</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>iPhone App of the Year</b>: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/alltrails-hike-bike-run/id405075943">AllTrails</a>, from AllTrails, Inc.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>iPad App of the Year</b>: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pr%C3%AAt-%C3%A0-makeup/id1434594204">Prêt-à-Makeup</a>, from Prêt-à-Template.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Mac App of the Year</b>: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/photomator-by-pixelmator-team/id1444636541">Photomator</a>, from UAB Pixelmator Team.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Apple TV App of the Year:</b> <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mubi-stream-great-cinema/id626148774">MUBI</a>, from MUBI, Inc.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Apple Watch App of the Year:</b> <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/smartgym-gym-home-workouts/id922744883">SmartGym</a>, from Mateus Abras.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Games</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>iPhone Game of the Year:</b> <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/honkai-star-rail/id1599719154">Honkai: Star Rail</a>, from COGNOSPHERE PTE. LTD.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>iPad Game of the Year:</b> <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lost-in-play/id6449434958">Lost in Play</a>, from Snapbreak Games.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Mac Game of the Year:</b> <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lies-of-p/id6459738231?mt=12">Lies of P</a>, from NEOWIZ.</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Apple Arcade Game of the Year:</b> <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/hello-kitty-island-adventure/id1553505132">Hello Kitty Island Adventure</a>, from Sunblink.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Apple selected five Cultural Impact Winners that were "recognized for their ability to drive positive change through apps and games."<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pok-pok-montessori-preschool/id1550204730">Pok Pok</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/proloquo/id1521978238">Proloquo</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/ca/app/too-good-to-go-end-food-waste/id1060683933">Too Good to Go</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/unpacking/id6450058135">Unpacking</a></li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/ro/app/finding-hannah/id1617252957">Finding Hannah</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
According to Apple, the Trend of the Year was generative AI, with apps integrating AI throughout the year in multiple ways.<br/>
<br/>
All App of the Year and Game of the Year winners will receive a physical App Store award modeled after the App Store logo.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/29/2023-app-store-award-winners/">Apple Announces 2023 App Store Award Winners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-2023-app-store-award-winners.2412425/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Everything We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/</link>
		<comments></comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:22:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18&#038;post_date=1701296544/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Roundup</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Cyber Week Sale Has Record Low Prices on Monitors, TVs, Galaxy Phones, Tablets, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/29/samsung-cyber-week-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-cyber-week-sale-has-record-low-prices-on-monitors-tvs-galaxy-phones-tablets-and-more.2412384/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 10:59:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/29/samsung-cyber-week-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung kicked off its <a href="https://howl.me/ck6A9ZkhXNT">Cyber Week sale</a> a few days ago, offering discounts across smartphones, smartwatches, tablets, computers, and home appliances. Many of the deals in this sale are the same exact prices we tracked during Samsung's Black Friday sale, making Samsung one of the few retailers to keep these best-ever prices around all week. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-best-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923404" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Right now, both the Smart Monitor M8 and ViewFinity S9 5K Display have all-time low prices on Amazon. The Smart Monitor M8 is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> (&#36;300 off) and the ViewFinity S9 5K Display is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,201.82</strong></a> (&#36;398 off). The latter deal has been fluctuating on Amazon, so if it does disappear, Samsung has a second-best offer at <a href="https://howl.me/ck3bAoFu1ed">&#36;1,299.99</a> for the next few days.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck6A9ZkhXNT"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Samsung Cyber Week</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung is encouraging users to shop through the Shop Samsung mobile app this season, which has some exclusive deals and deep discounts on smartphones, smartwatches, and mobile accessories. Clicking any of the Samsung links in this post while on mobile should give you the option to install the app.<br/>
<br/>
Other than monitors and TVs, we're also now tracking quite a few deals on refrigerators, tablets, and computers below. These sale prices will be live for this week only, so be sure to check out Samsung's event before the best prices of the year disappear.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smart-monitor-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923411" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Smart Monitor M8</a> - &#36;399.99 at Amazon, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bAoFu1ed">ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tF40hlZ8">27-inch Odyssey G32A Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;179.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tFfAKEc2">34-inch ViewFinity S50GC Monitor</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;379.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tEtLSIa0">49-inch Odyssey G9 QLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tDoV18FW">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/the-frame-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923410" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tOGqagCf">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6AVgEmjK2">The Frame QLED 4K TV</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000, starting at just &#36;549.99 for 32-inch</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tNGTQwIP">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,489.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tKrmpTeJ">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;2,599.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tLk05pDX">55-inch OLED TV</a> - &#36;1,899.99, down from &#36;2,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tL5nOtB2">85-inch Neo QLED 8K TV</a> - &#36;5,499.99, down from &#36;7,999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tPlYX1Pr">S-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;899.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tMHeYe4E">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;1,899.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Refrigerators</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/fridge-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923409" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bEJD0D8M">Bespoke Side-by-Side Fridge with Beverage Center</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;2,314.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bK4pflLh">Large Capacity 3-Door Fridge with AutoFill Water Pitcher</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;2,423.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bGNJbhW5">Bespoke 3-Door French Door Fridge with Beverage Center</a> - &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;3,114.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bJgrsA7u">Bespoke 4-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;3,114.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bFYM0t73">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge with Family Hub</a> - &#36;3,099.00, down from &#36;5,114.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smartphones</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smartphone-samsung.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923408" /><br/>
If you're shopping for a Samsung smartphone this week, there are extra cash discounts to be found on these devices when shopping via the Shop Samsung mobile app, beyond the trade-in bonus offers listed below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bP336HUQ">Galaxy S23 Ultra</a> - Get up to &#36;800 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bScBfKwa">Galaxy S23</a> - Get up to &#36;600 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bRePchi9">Galaxy S23+</a> - Get up to &#36;600 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bS9XCBv7">Galaxy Z Fold5</a> - Get a free storage upgrade and up to &#36;1,000 instant trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bTLe6f99">Galaxy Z Flip5</a> - Get up to &#36;600 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bUDQL4eU">Galaxy S23 FE</a> - Get up to &#36;400 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smartwatches</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Blue-Gradient.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923412" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b1V5tta3">Galaxy Watch6</a> - &#36;229.99, down from &#36;299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b0F2zDo6">Galaxy Watch6 Classic</a> - &#36;319.99, down from &#36;399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b2LyTQlI">Galaxy Watch5 Pro</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;449.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Earbuds</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-earbuds.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923407" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b470zj6i">Galaxy Buds FE</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b4wDOGNP">Galaxy Buds2</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b3WAwsgE">Galaxy Buds2 Pro</a> - &#36;169.99, down from &#36;229.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tablets</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-tablets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923406" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6A1rsEpPZ">Galaxy Tab A7 Lite</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck6A0OqR8bT">Galaxy Tab S8</a> - Get up to &#36;400 off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bXD80QQL">Galaxy Tab S9 FE</a> - Get &#36;30 off and up to &#36;350 instant trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bWuaccbI">Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra</a> - Get a free storage upgrade and up to &#36;700 instant trade-in credit</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/29/samsung-cyber-week-sale/">Samsung Cyber Week Sale Has Record Low Prices on Monitors, TVs, Galaxy Phones, Tablets, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-cyber-week-sale-has-record-low-prices-on-monitors-tvs-galaxy-phones-tablets-and-more.2412384/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
