<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:04:34 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Planning to Bring OLED to iPad Mini and iPad Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air.2407197/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:56:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Naver</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to bring OLED displays to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, according to a post on the Korean social media site Naver from a user with a track record for posting Apple rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/OLED-iPad-Air.jpg" alt="" width="2363" height="1329" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-806474" /><br/>
The <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223232907661&navType=by">post</a> cites supply chain sources and claims that Apple has now begun negotiations with Chinese suppliers, as well as Samsung and LG, related to OLED displays for future &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models. Apple reportedly seeks for the components to be mass produced from the end of 2025, suggesting that launch could follow in early 2026.<br/>
<br/>
The information lines up with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/oled-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air-2026/">report</a> from technology research firm Omdia that was published earlier this week, which forecasted Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> display panel purchase plans. The potential transition to OLED on Apple's two mid-range tablets is said to be part of its OLED strategy from 2026 onwards.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has apparently not yet fully committed to bringing the more advanced display technology to its mid-range tablets, and may be planning to review how the market responds to the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models that feature OLED displays, which are expected to launch next year, before locking in new panels for the 2026 &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The report also corroborated details about the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">iPad Pro models with OLED displays</a> that are widely anticipated to launch next year, with the panels due to be supplied by LG and Samsung. Apple was said to be seeking more suppliers for OLED displays designed for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, which aligns with the Naver post's mention of additional Chinese suppliers.<br/>
<br/>
Reports suggest that the seventh-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and sixth-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which are expected to launch relatively soon, will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/new-ipad-air-reportedly-in-development/">minor specification upgrades</a> that focus on newer processors, rather than major updates <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ipad-mini-7-no-promotion-display/">like more advanced display technology</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/naver/">Naver</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/">Apple Reportedly Planning to Bring OLED to iPad Mini and iPad Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-ipad-air.2407197/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Pays Apple &#36;18B to &#36;20B a Year to Be Default iOS Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-pays-apple-18b-to-20b-a-year-to-be-default-ios-search-engine.2407183/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 03:10:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's widely known that Apple and Google have a considerable monetary agreement that ensures Google's position as the default search engine on Apple's iOS devices, but neither company reveals the amounts involved. In 2021, financial advisor Bernstein <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/27/google-could-pay-apple-15-billion-default-search/">suggested</a> Google was paying Apple as much as &#36;10 billion a year to maintain the status quo. However, in a new investor note, the analyst claims Google's payment to Apple is now between &#36;18 billion and &#36;20 billion. <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/safari-google-search.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916340" /><br/>
First reported by <em><a href="https://www.theregister.com/2023/10/10/google_pays_apple_18_20_claims_bernstein/">The Register</a></em>, Bernstein published a report assessing the potential implications for Apple of the US government's ongoing antitrust trial against Google, with the Department of Justice considering Google's Information Services Agreement (ISA) with Apple as evidence that it has a search engine monopoly.<br/>
<blockquote>"We believe there is a possibility that federal courts rule against Google and force it to terminate its search deal with Apple," said Bernstein in the report seen by The Register. "We estimate that the ISA is worth &#36;18B-20B in annual payments from Google to Apple, accounting for 14-16 percent of Apple's annual operating profits."</blockquote>Bernstein says Google pays out 22 percent of total ad revenue under its traffic acquisition costs (TAC) and estimates Apple likely receives around 40 percent of this. Bernstein bases its numbers on Apple's public filings as well as a bottom-up analysis of Google's traffic acquisition costs. The DoJ has said in the trial that it thinks Apple receives around &#36;10 billion from the ISA with Google, although its information comes from external sources.<br/>
<blockquote>"Importantly, Google is on trial, not Apple, and Apple could (in theory) partner with another search engine to be the default (and/or retain the agreement with Google outside the US)," the report states. "One more likely scenario is that Apple offers a choice screen. We note that Apple controls access to its installed base, which generates ~&#36;60B + in advertising revenues, and accordingly, we believe that Apple would continue to command a commission (in the 25-30 percent range) for providing access to those search advertising revenues.<br/>
<br/>
"Moreover, introduction of a choice screen could offer Apple the opportunity to potentially launch its own search engine as an option – something it could likely not do today without raising the eyebrows of regulators," the Bernstein report adds.</blockquote>Last month, the trial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/microsoft-bing-acquisition-talks/">revealed</a> that Microsoft considered selling its Bing search engine to Apple. Had the acquisition happened, Bing would have replaced Google as the default search engine on Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
Experts say there is a chance Google could lose the case, which would put Apple's lucrative agreement, which has been in place for a decade, in significant jeopardy. However, a ruling in the case isn't expected before next year, and the likelihood is that proceedings will be extended by the lengthy appeals process.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/">Google Pays Apple &#36;18B to &#36;20B a Year to Be Default iOS Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-pays-apple-18b-to-20b-a-year-to-be-default-ios-search-engine.2407183/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Bringing Online Store to Chile on October 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-bringing-online-store-to-chile-on-october-16.2407177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 02:28:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Chile</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/">announced</a> that it plans to open an online store in Chile on Monday, October 16, providing customers located in the country with a way to purchase iPhones, Macs, iPads, and more directly from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/chile-online-store-opening-announcement.jpg" alt="" width="1291" height="760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916336" /><br/>
As in other countries, Apple's Chilean online store will offer a full range of Apple products and accessories, with shopping assistance from Apple Specialists, a trade-in program for iPhone sales, free one-on-one online training sessions with certain product purchases, build-to-order Mac options, and multiple payment options including financing.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, customers in Chile can only purchase Apple products through third-party Apple Authorized Distributors. The Apple online store will allow customers from all regions of Chile to purchase from Apple directly and have their orders shipped for free to all regions in the country. <br/>
<br/>
To celebrate the opening, Apple has made special Chile flyer wallpapers for the <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/i/banner-download/iPhone_Wallpaper.png">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/i/banner-download/iPad_Wallpaper.png">iPad</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/cl/apple-online-store/i/banner-download/Mac_Wallpaper.png">Mac</a> available to download on its website.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chile/">Chile</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-bringing-online-store-chile-october-16/">Apple Bringing Online Store to Chile on October 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-bringing-online-store-to-chile-on-october-16.2407177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Qualcomm to Take on Apple Silicon Chips With Snapdragon X Series for PCs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/qualcomm-to-take-on-apple-silicon-chips-with-snapdragon-x-series-for-pcs.2407143/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 16:49:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Qualcomm <a href="https://www.qualcomm.com/news/onq/2023/10/introducing-our-next-gen-intelligent-pc-platforms-the-snapdragon-x-series">today outlined</a> its plans for its next-generation chips designed for PCs. The Snapdragon X series is set to come out in 2024, and Qualcomm claims that it will mark an "inflection point for the PC industry" thanks to the "next-level performance" brought by the new chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x.jpg" alt="" width="1790" height="1007" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916314" /><br/>
Snapdragon X chips will use the Qualcomm Oryon CPU, which is built on the chip technology that it got <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/13/qualcomm-to-acquire-chip-startup-nuvia/">when it purchased Nuvia</a>. Founded by ex-Apple chip designers, Nuvia designed custom Arm-based chips that are expected to bring Apple silicon-like performance to PCs with improved power and efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to improved efficiency, Qualcomm's upcoming PC chips include on-device AI processing and 5G connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/10/23911431/qualcomm-snapdragon-x-platform-oryon-cpu-windows-pc-apple-silicon">The Verge</a></em>, Arm has sued Qualcomm and Nuvia for violating the licensing agreements for Arm processor designs and architecture. Arm claims that licenses provided to Nuvia are not valid now that the company has been sold to Qualcomm.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/qualcomm-snapdragon-x/">Qualcomm to Take on Apple Silicon Chips With Snapdragon X Series for PCs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/qualcomm-to-take-on-apple-silicon-chips-with-snapdragon-x-series-for-pcs.2407143/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Continues to Be Most Popular Smartphone Among Teens, Apple Watch Ownership Growing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/iphone-teen-survey-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-continues-to-be-most-popular-smartphone-among-teens-apple-watch-ownership-growing.2407139/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 16:20:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/iphone-teen-survey-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Teen Survey</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> continues to be the most popular smartphone among teens, according to data shared today by investment firm Piper Sandler in its <a href="https://www.pipersandler.com/teens">biannual teen survey</a>. 87 percent of teens surveyed own an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, while 88 percent expect the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to be their next phone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915641" /><br/>
Teen &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; ownership numbers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/11/teen-survey-iphone-ownership/">have not shifted</a> since last year, but over the last decade, interest in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; among teenagers has soared. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2013/10/08/ipad-and-iphone-usage-remains-strong-among-u-s-teenagers/">Back in October 2013</a>, 55 percent of teenagers reported owning an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, while 24 percent had an Android device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/teen-iphone-ownership-2023.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1037" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916329" /><br/>
Apple Watch ownership is also growing, albeit more slowly. 34 percent of teens surveyed own an Apple Watch, up from 31 percent last year. 10 percent of teens said they plan to buy an Apple Watch in the next six months, down from 16 percent in fall 2022. Apple was the favorite watch brand, beating out Rolex, Casio, Garmin, and Cartier.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> was the top payment app for teens, with 42 percent reporting using the service in the last month. &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; beat out Cash App (27 percent), Venmo (20 percent), and PayPal (10 percent).<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not dominate in the streaming music category, coming second to Spotify. 70 percent of teens surveyed said they use Spotify as their music service, while just over 30 percent use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>. 46 percent of teens that pay for a service pay for Spotify, while just 30 percent pay for &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Piper Sandler has also been asking teens about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Private Relay, and usage has jumped in the second half of 2023. 37 percent of teens said they use &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay, while another 17 percent said they're interested in using it in the next six months. Earlier this year, just 24 percent of teens were using &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay, which does require an &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; subscription fee.<br/>
<br/>
Teen surveys are conducted twice per year, with Piper Sandler putting out these reports for over 10 years. For this fall's report, 9,193 teens with an average age of 15.7 were surveyed across 49 states.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teen-survey/">Teen Survey</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/iphone-teen-survey-2023/">iPhone Continues to Be Most Popular Smartphone Among Teens, Apple Watch Ownership Growing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-continues-to-be-most-popular-smartphone-among-teens-apple-watch-ownership-growing.2407139/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Adobe Highlights New Generative AI Features for Photoshop and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/adobe-generative-ai-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-highlights-new-generative-ai-features-for-photoshop-and-more.2407137/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 15:31:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/adobe-generative-ai-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Adobe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At its annual MAX conference, Adobe today provided <a href="https://news.adobe.com/news/news-details/2023/Adobe-Releases-Next-Generation-of-Firefly-Models/default.aspx">insight into its plans</a> for generative AI technology in Photoshop, Illustrator, and other popular design apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/adobe-generative-fill-photoshop.jpg" alt="" width="1300" height="713" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916320" /><br/>
Adobe has iterated on Firefly, its AI image generation model, with the Firefly Image 2 Model. Improved Text to Image capabilities can be used on the <a href="https://www.adobe.com/sensei/generative-ai/firefly.html">Firefly web app</a>, and a Generative Match option lets users generate content in user-specified styles. Photo Settings allows for photography-style image adjustments, and Prompt Guidance helps users refine their suggestions for better end results.<br/>
<br/>
As for quality, Firefly Image renders better skin, hair, eyes, hands, and body structure, plus it offers better colors and improved dynamic range. The generative AI model is used for generative fill in Adobe Photoshop, allowing users to add, expand, and remove content with text prompts.<br/>
<br/>
There's now a Firefly Vector Model, which Adobe says is the world's first generative AI model for creating vector graphics. Integrated into Adobe Illustrator, Firefly Vector Model can be used to create all manner of vector graphics, including logos, website designs, and product packaging.<br/>
<br/>
According to Adobe, the Firefly Vector Model can create "human quality" vector and pattern outputs with a Text to Vector graphic feature. Generated graphics are organized into groups and fully editable, with options to match an artboard's existing style.<br/>
<br/>
Adobe Express also has a new Firefly Design model for generating templates for social media posts and marketing assets. Firefly Design Model can generate templates in popular aspect ratios that are editable in Express.<br/>
<br/>
More information about Adobe's new AI features can be <a href="https://www.adobe.com/">found on the Adobe website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/adobe/">Adobe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/adobe-generative-ai-features/">Adobe Highlights New Generative AI Features for Photoshop and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-highlights-new-generative-ai-features-for-photoshop-and-more.2407137/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Beta 3 Prevents Action Button From Activating the Camera or Flashlight in a Pocket</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-beta-3-prevents-action-button-from-activating-the-camera-or-flashlight-in-a-pocket.2407118/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:32:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the third beta of iOS 17.1 tweaked the functionality of the Action Button to prevent certain actions from being triggered while the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is in a pocket or a bag. The Camera, Flashlight, Voice Memo, Focus, and Magnifier functions will no longer activate when the Action Button is pressed if the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is tucked away in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-action-button-settings.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1624" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910653" /><br/>
Actions that make sense to trigger in a pocket like the mute function and a shortcut can still be activated while the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is inside of a pocket by long pressing on the Action Button, but other features are disabled.<br/>
<br/>
In earlier versions of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and iOS 17.1, all of the Action Button functions can be accidentally activated in a pocket, draining &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery and causing unwanted recordings and images.<br/>
<br/>
Though the Action Button requires a long press to activate, there have still been complaints about it triggering unintentionally while in a pocket, which this change will prevent for functions that cannot be used when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
Note that these changes apply only to the Action Button, so it is still possible to accidentally trigger the Camera or the Flashlight from the Lock Screen while the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in a pocket.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-action-button-tweak/">iOS 17.1 Beta 3 Prevents Action Button From Activating the Camera or Flashlight in a Pocket</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-beta-3-prevents-action-button-from-activating-the-camera-or-flashlight-in-a-pocket.2407118/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wallet App Now Shows Balances for Discover Credit Cards</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-now-shows-balances-for-discover-credit-cards.2407117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:25:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[U.S. Discover users who add their credit cards to Apple Wallet can now see their total card balance and transaction history right on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with iOS 17.1 beta 3, which came out today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/uk-bank-account-apple-wallet-2-discover-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916302" /><br/>
Apple added the transaction and card balance functionality to the Wallet app as part of its Connected Cards feature, according to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-integrates-balances-discover-us-credit-cards/">9to5Mac</a></em>. Tapping on one of the listed transactions in the Wallet app will take users to the Discover app or website for more information. As of right now, this feature is only available for Discover card holders as Apple must work with each U.S. credit card provider or bank to implement support.<br/>
<br/>
A limited number of credit cards have previously supported full transaction history, such as American Express but total credit card balance has not been available.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in the initial iOS 17.1 beta began allowing &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users in the UK to view the account balances of their bank cards and credit cards <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">in the Wallet app</a>. UK banks support Apple's Open Banking API to integrate with the Wallet app, and the feature is much more widely available to UK users. Barclays, Monzo, Starling, HSBC, Lloyds, and RBS all support card balances in the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
Following the release of the UK banking feature, <em>MacRumors</em> discovered that code in iOS 17.1 and references on Apple's website suggested that the feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-wallet-connected-cards-feature-in-us/">would expand to the United States</a>, which turned out to be accurate.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely partner with additional U.S. banks and credit institutions as the launch of iOS 17.1 approaches.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-wallet-app-discover-card-balance/">Apple Wallet App Now Shows Balances for Discover Credit Cards</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-now-shows-balances-for-discover-credit-cards.2407117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warning for iOS 17.1 Beta Testers: Update to Beta 3 or Your Wallet App May Crash</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-wallet-crash/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-for-ios-17-1-beta-testers-update-to-beta-3-or-your-wallet-app-may-crash.2407113/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:04:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-wallet-crash/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/">third developer beta of iOS 17.1</a>, an update that is set to come out in October. With this beta, Apple has a warning about the Wallet app, which may not function as intended for those running an earlier iOS 17.1 beta.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Wallet-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899453" /><br/>
According to the release notes for the update, now that beta 3 has been released, the Wallet app might crash on launch for those who have not yet updated and are still on iOS 17.1 beta 1 or iOS 17.1 beta 2. Note that this impacts those who have used Apple's "Connected Cards" feature, which is the function that allows UK users to see their debit and credit card balance info directly in the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on an earlier beta and wondering why the Wallet app isn't working, the answer is Apple changed something in the backend. You can fix the Wallet app by upgrading to beta 3. Right now, the update is only available to developers, so public beta testers could potentially run into issues. Apple will likely release the third public beta of iOS 17.1 tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also says that the connection between a card and a bank account could unexpectedly revoke, and that users who encounter this issue will need to follow an "Update Your Connection" repair flow that includes going to Settings, navigating to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> &amp; Wallet &gt; Connections, and re-connecting a card.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-wallet-crash/">Warning for iOS 17.1 Beta Testers: Update to Beta 3 or Your Wallet App May Crash</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-for-ios-17-1-beta-testers-update-to-beta-3-or-your-wallet-app-may-crash.2407113/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: 2024 Apple Watch &#039;Unlikely&#039; to Have &#039;Significant&#039; Innovation</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-2024-apple-watch-unlikely-to-have-significant-innovation.2407108/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:33:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Apple Watch X</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 2024 Apple Watch is "unlikely" to offer "significant innovative experiences," according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
For instance, in a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple-watch-estimates-and-predictions-apple-watch%E4%BC%B0%E7%AE%97%E8%88%87%E9%A0%90%E6%B8%AC-71aaeea2ffd4">post on Medium</a> today, Kuo said the Apple Watch will not be equipped with a micro-LED display or blood glucose monitoring in 2024. He believes these features are at least two years away from being added to the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear if Kuo's prediction rules out the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">rumored "Apple Watch X"</a> next year. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said a significantly overhauled "Apple Watch X" would launch in either 2024 or 2025, to mark the tenth anniversary of the device. The original Apple Watch was announced in September 2014 and released in April 2015.<br/>
<br/>
The information shared today by Kuo is quite vague, so there are a lot of possibilities and unanswered questions for now. For example, perhaps Kuo is referring to the model that will succeed the Apple Watch Series 9, and the "Apple Watch X" will be an additional high-end model that does offer more innovative changes. This would be similar to the iPhone X launching shortly after the iPhone 8 and iPhone 8 Plus in 2017.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the "Apple Watch X" would be equipped with a thinner case, and potentially a magnetic band attachment system. And if the device doesn't launch until 2025, perhaps the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/microled-apple-watch-still-on-track-for-2025/">rumored micro-LED display will also be ready</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo added that Apple Watch shipments are expected to decline to 36-38 million units in 2023, a decline of approximately 15% on a year-over-year basis. However, he said that Apple Watch integration with Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro</a> headset could "create an unparalleled and innovative health management experience" that boosts shipments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/kuo-2024-apple-watch-no-significant-innovation/">Kuo: 2024 Apple Watch &#039;Unlikely&#039; to Have &#039;Significant&#039; Innovation</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-2024-apple-watch-unlikely-to-have-significant-innovation.2407108/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2407106/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:26:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced new firmware for both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 with Lightning port and the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 with USB-C port. The new firmware is 6A303, up from the 6A301 update that was released in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not provide details on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware, so it is unclear what's new. Apple added multiple new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> such as Adaptive Audio, Conversation Awareness, and Personalized Volume, so there could be refinements to those updates.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not offer instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in these firmware releases, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-2/">Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2407106/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Big Deal Days: Get Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749 (&#36;50 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-ultra/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-get-apple-watch-ultra-2-for-749-50-off.2407104/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:47:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-ultra/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's Prime Big Deal Days event is in full swing today, and you can get the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.99 in multiple styles, down from &#36;799.00. This is a new all-time low price on the wearable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-watch-ultra-2-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916105" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has nearly every model of the new Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00 during Prime Day, down from &#36;799.00. This version of the wearable just launched in September and this sale beats the previous low price by about &#36;20.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9N594%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We will continue to track Prime Day deals as the event continues, so be sure to keep an eye on our front page for more news. We'll also be regularly updating this article as prices have been fluctuating and several products have gone in and out of stock throughout the event. Remember that you can <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>sign up for Amazon Prime for free for one month</strong></a> to take advantage of the deals.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-apple-watch-ultra/">Amazon Prime Big Deal Days: Get Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749 (&#36;50 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-get-apple-watch-ultra-2-for-749-50-off.2407104/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Will Fix iPhone 12 Radiation Levels in France</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-iphone-12-radiation-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-will-fix-iphone-12-radiation-levels-in-france.2407097/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:28:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-iphone-12-radiation-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>France</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213923">today said</a> that the upcoming iOS 17.1 software that is set to be released later in October will lower <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 radiation levels.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/purple-iphone-12-and-12-mini.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-805183" /><br/>
France in September ordered Apple to cease &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 sales and implement a "fix" for devices that would bring them into compliance with European electromagnetic radiation standards. Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213923">in a support document said</a> that it is disabling the off-body detection feature that allows for slightly higher transmit power when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is not held or in a pocket.<br/>
<br/>
The detection feature is going to be disabled only in France, and Apple says that it is being turned off despite the fact that the country's Agence Française Nationale des Fréquences or ANFR regulatory group made an error when doing its radiation tests. <br/>
<br/>
ANFR used a testing protocol that did not account for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s off-body detection mechanism, which Apple says has been "thoroughly tested and verified internationally to be an effective mechanism to comply with SAR requirements."<blockquote>iPhone has sensors that can detect when it is sitting on a static surface, like a table, as opposed to being held in the hand or placed in a pocket. This off-body detection mechanism, which has been used in all iPhones for over a decade, allows the device to increase transmit power slightly in off-body scenarios to optimize performance.<br/>
<br/>
The specific test protocol used by ANFR requires that devices meet the on-body SAR limits, even when the device is tested off-body on a static surface. This decision is not consistent with international standards, which allow for independent testing of power control mechanisms that may not be activated during standard SAR tests.</blockquote>According to Apple, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 is safe to use "and always has been." The company's iPhones must meet international energy transmission standards for health and safety to ensure limited energy transmission when a device is in contact with the human body.<br/>
<br/>
With the iOS 17.1 update, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models in France will no longer increase their allowed power when the off-body state is detected, so coverage in areas where cellular signal is low may cause slightly lower cellular performance in some off-body use cases, though most users are not expected to notice a change. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/france/">France</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ios-17-1-iphone-12-radiation-fix/">iOS 17.1 Will Fix iPhone 12 Radiation Levels in France</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-will-fix-iphone-12-radiation-levels-in-france.2407097/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Big Deal Days: 10.2-Inch iPad Drops to &#36;249 All-Time Low Price</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-10-2-inch-ipad-drops-to-249-all-time-low-price.2407096/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:28:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Prime Day deals have been appearing throughout the day, and now we're highlighting the best price of the year on Apple's 10.2-inch iPad. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;249.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. This is a record low price, and it's accompanied by numerous best-ever prices across the 2021 iPad lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916104" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The 256GB Wi-Fi iPad is available for &#36;389.00 (&#36;90 off), and you'll also find both cellular tablets on sale at all-time low prices. It's been months since we last tracked deals this steep on the 10.2-inch iPad, so now's a great time to buy for anyone who has been waiting for a good deal.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;389.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9GLLRN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Cellular) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96P9RM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Cellular) for &#36;519.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We will continue to track Prime Day deals as the event continues, so be sure to keep an eye on our front page for more news. We'll also be regularly updating this article as prices have been fluctuating and several products have gone in and out of stock throughout the event. Remember that you can <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>sign up for Amazon Prime for free for one month</strong></a> to take advantage of the deals.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-ipad/">Amazon Prime Big Deal Days: 10.2-Inch iPad Drops to &#36;249 All-Time Low Price</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-big-deal-days-10-2-inch-ipad-drops-to-249-all-time-low-price.2407096/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2407094/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:18:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 to developers for testing purposes, with the betas coming one week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-2-to-developers/">released the second betas</a> of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912331" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 adds the option to favorite songs, albums, playlists, artists, and more, with favorited content added to the Library and used for suggestions. Favoriting can be done from the Lock Screen using the Now Playing widget, plus when starting a playlist, you'll now see Song Suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
AirDrop transfers can be finished over the internet so close proximity does not need to be maintained, and an Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 can now use NameDrop with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running iOS 17.1.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include a flashlight indicator in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> for non <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, and a Wallet feature that lets those in the UK connect their banks to see balances and transactions. More information is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">available in our iOS 17.1 features article</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2407094/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 16.7.1 for Older iPhones and iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-ios-16-7-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-16-7-1-for-older-iphones-and-ipads.2407093/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:17:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-ios-16-7-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 16.7.1 and iPadOS 16.7.1, new software updates that can be downloaded on iPhones and iPads that are not able to run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, or those that have not yet been updated to the new operating system. iOS 16.7.1 comes a few weeks <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apple-releases-ios-17-0-1/">after Apple released iOS 16.7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-16.7.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916227" /><br/>
The software can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings &gt; General &gt; Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; now out, iOS 16 updates are limited to security improvements and performance optimizations. New features will be added to &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; rather than iOS 16.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 16.7.1 update likely addresses <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/04/apple-releases-ios-17-0-3/">the same kernel vulnerability</a> that Apple fixed in iOS 17.0.3 last week. The issue was exploited on versions of iOS before 16.6, according to Apple.<div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-16.238">iOS 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-ios-16-7-1/">Apple Releases iOS 16.7.1 for Older iPhones and iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-16-7-1-for-older-iphones-and-ipads.2407093/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.1 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1-to-developers.2407087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:11:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.1 update to developers for beta testing, with the update coming one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-beta-2/">launch of the second 14.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the Sonoma Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the developer beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1 includes updates for the Music app, introducing an option to favorite songs, albums, artists, and more, plus there's a new Coverage section in System Settings for keeping track of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+. No other major new additions have been found in the beta as of yet, but there are several promised features that did not make it into the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; launch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that these features are coming in an update later this year, so we could begin seeing some of them in this beta.<br/>
<br/>
Additions we are waiting on include interactive Music widgets, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Sync improvements, the option to use Stickers through the Tapback menu in Messages, Intelligent form detection and Enhanced AutoFill for PDF documents and forms, an option to complete words by pressing the space bar, collaborative playlists in the Music app, and a favorite songs playlist.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.1 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1-to-developers.2407087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.1 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-1-to-developers.2407090/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.1 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-beta-2-to-developers/">release of the second watchOS 10.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>‌.1 update, developers will need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the ‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌.1 Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, ‌watchOS 10.1‌ can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.1 adds NameDrop support for sharing contact information with another Apple Watch or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, plus it includes Double Tap.<br/>
<br/>
NameDrop can be used by tapping into the Apple Watch Contacts app, selecting your profile, and tapping on the "Share" option. From there, touching the Apple Watch to another Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 or an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> will initiate a contact transfer.<br/>
<br/>
Double Tap is a gesture exclusive to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and the Apple Watch Ultra, and it allows users to tap their thumb and index fingers together to do things like bring up the Smart Stack, start a call, pause a song, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.1 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-1-to-developers.2407090/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Removable Key That Works as a Mouse Could Come to Future MacBook</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/future-macbook-removable-key-patent/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/removable-key-that-works-as-a-mouse-could-come-to-future-macbook.2407077/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 08:54:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/future-macbook-removable-key-patent/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Patent</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has researched a MacBook keyboard that features a removable key designed to be used as a precision mouse, according to a newly granted patent application.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/removable-key-patent-1.jpg" alt="" width="1870" height="975" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-812359" /><br/>
The patent, first spotted by <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/21/08/19/future-apple-keyboard-could-have-one-key-that-can-pop-out-and-be-used-as-a-mouse"><em>AppleInsider</em></a>, is titled "<a href="https://image-ppubs.uspto.gov/dirsearch-public/print/downloadPdf/11782519">Deployable Key Mouse</a>." Apple first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/19/macbook-could-feature-removable-key/">applied for the patent</a> in 2021 and it was today granted by the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office.<br/>
<br/>
The patent envisages a seemingly conventional MacBook scissor-system keyboard that features a hidden removable key. This key would be designed to be used as a pointing device and contain a position sensor. Apple describes the system as providing a "comfortable, portable, and precise pointer input for a computer input system."<br/>
<br/>
The filing argues that some precise tasks, such as graphic design, computer-assisted design and modeling, and editing large and complex documents, are better suited to a handheld mouse than a trackpad. Apple acknowledges that carrying a separate mouse with the computer can be burdensome and may be "redundant when the computer already has built-in pointing devices."<br/>
<br/>
The removable key is a viable solution to this issue, according to Apple. In some embodiments, the key would be able to work as normal on the keyboard when it is not deployed and feature a small internal battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/removable-key-patent-2.jpg" alt="" width="1870" height="1200" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-812360" /><br/>
Apple outlines various mechanical systems to facilitate the removable key, including sliding a single or set of multiple keys out of the housing vertically, as well as sliding a key out from the side of the machine horizontally. The patent's illustrations show the deployable key located toward the edge of the keyboard so that it would not be a key that sees near constant use.<br/>
<br/>
Patent filings cannot be taken as evidence of Apple's immediate plans, but they do indicate areas of interest for the company and what it is considering developing behind the scenes. While the prospect of a removable key may seem like an outlandish potential MacBook feature, Apple is clearly interested enough in the prospect as to patent the concept. It may be less obtrusive than other unusual features such as the Touch Bar and could appeal to certain pro-users who require maximum portability but could still benefit from occasional precise input.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent/">Patent</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/future-macbook-removable-key-patent/">Removable Key That Works as a Mouse Could Come to Future MacBook</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/removable-key-that-works-as-a-mouse-could-come-to-future-macbook.2407077/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Discounts New ViewFinity S9 5K Display to &#36;1,299.99 (&#36;300 Off) and Smart Monitor M8 to &#36;499.99 (&#36;200 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/samsung-viewfinity-s9-5k-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-discounts-new-viewfinity-s9-5k-display-to-1-299-99-300-off-and-smart-monitor-m8-to-499-99-200-off.2407063/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:16:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/samsung-viewfinity-s9-5k-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung's all-new 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display has received its first discount today, now available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. This markdown is available on <a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh">Samsung's website</a> and on <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-ViewFinity-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Amazon for Prime Day</a>, and it's the first major deal we've ever seen for this monitor since its launch in August.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/samsung-viewfinity-s9.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903406" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The ViewFinity S9 is a 27-inch display with a Thunderbolt 4 port, three USB-C ports, and a Mini DisplayPort, and it includes 90 watts of power for machines connected through the Thunderbolt 4 port. A removable 4K SlimFit webcam supports tilt adjustments, as well as Auto Framing of subjects in the shot, similar to Apple's Center Stage feature. Built-in speakers with an Adaptive Sound+ option to automatically adjust noise levels are also included.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>ViewFinity S9 Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung also has the 32-inch Smart Monitor M8 on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;699.99. This is a match of the all-time low price on this new 2023 model of the Smart Monitor M8 and it's available in multiple colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>Smart Monitor M80C for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/samsung-viewfinity-s9-5k-sale/">Samsung Discounts New ViewFinity S9 5K Display to &#36;1,299.99 (&#36;300 Off) and Smart Monitor M8 to &#36;499.99 (&#36;200 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-discounts-new-viewfinity-s9-5k-display-to-1-299-99-300-off-and-smart-monitor-m8-to-499-99-200-off.2407063/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
