<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:01:00 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Watch Never-Before-Seen Footage of Steve Jobs Discussing the Future of Computers in 1983</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/steve-jobs-archive-1983-speech/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watch-never-before-seen-footage-of-steve-jobs-discussing-the-future-of-computers-in-1983.2431668/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:07:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/steve-jobs-archive-1983-speech/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Steve Jobs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Steve Jobs Archive today <a href="https://stevejobsarchive.com/exhibits/objects-of-our-life">shared never-before-seen footage</a> of 28-year-old Steve Jobs speaking at the 1983 International Design Conference in Aspen, Colorado. His speech was focused on the future of computers and how they would change daily life.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Steve-Jobs-Younger.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959273" /><br/>
The Steve Jobs Archive was launched in 2022 by Laurene Powell Jobs, Tim Cook, and Jony Ive. The website features a collection of quotes, photos, videos, and emails from Jobs, and offers fellowships to young creators looking to follow in his footsteps.<br/>
<br/>
The new page features an introduction from Ive, who led design at Apple for over two decades and was a close friend of Jobs:<blockquote>Steve rarely attended design conferences. This was 1983, before the launch of the Mac, and still relatively early days of Apple. I find it breathtaking how profound his understanding was of the dramatic changes that were about to happen as the computer became broadly accessible. Of course, beyond just being prophetic, he was fundamental in defining products that would change our culture and our lives forever. <br/>
<br/>
On the eve of launching the first truly personal computer, Steve is not solely preoccupied with the founding technology and functionality of the product’s design. This is extraordinarily unusual, as in the early stages of dramatic innovation, it is normally the primary technology that benefits from all of the attention and focus.<br/>
<br/>
Steve points out that the design effort in the U.S. at the time had been focused on the automobile, with little consideration or effort given to consumer electronics. While it is not unusual to hear leaders talk about the national responsibility to manufacture, I thought it was interesting that he talked about a nation’s responsibility to design.<br/>
<br/>
In the talk, Steve predicts that by 1986 sales of the PC would exceed sales of cars, and that in the following ten years, people would be spending more time with a PC than in a car. These were absurd claims for the early 1980s. Describing what he sees as the inevitability that this would be a pervasive new category, he asks the designers in the audience for help. He asks that they start to think about the design of these products, because designed well or designed poorly, they still would be made.<br/>
<br/>
Steve remains one of the best educators I’ve ever met in my life. He had that ability to explain incredibly abstract, complex technologies in terms that were accessible, tangible and relevant. You hear him describe the computer as doing nothing more than completing fairly mundane tasks, but doing so very quickly. He gives the example of running out to grab a bunch of flowers and returning by the time you could snap your fingers – speed rendering the task magical.<br/>
<br/>
When I look back on our work, what I remember most fondly are not the products but the process. Part of Steve’s brilliance was how he learned to support the creative process, encouraging and developing ideas even in large groups of people. He treated the process of creating with a rare and wonderful reverence.<br/>
<br/>
The revolution Steve described over 40 years ago did of course happen, partly because of his profound commitment to a kind of civic responsibility. He cared, way beyond any sort of functional imperative. His was a victory for beauty, for purity and, as he would say, for giving a damn. He truly believed that by making something useful, empowering and beautiful, we express our love for humanity.</blockquote>Head to <a href="https://stevejobsarchive.com/exhibits/objects-of-our-life">"The Objects of Our Life" page</a> to learn more about the speech that Jobs gave, and to view some related photos and exhibits from that time.<br/>
<br/>
The full video of Jobs speaking can be found towards the bottom of the page.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/steve-jobs/">Steve Jobs</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/steve-jobs-archive-1983-speech/">Watch Never-Before-Seen Footage of Steve Jobs Discussing the Future of Computers in 1983</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watch-never-before-seen-footage-of-steve-jobs-discussing-the-future-of-computers-in-1983.2431668/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Looking to License More Movies to Expand Apple TV+ Library</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies-to-expand-apple-tv-library.2431664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:37:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is in active talks to license more films from major Hollywood studios as it seeks to bolster <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-07-18/apple-is-in-talks-to-license-more-films-from-hollywood"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-TV-Ray-Light-2-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-774325" /><br/>
Apple has traditionally focused on original productions for its streaming platform, but it is increasingly looking to expand its offerings by acquiring programming from the extensive libraries of established studios, sources familiar with the matter claim. While &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; has seen some success with original series such as "Ted Lasso" and "The Morning Show," these hits have been relatively few and far between, and the service has struggled to match the extensive catalogs of competitors like Netflix and Disney+.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; launched in November 2019, positioning itself as a premium service with a slate of high-quality, original content. Despite receiving critical acclaim and numerous awards, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/">72 Emmy nominations this year</a>, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; has not garnered the same subscriber base as its competitors. According to the research firm MoffettNathanson, only 11% of U.S. households use &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, compared to 55% for Netflix. The limited scope of content available on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; is apparently seen as a significant factor contributing to its slower growth. Data from Antenna indicates that streaming services with larger content libraries, like Netflix, experience lower cancellation rates. <br/>
<br/>
In an effort to address this, Apple has already begun experimenting with licensing. Earlier this year, the company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time/">licensed approximately 50 movies</a> from Hollywood studios for its service in the United States, adding popular titles such as "Mean Girls" and "Titanic" to its catalog. The positive reception to this initial batch of licensed films is said to have encouraged Apple to pursue additional deals. These discussions aim to license even more titles, potentially expanding the service's offerings internationally as well as domestically. Simultaneously, major studios such as Warner Bros., Discovery, and Disney are increasingly open to selling their content to rivals to boost revenue.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies/">Apple Looking to License More Movies to Expand Apple TV+ Library</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies-to-expand-apple-tv-library.2431664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max Are Still on Sale at Their Ultra-Low Prime Day Prices Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-3-airpods-pro-2-and-airpods-max-are-still-on-sale-at-their-ultra-low-prime-day-prices-today.2431662/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:05:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Even though Prime Day has ended, there are a few AirPods models that are still seeing <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">record low prices today on Amazon</a>. We don't know how long these deals will last at this point, so if you're interested be sure to lock in these steep discounts on the AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max as soon as possible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Combo-Discount-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895386" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the AirPods 3 with the Lightning Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00, which is a new record low price introduced for Prime Day and beats the previous low price by about &#36;10. The AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;168.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00, and is another new all-time low Prime Day price that has stuck around after the event ended.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;119.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Amazon has the AirPods Max for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;394.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;549.00. This is the overall steepest AirPods-related discount still available on Amazon, and it beats the previous low price from before Prime Day by about &#36;55. Every color is available at this low price as well, including Green, Silver, Pink, Sky Blue, and Space Gray.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;154 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/">AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max Are Still on Sale at Their Ultra-Low Prime Day Prices Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-3-airpods-pro-2-and-airpods-max-are-still-on-sale-at-their-ultra-low-prime-day-prices-today.2431662/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Dyson&#039;s New OnTrac Headphones Rival AirPods Max With 55-Hour Battery Life and Customization Options</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/dyson-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dysons-new-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max-with-55-hour-battery-life-and-customization-options.2431660/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:35:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/dyson-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Dyson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Dyson <a href="https://www.dyson.com/sign-up/wearables">today introduced</a> its second pair of headphones, the OnTrac, focusing on customization and premium features to directly compete with the likes of Apple and Bose.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dyson-ontrack-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959226" /><br/>
The new headphones represent a significant shift from Dyson's previous attempt, the Dyson Zone, which combined noise-canceling headphones with an air purifying mask. Priced at &#36;499.99, the OnTrac headphones are designed with a modular approach that allows users to replace the ear cushions and outer caps, enabling over 2,000 potential color combinations. <br/>
<br/>
One of the standout features of the OnTrac is its active noise cancellation (ANC). Dyson employs an eight-microphone system that samples external noise 384,000 times per second, aiming to provide what it claims is best-in-class noise cancellation. This system is comparable to Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, which also uses multiple microphones for ANC, although the exact sampling rate of the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; is not known. The OnTrac's ANC is designed to block up to 40 decibels of noise, enhancing the listening experience in noisy environments.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dyson-ontrac-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959224" /><br/>
<br/>
In terms of battery life, the OnTrac headphones offer 55 hours of continuous listening on a single charge with ANC enabled. This surpasses the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;, which provides up to 20 hours of battery life with ANC and spatial audio enabled. Dyson achieves this extended battery life by housing two high-capacity lithium-ion cells in the headband, which also helps distribute weight evenly for comfort. Charging is facilitated via a USB-C port, and a 10-minute quick charge can provide up to 2.5 hours of playback.<br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac headphones are equipped with 40mm drivers that reproduce frequencies from as low as 6Hz to as high as 21kHz. This wide frequency range aims to deliver deep bass and clear highs, with the drivers angled towards the ears for more direct audio delivery. In comparison, the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; feature custom-built 40mm dynamic drivers and support a frequency range from 20Hz to 20kHz. While both sets of headphones aim to provide high-fidelity sound, the OnTrac's extended frequency range may offer more detailed audio, particularly in the low-end frequencies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dyson-ontrac-3.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959225" /><br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac headphones also feature a unique control system, including a joystick for playback control and touch-sensitive ear cups for toggling ANC. The MyDyson app allows users to monitor noise exposure levels and customize the EQ settings with presets like Bass Boost, Enhanced, and Natural.<br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac includes replaceable ear cushions and outer caps, available in various colors and finishes, allowing users to deeply customize the look of their headphones. The headphones come in four main colorways at launch: CNC Aluminum with bright yellow ear cushions, CNC Copper with purple headband and copper ear cups, Ceramic Cinnabar with a light red headband and matte ear cups, and CNC Black Nickel with an all-black design.<br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac headphones will be available from Dyson's website starting on August 1, with additional customization options sold separately. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dyson/">Dyson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/dyson-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max/">Dyson&#039;s New OnTrac Headphones Rival AirPods Max With 55-Hour Battery Life and Customization Options</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dysons-new-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max-with-55-hour-battery-life-and-customization-options.2431660/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Earns Record 72 Emmy Award Nominations for &#039;Lessons in Chemistry,&#039; &#039;Slow Horses,&#039; &#039;The Morning Show,&#039; and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations-for-lessons-in-chemistry-slow-horses-the-morning-show-and-more.2431659/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:21:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple TV+ has earned a record <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/apple-scores-record-72-emmy-award-nominations-and-sweeps-across-top-categories/">72 Emmy nominations</a> across 16 Apple Originals, including its first-ever nominations Outstanding Limited Series for "Lessons in Chemistry," Outstanding Drama Series for "The Morning Show" and "Slow Horses," and Outstanding Comedy Series for "Palm Royale."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-TV-Plus-Black-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952746" /><br/>
You can read the full list of Emmy nominations on the <a href="https://www.emmys.com/sites/default/files/Downloads/76thnominations-list-v1.pdf?q=2024&q1=">Television Academy's website</a>. We've gathered all of Apple's nominations in the list below.<br/>
<h2>The Morning Show (16)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Drama Series: Jennifer Aniston</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Drama Series: Reese Witherspoon</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Nicole Beharie</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Greta Lee</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Karen Pittman</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Holland Taylor</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Billy Crudup</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Jon Hamm</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Mark Duplass</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Guest Actress in a Drama Series: Marcia Gay Harden</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Drama Series: Mimi Leder</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Casting for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Production Design for a Narrative Contemporary Program (One Hour or More)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Contemporary Hairstyling</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Contemporary Makeup (Non-Prosthetic)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Palm Royale (11)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Comedy Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Comedy Series: Kristen Wiig</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Comedy Series: Carol Burnett</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period Costumes for a Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Choreography for Scripted Programming</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Production Design for a Narrative Period or Fantasy Program (One Hour or More)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period or Fantasy/Sci-Fi Hairstyling</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period or Fantasy/Sci-Fi Makeup (Non-Prosthetic)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Series (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Main Title Design</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Original Main Title Theme Music</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Lessons in Chemistry (10)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Limited or Anthology Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Brie Larson</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Aja Naomi King</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Lewis Pullman</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Limited or Anthology Series, Movie, or Special (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Millicent Shelton</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period Costumes for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Main Title Design</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Original Main Title Theme Music</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Slow Horses (9)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series: Gary Oldman</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Jack Lowden</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Guest Actor in a Drama Series: Jonathan Pryce</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Casting for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Writing for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Drama Series: Saul Metzstein</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Picture Editing for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Series (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Loot (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Comedy Series: Maya Rudolph</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hijack (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series: Idris Elba</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>The New Look (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period Costumes for a Series</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Masters of the Air (3)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Original Main Title Theme Music</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Editing for a Limited or Anthology Series, Movie, or Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Mixing for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Physical (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Single-Camera Series (Half-Hour)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Choreography for Scripted Programming</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Silo (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Series (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Main Title Design</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Girls State (3)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Documentary or Nonfiction Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Documentary/Nonfiction Program: Amanda McBaine and Jesse Moss</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sugar (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Single-Camera Series (Half-Hour)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hannah Waddingham: Home for Christmas (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Production Design for a Variety Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Technical Direction and Camerawork for a Special</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Reluctant Traveler With Eugene Levy (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Hosted Nonfiction Series or Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Writing for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>STEVE! (martin) a documentary in 2 pieces (5)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Documentary or Nonfiction Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Documentary/Nonfiction Program: Morgan Neville</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Picture Editing for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Editing for a Nonfiction or Reality Program</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Mixing for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Carpool Karaoke: The Series (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Short Form Comedy, Drama, or Variety Series</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Nominees for Outstanding Commercial (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>"Album Cover" — Apple iPhone 15</li><br/>
  <li>"Fuzzy Feelings" — iPhone + Mac</li><br/>
</ul>Apple Original films, documentaries, and series have earned 499 wins and 2,262 award nominations so far, including multi-Emmy Award-winning comedy "Ted Lasso" and Oscar Best Picture winner "CODA." The final winners of the 76nd Emmy Awards will be revealed on Sunday, September 15, on ABC.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/">Apple Earns Record 72 Emmy Award Nominations for &#039;Lessons in Chemistry,&#039; &#039;Slow Horses,&#039; &#039;The Morning Show,&#039; and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations-for-lessons-in-chemistry-slow-horses-the-morning-show-and-more.2431659/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pencil Pro Drops to &#36;109.99 on Amazon Alongside Record Low Prices for M4 iPad Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-109-99-on-amazon-alongside-record-low-prices-for-m4-ipad-pro.2431658/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:09:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Pencil Pro has dropped to a new record low price today on Amazon, and we're also tracking a big collection of discounts on the M4 iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956283" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon today has the Apple Pencil Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;109.99</strong></a>, down from the regular price of &#36;129.00. This is a new record low price for the accessory, beating the previous sale price by &#36;10. The Apple Pencil 2 is also at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Pencil Pro launched in May alongside the new 2024 iPad lineup, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/09/apple-pencil-pro-features/">new gestures and capabilities</a> into the stylus. The Apple Pencil Pro is compatible with the M4 iPad Pro and the M2 iPad Air, and marks the first update to the Apple Pencil since the Apple Pencil 2 in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
Moving to the iPads, Amazon has all-time low prices on a few models of the 11-inch M4 iPad Pro. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;919.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and also include multiple cellular tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;919.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,328.99, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9KW87%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8GYMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,299.00, down from &#36;1,399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6WQCK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,699.00, down from &#36;1,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB59ZT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Cellular (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,099.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<br/>
</ul><h3>13-inch</h3><br/>
Prices for the larger models start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet. Overall, nearly every 13-inch M4 iPad Pro is on sale right now on Amazon, all at all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,389.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6S6LS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,839.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,099.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7ZX58%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,389.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6W9TW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,574.00, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J98VKZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,939.00, down from &#36;2,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8TSQN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Cellular (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;2,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9H49F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Cellular</a> - &#36;2,304.00, down from &#36;2,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9KW8F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Cellular (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,214.00, down from &#36;2,599.00</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">Apple Pencil Pro Drops to &#36;109.99 on Amazon Alongside Record Low Prices for M4 iPad Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-109-99-on-amazon-alongside-record-low-prices-for-m4-ipad-pro.2431658/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Humorous &#039;The Underdogs&#039; Video Featuring iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-humorous-the-underdogs-video-featuring-iphone-ipad-mac-and-apple-vision-pro.2431657/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:52:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a humorous <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SbYckRAt5os">new video on its YouTube channel</a> that dramatizes many of the uses of Apple devices, including its Apple Vision Pro spatial computing device.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SbYckRAt5os?si=KavZs80xSDHHOxt7" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Titled "OOO (Out of Office)," the 10-minute video follows design team "The Underdogs" as they travel to Thailand in a last-ditch attempt fulfill a client's wishes. In order to do so, they must find a new packaging factory, solve last-minute design changes, create prototypes, break down language barriers, and more. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has shared longer ads in the past featuring "The Underdogs" design team racing against time to fulfill the needs of a client, but this is the first one to feature one of the characters using an Apple Vision Pro headset to multi-task across several open windows in virtual space.<br/>
<br/>
The short comes after similar "Apple at Work" videos that Apple published in 2019, 2020, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/apple-security-at-work-video-short/">2023</a> using the same actors. Other highlighted products, apps, and features in the video include Live Voicemail, Translate, AirDrop, NameDrop, Apple Wallet, Standby Mode, Animoji, FaceTime, Ringtones, AR, Object Capture, Mac Virtual Display, and more.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/">Apple Shares Humorous &#039;The Underdogs&#039; Video Featuring iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-humorous-the-underdogs-video-featuring-iphone-ipad-mac-and-apple-vision-pro.2431657/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Cellebrite Unable to Unlock iPhones on iOS 17.4 or Later, Leak Reveals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/cellebrite-unable-to-unlock-iphones-on-ios-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/cellebrite-unable-to-unlock-iphones-on-ios-17-4-or-later-leak-reveals.2431651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 04:18:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/cellebrite-unable-to-unlock-iphones-on-ios-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Security</category>
		<category>Cellebrite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Israel-based mobile forensics company <a href="https://cellebrite.com/en">Cellebrite</a> is unable to unlock iPhones running iOS 17.4 or later, according to leaked documents verified by <em><a href="https://404media.co/leaked-docs-show-what-phones-cellebrite-can-and-cant-unlock/">404 Media</a></em>. The documents provide a rare glimpse into the capabilities of the company's mobile forensics tools and highlight the ongoing security improvements in Apple's latest devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/iphone-14-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2458" height="1355" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862499" /><br/>
The leaked "<a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/24833832-cellebrite-ios-document-april-2024?ref=404media.co">Cellebrite iOS Support Matrix</a>" obtained by <em>404 Media</em> reveals that for all locked iPhones capable of running iOS 17.4 or newer, Cellebrite's status is listed as "In Research," indicating they cannot reliably unlock these devices with their current tools. This limitation likely extends to a significant portion of modern iPhones, as <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/app-store/?ref=404media.co">Apple's own data from June</a> shows that 77% of all iPhones and 87% of iPhones introduced in the last four years are running some version of iOS 17.<br/>
<br/>
Interestingly, the documents indicate that Cellebrite recently added support for the iPhone XR and iPhone 11 series running iOS 17.1 to 17.3.1. However, for iPhone 12 and newer models running these same iOS versions, the status is listed as "Coming soon," suggesting Cellebrite's continuing attempts to keep pace with Apple's security advancements.<br/>
<br/>
Another document shows that Cellebrite can break into most Android devices, but not all of them. Cellebrite cannot, for example, brute force a turned-off Google Pixel 6, 7, or 8 to get the users' data. <br/>
<br/>
The revelation comes despite Cellebrite's marketing claims that their Premium service, which offers additional capabilities, can obtain passcodes for "nearly all of today's mobile devices, including the latest iOS and Android versions." <br/>
<br/>
Cellebrite's <a href="https://cellebrite.com/en/ufed/">Universal Forensic Extraction Device (UFED)</a> is widely used by law enforcement agencies worldwide for extracting data from mobile phones. Cellebrite first garnered significant attention in 2016, when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/23/fbi-israeli-firm-cellebrite-to-unlock-iphone/">it was believed</a> the company was enlisted to help the FBI break into the ‌iPhone‌ 5c of San Bernardino shooter Syed Farook after Apple refused to provide the FBI with tools to unlock the device.<br/>
<br/>
The FBI <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/04/12/iphone-5c-flaw-fbi-professional-hackers/">did not use</a> Cellebrite's services for that particular case, but several US government agencies do regularly <a href="http://government-contractors.insidegov.com/l/217606/Cellebrite-Inc">work with Cellebrite to unlock iOS devices</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Apple continually introduces improvements to the security of its operating systems in order to keep ahead of companies like Cellebrite that are always searching for flaws and vulnerabilities to exploit in order to access the data on locked iOS devices.<br/>
<br/>
For example, in October 2018 Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/10/24/graykey-iphone-unlocking-box-disabled-by-ios-12/">successfully thwarted</a> the "GrayKey" ‌iPhone‌ passcode hack, sold by Atlanta-based company Grayshift, which had also been in use by U.S. law enforcement.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/security/">Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cellebrite/">Cellebrite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/cellebrite-unable-to-unlock-iphones-on-ios-17-4/">Cellebrite Unable to Unlock iPhones on iOS 17.4 or Later, Leak Reveals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/cellebrite-unable-to-unlock-iphones-on-ios-17-4-or-later-leak-reveals.2431651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Not Trained on YouTube Content, Says Apple</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-intelligence-not-trained-on-youtube/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-not-trained-on-youtube-content-says-apple.2431646/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 03:00:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-intelligence-not-trained-on-youtube/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Thursday addressed concerns about its use of AI training data, following an investigation that revealed Apple, along with other major tech companies, had used YouTube subtitles to train their artificial intelligence models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
The investigation by <em><a href="https://www.wired.com/story/youtube-training-data-apple-nvidia-anthropic/">Wired</a></em> earlier this week reported that over 170,000 videos from popular content creators were part of a dataset used to train AI models. Apple specifically used this dataset in the development of its open-source OpenELM models, which were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/apple-ai-open-source-models/">made public in April</a>.<br/>
<br/>
However, Apple has now confirmed to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/07/17/apple-intelligence-openelm-training-youtube/">9to5Mac</a></em> that OpenELM does not power any of its AI or machine learning features, including the company's Apple Intelligence system. Apple clarified that OpenELM was created solely for research purposes, with the aim of advancing open-source large language model development.<br/>
<br/>
On releasing OpenELM on the <a href="https://huggingface.co/apple/OpenELM">Hugging Face Hub</a>, a community for sharing AI code, Apple researchers described it as a "state-of-the-art open language model" that had been designed to "empower and enrich the open research community." The model is also available through Apple's <a href="https://machinelearning.apple.com">Machine Learning Research website</a>. Apple has stated that it has no plans to develop new versions of the OpenELM model.<br/>
<br/>
The company emphasized that since OpenELM is not integrated into Apple Intelligence, the "YouTube Subtitles" dataset is not being used to power any of its commercial AI features. Apple reiterated its previous statement that Apple Intelligence models are trained on "licensed data, including data selected to enhance specific features, as well as publicly available data collected by our web-crawler."<br/>
<br/>
The <em>Wired</em> report detailed how companies including Apple, Anthropic, and NVIDIA had used the "YouTube Subtitles" dataset for AI model training. This dataset is part of a larger collection known as "The Pile," which is compiled by the non-profit organization EleutherAI.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-intelligence-not-trained-on-youtube/">Apple Intelligence Not Trained on YouTube Content, Says Apple</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-not-trained-on-youtube-content-says-apple.2431646/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 199 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-199/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-199-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2431630/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:40:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-199/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 199 includes fixes and updates for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, CSS, Editing, JavaScript, Media, Rendering, and WebRTC.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta, the newest version of macOS that Apple is beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-199/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 199 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-199-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2431630/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TinyPod Turns Your Apple Watch Into an iPod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/tinypod-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tinypod-turns-your-apple-watch-into-an-ipod.2431625/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 15:18:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/tinypod-apple-watch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you have an old Apple Watch and you're not sure what to do with it, a new product called <a href="https://thetinypod.com">TinyPod</a> might be the answer. Priced at &#36;79, the TinyPod is a silicone case with a built-in scroll wheel that houses the Apple Watch chassis.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/tinypod-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959183" /><br/>
When an Apple Watch is placed inside the TinyPod, the click wheel on the case is able to be used to scroll through the Apple Watch interface. The feature works through "carefully mechanized components" that make direct contact with the Digital Crown on Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
The TinyPod website suggests that a cellular version of the Apple Watch could be placed inside the TinyPod and used as a miniature phone, without the need to carry an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. The case leaves the back of the Apple Watch exposed, but it is worth noting that actually using an Apple Watch this way would be frustrating because it uses skin contact for authentication.<br/>
<br/>
If the TinyPod were tucked away in a pocket, the Apple Watch would need to be unlocked with a passcode every time it was used, since there is no <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or Touch Id. The alternative would be leaving the watch unlocked without a passcode, but that's not particularly secure.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Say hello to tinyPod! Available now at <a href="https://t.co/v0B49YxW5g">https://t.co/v0B49YxW5g</a> <a href="https://t.co/6LpGytwoQ1">pic.twitter.com/6LpGytwoQ1</a></p>&mdash;  (@thetinypod) <a href="https://twitter.com/thetinypod/status/1813589903722311784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Using TinyPod requires turning off wrist detection, which is the feature that keeps the Apple Watch unlocked with skin contact. TinyPod positions this as a bonus that allows for longer multi-day battery life, but at the same time highlights <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> and Name Drop, features that would require authentication via passcode. With the back of the Apple Watch exposed, charging can be done with a standard Apple Watch charging puck.<br/>
<br/>
TinyPod is available in 40/41mm, 44/45mm, and 49mm sizes to fit all Apple Watch models. It is compatible with the Series 4 and later, as well as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> and Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
TinyPod's creators introduced it earlier this year, but the device is now available for purchase. It can be <a href="https://thetinypod.com/#buy">ordered from the TinyPod website</a> for &#36;80, with a lite model that does not feature a click wheel available for &#36;30.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/tinypod-apple-watch/">TinyPod Turns Your Apple Watch Into an iPod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tinypod-turns-your-apple-watch-into-an-ipod.2431625/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Product Managers Discuss Cool New iPadOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-product-managers-discuss-ipados-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-product-managers-discuss-cool-new-ipados-18-features.2431616/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:20:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-product-managers-discuss-ipados-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, Apple added some useful iPad-specific features in the Notes app, including Smart Script and Math Notes. Both of these additions are designed to work with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, and they're some of the neater new features on Apple's tablets. Apple product manager Ty Jordan and engineering manager Jenny Chen recently did an interview with Chris Lawley to discuss the work that went into the &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; updates.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Talking to Apple about Smart Script and Math Notes" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LiAvrlKoEjk" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Smart Script is one of the ways that Apple is using machine learning in &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;. It refines handwritten text, making your handwriting look neater without losing the personal flare that makes it <em>your</em> handwriting rather than generic writing. Smart Script learns your handwriting style, which Jordan said makes it as useful as typed text.<br/>
<blockquote>You'll notice that as soon as you start writing words, it refines your handwriting. You'll notice that it spell checks, so if you make a spelling mistake, it'll be underlined. It can also do some really cool things with reflowing your text, so if you tap and hold your Pencil, you can move words around, and you'll see that it reflows in your paragraph so you can get some more space.<br/>
<br/>
You can even paste typed text as your own handwritten text right in the middle of a paragraph, so a lot of things that we take for granted with typed text, you can now do with handwritten text.</blockquote>Smart Script learns continually and while it is designed to work quickly, it will get better over time as you write more, especially for features such as paste as handwriting. Recognition does not persist from note to note, however. Apple wanted the feature to feel personal and not like a font, which is why it refines dynamically with each note. <blockquote>It's very contextual. So, for example, if you were to go to a previous paragraph where you had some band handwriting, we're going to match the handwriting that was refined there and not sort of try to replicate what you've had in other notes.</blockquote><br/>
As for Math Notes, Jordan said that Apple took the time to "really reimagine" the calculator feature could be designed for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>'s interface. If you're unfamiliar with the feature, Math Notes on &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lets you write out equations with the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, with the Notes app solving the equation automatically when an equals sign is added.<br/>
<blockquote>It sort of works like magic. It combines the natural input of a pencil with the amazing on-device machine learning models that Jenny and her teams work on. You just write math like on a piece of paper and like magic, it just gives you the answer. It's so simple and intuitive.</blockquote><br/>
Math Notes is able to recognize variables and the numbers associated with them. So if you define variables like price and area in one part of the note, and then write "price x area," Math Notes is able to provide an answer using the numbers specified earlier. Jordan explains:<br/>
<blockquote>I'll do my best shot and go back to high school. So a variable is just a named value, right? So you probably know a lot of them from school, like X and Y, and you could declare a variable with that [...] but you can do this with any word that you want.<br/>
<br/>
I've personally loved using it for natural experiences, where I might declare like drinks equal something and food equals something else, and then I can just say that plus that and divided by the number of people, and I get an answer. So it just creates this very natural way to work with your math.</blockquote><br/>
Math Notes is intelligent enough to understand the difference between separate variables in a note, so if you have multiple math problems with the same variable like X, it won't get confused. You can have graphs added automatically in Math Notes if an equation can be grafted, which Chen says uses the work that Apple has previously done for the Swift Charts API.<br/>
<br/>
If you're interested in more context on the new Notes features in &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, the full video is well worth watching. Both Math Notes and Smart Script are available in the &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; beta, which developers and public beta testers can download. The new features will launch in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-product-managers-discuss-ipados-18/">Apple Product Managers Discuss Cool New iPadOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-product-managers-discuss-cool-new-ipados-18-features.2431616/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are the Best Apple Deals You Can Still Get Before Amazon Prime Day Ends</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-deals-before-prime-day-ends/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-best-apple-deals-you-can-still-get-before-amazon-prime-day-ends.2431605/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:01:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-deals-before-prime-day-ends/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimeday">Prime Day</a> is coming to a close later today, so we're quickly recapping all of the best Apple deals that are still live on Amazon right now. Since many of these products have been on sale for a few days, shipping may be delayed, but they're all at some of the lowest prices we've ever seen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Last-Chance-Prime-Day-Sales-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903068" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You will need an active <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon Prime subscription</a> to see these deals. You can get one month of Amazon Prime for free when signing up this week, and afterwards the service will renew at &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;139 per year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/airpods-prime-day-24.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958559" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon had huge discounts on AirPods this Prime Day, with all-time low prices hitting every current model at some point during the event. As of today, we're still tracking great low prices on AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;155 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/prime-day-series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958519" /><br/>
<br/>
Prime Day this year included new best-ever prices on both the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch SE, and both are still available to purchase today. This includes &#36;120 off Series 9 models and &#36;80 off SE models, plus &#36;99 off Ultra 2 for anyone looking for a high-end wearable.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTJ2Y5F%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us1%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;279.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><h2>M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m3-macbook-air-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958729" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week introduced &#36;250 discounts across the board on the new M3 MacBook Air, with the cheapest model now priced at just &#36;849.00, down from &#36;1,099.00. You'll find these &#36;250 discounts on both 13-inch and 15-inch still available today on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><h3>13-inch M3 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 256GB SSD</a> - &#36;849.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQBNsFbNk">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX246FNZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">16GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQCCPC5E3">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>15-inch M3 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 256GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQDrLzdh5">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQDI1Z9Ul">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BN3L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">16GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,449.00, down from &#36;1,699.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQD4AX4A0">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m2-macbook-air-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958554" /><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> this week have Apple's 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for the record low price of &#36;799.00, down from &#36;999.00. You'll find all four colors on sale at this price, including Midnight, Silver, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/2022-ipad-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958608" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking &#36;50 off the Wi-Fi models of the 2022 iPad, starting at &#36;299.00 for 64GB Wi-Fi. This model was down to a lower price at the start of Prime Day, but that deal quickly expired and today's is still a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/ipad-mini-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1384" height="776" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853365" /><br/>
<br/>
All-time low prices have also hit Apple's iPad mini 6, starting at &#36;379.99 for the 64GB Wi-Fi model and increasing to &#36;529.99 for the 256GB Wi-Fi model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G99Y4NL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;529.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-deals-before-prime-day-ends/">Here Are the Best Apple Deals You Can Still Get Before Amazon Prime Day Ends</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-best-apple-deals-you-can-still-get-before-amazon-prime-day-ends.2431605/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Year&#039;s Best Deals on MacBook Pro End Today, Save Up to &#36;700 on M3 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/best-deals-macbook-pro-700-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-years-best-deals-on-macbook-pro-end-today-save-up-to-700-on-m3-models.2431601/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 10:17:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/best-deals-macbook-pro-700-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Prime Day (and Prime Day adjacent) deals are coming to an end later today, so we're once again highlighting massive discounts that you can get on Apple's M3 MacBook Pro at both <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmGLCwHgm44">Best Buy</a>. If you're shopping at Best Buy, it'll be required to have a <a href="https://howl.me/cmGLPqTniJO">My Best Buy Plus or Total membership</a> for many of the deals in this article.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-blue-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935646" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's and Amazon's deals include all-time low prices on the 14-inch and 16-inch models, and the best discounts will be found on the larger screen computers. The 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro is currently discounted by &#36;500 for all customers on Best Buy, but if you have a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, you can <a href="https://howl.me/cmFVSBa773D">add up to an extra &#36;200 off select models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;700 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the 16-inch MacBook Pro, stock at Amazon appears to be dwindling and many are marked as temporarily out of stock. You can still lock in these ultra-low prices now before they disappear and Amazon will ship out the computers when stock returns.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,399.00 (&#36;200 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmGLCwHgm44">matched at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">only at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,899.00 (&#36;600 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5L3PPZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,299.00 (&#36;600 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">matched at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5MKMD4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,799.00 (&#36;700 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">matched at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5K7BCR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;3,299.00 (&#36;700 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">matched at Best Buy for members</a>]</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/best-deals-macbook-pro-700-off/">The Year&#039;s Best Deals on MacBook Pro End Today, Save Up to &#36;700 on M3 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-years-best-deals-on-macbook-pro-end-today-save-up-to-700-on-m3-models.2431601/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Ugreen Nexode 100W 20000mAh Power Bank Offers Ample Juice to Go</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/review-ugreen-nexode-100w-20000mah-power-bank/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ugreen-nexode-100w-20000mah-power-bank-offers-ample-juice-to-go.2431595/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:47:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/review-ugreen-nexode-100w-20000mah-power-bank&#038;post_date=1721242047/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Ugreen</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular accessory brand <a href="https://www.ugreen.com">Ugreen</a> has built up a veritable lineup of portable power banks and chargers in the last few years, with several options to serve the needs of gadget users on the road. It can be hard to work out what kind of unit will meet your particular requirements, but if you are looking for a compact USB-C/A bank that has enough juice to fully recharge your smartphone and laptop and then some, Ugreen's Nexode 100W power bank could be worth considering.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/1ugreen-nexode-100w-power-bank.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959117" /><br/>
I've been testing out the Nexode for a few weeks now, and I've come away impressed enough that it's become an ever-present accessory in my laptop bag, and I don't leave the house without it when I'm working away from home. <br/>
<br/>
Normally priced at &#36;79.99 (and sometimes quite a lot cheaper if you shop around online), it's a compact, unassuming unit that weighs about 513 grams. While it's almost three times as heavy as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, its dimensions are pretty similar, and it's around 1.5x as thick as Apple's smartphone, which makes it pocketable if you're wearing a coat.<br/>
<br/>
The flame-retardant plastic case is black on the back and painted in metallic grey on one side and around the edges. It's soft to the touch, but its smoothness suggests it will scratch easily, which is why I keep it in the supplied draw-string velvety pouch when it's not in use. The included USB-C to USB-C cable is around 18 inches long, and also fits snugly inside.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/3ugreen-nexode-100w-power-bank.jpg" alt="" width="3691" height="2300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959119" /><br/>
On one side of the unit is a button that when pressed illuminates a simple LCD readout that tells you the percentage of charge left in its five 21700 battery cells, which together total 20,000mAh capacity. The power bank itself supports fast charging at a maximum 65W. With a charger that takes advantage of that, the unit reaches 50% capacity in about 50 minutes, and full capacity in about 110 minutes, so you can basically look at the LCD percentage readout to get a fairly good idea of how its progressing. The bank is also capable of charging your devices while being charged itself.<br/>
<br/>
On one side of the bank are three ports: The IN1/OUT1 is a USB-C port that's used to charge the Nexode, but it's also the connector to use if you want to charge a device at the maximum 100W output. Then there's secondary USB-C and USB-A ports, allowing you to charge up to three devices simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
I've been charging my M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> 13-inch using the maximum 100W fast charging speed, and from 10% battery it can bring my laptop up to a 50% charge in around 25 minutes, and fully charge it in about an hour, with around 10% of juice in the bank to spare. When I plug in my &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; when it's hovering around 10%, it hits 60% charge in half an hour, and fully charges in under an hour, with enough left in the power bank's tank to fully recharge the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from almost dead more than twice over. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/7ugreen-nexode-100w-power-bank.jpg" alt="" width="5712" height="3597" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959118" /><br/>
Those charge times, while swift, do depend on nothing else being connected to the power bank, because that's when the variable output changes. With more than one device plugged in, the 100W port is limited to 65W, which still isn't bad, but the wait time obviously goes up. On their own, the second USB-C port maxes out at 30W, while the USB-A port can handle 22.5W, both of which are good for AirPods or an Apple Watch (if both gadgets are connected, pressing the unit's button three times in succession activates a small-current mode). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/2ugreen-nexode-100w-power-bank.jpg" alt="" width="4032" height="3024" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959120" /><br/>
That said, if all three ports are active, the two secondary ports share 20W, although that doesn't affect the 100W rate, which feels reasonable for a power bank on a single charge. Regardless, the overall capacity of the unit means that I've been able to work away from home all day without having to worry if I'll have access to a power outlet – even if my MacBook hasn't been charged to full overnight. <br/>
<br/>
Similarly, heading out for a weekend away with a fully charged MacBook and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it's easily met my needs, even when I've not had easy access to power. All in all, the Ugreen Nexode 100W hasn't let me down. There may be no bells and whistles to speak of, but that helps keep the price reasonable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ugreen-nexode-100w.jpg" alt="" width="1399" height="919" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959113" /><br/>
As an Amazon Prime Day deal, the Ugreen Nexode 100W 20000mAh Power Bank is available from <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C3GTMX5M%2F">Amazon</a> and the <a href="https://www.ugreen.com/products/ugreen-100w-20000mah-power-bank">Ugreen website</a>, priced at &#36;54.39 (down from the regular &#36;79.99 list price). <br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: Ugreen provided MacRumors with the Nexode 100W 20000mAh Power Bank for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ugreen/">Ugreen</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/review-ugreen-nexode-100w-20000mah-power-bank/">Review: Ugreen Nexode 100W 20000mAh Power Bank Offers Ample Juice to Go</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ugreen-nexode-100w-20000mah-power-bank-offers-ample-juice-to-go.2431595/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Delays Change Aimed at Saving Space Inside Future iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/kuo-iphone-17-wont-use-resin-coated-copper/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-delays-change-aimed-at-saving-space-inside-future-iphones.2431588/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:09:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/kuo-iphone-17-wont-use-resin-coated-copper/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple no longer plans to use resin-coated copper for logic boards in iPhone 17 models next year, supply chain analyst <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1813561418316443713">Ming-Chi Kuo said today</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/iphone-15-a16-bionic.jpg" alt="" width="2030" height="1142" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912526" /><br/>
Kuo said resin-coated copper failed to meet Apple's "high-quality requirements," leading to the company scrapping its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/rcc-thinner-circuit-boards-2025/">plans to adopt the material for iPhone 17 models</a>. It is unclear if Apple will revisit resin-coated copper for iPhone 18 models or later, but it appears that the material is at least a few years away from being used in iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
Resin-coated copper is a thin layer of copper foil coated with a resin, such as an epoxy. The material would allow for a thinner logic board, which in turn would provide more internal space for other components and sensors in future iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
It was also rumored that at least one new Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/24/next-apple-watch-thinner-logic-board-rumor/">would use resin-coated copper</a> this year, but it is unclear if that plan has been delayed too.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/kuo-iphone-17-wont-use-resin-coated-copper/">Kuo: Apple Delays Change Aimed at Saving Space Inside Future iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-delays-change-aimed-at-saving-space-inside-future-iphones.2431588/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Prime Day Deals on Monitors, Charging Accessories, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/the-best-prime-day-deals-accessories/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-prime-day-deals-on-monitors-charging-accessories-and-more.2431583/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 06:29:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/the-best-prime-day-deals-accessories/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yesterday we highlighted some of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">best Apple-related product discounts</a> that you can find on Amazon during <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimeday">Prime Day</a>, and now we're focusing on third-party accessory markdowns during the event. In this article you'll find all the best accessories for charging, smart homes, smartphones, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/primeday2020_feature3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-763521" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should remember that Prime Day sales are typically time sensitive, so purchase quickly if you're interested. Remember that you'll need an <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon Prime membership</a> to get Prime Day deals. You can sign up for a free 30-day trial of Prime on Amazon if you're a new customer; afterwards the service runs for &#36;14.99/month or &#36;139/year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/anker-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959106" /><br/>
<br/>
Prime Day deals have hit Anker's most popular portable batteries, Bluetooth speakers, wall chargers, USB-C hubs, and portable power stations. We've collected some of the best Anker discounts in the list below, but be sure to browse Amazon for even more sales.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;79.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1717512554052">MagGo Power Bank 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;64.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1717512037932">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;35.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wireless Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;71.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1717513024737">MagGo 3-in-1 Folding Charging Station</a> - &#36;87.99, down from &#36;109.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;104.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;112.46, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1754-SOLIX-C800-Plus%2Fdp%2FB0C5CBDX2P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C800 Power Station with Camping Lights</a> - &#36;449.00, down from &#36;649.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Generator-UltraFast-Optional%2Fdp%2FB0C5C89QKZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Station-Generator-LiFePO4%2Fdp%2FB0CDGKRX4X%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C1000 Power Station with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;799.00, down from &#36;1,549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-PowerHouse-Generator-Batteries%2Fdp%2FB0BX64LGFT%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station with 200W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;1,299.00, down from &#36;2,549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Generator-Portable-Batteries-Technology%2Fdp%2FB0CBB6HFMM%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station with 400W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Station-Generator-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0CRB3MQT5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F3800 Power Station with 400W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;3,099.00, down from &#36;4,899.00</li></ul></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;42.99, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/jackery-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959105" /><br/>
<br/>
Jackery's Prime Day deals include a large selection of portable power stations at big discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM_1720797135027">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;169.00, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.RBRZCEOCA88O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.RBRZCEOCA88O_1720797474320">Solar Generator 240 with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1XYRT4EQJET79%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1XYRT4EQJET79_1720797554886">Solar Generator 300 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;398.98, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETFENZHJJVP7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETFENZHJJVP7_1720797190458">Expansion Battery Pack 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;479.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34M7T7T7RIMAV%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34M7T7T7RIMAV_1720797593312">Solar Generator Explorer 500</a> - &#36;479.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3N2AT8FS2RCU5%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3N2AT8FS2RCU5_1720797246445">Explorer 1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;599.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS_1720797331085">Expansion Battery Pack 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NIEM436WQUAO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NIEM436WQUAO_1720797439732">Explorer 2000 PRO Power Station</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS_1720799483508">Explorer 2000 Plus + Expandable Battery + Solar Panel</a> - &#36;2,599.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beats</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/beats-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959103" /><br/>
<br/>
There's a big collection of Beats headphones discounted for Prime Day this year, starting with the Beats Studio Buds for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB096SV8SJG%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us6"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;149.95. The newer Beats Studio Buds+ are on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZK2Z2TC%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us4"><strong>&#36;129.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.95.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F03667DF9-C068-4DFF-B1F2-A822918F9ABA"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 51% OFF</div>Beats Headphones for Prime Day</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Beats Studio Pro are on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C8PR4W22%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us3"><strong>&#36;169.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;349.99, which is a new record low price. You can also get the Beats Solo 4 Headphones for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CZPLV566%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us2"><strong>&#36;119.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;199.99 and the Beats Fit Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09JL41N9C%2Fref%3Dfs_a_bt2_us5"><strong>&#36;149.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;199.99.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959102" /><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's popular 32-inch Smart Monitor M8 (Model M80D) is down to the best price we've ever seen it on Amazon, available for &#36;499.99, down from &#36;699.99. This is the newest model of the Smart Monitor M8, and it beats the first discount we tracked last week by &#36;50.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Streaming-Upscaling-Ergonomic-LS32DM801UNXZA-dp-B0D1DBQRRS%2Fdp%2FB0D1DBQRRS%2Fref%3Ddp_ob_title_ce%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200</div>Samsung 32-inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-Slimfit-Camera-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700</div>Samsung 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the Smart Monitor M8, Amazon has a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimeday%3Fref_%3Dnav_cs_td_pd_dt_cr%26discounts-widget%3D%252522%25257B%25255C%252522state%25255C%252522%25253A%25257B%25255C%252522refinementFilters%25255C%252522%25253A%25257B%25257D%25257D%25252C%25255C%252522version%25255C%252522%25253A1%25257D%252522%26bubble-id%3Ddeals-collection-computers-and-accessories">wide array of monitors and PCs on sale</a> from HP, Acer, Samsung, and more for Prime Day. One of the highlights is Samsung's 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-Slimfit-Camera-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/prime-day-tvs.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959104" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FVIZIO-50-inch-Premium-Compatibility-M50QXM-K01%2Fdp%2FB09VCZCR1W%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B09VCZCR1W_dt_sl7_4a%26th%3D1">50-inch Vizio 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;629.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FTCL-55QM751G-Accelerator-Streaming-Television%2Fdp%2FB0CZML9HLC%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B0CZML9HLC_dt_sl7_4a%26th%3D1">55-inch TCL 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;498.00, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-55-Inch-Anti-Reflection-Included-QN55LS03BAFXZA%2Fdp%2FB09VCVGH7B%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B09VCVGH7B_dt_sl7_4a%26th%3D1">55-inch The Frame 4K TV</a> - &#36;997.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLG-65-Inch-Processor-AI-Powered-OLED65G3PUA%2Fdp%2FB0BVWZJ2YV%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B0BVWZJ2YV_dt_sl7_4a%26th%3D1">65-inch LG G3 OLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,846.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Tracking-Symphony-Xcelerator-QN65S95C%2Fdp%2FB0BWFT262P%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B0BWFT262P_dt_sl7_4a%26th%3D1">65-inch Samsung Quantum HDR Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,797.99, down from &#36;3,297.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Amazon Devices</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/prime-day-amazon-thing.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959101" /><br/>
<br/>
Of course, some of the best discounts can be found on Amazon's own line of products. This includes Kindle e-readers, Blink security cameras, Fire tablets, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAll-New-release-Smart-speaker-Charcoal%2Fdp%2FB09B8V1LZ3%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B09B8V1LZ3_dt_sl7_4a">Echo Dot</a> - &#36;24.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAll-New-Echo-Show-8%2Fdp%2FB0BLS3Y632%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B0BLS3Y632_dt_sl7_4a">Echo Show 8</a> - &#36;84.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fkindle-the-lightest-and-most-compact-kindle%2Fdp%2FB09SWW583J%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B09SWW583J_dt_sl7_4a">Kindle</a> - &#36;84.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAmazon-digital-notebook-Paperwhite-display%2Fdp%2FB09BRZBK15%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B09BRZBK15_dt_sl7_4a">Kindle Scribe</a> - &#36;259.99, down from &#36;369.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAmazon_Fire_HD_10_Kids_Pro%2Fdp%2FB0BL6DCNGR%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B0BL6DCNGR_dt_sl7_4a">Fire HD Kids Tablet</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;189.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FRing-Video-Doorbell-Venetian-Bronze-2020-Release%2Fdp%2FB08N5NQ69J%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B08N5NQ69J_dt_sl7_4a">Ring Video Doorbell</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBlink-Outdoor-4th-Gen-5-Camera%2Fdp%2FB0B1N4LM4J%3Fref%3Ddlx_prime_dg_dcl_B0B1N4LM4J_dt_sl7_4a">Blink Outdoor 4 Camera</a> - &#36;159.99, down from &#36;399.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Google Nest Thermostat</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/prime-day-nest.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903051" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Google Nest Thermostat for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FGoogle-Nest-Thermostat-Smart-Programmable%2Fdp%2FB08HRWWCTR%2Fref%3Dlp_116584751011_1_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26sbo%3DTc8eqSFhUl4VwMzbE4fw%252Fw%26geniuslink%3Dtrue%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;84.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.99 during Prime Day. This is one of the lowest prices we've seen for the Nest Thermostat, and it's available at this price in two colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FGoogle-Nest-Thermostat-Smart-Programmable%2Fdp%2FB08HRWWCTR%2Fref%3Dlp_116584751011_1_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26sbo%3DTc8eqSFhUl4VwMzbE4fw%252Fw%26geniuslink%3Dtrue%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;45 OFF</div>Nest Thermostat for &#36;84.99</div></a></div><h2>More Sales</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2FC822DB0E-001F-4CF0-9CB7-00B831B0A82C%3Fingress%3D0%26visitId%3D02b6e0ad-9e85-4750-bb49-48170d05a087">Belkin</a> - Save on headphones, chargers, and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2FEEA050EE-2B9B-4F18-96AD-1541560B1067%3Fingress%3D2%26visitId%3D7cf50e00-2783-445a-a030-30b465ff4337%26store_ref%3Dbl_ast_dp_brandLogo_sto%26ref_%3Dast_bln">Eufy</a> - Save on smart home products</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=2178566&u=63177&m=132800&urllink=&afftrack=">iVANKY</a> - Save on USB docks for Macs</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F306AA3DD-F55E-4925-9894-F1E9C02F8BC7">Flexispot</a> - Save on standing desks</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/the-best-prime-day-deals-accessories/">The Best Prime Day Deals on Monitors, Charging Accessories, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-prime-day-deals-on-monitors-charging-accessories-and-more.2431583/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M5 MacBook Models to Use New Compact Camera Module in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-camera-module-supplier-macbook-models-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m5-macbook-models-to-use-new-compact-camera-module-in-2025.2431570/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:58:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-camera-module-supplier-macbook-models-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in 2025 will take on a new compact camera module (CCM) supplier for future MacBook models powered by its next-generation M5 chip, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/New-MacBook-Pros-Launching-Tomorrow-With-These-4-New-Features-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921192" /><br/>
Writing in his latest investor note on <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/舜宇光學2025年營運動能可望顯著受益於成為apple新相機模組供應商與iphone訂單回流-sunny-opticals-2025-business-momentum-to-benefit-509819818c2a">Medium</a>, Kuo said Apple will turn to Sunny Optical for the CCM in its M5 MacBooks. The Chinese optical lens company will mass produce the CCMs in Vietnam, and provide a complete imaging system integrated into a compact form factor for the new laptops. <br/>
<br/>
The primary suppliers of camera modules for MacBooks are currently LG InnoTek and Sharp. In Apple's optical component supply chain, only Sunny Optical can simultaneously supply CCM and lenses in a single package, which gives the company the advantage of vertical integration. If shipments for the MacBooks go smoothly, Kuo predicts that Sunny Optical could also become the new CCM supplier for future iPhone and iPad models. <br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to update the 14-inch MacBook Pro with an M4 chip as soon as late 2024, and we could perhaps see a refresh before the end of the year. The high-end 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models are also expected to see a late 2024 refresh with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/">thinner version of the MacBook Pro</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. The ultrathin 2024 iPad Pro serves as a model for Apple's upcoming design philosophy, with the company planning to offer "the thinnest and lightest products" in each category across the tech industry. <br/>
<br/>
It's not clear when a thinner MacBook Pro might come out, since no design changes are rumored for the 2024 refresh, but it's possible that 2025 could be the year that Apple debuts redesigned laptops based on its M5 chip. Apple is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/07/25/face-id-for-mac-couple-of-years/">rumored</a> to be working on Face ID for the Mac, and it's likely that the MacBook Pro will be one of the first Macs to get Face ID, but there are no concrete details about when that might happen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-camera-module-supplier-macbook-models-2025/">M5 MacBook Models to Use New Compact Camera Module in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m5-macbook-models-to-use-new-compact-camera-module-in-2025.2431570/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Install the macOS Sequoia Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-macos-sequoia-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-install-the-macos-sequoia-public-beta.2431566/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:16:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-macos-sequoia-public-beta&#038;post_date=1721214995/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has made a macOS 15 Sequoia beta available for its public beta testing group, letting public beta testers try out the software before it launches this fall. Keep reading to learn whether you should install it on your Mac, and if so, how to go about it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-macOS-Sequoia-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954631" /><br/>
Signing up to get the macOS Sequoia beta is simple, and can be done by enrolling a Mac in Apple's free Apple Beta Software Program. The steps you need to complete to install the software on your device are provided towards the end of this article, but before you jump ahead, here are a few things worth considering.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Should I Install macOS Sequoia Public Beta?</h2><br/>
Before downloading the update, it's worth noting that Apple does not recommend installing the macOS Sequoia Beta on your main Mac, so if you have a secondary Mac that has no important data on it, use that. This is beta software, which means there are often bugs and issues that pop up that can prevent software from working properly or cause other problems. <br/>
<br/>
With that caveat in mind, the steps in the remainder of this article show you how to get the macOS 15 beta on your Mac. First though, check that you have a compatible Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will macOS Sequoia run on My Mac?</h2><br/>
macOS 15 Sequoia works with the same Macs as macOS 14 Sonoma other than the 2018 and 2019 MacBook Air. They include:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>MacBook Air (2020 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>MacBook Pro (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Mini (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac Pro (2017 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Pro (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Studio (2022 and later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can check your Mac's model by clicking the Apple in the menu bar and choosing About This Mac. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Don't Forget to Back Up Your Mac</h2><br/>
Be sure to back up your Mac using Time Machine before installing the software using the method, otherwise you won't be able to revert back to the previous version of macOS if things go wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Download macOS Sequoia Public Beta</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-beta-software-program.jpg" alt="" width="2774" height="1494" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958873" /><ol><br/>
 	<li>On your Mac, open up Safari and navigate to the <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple Beta Software Program website</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap the <strong>Sign up</strong> button and enter your Apple ID credentials, or sign in with your Apple ID if you've signed up to beta test a previous update.</li><br/>
 	<li>Agree to the Apple Beta Software Program terms and conditions if required.</li><br/>
 	<li>After signing in, you'll see a main screen that's a Guide for Public Betas. Click on <strong>macOS</strong>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Read through Apple's instructions carefully, and then using the link in the "Get Started" section, select <strong>enroll your Mac</strong>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Make sure to make a backup of your current version of macOS using Time Machine by following Apple's instructions. This will allow you to downgrade back to your earlier version of macOS if necessary and is crucial if you don't enjoy the macOS Sequoia testing experience.</li><br/>
<li>If your Mac is running macOS Ventura 13.4 or later, go to <strong>System Settings -> General -> Software Update</strong> and click the <strong>Info</strong> button next to "Beta updates." Then choose the macOS beta you'd like to install. If your Mac is running macOS Ventura 13.3 or earlier, download Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com/download/1016471">macOS Beta Access Utility</a> and run the installer. Then follow the onscreen instructions to complete installation. Note that your Mac must be signed in with the same Apple ID you used to enroll in the Apple Beta Software Program.</li></ol>Installation of the macOS beta is manually chosen in <strong>System Settings -> General -> Software Update</strong>. If a newly released beta is not available when you check, you will receive a notification when it is available to download.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>macOS Sequoia Features</h2><br/>
macOS Sequoia's standout feature is iPhone Mirroring, enabling you to control your iPhone from your Mac using your keyboard and mouse. This includes viewing notifications and using iPhone apps even when the device is tucked away and locked. Later this year, you'll also be able to drag and drop apps between your Mac and iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
Window tiling has been enhanced for easier management of multiple windows. Safari now offers webpage summaries and highlights, while the Messages app supports message scheduling and Tapback reactions with any emoji. A new Passwords app simplifies managing passwords, logins, and passkeys. The Photos app has a redesigned interface, and the Notes app now includes audio transcription and summarization, along with automatic equation solving.<br/>
<br/>
macOS Sequoia incorporates all new Apple Intelligence features coming to iOS 18, providing various quality of life improvements. These include writing tools for proofreading and polishing your text across apps, the Image Playground for creating unique images, and Genmoji for designing custom emojis. The Photos app features a Clean Up tool for removing unwanted images, and Siri has improved AI for better language understanding and contextual relevance, even consulting ChatGPT for complex queries.<br/>
<br/>
Additional features are also coming to macOS Sequoia. More details are available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-macos-sequoia-public-beta/">How to Install the macOS Sequoia Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-install-the-macos-sequoia-public-beta.2431566/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Passwords App: All the Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-passwords-app-all-the-features.2431538/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:23:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords&#038;post_date=1721183000/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple created a standalone Passwords app that streamlines login and password management. You've been able to store password information on your Apple devices through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain for years, but accessing passwords was a little difficult because the data was tucked away in the Settings app. That's no longer the case, and in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, it's much simpler to create and manage passwords for websites and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Passwords-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959050" /><br/>
This guide goes over everything you need to know about the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; Passwords app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="layout">Layout</h2><br/>
The Passwords app is installed automatically when upgrading to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>. The app has a simple layout with a search bar right at the top, so you can look up the information that you're looking for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959069" /><br/>
If you've already used the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain feature, all of your saved logins and passwords will be ready to go as soon as you authenticate with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>. There are separate sections for passwords and logins (under All), Passkeys, two-factor authentication codes, Wi-Fi passwords, security warnings, and logins that have been deleted.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957056" /><br/>
You can tap in to any of the sections to see what's listed there, and tapping on an individual entry shows the login and password. Each entry has fields for site or app name, username, login, verification code, websites where the login is used, and notes. There's also a one-tap option for changing your password for any given entry.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-app-wifi.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959075" /><br/>
The layout of the Passwords app is similar to what you see in the Passwords section of the Settings app in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="adding_logins_and_passwords">Adding Logins and Passwords</h2><br/>
To add a login or password to the Passwords app, it's as simple as tapping on the "+" button at the bottom of the main interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-add-password.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959071" /><br/>
The Passwords app populates a new entry with a password automatically, and you just need to add the website name and username, then copy the password and put it in the app, website, or service you're signing up for. Tapping on Save will save the information.<br/>
<br/>
If you want to add information to an existing entry, you can tap into the relevant section, such as All, search for the login you want to update, tap it, and then select the "Edit" option to get to the editing interface for adding notes, changing a password, or adding a verification code.<br/>
<br/>
Passwords and logins are added automatically to the Passwords app when you have &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain enabled and you create a new login in Safari or in an app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="changing_passwords">Changing Passwords</h2><br/>
To change a Password, you just need to open up the Passwords app, search for the login you want to update, tap on Edit, and then tap on the "Change Password..." option. You can also browse through Passwords using the "All" section.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping on Change Password opens up the website associated with the login and password, but you will need to initiate the password change process on the site by logging into your account and finding the appropriate option for updating a password.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="deleting_passwords">Deleting Passwords</h2><br/>
To delete a password, go to the "All" section and browse until you find it, or search for a specific login. From the "All" overview, you can swipe from right to left to bring up a delete option. Just tap on delete to remove the password.<br/>
<br/>
You can also tap into any of your logins, choose Edit, and select Delete Password from there. To delete multiple logins, tap on the Select tool at the top right of the display (it looks like a list with a checkmark) and then tap any of the logins you want to delete. When you're done, tap on Delete again to delete them all.<br/>
<br/>
Passwords that you have deleted are stored in a Deleted folder in the Passwords app for 30 days before they're permanently deleted. You can tap into that folder and swipe to delete logins and passwords right away. Alternatively, you can use the select button at the top to delete multiple logins at one time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="authentication_codes">Authentication Codes</h2><br/>
The Passwords app can provide two-factor authentication codes for sites that make additional security options available. To add a two-factor authentication code, tap on the "Codes" section of the main Passwords interface.<br/>
<br/>
From there, tap on the "+" button. You can either scan a QR code with a camera, which is a common way two-factor authentication apps work, or enter a setup key. Once the code is stored in the Passwords app, you can open up the Codes section at any time to get a temporary code to log in to a site or app.<br/>
<br/>
Two-factor authentication codes also show up when you search for a password and login or browse through logins in the "All" section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="passkeys">Passkeys</h2><br/>
Websites have started transitioning from passwords to passkeys, and the Passwords app stores your passkeys as well as your logins and passwords.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-passkey.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959070" /><br/>
Passkeys are more secure than passwords, and they let you log into your accounts using &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; authentication on an Apple device. Passkeys basically use a cryptographic key pair, with one public key stored on a server and a private key stored on your device.<br/>
<br/>
Private keys are not shared, they remain on-device only, and can't be sent to other people, protecting your accounts from phishing attempts.<br/>
<br/>
You can see your stored passkeys in the Passkeys section of the Passwords app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="password_sharing">Password Sharing</h2><br/>
The Passwords app lets you set up and share select passwords with trusted contacts. You can create one or more groups of people that include family and friends, providing them with access to shared logins and passwords.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-shared-groups.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959072" /><br/>
Creating a group can be done by tapping on the folder on the left hand side of the main Passwords interface. Type in a name, and then select people to add. Note that anyone you add needs to be in your contacts list.<br/>
<br/>
From there, you can select logins and passwords that you want to share. Logins and passwords can be removed at any time, and all members of a group can contribute logins. The group creator can remove people from the group at any time.<br/>
<br/>
To share a password with someone in person, you can search for the login that you want to share and then use the Share Sheet to open up an AirDrop interface that will let you AirDrop the login and password information. The Share Sheet is only designed for this kind of in-person sharing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="autofill">AutoFill</h2><br/>
If you have AutoFill enabled on your devices, your logins and passwords will be entered automatically when you visit a website in Safari that you have stored login information for. AutoFill will pop up an option for the appropriate login and password on any account login field in Safari or in an app.<br/>
<br/>
AutoFill works the same as it did when passwords were limited to the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="sorting">Sorting</h2><br/>
In the "All" section of the Passwords app, you can tap on the icon that features two arrows to get to sorting options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-password-app-sorting.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959073" /><br/>
Sorting options include Date Edited, Date Created, Website, or Title, and each of these can be displayed in a Descending or Ascending list by tapping on the desired option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="syncing">Syncing</h2><br/>
Passwords are synced automatically between all of your Apple devices using &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain. You just need to have the option turned on and you need to be logged in to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> on any device where you want to access your passwords.<br/>
<br/>
You can even get to your logins and passwords on a Windows PC because Apple is adding the Passwords app to iTunes for Windows.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="security">Security</h2><br/>
There is a dedicated Security section in the Passwords app, and it lets you know if you have a password that is reused, too weak, or has been compromised in a data leak.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-app-security.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1289" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959074" /><br/>
Warnings are accompanied by information letting you know that a password change is in order, and you can tap on the Change Password option to go to the website where you need to update your information.<br/>
<br/>
For any individual login, you'll also see information letting you know if your password is weak or strong.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="importing_passwords">Importing Passwords</h2><br/>
Apple plans to provide a tool for importing passwords from other services like 1Password and LastPass, but as of now, this functionality has not yet been implemented.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For more on the new features that Apple is adding in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">we have a dedicated iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/">iOS 18 Passwords App: All the Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-passwords-app-all-the-features.2431538/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
