<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:01:24 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Could Feature Advanced Camera Sensor From Samsung</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-could-feature-samsung-advanced-sensor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-could-feature-advanced-camera-sensor-from-samsung.2430541/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 08:35:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-could-feature-samsung-advanced-sensor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is testing advanced CMOS image sensors (CIS) from Samsung that could debut in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> later this year, <a href="https://www.thelec.net/news/articleView.html?idxno=4899"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/iphone_12_pro_sensor_shift.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1118" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-764639" /><br/>
Apple is currently conducting a final quality assessment on CMOS image sensors provided by Samsung System LSI, the logic business unit of Samsung, according to the report. These sensors are slated for use in the main camera of the upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;. Historically, Apple has exclusively sourced CIS for its iPhones from Sony, but recent developments are said to indicate a strategic pivot away from the Japanese supplier due to concerns about reliability and the need to incorporate new technologies into its camera system.<br/>
<br/>
The decision to engage Samsung is said to stem from issues Apple faced with Sony last year. Apple requested that Samsung begin the development of new image sensors in 2023 after Sony failed to deliver them in a sufficiently timely manner, which contributed to difficulties in setting a launch date for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>. If Samsung passes the ongoing quality tests, it will be the first time the company supplies an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> CIS. <br/>
<br/>
The new image sensor developed by Samsung features a more advanced three-wafer stack design. These three wafers each house distinct elements: the photodiode, transistors, and analog digital converter logics. In contrast, current and previous &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; image sensors have a two-stack design that combines the photodiode and transistors on a single wafer.<br/>
<br/>
In a CIS, the photodiode converts light into electrical signals, while four transistors are responsible for transferring, amplifying, reading, and erasing these signals. The separation of these components into three wafers allows for higher pixel density, reduced noise, and smaller pixel sizes.<br/>
<br/>
The new technology employs wafer-to-wafer hybrid bonding, which attaches these wafers directly through a copper pad, eliminating the need for signal-transferring bumps. This enables the CIS to be smaller and increases data transfer speeds. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is widely expected to be announced in the fall with new camera features such as a dedicated "Capture" button, a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-could-feature-samsung-advanced-sensor/">iPhone 16 Could Feature Advanced Camera Sensor From Samsung</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-could-feature-advanced-camera-sensor-from-samsung.2430541/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 3: Everything We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know-so-far.2430530/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:14:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know&#038;post_date=1719936885/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Ultra 3, likely to be released in September 2024 alongside the iPhone 16, is expected to offer fewer upgrades compared to its predecessor, the Apple Watch Ultra 2. Keep reading to learn what the rumored changes are.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-blorange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911679" /><br/>
When Apple Watch Ultra 2 debuted last year, key new features included a 50% brighter display, a faster S9 chip, a "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watch without touching the screen, on-device Siri, and increased internal storage. Unfortunately, the next version of the device is unlikely to reach those lofty heights. Here's what the rumors say.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="display_technology">Display Technology</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-night-mode.jpg" alt="" width="1598" height="953" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866222" /><br/>
Initially, it was believed that Apple was working on an Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display, which would provide increased brightness, better contrast, and improved battery efficiency. However, these plans appear to have been postponed indefinitely. Apple worked on microLED display technology for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-still-dedicated-microled-apple-watch-ultra/">several years</a>, but the project was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">scrapped in 2024</a> and there are no current plans for a microLED Apple Watch in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
On the flip side, Apple is rumored to be adopting new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/09/2024-apple-watch-more-power-efficient-display/">low-energy OLED panel technology</a> in new Apple Watch models to further reduce the power consumption of its always-on display. If that's the case, it's unlikely that Apple would use the technology in its latest Series model without also bringing it to its latest Apple Watch Ultra model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-Orange-Alpine-Loop-Action-button-220907_big.jpg.large_.jpg" alt="" width="980" height="402" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862625" /><br/>
The design of the Apple Watch Ultra 3 is likely to remain largely unchanged. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4">recently said</a> that this year's third-generation Apple Watch Ultra will have "roughly the same look as the original." He has previously suggested a totally redesigned "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>" with a thinner case and magnetic bands is coming, but this is likely to be a different model to the Ultra, and he said it would be released "in 2024 or 2025."<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_features">New Features</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-sandy.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864665" /><br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 is likely to include improved health tracking capabilities such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/2024-apple-watch-blood-pressure-sleep-apnea/">blood pressure monitoring and sleep apnea detection</a>, aligning with the rumored features of the Apple Watch Series 10 / X. <br/>
<br/>
The blood pressure monitoring featuring will let users know if their blood pressure is trending upward, and will provide an option for users to note what they were doing when hypertension occurred. Specific blood pressure numbers will not be provided, though. Meanwhile, sleep apnea detection will use sleep history and breathing patterns to estimate whether someone suffers from sleep apnea, with the watch suggesting that users contact a doctor if so.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hardware_updates">Hardware Updates</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-1-1.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866346" /><br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 is expected to have "almost no" new hardware upgrades compared to the Apple Watch Ultra 2, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/kuo-on-apple-watch-ultra-3-hardware/">Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. His phrasing suggests that the rumored blood pressure and sleep apnea detection features will be machine learning / software-based, relying on existing sensors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="colors">Colors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/Apple-Watch-Ultra-Black-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905396" /><br/>
Apple currently offers the Apple Watch Ultra 2, released in September 2023, in the same natural titanium color as the first-generation model. Prior to launch of the second-generation model, some rumors suggested Apple could release a new darker color option. It didn't happen.<br/>
<br/>
However, we know that Apple originally designed a first-generation Apple Watch Ultra with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-apple-watch-ultra-black-prototype-images/">dark ceramic back</a> that was never launched. Moreover, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman in 2023 said it was "theoretically" possible the finish could be released for a later model. Previously, the high-end Edition model of the Apple Watch Series 7 was available with a Space Black titanium case.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="watchos_11">watchOS 11</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Thumb-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955941" /><br/>
One thing we can be sure of is that Apple Watch Ultra 3 will run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, the latest version of the Apple Watch operating system. Apple previewed the software during WWDC in June, and users can expect a range of updates and improvements, such as additional Smart Stack widgets, Check In for Messages and workouts, a Vitals app to view key health metrics, a Translate app, a new Apple Pay feature called Tap to Cash, training load for workouts, additional workout types, more customizable Activity rings, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know/">Apple Watch Ultra 3: Everything We Know So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-3-everything-we-know-so-far.2430530/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are the macOS Sequoia Features Intel Macs Won&#039;t Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support.2430519/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:24:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When Apple released macOS Monterey in 2021, some key features required a Mac with Apple silicon. The same scenario played out with macOS Ventura in 2022, and then again the following year with the release of macOS Sonoma. With macOS Sequoia set to arrive in the fall, which new features can Intel Mac owners expect to be unavailable to them this time around?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-macOS-Sequoia-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954631" /><br/>
Apple says that macOS Sequoia is compatible with the same Macs as macOS Sonoma, but Apple's fine print reveals that certain new features won't work on Intel machines. If you're still on an Intel Mac, here's what you won't have access to.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954498" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence</a>, a deeply integrated, personalized AI feature set for Apple devices that uses cutting-edge generative artificial intelligence to enhance the user experience, won't be available on Intel Macs. Apple says the advanced features require its M1 chip or later, so if your Mac was released before November 2020, you're out of luck.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-siri-improvements-coming-2025/">These Apple Intelligence Features Won't Be Ready Until 2025</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Live Audio Transcription</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-notes-live-audio-transcription.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957406" /><br/>
Live audio transcription lets you record audio sessions within notes in Apple Notes, and generate live audio transcriptions that can be searched through or combined with other documents, checklists, or documents. According to Apple, support for live audio transcription in the Notes app is limited to machines powered by Apple silicon. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>What Else?</h2><br/>
Surprisingly, nothing! Apple is not withholding any other new features in macOS Sequoia, meaning users with supported Intel Macs will be able to enjoy things like the ability to schedule messages to send later, Reminder integration with Calendars, a new standalone Passwords app, window tiling, and more. Even Apple's latest continuity feature, iPhone Mirroring, works on Intel-based Mac computers that have a T2 Security Chip. For all the details, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS 15 roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
On that note, let's review which Mac models that macOS Sequoia supports. As mentioned above, macOS 15 works with the same Macs as macOS Sonoma. They include:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>MacBook Air (2020 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>MacBook Pro (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Mini (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac Pro (2017 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Pro (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Studio (2022 and later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can check your Mac's model by clicking the Apple in the menu bar and choosing About This Mac. macOS Sequoia is currently in developer beta, with a public beta expected later this month, before Apple's latest Mac software gets a general release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support/">Here Are the macOS Sequoia Features Intel Macs Won&#039;t Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-macos-sequoia-features-intel-macs-wont-support.2430519/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Boosts A18 Chip Orders in Anticipation of High iPhone 16 Demand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-increases-a18-chip-orders-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-boosts-a18-chip-orders-in-anticipation-of-high-iphone-16-demand.2430516/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:03:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-increases-a18-chip-orders-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is said to have upped its order of next-generation chips from TSMC to between 90 million and 100 million units, following heightened demand expectations for its iPhone 16 series. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Update-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953750" /><br/>
Last year's initial chip order volume for the iPhone 15 series launch is believed to have been in the region of 80-90 million units, suggesting Apple is anticipating higher demand for its 2024 devices in the region of 10 million units, according to Taiwanese outlet <em><a href="https://www.ctee.com.tw/news/20240701700050-430501">CTEE</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
The arrival of Apple Intelligence in iOS 18 is expected to boost initial sales of the devices. One of the reasons is that Apple Intelligence requires at least an iPhone 15 Pro to run, which means owners of last year's iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus will miss out on Apple's new AI features unless they upgrade to an iPhone 15 Pro or plump for one of the iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus were equipped with the A16 Bionic chip – the same chip that was in the iPhone 14 Pro models – whereas the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max featured an A17 Pro chip manufactured using TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, also known as "N3E." N3E is less expensive and has improved yield compared to the previous-generation N3B, according to TSMC.<br/>
<br/>
This year, all four models in the iPhone 16 lineup are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/iphone-16-jump-from-a16-to-a18-chip-rumor/">expected to use A18-branded chips</a> manufactured using the N3E process. Despite switching to N3E, the A18 chip in the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus is likely to adopt the A17 Pro design that was used in the iPhone 15 Pro models. Meanwhile, the iPhone 16 Pro and ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max will likely use a chip branded as an "A18 Pro," which could feature an upgraded Neural Engine with more cores enabling improved AI/machine learning performance. <br/>
<br/>
The standard iPhone 16 models could also be upgraded with 8GB of RAM, up from 6GB in the iPhone 15 models. That would see all four iPhone 16 models offering 8GB of RAM, which Apple has suggested is a minimum requirement for running large-language models (the algorithms that power AI) locally on device, rather than in the cloud.<br/>
<br/>
Based on previous years, Apple is expected to release the iPhone 16 series in the fall, around mid-September. For more information, be sure to check our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> roundups.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-increases-a18-chip-orders-iphone-16/">Apple Boosts A18 Chip Orders in Anticipation of High iPhone 16 Demand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-boosts-a18-chip-orders-in-anticipation-of-high-iphone-16-demand.2430516/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Owners With Faulty Butterfly Keyboards to Get Payouts Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard-payout/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-owners-with-faulty-butterfly-keyboards-to-get-payouts-soon.2430485/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:09:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard-payout/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Butterfly Keyboard Issues</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Two years after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/19/apple-butterfly-keyboard-lawsuit-settlement/">paid &#36;50 million to settle a class-action lawsuit</a> over faulty MacBook butterfly keyboards, funds from the settlement will be going out to affected customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-790219" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1955" height="1100" /><br/>
An update on the <a href="https://www.keyboardsettlement.com">MacBook Keyboard Litigation Settlement website</a> says that the court issued a payment order on June 27, 2024, with payments set to be issued for approved claims by August 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Emails about the lawsuit were sent out in December 2022 to MacBook owners eligible for a payment. MacBook owners who had at least two topcase replacements from Apple within four years of purchase are set to receive a maximum of &#36;395, while customers who had one topcase repair will receive up to &#36;125. Those who had keycap replacements are eligible for up to &#36;50.<br/>
<br/>
Claims were accepted through March 6, 2023, and the settlement was ultimately approved on May 25, 2023. There is no word on why there has been more than a year's delay getting payments sent out to customers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple used butterfly keyboards in Macs between 2015 and 2019, and while the design was updated several times during that four-year period, the butterfly mechanism was prone to failure. Thousands of customers had issues with repeating keys, sticking keys, and keyboard failures due to crumbs, dust, and other issues.<br/>
<br/>
Apple launched <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/06/22/apple-macbook-pro-keyboard-repair-program/">a repair program</a> in June 2018 covering the MacBook, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, and MacBook Pro models manufactured from 2015 on, but it only covered machines for four years after purchase and because butterfly keyboards were replaced with another butterfly keyboard, no permanent fix was available.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the major failure of the butterfly keyboard, Apple swapped back to a scissor switch mechanism. Macs manufactured since late 2019 have had the much more reliable scissor switch keyboard that is able to stand up to wear and tear.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/butterfly-keyboard-issues/">Butterfly Keyboard Issues</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/macbook-pro-butterfly-keyboard-payout/">MacBook Owners With Faulty Butterfly Keyboards to Get Payouts Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-owners-with-faulty-butterfly-keyboards-to-get-payouts-soon.2430485/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers.2430470/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:13:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 update to developers, with the second software coming two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-1/">released the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/macOS-Sonoma-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-957372" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what might be included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.6, and no new features were discovered in the first beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers.2430470/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers.2430465/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:08:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the second betas coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-1-to-developers/">first iOS and iPadOS 17.6 betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The features Apple promised for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no major new additions were discovered in the first beta.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers.2430465/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2430467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.3 update to developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The second &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 beta comes over two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may make further improvements to Personas, EyeSight, and other features with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3, as well as implement additional bug fixes. No new features were found in the first &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Releases Second Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2430467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2430466/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:03:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.6 update to developers for testing purposes, with the second beta coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-1-to-developers/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.6 update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.6 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what's included in watchOS 10.6, and with Apple's focus shifting to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, it likely features bug fixes and other minor improvements. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2430466/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers.2430468/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 10:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.6 to developers for testing purposes, with the second beta coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.6 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.6.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers.2430468/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone and Apple Watch Likely to Support NFC Multi-Purpose Tap in the Future</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-and-apple-watch-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap-in-the-future.2430457/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:43:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>NFC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhones and Apple Watches could support multiple actions via NFC simultaneously in the future, the NFC Forum today suggested.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/apple-card-via-apple-pay.jpeg" alt="" width="1524" height="909" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-843215" /><br/>
The NFC Forum, the leading standards body for Near Field Communication (NFC) technology, <a href="https://nfc-forum.org/news/2024-07-nfc-forum-defines-next-generation-of-contactless-user-experience-with-multi-purpose-tap/">today published</a> its first overview of NFC Multi-Purpose Tap. The technology, which supports multiple actions with one tap, is designed to bring more convenience to various NFC use cases such as point-to-point receipt delivery, loyalty programs, identification, and total-journey transit ticketing.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is a prominent member of the NFC Forum and likely contributed to the development of the technology. The company first introduced NFC in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6 and original Apple Watch, initially focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, allowing users to make contactless payments. <br/>
<br/>
NFC Multi-Purpose Tap would allow &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to perform multiple transactions with a single tap. For instance, consumers could make payments, log loyalty points, and receive receipts instantaneously. The potential applications are considerable, from retail payments to public transportation, where users could tap their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to pay for a journey, apply discounts, and get travel receipts all at once.<br/>
<br/>
Since Apple is a member of the NFC Forum, it seems highly likely that NFC Multi-Purpose Tap will come to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch at some point in the future. The company often adds support for new NFC functionalities, such as reading NFC tags and facilitating more interactions with a broader range of NFC devices. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nfc/">NFC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/">iPhone and Apple Watch Likely to Support NFC Multi-Purpose Tap in the Future</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-and-apple-watch-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap-in-the-future.2430457/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reclassifies iPhone X, HomePod, and Original AirPods as &#039;Vintage&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reclassifies-iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-as-vintage.2430454/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:52:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>iPhone X</category>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today reclassified the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> X, first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, and first-generation AirPods as "vintage" products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/homepod-feature-blue2.jpg" alt="" width="2144" height="1206" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-788875" /><br/>
The products appeared on Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage and obsolete products list</a> earlier today. Products are considered vintage when Apple stopped distributing them for sale more than five and less than seven years ago. Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers continue to offer repairs for vintage products for up to two more years, subject to parts availability.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X, announced on September 12, 2017 and released on November 3, 2017, represented a significant leap forward in Apple's smartphone design and feature-set. Marking the 10th anniversary of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it introduced several significant changes such as the removal of the home button, allowing for an edge-to-edge 5.8-inch Super Retina OLED display. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, a facial recognition system, replaced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> for authentication, utilizing a TrueDepth camera system in a "notch" that also enabled Animojis. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X was powered by the A11 Bionic chip, featuring the company's first dedicated Neural Engine for enhanced machine learning capabilities, and it supported wireless charging for the first time. Its stainless steel frame and glass back design marked a return to a more premium aesthetic.<br/>
<br/>
The original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was announced on June 5, 2017, at the Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) and released on February 9, 2018. Initially priced at &#36;349, the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was designed to deliver high-quality audio and integrate closely with Apple's ecosystem, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>. It featured a custom-engineered high-excursion woofer and an array of seven beamforming tweeters. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was powered by the Apple A8 chip, enabling real-time acoustic modeling, audio beamforming, and multi-channel echo cancellation. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> came built-in, allowing users to control music playback, manage smart home devices, and access information and services via voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced the original AirPods on September 7, 2016 and officially released them on December 13, 2016, with a retail price of &#36;159. The wireless earbuds were groundbreaking due to their seamless integration with Apple's ecosystem, facilitated by the custom-designed W1 chip. The chip enabled effortless pairing with Apple devices, long battery life, and efficient wireless connectivity. The AirPods also featured optical sensors and motion accelerometers, allowing them to detect when they were in the user's ears, automatically pausing playback when removed. Their unusual, compact design, combined with the convenience of a portable charging case, set a new standard for wireless earphones, making them highly popular and influential in the audio accessory market.<br/>
<br/>
Sometime after becoming "vintage," an Apple product will be reclassified as "obsolete." Apple says it considers a product obsolete once seven years have passed since the company last distributed it for sale. When this happens, Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers no longer offer repairs or other hardware service for it. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/">Apple Reclassifies iPhone X, HomePod, and Original AirPods as &#039;Vintage&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reclassifies-iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-as-vintage.2430454/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fortnite and Epic Games Store Submitted to Apple for iOS Launch in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-and-epic-games-store-submitted-to-apple-for-ios-launch-in-eu.2430446/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 05:37:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Epic Games says it has <a href="https://x.com/epicnewsroom/status/1806819627181219995">submitted</a> the Epic Games Store to Apple for notarization under Apple's alternative app marketplace policy in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite-apple-logo-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-756080" /><br/>
The ‌Epic Games‌ Store will include popular game Fortnite, which means ‌iPhone‌ users in the EU will be able to install and play the title without having to use a cloud gaming service. Epic said it was "targeting the next couple months for the store and Fortnite on iOS in the EU." An ‌iPad‌ version of Fortnite is expected to follow this year.<br/>
<br/>
Fortnite has been banned from the iOS App Store for the last several years due to the legal dispute between Apple and ‌Epic Games‌. An avenue for its return was only made possible after Apple made it possible for iPhone‌ users in the EU to download apps from alternative app marketplaces rather than the App Store, as well as directly from developer websites.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is charging a 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee per year for apps installed outside of the ‌App Store‌ (and in the ‌App Store‌ for developers who opt in to the new terms and also still choose to use Apple's system), but there are no ‌App Store‌ commissions or in-app fees. While Apple is waiving fees for the first one million installs, the 0.50 per user fee will cost app developers like ‌Epic Games‌ a notable amount of money, especially given that Epic will often be charged twice – once for its app marketplace and once again for every Fortnite install. <br/>
<br/>
Epic CEO Tim Sweeney has been critical of Apple's App Store changes to bring its policies in line with the Digital Markets Act (DMA). Sweeney has <a href="https://x.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1750589570880516402">described</a> the changes as a "devious new instance of malicious compliance," and called Apple's charges "junk fees." The European Commission last week formally announced its preliminary view that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">Apple's App Store policies are in breach of the DMA</a>. The Commission also said it would open a new non-compliance procedure against Apple over concerns that its contractual requirements for third-party app developers and app marketplaces, including its Core Technology Fee, "fall short of ensuring effective compliance with Apple's obligations under the DMA."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/">Fortnite and Epic Games Store Submitted to Apple for iOS Launch in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-and-epic-games-store-submitted-to-apple-for-ios-launch-in-eu.2430446/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google to Unveil Pixel 9 Phones Next Month Ahead of iPhone 16 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-august/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-next-month-ahead-of-iphone-16-launch.2430443/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 04:41:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-august/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google will refresh its product lineup this year in the middle of August rather than its usual October timing, which means its latest flagship Pixel smartphones will debut ahead of Apple's annual iPhone upgrade cycle for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/google-pixel-announcements.jpg" alt="" width="2060" height="1159" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915310" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Google Pixel 8 series</em></div><br/>
Google last week began sending out media invitations to an August 13 hardware event that will "showcase the base of Google AI, Android software and the Pixel portfolio of devices." Google typically holds its annual Made by Google event in early October to unveil its latest Pixel phones, smartwatches, and Nest-branded devices. <br/>
<br/>
Rumors indicate Google will launch three devices in its forthcoming Pixel 9 lineup, with a new larger 6.2-inch Pixel 9 Pro XL device joining the regular Pixel 9 and Pixel 9 Pro. Leaks suggest the Pixel 9 Pro will have a triple rear camera setup. Google is also expected to launch Android 15 touting Gemini AI enhancements and other services. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Get ready for magic at <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MadeByGoogle?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#MadeByGoogle</a> <br><br>Learn more and sign up for updates: <a href="https://t.co/ZnBcg6S6vK">https://t.co/ZnBcg6S6vK</a> <a href="https://t.co/C6Of1L9g4a">pic.twitter.com/C6Of1L9g4a</a></p>&mdash; Made by Google (@madebygoogle) <a href="https://twitter.com/madebygoogle/status/1805713788416434332?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Alongside new phones, Google is expected to release a Pixel Fold 2 tablet, a Pixel Watch 3 series, and new Pixel earbuds, all of which will compete with Apple devices. The decision to bring forward the hardware upgrades was likely made with one eye on Apple's hardware launches in September, when the iPhone 16 and Apple Watch Series 9 are expected to be revealed alongside iOS 18 with Apple Intelligence.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-august/">Google to Unveil Pixel 9 Phones Next Month Ahead of iPhone 16 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-next-month-ahead-of-iphone-16-launch.2430443/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some Apple Intelligence Features Likely to Require Paid Subscription</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-intelligence-features-likely-paid-sub/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-intelligence-features-likely-to-require-paid-subscription.2430439/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:51:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-intelligence-features-likely-paid-sub/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple eventually plans to turn some of its artificial intelligence features into paid services, similar to iCloud+ subscriptions, according to <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
Writing in his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman said that while Apple Intelligence will be free to start, Apple's long-term plan is to launch something like "Apple Intelligence+," with extra features that users pay monthly fees to access.<br/>
<br/>
Making its own AI features another services revenue stream should allow Apple to compensate for the slowing pace of hardware upgrades and make the company less reliant on hardware tweaks to drive its business, argues Gurman. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is also expected to receive a cut of revenue whenever a user signs up to features offered by its AI partners, such as ChatGPT provided by OpenAI. Gurman says he expects Apple to agree a deal with Google and Anthropic to offer their AI services through its devices, with the former expected to be announced when Apple Intelligence launches in the fall as part of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> previously reported that Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-meta-ai-privacy-concerns/">turned down</a> an AI partnership with Facebook parent company Meta due to privacy concerns. Meanwhile, Apple is said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-ai-partner-china/">seeking partnerships for the Chinese market</a>, where ChatGPT and other similar AI services are not available. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-intelligence-features-likely-paid-sub/">Some Apple Intelligence Features Likely to Require Paid Subscription</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-intelligence-features-likely-to-require-paid-subscription.2430439/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Models to Adopt &#039;M14&#039; Advanced Samsung OLED Panels for Improved Brightness and Lifespan</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-16-pro-max-advanced-oled-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-adopt-m14-advanced-samsung-oled-panels-for-improved-brightness-and-lifespan.2430434/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:52:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-16-pro-max-advanced-oled-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be the first Apple smartphones to adopt Samsung's high performance "M14" OLED display panel, claims a new report coming out of South Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Update-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953750" /><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.etnews.com/20240628000294">ETNews</a></em>, Samsung's "M" series of OLED panels are made for flagship smartphones, while "14" refers to the number of high-performance materials used to produce them. "M14" is the first series of its kind, and the panel is said to have been developed to deliver superior brightness and longevity.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung has reportedly placed orders for the M14 materials and is preparing to mass produce the displays in the second half of the year for Apple's iPhone 16 Pro models. Google's Pixel 9 smartphone is the only other device that is expected to adopt the high-performance displays in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
A previous report out of China <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/iphone-16-pro-brighter-display/">claimed</a> that this year's ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ models will feature up to 1,200 nits of typical SDR brightness – a 20% increase over the current models – so Samsung's new panel could be the reason for the expected improvement. That said, peak HDR brightness is expected to remain at 1,600 nits, the same as the current iPhone 15 Pro Display.<br/>
<br/>
Another rumor last year suggested that all iPhone 16 models will adopt new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">micro-lens OLED display technology</a> for improved brightness and reduced power consumption, although it's not clear if this is related to M14 panels specifically.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">larger display sizes</a> than the iPhone 15 Pro models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/iphone-16-display-sizes/">according to multiple sources</a>. The iPhone 16 Pro will have a display that's 6.27 inches in size (rounded to 6.3), while the iPhone 16 Pro Max is expected to have a display that's 6.85 inches in size (rounded to 6.9). <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/iphone-16-pro-max-biggest-rumored-features/">5 Biggest Changes Rumored for iPhone 16 Pro Max</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple is expected to launch the iPhone 16 series in the fall, or around mid-September going on previous years.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-16-pro-max-advanced-oled-display/">iPhone 16 Pro Models to Adopt &#039;M14&#039; Advanced Samsung OLED Panels for Improved Brightness and Lifespan</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-adopt-m14-advanced-samsung-oled-panels-for-improved-brightness-and-lifespan.2430434/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Likely Planning to Use Bigger, Lower Resolution Displays for Cheaper Vision Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-use-bigger-lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-vision-headset.2430415/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:41:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is exploring new suppliers for OLED-on-Silicon panels, likely signaling the development of a more affordable headset destined to sit alongside the Vision Pro, <a href="http://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=28806"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-lenses.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898584" /><br/>
The Korean website has apparently detected a shift in Apple's supply chain management for OLED-on-Silicon (OLEDoS) panels, a key component in the Vision Pro headset. Currently, Sony provides these high-resolution microdisplays, but its limited production capacity of up to 900,000 panels per year and lack of expansion plans have prompted Apple to seek alternatives for the future. Apple has apparently issued a request for information (RFI) to Samsung Display and LG Display to evaluate their capabilities in producing larger OLEDoS panels, ranging from 2.0 to 2.1 inches in size with a display density of around 1,700 pixels per inch (PPI).<br/>
<br/>
These displays would be larger than those currently used in the Vision Pro and feature a lower resolution. The Vision Pro uses Sony's OLEDoS panels featuring a 1.42-inch screen with a pixel density of nearly 3,400 PPI, employing a white OLED display with color filter (wOLED+CF) technology. This sophisticated display technology is one of the main reasons for the headset's high price point.<br/>
<br/>
At Displayweek 2024, both Samsung and LG showcased advancements in OLED microdisplay technology that could appeal to Apple. Samsung presented a 1.03-inch RGB (direct-emission) OLED microdisplay, developed in collaboration with eMagin, which promises higher brightness levels compared to the wOLED+CF method. Meanwhile, LG revealed a 10,000 nits 1.3-inch 4K OLED microdisplay, utilizing a micro lens array (MLA) to boost brightness by around 40 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's interest in larger OLEDoS panels with lower resolution than those used in the Vision Pro suggests these could be intended for a new, lower-cost mixed reality headset. Apple has been rumored to be working on such a device for over a year, and the latest indications suggest that it may be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/cheaper-apple-vision-pro-tethered-iphone-mac/">designed to tether to an iPhone or Mac</a> to eliminate the need for a costly processor. The lower-cost Apple Vision headset could launch as soon as the end of next year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-headset/">Apple Likely Planning to Use Bigger, Lower Resolution Displays for Cheaper Vision Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-use-bigger-lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-vision-headset.2430415/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Starts Work on iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/apple-starts-work-on-ios-19-and-macos-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-starts-work-on-ios-19-macos-16-watchos-12-and-visionos-3.2430409/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:01:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/apple-starts-work-on-ios-19-and-macos-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has already begun work on the iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 3 software updates for next year, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/aapl-logo-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="890" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-776656" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined">most recent</a> "Power On" newsletter, Gurman said that Apple has formally begun development of its major operating systems for 2025 with the codenames "Luck" for iOS 19, "Cheer" for macOS 16, "Nepali" for watchOS 12, and "Discovery" for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 3.<br/>
<br/>
While <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, macOS 15 Sequoia, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> have not yet been released to the public, the initiation of work on the next major software updates for Apple's major devices is in line with its normal schedule. This is partly due to the fact that hardware products destined for launch next year require software for testing purposes, but it is currently too early to know what sort of features the new operating systems will offer.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also said that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/">Vision Pro headset should gain Apple Intelligence</a> as soon as next year, so this could make sense for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 3. Meanwhile, the public beta versions of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, macOS 15 Sequoia, &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, and &zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; should arrive next month ahead of official release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/apple-starts-work-on-ios-19-and-macos-16/">Apple Reportedly Starts Work on iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-starts-work-on-ios-19-macos-16-watchos-12-and-visionos-3.2430409/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPhone Battery Should Be Up to 10% Denser for Longer Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-iphone-battery-denser-for-longer-life/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-battery-should-be-up-to-10-denser-for-longer-life.2430407/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:48:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-iphone-battery-denser-for-longer-life/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> battery with a metal casing should allow for higher energy density to deliver longer battery life, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> claims. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-battery-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1333" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-923492" /><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/"><em>Alleged iPhone 16 Pro battery</a> with new metal casing.</em></div><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1807432542934732953">post on X</a> (formerly Twitter), Kuo said that Apple's adoption of a stainless steel casing for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery will allow for five to 10 percent higher cell density while remaining within safety limits, as well as meeting the requirements of new EU regulations. Alleged images of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">iPhone 16 Pro battery with a metal casing</a> leaked in late 2023 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/"><em>The Information</em></a> has since detailed Apple's work to simplify &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery replacement starting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<br/>
New EU law requires smartphone manufacturers to ensure batteries can be replaced by owners using easily accessible tools by 2025. Apple plans to achieve this with the use of electrically induced adhesive debonding technology, allowing users to apply a low voltage of electricity to quickly dislodge the battery instead of finicky adhesive strips. This new battery replacement method is anticipated to debut in at least one &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model later this year and could extend to all versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> next year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-iphone-battery-denser-for-longer-life/">New iPhone Battery Should Be Up to 10% Denser for Longer Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-battery-should-be-up-to-10-denser-for-longer-life.2430407/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple Intelligence Coming to Vision Pro, but Not HomePod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro-but-not-homepod.2430404/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:17:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has no plans to bring Apple Intelligence to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, but it should arrive on the Vision Pro headset in the future, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined">latest edition</a> of his "Power On" newsletter, Gurman said that Apple is preparing to bring Apple Intelligence to its Vision Pro headset, but not this year. The device has sufficient memory to run on-device Apple Intelligence features such as notification summaries, writing tools, and an updated version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. Apple's user interface design team apparently needs to ensure that Apple Intelligence looks appropriate in a mixed-reality environment. The company also needs to guarantee that it has sufficient cloud-computing capacity to support more devices.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman does not expect the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; to offer Apple Intelligence, instead focusing on "an entirely new robotic device with a display that includes Apple Intelligence at its core." Apple Intelligence requires a minimum of eight gigabytes of memory, but the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> only feature a single gigabyte of memory. The current &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; is said to be "too low-volume a product to waste the engineering time" bringing Apple Intelligence to the device.<br/>
<br/>
Going forward, Gurman believes that Apple Intelligence will become increasingly critical to Apple devices and form a pillar of its business. Apple Intelligence should get updated more frequently than services like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>, at least as often as the company's hardware and software offerings. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/">Gurman: Apple Intelligence Coming to Vision Pro, but Not HomePod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro-but-not-homepod.2430404/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
