<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 03:02:45 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Is Now the Time to Upgrade Apple Devices Before Tariffs Lead to Price Increases?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-upgrades-tariff-impact/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/is-now-the-time-to-upgrade-apple-devices-before-tariffs-lead-to-price-increases.2454727/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:41:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-upgrades-tariff-impact/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you have an older Apple device that you've been considering upgrading, you're probably wondering how the newly announced tariffs might impact prices going forward, and whether it's worth buying now before there's a price hike.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-colors-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964753" /><br/>
Given analyst and economist responses to the tariffs, market panic, and Trump's stance on the current financial chaos, the answer is that making a purchase immediately might save you some cash if things don't change.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhones Could Get Much More Expensive</h2><br/>
Trump announced a 34 percent tariff on China, which combines with the previous 20 percent tariff for a total of a 54 percent tax on imports from China. China is still one of Apple's major suppliers, and industry analysts consulted by <em>Reuters</em> suggest that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> prices <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/2300-dollar-iphone/">could increase by up to 43 percent</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, the most affordable current-generation &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a>, is priced starting at &#36;599. If Apple doesn't receive some kind of exemption or if tariffs don't change, the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; could be priced starting at &#36;856. The &#36;799 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> could cost &#36;1,142, close to the starting price of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max.<br/>
<br/>
Equity research company Rosenblatt Securities believes Apple will need to raise &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch prices 43 percent to cover tariffs, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> prices 42 percent, and Mac and AirPod prices 39 percent. Counterpoint Research co-founder Neil Shah believes Apple would need to raise prices by at least 30 percent on average to offset the tariffs.<br/>
<br/>
Morgan Stanley analyst Erik Woodring told <em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/03/trump-tariffs-will-impact-apples-non-china-supply-chains.html">CNBC</a></em> that Apple would likely need to raise prices by 17 to 18 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has moved some of its production to other countries like Vietnam, India, Thailand, and Malaysia, but all of those locations <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-stock-trump-tariffs/">are subject to tariffs as well</a>. A 40 percent+ price increase is a worst case scenario, and there are a lot of variables at play and factors that could shift in the near future, but it doesn't look like prices are going to remain static.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Could Apple Absorb the Increase?</h2><br/>
Trump said that he would implement tariffs, and tech companies like Apple knew that this was coming. It's likely that Apple has been ramping up U.S. supply of current devices so that it can temporarily avoid raising prices. Under the terms of the tariff executive order, Apple won't have to pay tariffs for goods that are on a vessel and in transit to their destination before 12:01 a.m. Eastern Time on April 9, so the company has a few more days to stock up as much as possible.<br/>
<br/>
When available stock in the United States starts dwindling, Apple will have hard decisions to make. Raising prices significantly will impact demand for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in a market where people are already wary of spending because of economic uncertainty, but such high tariffs would significantly eat into Apple's profit margin and further tank its stock.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could have enough &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models in the U.S. already to avoid price increases until the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> models launch, but it is hard to imagine a scenario where &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; prices don't go up at least somewhat.<br/>
<br/>
CFRA Research analyst Angelo Zino said Apple could struggle to increase consumer costs more than 5 to 10 percent. "We expect Apple to hold off on any major increases on phones until this fall when its &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; is set to launch, as it is typically how it handles planned price hikes," he said.<br/>
<br/>
Bank of America securities analyst Wamsi Mohan said that if Apple were to absorb the entire impact, there could be a &#36;1.24 reduction to earnings per share in 2026. Apple could adjust prices, optimize supply chains, and seek exemptions to deal with the tariffs, according to Mohan, so it's possible Apple will have a multi-prong strategy.<br/>
<br/>
Yale Budget Lab executive director Martha Gimbel <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/04/us/politics/trump-tariffs-us-economy-prices.html">told <em>The New York Times</em></a> that companies are going to have to increase costs. "These are really big tariffs," she said. "These are not things we can expect companies to just absorb."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will Trump Back Down?</h2><br/>
On his Truth Social site, Trump said today that he does not plan to change his policies. Yesterday, he said "I think it's going very well - The MARKETS are going to BOOM..."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/donald-trump-tariffs.jpg" alt="" width="1196" height="330" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997751" /><br/>
He also said, however, that he had a "productive call" with Vietnam about lowering tariffs, and that he is looking forward to a meeting "in the near future."<br/>
<br/>
Trump has gone back and forth on tariffs levied against Canada and Mexico, so it is hard to say what he'll do next. The executive order states that he can increase or expand tariffs based on retaliation, or decrease or limit in scope the tariffs should countries "take significant steps to remedy non-reciprocal trade arrangements and align sufficiently with the United States on economic and national security matters."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What About Congress?</h2><br/>
Congress could act, but with a Republican majority, there are barriers. The Senate passed a resolution that would block tariffs on Canadian products, but it will fizzle out in the House. Republican Senator Chuck Grassley <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/republicans-weigh-using-power-congress-rein-trump-tariffs-rcna199555">proposed a bipartisan bill</a> that would require Trump to notify Congress about new tariffs with Congress given a 60-day period to approve them, but it doesn't have <a href="https://apnews.com/article/trump-tariffs-republicans-senate-house-2409e9ff50290edac738ad6e4e8e78b9">enough Republican support</a>. It's not clear if it will make progress, and it would need to overcome a presidential veto if it did.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will Apple Get an Exemption?</h2><br/>
The last time Trump was in office, he levied tariffs that did not apply to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and he gave Apple an exemption for products like the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
This time, Trump has given no exemptions, and it's not clear if he will. Cook met with Trump in February, and even donated &#36;1 million to Trump's inauguration. Cook has no doubt been wooing Trump for an exemption from Apple, but it hasn't worked so far.<br/>
<br/>
Trump used the International Emergency Economic Powers Act to implement tariffs, so any exemption would need to come directly from Trump. There is no mechanism for individual product exemptions, so Apple doesn't even have a way to petition for an exception.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>When Will Prices Increase?</h2><br/>
If Apple needs to increase prices, it would make the most sense for the company to introduce &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; price hikes with the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, but it's not clear if it will be able to hold off that long, nor when prices on other devices could increase.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Companies Are Already Evaluating Price Hikes and Tariff Responses</h2><br/>
This morning, Nintendo canceled U.S. pre-orders for the Nintendo Switch 2. Pre-orders were set to start on April 9, but Nintendo says that it will now "assess the potential impact of tariffs and evolving market conditions" before providing updated timing at a later date.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet made any comment on the tariffs or its plans going forward, but the company is likely working behind the scenes to calculate the impact.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
With all of the uncertainty, if you're in need of a new Apple device and have the funds available, it's probably best to buy very soon. That may mean opting to upgrade an older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model instead of an &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, or choosing to get a Mac now rather than holding out for a sale.<br/>
<br/>
Trump could fold, other countries could negotiate lower tariffs, or Apple could get an exemption, but there is no clear picture of what's going to happen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tariff Timing</h2><br/>
The tariffs that Trump announced on Wednesday will go into effect on Wednesday, April 9.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-upgrades-tariff-impact/">Is Now the Time to Upgrade Apple Devices Before Tariffs Lead to Price Increases?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/is-now-the-time-to-upgrade-apple-devices-before-tariffs-lead-to-price-increases.2454727/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Gets Another 75-Day Reprieve From Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/tiktok-75-day-ban-extension/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-gets-another-75-day-reprieve-from-ban.2454702/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:18:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/tiktok-75-day-ban-extension/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump today said that he is signing an executive order to keep TikTok running for an additional 75 days as his administration continues to work on the sale of the social network's U.S. operations.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986195" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/TikTok-on-iPhone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
TikTok was barred from operating in the United States when the Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/17/tiktok-january-19-ban-imminent/">went into effect on January 19</a>, but Trump at the time ordered the Department of Justice not to enforce the law for a 75-day period. The window was set to expire on Saturday, April 5 if TikTok did not reach a deal to sell to an American company, but TikTok now has another two and a half months.<br/>
<br/>
Trump said on his Truth Social network that his administration has made "tremendous progress" on a deal to "save" TikTok, but more work is required. Rumors suggest that Trump's team has been considering offers from companies like Oracle and Perplexity, along with individuals like Jimmy Donaldson (also known as MrBeast), Shark Tank host Kevin O'Leary, Employer.com founder Jesse Tinsley, and billionaire Frank McCourt. Amazon <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/amazon-tiktok-offer/">even made an offer</a> this week.<br/>
<br/>
TikTok parent company ByteDance has said that it does not plan to sell TikTok, and China has also not agreed to a deal, but Trump believes that tariffs could be used for leverage. It is possible that Trump will aim for an agreement that includes bringing on multiple U.S. investors with the TikTok algorithm leased from ByteDance, but it is not yet clear if that will meet the requirements of the law.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/tiktok-75-day-ban-extension/">TikTok Gets Another 75-Day Reprieve From Ban</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-gets-another-75-day-reprieve-from-ban.2454702/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win Custom Retro AirPods From ColorWare</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-retro-airpods/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-custom-retro-airpods-from-colorware.2454700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:59:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-retro-airpods/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've <a href="https://www.colorware.com/collections/colorware-airpods-retro">teamed up with ColorWare</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a set of <a href="https://www.colorware.com/collections/colorware-airpods-4th-gen-anc-retro">AirPods Pro 2</a> or <a href="https://www.colorware.com/collections/colorware-airpods-pro-2nd-gen-retro">AirPods 4</a> that have been custom designed with a classic Mac aesthetic.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/retro-airpods-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="859" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991987" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.colorware.com">ColorWare</a> is known for making custom-painted Apple products and accessories, and it is essentially the only company that offers non-standard colors for AirPods, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, and other Apple accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/colorware-airpods-retro-black.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997721" /><br/>
In addition to letting you order custom AirPods in <a href="https://www.colorware.com/collections/apple">a wide range of colors</a>, ColorWare often comes up with fun special edition products. This February, ColorWare debuted its ColorWare Retro Collection with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a> that have a unique design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/retro-airpods-1.jpg" alt="" width="1776" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991986" /><br/>
The Retro &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 and &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; come in a matte cream color ColorWare is calling "Light Mode," and a matte black "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a>" shade. Both models feature colorful rainbow accents that harken back to the rainbow colors that Apple used for some of its original Macs.<br/>
<br/>
The Retro &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 are priced at &#36;499, and the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; with ANC are priced at &#36;439, so there is a premium for a custom design, but it's worth it if you want a look you can't get elsewhere. ColorWare uses a proprietary painting process to ensure the finish will hold up over time, and it's been customizing devices for more than a decade.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/colorware-supernova.jpg" alt="" width="1776" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-861104" /><br/>
ColorWare uses a multi-step coating process that includes a primer, the application of a proprietary color formula, and an X2 liquid plastic coating that protects the color, with all products warrantied for 12 months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/01/colorwareairpodsproblack.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-725425" /><br/>
We have two sets of &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 or &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; (winner picks) to give away to a lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/79Mef/colorware-giveaway" rel="nofollow"><br/>
  ColorWare Giveaway<br/>
</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (April 4) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on April 11. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after April 11 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-retro-airpods/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win Custom Retro AirPods From ColorWare</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-custom-retro-airpods-from-colorware.2454700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhones Could Cost Up to &#36;2,300 in the U.S. Due to Tariffs, Analyst Says</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/2300-dollar-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphones-could-cost-up-to-2-300-in-the-u-s-due-to-tariffs-analyst-says.2454687/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:30:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/2300-dollar-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Rosenblatt Securities</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/business/economy/goods-imported-china-are-now-facing-54-tariffs-rate-rcna199401">announced</a> that steep tariffs will be applied to imports from many countries, starting April 9. The tariffs could have a significant impact on Apple, as the company assembles the majority of iPhones in China, and products imported to the U.S. from China will be subject to a 54% tariff.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/2024-iPhone-Boxes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1322" height="744" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985648" /><br/>
iPhone prices could increase by up to 43% in the U.S. due to the tariffs, according to analysts at equity research firm Rosenblatt Securities (<a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/will-trump-tariffs-make-apple-iphones-more-expensive-2025-04-03/">via <em>Reuters</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
Based on that prediction, the top-of-the-line iPhone 16 Pro Max model with 1TB of storage could rise from &#36;1,599 to nearly &#36;2,300 in the U.S., should Apple actually follow through with raising prices by 43% to offset the cost of tariffs.<br/>
<br/>
At the other end of the iPhone lineup, the most affordable iPhone 16e model would increase from &#36;599 to just over &#36;850 with a 43% price increase.<br/>
<br/>
An iPhone 16 Pro with 256GB of storage could rise from &#36;999 to more than &#36;1,400.<br/>
<br/>
Apple would need to raise its prices by at least 30% on average, in order to offset the tariffs, according to Counterpoint Research's Neil Shah.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to publicly comment on the tariffs, so it is unclear if the company will actually raise prices, or if it will get creative and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/kuo-on-how-apple-can-reduce-tariff-impact/">find alternative ways</a> to offset the impact. It is also unclear if iPhone 16 models would increase in price, or if Apple would simply set higher prices on iPhone 17 models from the get-go later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's stock price is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-shares-plunge-china-unveils-tariffs/">down nearly 15%</a> since Trump announced the planned tariffs.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rosenblatt-securities/">Rosenblatt Securities</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/2300-dollar-iphone/">iPhones Could Cost Up to &#36;2,300 in the U.S. Due to Tariffs, Analyst Says</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphones-could-cost-up-to-2-300-in-the-u-s-due-to-tariffs-analyst-says.2454687/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: WWDC 2025 Announced and iOS 18.4 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/the-macrumors-show-wwdc25-announced-and-ios-18-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-wwdc-2025-announced-and-ios-18-4-features.2454685/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:13:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/the-macrumors-show-wwdc25-announced-and-ios-18-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/wwdc-2025-announced-and-new-ios-18-4-features/id1602394741?i=1000702223794">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the announcement of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a>, key iOS 18.4 features, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c7VZyuwMeV8?si=vnFIeA1sPBvT6_j9" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple last week officially announced that its 36th annual Worldwide Developers Conference will begin on Monday, June 9, and end on Friday, June 13. As with WWDC events since 2020, &zwnj;WWDC 2025&zwnj; will primarily be an online event that is open to all developers. We discuss how the event artwork <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/wwdc-2025-logo-hints-at-ios-19-design/">appears to allude</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/ios-19-visionos-redesign-rumors/">complete redesign</a> rumored for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/ios-19-4-revamped-health-app-rumor/">recent report</a> which claims Apple is working on an AI health coach feature for the Health app.<br/>
<br/>
We look at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features-2/">key new features</a> debuting in iOS 18.4,  including Priority Notifications, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/apple-news-food-ios-18-4/">Apple News+ Food</a>, Ambient Music, and more. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> with USB-C also received a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/airpods-max-lossless-audio-coming-april/">significant update</a>, adding support for lossless audio, ultra-low latency mode, and more.<br/>
<br/>
We also talk through a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons/">recent report</a> which claims that Apple is still exploring solid-state buttons with haptic feedback for a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> also has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-mark-gurman/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up to hear our discussion with <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> about the controversy surrounding <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, what to expect from &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/the-macrumors-show-wwdc25-announced-and-ios-18-4/">The MacRumors Show: WWDC 2025 Announced and iOS 18.4 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-wwdc-2025-announced-and-ios-18-4-features.2454685/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Most Famous Rival Turns 50 Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/microsoft-turns-50-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-most-famous-rival-turns-50-today.2454684/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:46:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/microsoft-turns-50-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft today marks its 50th anniversary, during which time it has been one of Apple's longest-standing and most prolific competitors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Apple-vs-Microsoft-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-799112" /><br/>
Microsoft was founded on April 4, 1975 by Bill Gates and Paul Allen, starting out as a software company developing a BASIC interpreter for the Altair 8800. It quickly become central to the personal computing revolution, including through its early collaboration with Apple, where Apple licensed Microsoft's BASIC for the Apple II in 1977.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft's most significant early involvement with Apple came with the development of applications for the original Macintosh, including Word and Excel, which helped legitimize the Mac as a productivity tool. The 1985 launch of Microsoft Windows, which featured a graphical user interface similar to the Macintosh, prompted accusations from Apple that Microsoft had copied key elements of its design.<br/>
<br/>
The ensuing legal and public disputes would define the rivalry for years. In 1988, Apple filed a lawsuit against Microsoft and Hewlett-Packard, claiming infringement of its Macintosh GUI, which it ultimately lost.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the rivalry, Microsoft invested &#36;150 million in Apple in 1997, when the company was in financial crisis following years of declining market share and internal missteps. As part of the agreement, Microsoft committed to continuing development of Office for Mac and making Internet Explorer the default browser on Macintosh systems. During his keynote at Macworld Boston 1997, Steve Jobs announced the deal, stating:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>We have to let go of the notion that for Apple to win, Microsoft has to lose. We need to embrace a notion that for Apple to win, Apple has to do a really good job.</blockquote>  <br/>
<br/>
Throughout the 2000s and early 2010s, Microsoft and Apple continued to compete on multiple fronts with operating systems, productivity software, mobile devices, and later, cloud services. Apple's resurgence under Jobs was driven by the success of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, iPod, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, while Microsoft struggled to gain traction with mobile devices like the Windows Phone and Surface. Apple has developed alternatives to Microsoft products, including iWork, but Microsoft Office continues to be prevalent and play an important role on Apple devices, including the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Today, both companies remained dominant in their respective ecosystems. Microsoft's focus on software licensing, large-scale business use-cases, and enterprise cloud computing with Azure now forms a business model that contrasts sharply with Apple's emphasis on consumer-facing products, hardware-software integration, and user experience.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/microsoft-turns-50-today/">Apple&#039;s Most Famous Rival Turns 50 Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-most-famous-rival-turns-50-today.2454684/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get the AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99, Plus Big Discounts on MacBook Air and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-4-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-the-airpods-4-anc-for-148-99-plus-big-discounts-on-macbook-air-and-more.2454683/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:10:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-4-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's Big Spring Sale happened earlier this week, and although it has now ended, there are still a few remaining deals that have stuck around. This includes low prices on the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation, Apple Pencil Pro, M3 iPad Air, and more. We're also tracking a few solid discounts at Samsung and Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-new-purple-hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960078" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/airpods-4-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996973" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;30 off AirPods 4 with ANC</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
AirPods 4 with ANC dropped to &#36;148.99 this week on Amazon, and they are still available at this all-time low price. Right now, it's the only notable AirPods discount still around from the Big Spring Sale.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/samsung-odyssey-g9.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996974" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Samsung monitors, TVs, and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/p47ap5bqljf7s">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/samsung-spring-sale-monitors/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/p47ap5bqljf7s"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DISCOUNTS</div>Samsung Spring Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung this week kicked off a new springtime sale, which includes savings on monitors, TVs, Galaxy products, and more. This sale also covers the newest Galaxy S25 smartphones, The Frame TV, and Samsung's line of home appliances, including refrigerators and washer/dryers. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/m2-macbook-air-new-hue-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997664" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;250 off M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/o2iokizxm136a">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/m2-macbook-air-749/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/o2iokizxm136a"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (16GB/256GB) for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy is discounting Apple's 13-inch M2 MacBook Air with 16GB of RAM and 256GB SSD storage down to &#36;749.00 in a few colors. This is a &#36;250 discount on the previous generation M2 MacBook Air, and a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m3-ipad-air-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996976" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;70 off new iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76QBLQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;61 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;738.08</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Last week Apple launched the new M3 iPad Air, and Amazon has been providing solid launch window discounts on numerous models this week. You can find up to &#36;70 off these tablets on Amazon, with prices starting at &#36;549.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m4-macbook-air-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996977" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off M4 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC3WW5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/01/new-m4-macbook-air-50-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBDCFH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,139.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week has all-time low prices on the new M4 MacBook Air, with up to &#36;60 off the 13-inch and 15-inch versions of the computer. Right now these discounts are only available on Amazon, and most of them have estimated delivery windows of early April.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/apple-pencil-pro-blue-hue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996978" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;30 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Another all-time low price available on Amazon this week was on the Apple Pencil Pro, and it's still available for &#36;99.00 today, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-4-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get the AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99, Plus Big Discounts on MacBook Air and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-the-airpods-4-anc-for-148-99-plus-big-discounts-on-macbook-air-and-more.2454683/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stock Sell-Off Continues After China Unveils Matching Tariffs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-shares-plunge-china-unveils-tariffs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stock-sell-off-continues-after-china-unveils-matching-tariffs.2454677/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:05:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-shares-plunge-china-unveils-tariffs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple stock dropped 4% in early Friday trading, broadly following yesterday's trend after China announced reciprocal tariffs in response to U.S. President Trump's trade policies. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/Apple-Logo-Cash-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796909" /><br/>
The latest decline follows Thursday's dramatic 9% plunge that erased nearly &#36;300 billion from Apple's market value – the company's worst single-day performance in five years – amid growing fears that Trump's trade war will hurt the global economy. Apple's market value was expected to be reduced further today as markets processed China's matching 34% tariff announcement.<br/>
<br/>
China's finance ministry announced it would impose a matching 34% tariff on U.S. imports starting April 10, one day after Trump's new duties take effect. The country also restricted exports of rare earth elements critical for technology manufacturing and added 11 American businesses to its "Unreliable Entity List."<br/>
<br/>
Trump's "Liberation Day" tariff plan particularly threatens Apple, which relies heavily on Chinese manufacturing despite years of diversification efforts. The 54% effective rate on Chinese imports combines the new 34% tariff with an existing 20% charge.<br/>
<br/>
Countries where Apple has been expanding its supply chain, including India, Thailand, Malaysia, and Vietnam, were also targeted with tariffs above Trump's global baseline rate of 10%.<br/>
<br/>
Analysts warn Apple faces difficult choices ahead, potentially needing to raise U.S. hardware prices by approximately 30% to offset the tariff impact or accept significant hits to its profit margins.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/apple-shares-plunge-china-unveils-tariffs/">Apple Stock Sell-Off Continues After China Unveils Matching Tariffs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stock-sell-off-continues-after-china-unveils-matching-tariffs.2454677/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Dolby Atmos in Apple Music Now Available for Windows PCs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/dolby-atmos-in-apple-music-available-for-windows/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dolby-atmos-in-apple-music-now-available-for-windows-pcs.2454674/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:35:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/dolby-atmos-in-apple-music-available-for-windows/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		<category>Dolby Atmos</category>
		<category>Windows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Dolby Atmos music playback is now supported in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> for Windows, bringing true immersive audio to PCs with compatible hardware via Apple's music streaming service for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-962031" /><br/>
Dolby Atmos is a surround-sound audio format that allows sound to be heard in an immersive, three-dimensional audio experience with compatible stereo headphones and speakers. Apple's Spatial Audio technology takes Dolby Atmos content and applies its own directional audio filters to make sounds appear to be coming from all around you.<br/>
<br/>
The feature was added in version 1.1284.20225 of &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; for Windows. A <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-ph/guide/music-windows/musf7d98bef8/windows">new Apple Support document</a> called "Play Dolby Atmos in Music on Windows" explains how to use it on a PC.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, Vision Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and Android already supported Dolby Atmos audio. Spatial Audio via Dolby Atmos debuted on Apple's music streaming service in June 2021.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dolby-atmos/">Dolby Atmos</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/windows/">Windows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/dolby-atmos-in-apple-music-available-for-windows/">Dolby Atmos in Apple Music Now Available for Windows PCs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dolby-atmos-in-apple-music-now-available-for-windows-pcs.2454674/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4: Access Hidden Ambient Music Playlists</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-4-access-hidden-ambient-music-playlists/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-access-hidden-ambient-music-playlists.2454672/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:14:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-4-access-hidden-ambient-music-playlists&#038;post_date=1743776098/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In Apple's iOS 18.4 software update, there's a new Ambient Music feature available in the Control Center options on iPhone. It's free to use, and does not require an Apple Music subscription. It's also more customizable than most users probably realize. Keep reading to learn how.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-4-Ambient-Music-Control-Center.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996862" /><br/>
There are four different sound categories to Ambient Music, including Sleep, Chill, Productivity, and Wellbeing. You can add each category individually to your Control Center, and then tap on one to start a playlist of songs in the chosen category. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Add Ambient Music Buttons to Control Center</h2><br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open Control Center by swiping down from the top-right corner of your screen.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the + button in the top-left corner, or long press on a blank space.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Add a Control</strong> at the bottom of the screen.</li><br/>
  <li>Scroll down to the new "Ambient Music" controls section and choose from <strong>Sleep</strong>, <strong>Chill</strong>, <strong>Productivity</strong>, and <strong>Wellbeing</strong>.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap any blank space to exit out of edit mode.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/ambient-music-buttons-control-center-ios.jpg" alt="control center" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997640" /><br/>
When you turn on one of the Ambient Music options in Control Center, playback controls will appear on the screen. You can also tap or long press the Dynamic Island on newer iPhones to access playback controls or bring up a fullscreen music player with album art.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Changing Ambient Music Category Playlists</h2><br/>
It's not obvious, but you can actually choose different playlists for each Ambient Music category. In fact, this option is so hidden in the interface that some might even call it an "easter egg" – or perhaps a non-intuitive UI design choice. Apple describes the playlists as follows:<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Sleep:</strong> Sleep Sounds, Bedtime Beats, Sound Bath, and Piano Sleep.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Chill:</strong> Piano Chill, Ambient Chill, Lo-Fi Jazz, and Pure Chill.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Productivity:</strong> BEATstrumentals, Binaural Frequencies, Pure Focus, and Classical Concentration.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Wellbeing:</strong> Pure Meditation, Spa, Beats & Breath, and Pure Calm.</li></ul>Here's what you need to do to choose a different playlist – or even one of your own:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open Control Center, then tap the <strong>+</strong> icon in the top-left corner of the screen.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap one of the Ambient Music buttons that you added to your Control Center (try to avoid tapping the minus symbol or the button will disappear).</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the playlist name in blue next to "Playlist," then select one of the playlists from the dropdown. If you select <strong>From Library</strong>, tap <strong>Choose</strong> to pick a playlist from your Music library.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap any blank space, then tap again to exit out of edit mode.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/change-ambient-music-playlist-ios.jpg" alt="control center" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997639" /><br/>
So now you know how to switch up the playlists when listening to Ambient Music, whether that's for restful sleep, relaxation, focusing on tasks, or for meditation and self-care. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-4-access-hidden-ambient-music-playlists/">iOS 18.4: Access Hidden Ambient Music Playlists</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-access-hidden-ambient-music-playlists.2454672/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Users Report CarPlay Connectivity Issues With iOS 18.4 Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/ios-18-4-carplay-bugs-multiple-vehicle-brands/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-users-report-carplay-connectivity-issues-with-ios-18-4-update.2454667/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:41:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/ios-18-4-carplay-bugs-multiple-vehicle-brands/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Multiple iPhone users are reporting problems with CarPlay functionality after updating to iOS 18.4, based on complaints on <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CarPlay/comments/1jp6ifw/updated_to_ios_184_and_now_carplay_doesnt_extend/">Reddit</a> and elsewhere.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-carplay.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991400" /><br/>
The most widespread issue appears to affect vehicles equipped with CarPlay instrument cluster integration. Some users said that after installing iOS 18.4, CarPlay no longer displays the currently playing song information on their car's instrument panel. <br/>
<br/>
The instrument cluster bugs have been reported across numerous vehicle models including the 2025 Honda Civic Hybrid, 2025 Mazda CX-30, various 2024 Honda models, multiple Volkswagen vehicles, the 2023 Audi S3, and the 2023 Nissan Frontier.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, several users have complained that CarPlay completely fails to launch after the update, requiring multiple reconnection attempts - sometimes up to five tries - before the system will work. Others report broken Siri audio functionality that persists despite restarting both their iPhones and vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
Users say they have attempted the standard troubleshooting steps like device reboots and system resets, but in many cases these workarounds have not resolved the issues. The problems appear to be directly linked to the iOS 18.4 update, as affected users report that everything worked properly before installing the latest version.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet acknowledged any CarPlay issues with iOS 18.4, so it's unclear whether a fix is in the works. Apple released iOS 18.4 earlier this week, and the only notable intended change to CarPlay is that the interface now shows a third row of icons (up from two rows previously), but only on vehicles with a larger display center. Have you had problems with CarPlay after updating? Let us know in the comments.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://www.autoevolution.com/news/latest-iphone-update-wreaks-havoc-on-carplay-249409.html">autoevolution.com</a>.)</em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/ios-18-4-carplay-bugs-multiple-vehicle-brands/">iPhone Users Report CarPlay Connectivity Issues With iOS 18.4 Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-users-report-carplay-connectivity-issues-with-ios-18-4-update.2454667/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sending WWDC 2025 Invites to Special Event Lottery Winners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-wwdc-developer-special-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sending-wwdc-2025-invites-to-special-event-lottery-winners.2454647/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:37:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-wwdc-developer-special-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to hold a WWDC keynote viewing party for select students and developers on Monday, June 9, with a limited number of invites available for an in-person <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> event. Apple accepted applications for attendance until yesterday, and the company is now sending out notices to those who have been selected to go via its lottery process.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/apple-park-special-event-2025.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996616" /><br/>
The event is set to include WWDC-related special activities like the keynote viewing, the Platforms State of the Union, Apple Design Awards, &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; tours, and a dinner. Developers and students will also have opportunities to interface with Apple engineers and experts.<br/>
<br/>
Current Apple Developer Program members, Apple Developer Enterprise Program members, Apple Entrepreneur Camp alumni, and Swift Student Challenge winners from 2023 to 2025 were eligible to apply, with attendees chosen by random selection.<br/>
<br/>
There is no cost to attend the &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; special event, but Apple does not cover transportation or lodging. Out-of-state attendees will need to purchase airfare, hotel accommodations, and transportation to &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a> will take place from June 9 to June 13. Developers that were not selected to attent the &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; event can watch the keynote, get help from Apple engineers, and watch WWDC sessions online through the Apple Developer website and app.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-wwdc-developer-special-event/">Apple Sending WWDC 2025 Invites to Special Event Lottery Winners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sending-wwdc-2025-invites-to-special-event-lottery-winners.2454647/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Supplier TSMC May Operate Intel’s Chipmaking Facilities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/intel-tsmc-preliminary-agreement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-supplier-tsmc-may-operate-intel’s-chipmaking-facilities.2454645/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:02:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/intel-tsmc-preliminary-agreement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Intel</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple supplier TSMC has reached a preliminary agreement with Intel that will see TSMC operating Intel’s chipmaking facilities, reports <em><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/intel-tsmc-tentatively-agree-form-chipmaking-joint-venture">The Information</a></em>. TSMC will own a 20 percent stake in the new combined company, while Intel and other semiconductor companies will own the majority of the shares.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/intel-logo.jpg" alt="" width="2392" height="1345" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-776742" /><br/>
As part of the deal, TSMC may share some of its chip manufacturing methods with Intel, and train Intel employees to use them. Discussions are still underway, and the final details have not been established. The talks between Intel and TSMC were reportedly initiated by the Trump administration in an effort to stymy Intel’s decline and bring advanced chipmaking to the U.S.<br/>
<br/>
Intel is one of TSMC’s major competitors, and the two have long been rivals. Apple previously used Intel chips in its Macs, but transitioned to its own Apple silicon chips manufactured by TSMC starting in 2020. No Apple devices use Intel processors, with Apple now relying entirely on its own technology.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC focuses on chip manufacturing, not design, which is handled by TSMC customers like Apple and Nvidia. The focus solely on manufacturing has allowed TSMC to outpace Intel, and Intel’s foundary operations are less attractive to companies because Intel’s chips cost more than TSMC’s and its yields are lower.<br/>
<br/>
Some Intel executives are said to be worried that the deal would result in layoffs, because Intel would need to eliminate engineers and may need to change or sell the equipment that it uses. Intel and TSMC have different manufacturing machines and materials, so if Intel is expected to adopt TSMC manufacturing processes, it could have to sell most of its existing equipment.<br/>
<br/>
In 2024, Intel had an &#36;18.8 billion loss because of its investments in chip manufacturing and a weakening PC market.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/intel/">Intel</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/intel-tsmc-preliminary-agreement/">Apple Supplier TSMC May Operate Intel’s Chipmaking Facilities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-supplier-tsmc-may-operate-intel’s-chipmaking-facilities.2454645/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 216 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-216/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-216-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2454643/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:47:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-216/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser that was <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to allow users to test features that are planned for future release versions of the Safari browser.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960117" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Safari-Technology-Preview-Updated-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 216 includes fixes and updates for Accessibility, CSS, Forms, Media, Rendering, Service Workers, SVG, Text, URLs, Web Animations, Web API, and Web Inspector. <br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Sonoma and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, the newest version of macOS.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a> from Apple’s website. Complete release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple’s aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while it is designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download and use.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-216/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 216 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-216-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2454643/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Video: Choosing the Best Mac For You</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/mac-buyers-guide-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-choosing-the-best-mac-for-you.2454623/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:49:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/mac-buyers-guide-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you're new to Macs, or haven't upgraded for some time, it can be difficult to decide just what to get. Is the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> the best option? Do you need the power of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>? What about desktop options?<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XAlrSn7KhLY" title="Ultimate Mac Buyers Guide 2025: Which Mac is Right For You?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
In our latest video, we walk through the current Mac lineup and provide some tips on things to consider when you're trying to decide on a new machine. Trying to figure out if you need more RAM or a storage upgrade? Our video just might help.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/mac-buyers-guide-video/">Video: Choosing the Best Mac For You</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-choosing-the-best-mac-for-you.2454623/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates iWork Apps With New iOS 18.4 and macOS 15.4 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/iwork-ios-18-4-and-macos-15-4-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-iwork-apps-with-new-ios-18-4-and-macos-15-4-features.2454621/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:13:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/iwork-ios-18-4-and-macos-15-4-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iWork</category>
		<category>Keynote</category>
		<category>Numbers</category>
		<category>Pages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated its iWork apps <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/-/id361285480">Keynote</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/-/id361304891">Numbers</a>, and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/-/id361309726">Pages</a> with new features that require iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, or macOS 15.4.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iWork-macOS-Trio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-818315" /><br/>
For example, in the latest version of each app, you can now make text edits using Writing Tools directly in a presentation, spreadsheet, or document. This feature requires Apple Intelligence, which is available on iPhone 15 Pro models, all iPhone 16 models, any Mac or iPad model with an M1 chip or newer, or the iPad mini with the A17 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, Apple says you can now export a presentation, spreadsheet, or document in another format using the Shortcuts app, and all three apps gained improved copy and paste integration with the Freeform app. Each app also received a few other enhancements that are not tied to the latest software updates.<br/>
<br/>
The release notes for version 14.4 of each app on iOS follow.<br/>
<br/>
Keynote:<blockquote>• Make text edits using Writing Tools directly in your presentation (requires Apple Intelligence and iOS or iPadOS 18.4)<br/>
• Export presentations into other formats using Shortcuts (requires iOS or iPadOS 18.4)<br/>
• Improved copy and paste with Freeform (requires iOS or iPadOS 18.4)</blockquote>Numbers:<blockquote>• Use over 30 new advanced functions including LET, LAMBDA, FILTER, SORT, and UNIQUE<br/>
• See results from a single formula across multiple cells using spilling arrays<br/>
• Make text edits using Writing Tools directly in your spreadsheet (requires Apple Intelligence and iOS or iPadOS 18.4)<br/>
• Export spreadsheets into other formats using Shortcuts (requires iOS or iPadOS 18.4)<br/>
• Improved copy and paste with Freeform (requires iOS or iPadOS 18.4)<br/>
• Improved compatibility when importing or exporting Microsoft Excel spreadsheets</blockquote>Pages:<blockquote>• Make text edits using Writing Tools directly in your document (requires Apple Intelligence and macOS 15.4)<br/>
• Add additional pages into a word-processing document more easily<br/>
• Export documents into other formats using Shortcuts (requires macOS 15.4)<br/>
• Improved copy and paste with Freeform (requires macOS 15.4)</blockquote>iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and macOS 15.4 were all released to the general public this week, following more than a month of beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
The updated iWork apps are available in the App Store across the iPhone, iPad, and Mac.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iwork/">iWork</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/keynote/">Keynote</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/numbers/">Numbers</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/pages/">Pages</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/iwork-ios-18-4-and-macos-15-4-features/">Apple Updates iWork Apps With New iOS 18.4 and macOS 15.4 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-iwork-apps-with-new-ios-18-4-and-macos-15-4-features.2454621/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Now Get Visual Intelligence on iPhone 15 Pro – Here&#039;s How</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/visual-intelligence-iphone-15-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-get-visual-intelligence-on-iphone-15-pro-–-heres-how.2454618/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/visual-intelligence-iphone-15-pro&#038;post_date=1743706800/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On iPhone 16 models, Visual Intelligence lets you use the camera to learn more about places and objects around you. It can also summarize text, read text out loud, translate text, search Google for items, ask ChatGPT, and more. And thanks to the latest iOS 18.4 update from Apple, iPhone 15 Pro models can now get in on the action, too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-Visual-Intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970984" /><br/>
Until recently, ‌Visual Intelligence‌ was a feature limited to iPhone 16 models with a Camera Control button, which was necessary to activate the feature. However, Apple in February debuted the iPhone 16e, which lacks Camera Control and yet supports Visual Intelligence. This is because the device ships with a version of iOS that includes Visual Intelligence as an assignable option to the device's Action button.<br/>
<br/>
Apple later confirmed that the same Visual Intelligence customization setting would be coming to iPhone 15 Pro models via a software update. That update is iOS 18.4, and it's available now. If you haven't updated yet, you can do so by opening <strong>Settings ➝ General ➝ Software Update</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
After your device is up-to-date, you can assign Visual Intelligence to the device's Action button in the following way.<br/>
<ol><li>Open <strong>Settings</strong> on your iPhone 15 Pro.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Action Button</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Swipe to <strong>Visual Intelligence</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/visual-intelligence-action-button.jpg" alt="settings" width="2760" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994733" /><br/>
<br/>
Pressing and holding the Action button will now activate Visual Intelligence. Note that you can also activate Visual Intelligence using the new button option in Control Center. Here's how.<br/>
<ol><li>Swipe down from the top-right corner of your iPhone's display, then long press on the Control Center.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Add a Control</strong> at the bottom.</li><br/>
<li>Use the search bar at the top to search for <strong>Visual Intelligence</strong>, or swipe up to the "Apple Intelligence" section and choose the button.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the screen to exit the Control Center's edit mode.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/visual-intelligence-control-center.jpg" alt="control center" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994734" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Using Visual Intelligence</h2><br/>
The Visual Intelligence interface features a view from the camera, a button to capture a photo, and dedicated "Ask" and "Search" buttons. Ask queries ChatGPT, and Search sends an image to Google Search.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/visual-intelligence-buttons.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-987374" /><br/>
When using Visual Intelligence you can either snap a photo using the shutter button and then select an option, or you can select an option in live camera view. You cannot use photos that you took previously.<br/>
<br/>
To learn about everything that you can do with Visual Intelligence, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">dedicated guide</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/visual-intelligence-iphone-15-pro/">You Can Now Get Visual Intelligence on iPhone 15 Pro – Here&#039;s How</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-get-visual-intelligence-on-iphone-15-pro-–-heres-how.2454618/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4: Stop Your Recent Searches Showing in New Safari Tabs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-off-safari-recent-searches-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-stop-your-recent-searches-showing-in-new-safari-tabs.2454608/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:04:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-off-safari-recent-searches-ios&#038;post_date=1743703472/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in iOS 18.4 has introduced a potentially privacy-compromising change to Safari that puts your search history on full display when opening new tabs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-safari-search.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991973" /><br/>
Previously in iOS, opening a new tab and tapping the search field brought up the keyboard while continuing to display the personalized Safari home page. However, Apple's latest iOS 18.4 software update modifies how Safari handles new tabs by automatically showing your recent search history whenever someone taps into the search field. <br/>
<br/>
Privacy-conscious users are likely to raise eyebrows at the change, as it could expose previous searches in situations where users hand their devices to friends, family members, or colleagues – or just search for something when someone else is looking at their screen. A quick tap on the search field would immediately reveal what the device owner has been searching for online.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, Apple has added a toggle that reverts the new Safari tab behavior so that your recent searches are no longer on full view.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app on your iPhone.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down to the bottom and tap <strong>Apps</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Find <strong>Safari</strong> in the alphabetical list and tap on it, then toggle off the switch called <strong>Show Recent Searches</strong>.</li></ol> <img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/turn-off-safari-recent-searches.jpg" alt="" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997588" /><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there's an upside to the change that you may appreciate. It makes frequently used search terms more conveniently accessible, potentially saving time if you often search for similar topics. But the convenience still comes with the tradeoff of reduced privacy, and that might be a step too far for some users.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-off-safari-recent-searches-ios/">iOS 18.4: Stop Your Recent Searches Showing in New Safari Tabs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-stop-your-recent-searches-showing-in-new-safari-tabs.2454608/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Introduces Discounts on Popular Monitors, TVs, Smartphones, and More in Spring Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/samsung-spring-sale-monitors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-introduces-discounts-on-popular-monitors-tvs-smartphones-and-more-in-spring-sale.2454606/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:46:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/samsung-spring-sale-monitors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung this week kicked off a <a href="https://howl.link/p47ap5bqljf7s">new springtime sale</a>, which includes savings on monitors, TVs, Galaxy products, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/the-frame-tv-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-987867" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
One of the best overall deals during this sale is on The Frame TVs, which are available for up to &#36;1,800 off, depending on the size of the model you purchase. Every size is being discounted during this event, with the popular 65-inch The Frame TV available for <a href="https://howl.link/236b0aewj1fir"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,999.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/p47ap5bqljf7s"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DISCOUNTS</div>Samsung Spring Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best monitor deals include the popular 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"><strong>&#36;999.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. At &#36;600 off this is a solid second-best price on the display, which has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/17yctwgf8s42i"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>32-inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/d69qwqpz4m8cu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;600 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;999.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there's a lot more on sale than just monitors. This sale also covers the newest Galaxy S25 smartphones, The Frame TV, and Samsung's line of home appliances, including refrigerators and washer/dryers. We've accumulated some of these deals in the lists below, but be sure to check out Samsung's website for the full sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/samsung-s25-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-987861" /><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/faul5vo4dharo">TVs</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/236b0aewj1fir">The Frame</a> - Save up to &#36;1,800</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/basyw1q0kj7hr">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ykww20f4u23u4">65-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/btdmfxv0poeju">65-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;2,699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVRaSFAOn">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,179.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9xnvn5zl1fo05">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,749.99, down from &#36;3,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/p7y8pcx52jg1k">Monitors and Storage</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVMG7DfcK">990 EVO 5.0 NVMe SSD 2TB</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVLMVgenn">2TB Portable SSD</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;284.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/dimoodgjkv1b1">27-inch Odyssey G6 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;549.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/bog227afoqoi8">43-inch Odyssey Neo G7 Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;569.99, down from &#36;999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/cspcria6yvngs">49-inch Odyssey G9 (G95C) Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;849.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZtLQWw9">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 (G95SC) Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/3knbth7s9xh26">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 (G93SD) Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ck1tDoV18FW">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,799.99, down from &#36;2,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/sbn4b7dlrp8pq">Refrigerators</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/rj0skwxvkajxt">Large Capacity Side-by-Side Fridge</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,666.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/wvh01oaq72v2w">4-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ozmz1x8zug5xn">Mega Capacity 3-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;2,399.00, down from &#36;3,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/2ywoezhcm8c5r">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;4,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ot6h8iqi1q361">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;3,099.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/5tyldrblhkwko">Galaxy Products</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/j67ycz3zwo7q9">Galaxy S25 Smartphone</a> - Save up to &#36;850</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/wh46f62wzw5s8">Galaxy S25+ Smartphone</a> - Save up to &#36;850</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/abx8a0atqckdm">Galaxy S25 Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9rn5heo5brtwc">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,300</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/xqamoxz18az2f">Galaxy Ring</a> - Get up to &#36;100 trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/14vx5j52aye6j">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;325</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/zyhlv7pgnni0m">Galaxy Watch 7</a> - Save up to &#36;175</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/gnqxpqhxaeowp">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;125</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/samsung-spring-sale-monitors/">Samsung Introduces Discounts on Popular Monitors, TVs, Smartphones, and More in Spring Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-introduces-discounts-on-popular-monitors-tvs-smartphones-and-more-in-spring-sale.2454606/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>RollerCoaster Tycoon and More Games Now Available on Apple Arcade</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/rollercoaster-tycoon-apple-arcade/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rollercoaster-tycoon-and-more-games-now-available-on-apple-arcade.2454605/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:25:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/rollercoaster-tycoon-apple-arcade/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Arcade gained six more games today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/11/apple-arcade-six-new-games-next-month/">as promised</a>, including <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/rollercoaster-tycoon-classic/id6702028686">RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/katamari-damacy-rolling-live/id6449352814">Katamari Damacy Rolling LIVE</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/the-game-of-life-2/id6740409686">The Game of Life 2</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sesame-street-mecha-builders/id6738959688">Sesame Street Mecha Builders</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spaceinvaders-infinitygene-evo/id6450520348">Space Invaders Infinity Gene Evolve</a>, and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/puffies/id1659992476">puffies.</a><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-Arcade-RollerCoaster-Tycoon.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994292" /><br/>
Notably, the Apple Arcade version of RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic is available on the Mac:<blockquote>Combining features from two of the series' most successful and beloved games, RollerCoaster Tycoon and RollerCoaster Tycoon 2, this new game invites players to create and run amazing parks with the most outrageous rides imaginable. Enhanced for iPhone and iPad, RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic+ delivers the same depth of gameplay and unique graphical style of Chris Sawyer's original best-selling PC games. It also includes three expansion packs — Wacky Worlds, Time Twister, and Toolkit — and is playable across iPhone, iPad, and Mac.</blockquote>The first original Katamari game in nearly eight years also arrived on Apple Arcade today, across the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-Arcade-Katamari.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994298" /><br/>
Here is how Apple describes that game:<blockquote>In this quirky action game — an Apple Arcade exclusive — players expand their Katamari by rolling up objects scattered across the earth. Featuring unique and whimsical gameplay, and a captivating soundtrack that blends different genres, the game invites players to energize the king's "live stream" by rolling their Katamari to create stars. As users advance, comments from in-game fans appear, and the longer they play, the larger their audience grows. By completing the king's challenges and boosting their subscriber count, players can unlock dynamic new stages.</blockquote>More details about all six games can be found <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/03/apple-arcade-launches-new-katamari-and-space-invaders-games-in-april/">in Apple's announcement</a> from last month.<br/>
<br/>
Accessible through the App Store, Apple Arcade is a subscription-based service that provides access to hundreds of games across the iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple TV, and Apple Vision Pro, all free of ads and in-app purchases. In the U.S., Apple Arcade costs &#36;6.99 per month and is bundled with other Apple services in all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One plans</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/rollercoaster-tycoon-apple-arcade/">RollerCoaster Tycoon and More Games Now Available on Apple Arcade</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rollercoaster-tycoon-and-more-games-now-available-on-apple-arcade.2454605/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
