<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 16:10:58 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Received 13 Academy Award Nominations for Killers of the Flower Moon and Napoleon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-academy-award-nominations-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-received-13-academy-award-nominations-for-killers-of-the-flower-moon-and-napoleon.2417249/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:19:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-academy-award-nominations-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple scored <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-scores-record-13-academy-award-nominations/">13 Academy Award nominations</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> movies Killers of the Flower Moon and Napoleon, doubling its record for Academy Award nominations in a single year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/killers-of-the-flower-moon-apple-tv-plus.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1333" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810272" /><br/>
Directed by Martin Scorsese, Killers of the Flower Moon has been nominated for Best Picture, Best Director, Best Actress in a Leading Role (Lily Gladstone), Best Supporting Actor (Robert De Niro), Best Costume Design, Best Production Design, Best Original Score, Best Original Song, Best Film Editing, and Best Cinematography.<br/>
<br/>
Scorsese has now received 10 total lifetime Academy Award nominations for Best Director, making him the most-nominated living director.<br/>
<br/>
Napoleon, directed by Ridley Scott and starring Joaquin Phoenix, received Academy Award nominations for Best Costume Design, Best Production Design, and Best Visual Effects.<br/>
<br/>
Killers of the Flower Moon <a href="https://www.oscars.org/oscars/ceremonies/2024">will compete against</a> movies that include Barbie, Oppenheimer, Past Lives, Poor Things, and Maestro for Best Picture. It was previously nominated for nine BAFTA awards, and was named Best Film of the Year by the National Board of Review.<br/>
<br/>
Apple won a 2022 Academy Award for CODA and short film The Boy, the Mole, the Fox, and the Horse.<br/>
<br/>
Killers of the Flower Moon is available on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; now, while Napoleon will be available to stream on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-academy-award-nominations-2024/">Apple Received 13 Academy Award Nominations for Killers of the Flower Moon and Napoleon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-received-13-academy-award-nominations-for-killers-of-the-flower-moon-and-napoleon.2417249/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Updated Firmware for First-Generation AirPods Pro and AirPods 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/airpods-pro-1-firmware-6a321/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-updated-firmware-for-first-generation-airpods-pro-and-airpods-2.2417229/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 11:25:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/airpods-pro-1-firmware-6a321/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced a new firmware update for the first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> and second-generation AirPods. The new firmware is the same 6A321 version that was released for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-3-firmware-6a321/">third-generation AirPods last week</a> and is up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-releases-new-airpods-firmware-2//">6A300 firmware</a> introduced last September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/AirPods-Pro-Firmware-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2322" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-825981" /><br/>
Apple's AirPods firmware updates often do not come with details on new features, so it is unclear what might be included in the software. For last week's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a> update with this firmware version, Apple listed only "bug fixes and other improvements."<br/>
<br/>
Apple also does not offer instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your AirPods or ‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌‌ firmware version by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌AirPods to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the AirPods firmware release, we'll update this article.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update 1:50 pm</b>: This article has been updated to note the 6A321 update has also been released for the second-generation AirPods.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/airpods-pro-1-firmware-6a321/">Apple Releases Updated Firmware for First-Generation AirPods Pro and AirPods 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-updated-firmware-for-first-generation-airpods-pro-and-airpods-2.2417229/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Car Autonomous Driving Scaled Down, Launch Planned for 2028</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-car-scaled-down-2028-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-car-autonomous-driving-scaled-down-launch-planned-for-2028.2417226/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 11:02:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-car-scaled-down-2028-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has pivoted to simpler, less ambitious design for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a> in order to actually bring the vehicle to market, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-23/apple-car-ev-set-to-debut-in-2028-with-limited-autonomous-driving">Bloomberg</a></em>. Apple initially wanted a driverless car with full autonomous capabilities, but it is now developing an electric vehicle with fewer features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774149" /><br/>
After abandoning the driverless plans, Apple aimed for a car with Level 4 autonomous functionality that would have allowed the car's system to take over driving in limited circumstances such as on highways, but even that was too ambitious. Apple is said to be focusing on driver-assistance features that are closer to how Tesla vehicles operate, and it will have a Level 2+ system. Level 2 autonomous driving includes steering and brake/acceleration support, but the driver remains in control of the car and must pay attention on the road.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the scaling back of the project, Apple's launch timeline for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; has been adjusted. Apple wanted to introduce the car sometime around 2026, but Apple is now targeting a 2028 release at the earliest. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, this marks a "pivotal moment" for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;. If the company is not able to deliver an electric vehicle with this feature set, executives may "seriously reconsider the project's existence."<br/>
<br/>
Since the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; was unveiled in 2014, the project has shifted and evolved several times. Rumors have at times suggested that Apple had scrapped a car altogether, focusing instead on an autonomous system, but it appears that Apple is sticking with plans to debut a full Apple-branded vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project has been riddled with leadership changes and internal strife over the direction of development. Apple Watch chief Kevin Lynch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/09/kevin-lynch-apple-car-project/">took over the project</a>, and he worked with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> to adopt a new strategy after pressure from Apple's board. Apple is now meeting with potential partners in Europe to discuss the new plan.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-car-scaled-down-2028-launch/">Apple Car Autonomous Driving Scaled Down, Launch Planned for 2028</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-car-autonomous-driving-scaled-down-launch-planned-for-2028.2417226/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launching 2024 Swift Student Challenge on February 5</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-swift-student-challenge-february-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launching-2024-swift-student-challenge-on-february-5.2417218/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 10:14:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-swift-student-challenge-february-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		<category>Swift Playgrounds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will begin accepting submissions for its next Swift Student Challenge on Monday, February 5, Apple said today in news provided to developers. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/swift-student-challenge-february-2024/">first announced plans</a> for an early 2024 launch in November, giving students plenty of time to prepare.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/swift-student-challenge-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932478" /><br/>
The Swift Student Challenge tasks students with creating an innovative coding project using the Swift Playgrounds app. Apple plans to select 350 winners for this year's challenge, and there will be a category that recognizes a total of 50 Distinguished Winners for standout submissions.<br/>
<br/>
Distinguished Winners will be invited to Apple's headquarters in Cupertino, California, where they will be able to connect with their peers and the Apple team, while all winners will be granted a free one-year membership in the Apple Developer program.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been holding an annual Swift Student Challenge for several years now, but it is typically announced when the dates for WWDC are announced, and past winners have been invited to attend the Worldwide Developers Conference. Apple says that this year's 50 Distinguished Winners will be invited to Cupertino "next summer."<br/>
<br/>
When February 5 rolls around, students will have three weeks to submit their app playgrounds to Apple. Apple judges entries on technical accomplishment, creativity of ideas, and content of written responses explaining the project.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/swift-playgrounds/">Swift Playgrounds</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-swift-student-challenge-february-5/">Apple Launching 2024 Swift Student Challenge on February 5</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launching-2024-swift-student-challenge-on-february-5.2417218/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Death Stranding Director&#039;s Cut Launching on iPhone 15 Pro and Apple Silicon Macs on January 30</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/death-stranding-iphone-15-pro-macs-release-date/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/death-stranding-directors-cut-launching-on-iphone-15-pro-and-apple-silicon-macs-on-january-30.2417212/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:11:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/death-stranding-iphone-15-pro-macs-release-date/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Kojima Productions and 505 Games today announced that <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/death-stranding-directors-cut/id6449748961">Death Stranding Director's Cut</a> will be launching on select Apple devices on Tuesday, January 30. The popular game will be available on the iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max with the A17 Pro chip, along with all iPad and Mac models equipped with M-series chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Death-Stranding.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932460" /><br/>
The game can be <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/death-stranding-directors-cut/id6449748961">pre-ordered now on the App Store</a> for a discounted price of &#36;19.99 in the U.S. for a limited time. Regular pricing will be &#36;39.99.<br/>
<br/>
Directed by Hideo Kojima, and starring Norman Reedus of <em>The Walking Dead</em> fame, Death Stranding Director's Cut is a post-apocalyptic open world adventure game that tasks players with exploring and completing missions in a fictional sci-fi wasteland. The game was first released for the PlayStation 5 in 2021, and for Windows in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Both the A17 Pro chip for iPhone 15 Pro models and the M3 chip for Macs support hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for improved graphics rendering, including more accurate lighting, reflections, and shadows.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/death-stranding-iphone-15-pro-macs-release-date/">Death Stranding Director&#039;s Cut Launching on iPhone 15 Pro and Apple Silicon Macs on January 30</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/death-stranding-directors-cut-launching-on-iphone-15-pro-and-apple-silicon-macs-on-january-30.2417212/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Chrome for Mac Gets Generative AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/chrome-mac-generative-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-chrome-for-mac-gets-generative-ai-features.2417210/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/chrome-mac-generative-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today announced plans to add experimental generative AI features to the latest version of Chrome for Mac (M121), helping users organize tabs, create themes, and draft content.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/chrome-generative-ai.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932250" /><br/>
The Tab Organizer is able to suggest and create tab groups based on the tabs that are open, an option that can be accessed by right-clicking on a tab and choosing the Organize Similar Tabs option.<br/>
<br/>
With a text-to-image diffusion model, Chrome users can generate custom themes based on a subject, mood, visual style, and color. The "Create with AI" theme option is available under the Customize Chrome side panel.<br/>
<br/>
When writing something on the web, such as on a forum, Chrome will be able to help users generate content. The feature will let users right-click in any text box or field to access a "Help me write" option.<br/>
<br/>
The Tab Organizer and theme creator will be coming to U.S. Chrome users over the next few days, while the writing assistant will be available in next month's Chrome update. The experimental features can be enabled in the Settings section of Chrome by clicking on the three-dot menu and navigating to the Experimental AI page.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/chrome-mac-generative-ai/">Google Chrome for Mac Gets Generative AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-chrome-for-mac-gets-generative-ai-features.2417210/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Mac Turns 40: Read Apple&#039;s Announcement From 1984</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-macintosh-turns-40/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-mac-turns-40-read-apples-announcement-from-1984.2417209/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:31:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-macintosh-turns-40/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Macintosh</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[January 24 marks the 40th anniversary of Steve Jobs unveiling the Macintosh, the first successful mass-marketed computer with a graphical user interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Classic-Mac-40-Years-Old-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932454" /><br/>
The original Macintosh popularized the computer mouse, allowing users to control an on-screen pointer. This point-and-click method of computer navigation was still a novel concept to most people at the time, as personal computers in this era typically had text-based command-line interfaces controlled with a keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
An excerpt from <a href="https://web.stanford.edu/dept/SUL/sites/mac/primary/docs/pr1.html">Apple's press release</a> in 1984:<blockquote>Users tell Macintosh what to do simply by moving a "mouse" — a small pointing device — to select among functions listed in menus and represented by pictorial symbols on the screen. Users are no longer forced to memorize the numerous and confusing keyboard commands of conventional computers. The result is radical ease of use and a significant reduction in learning time. In effect, the Macintosh is a desk-top appliance offering users increased utility and creativity with simplicity.</blockquote>Apple said the Macintosh typically took "only a few hours to learn," and it touted what are now basic computer features, such as a desktop with icons, the ability to use multiple programs in windows, drop-down menus, and copy and paste. <br/>
<br/>
A quote from Jobs in Apple's press release:<blockquote>Macintosh easily fits on a desk, both in terms of its style of operation and its physical design. It takes up about the same amount of desk space as a piece of paper. With Macintosh, the computer is an aid to spontaneity and originality, not an obstacle. It allows ideas and relationships to be viewed in new ways. Macintosh enhances not just productivity, but also creativity.</blockquote>Pricing for the original Macintosh started at &#36;2,495, equivalent to over &#36;7,000 today. Key specs and features included an 8 MHz processor, 128 KB of RAM, a 400 KB floppy disk drive for storage, and serial ports for connecting a printer and other accessories.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's full press release for the Macintosh can be found <a href="https://web.stanford.edu/dept/SUL/sites/mac/primary/docs/pr1.html">on Stanford University's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macintosh/">Macintosh</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-macintosh-turns-40/">The Mac Turns 40: Read Apple&#039;s Announcement From 1984</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-mac-turns-40-read-apples-announcement-from-1984.2417209/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;149 Off Apple&#039;s M2 Mac Mini, Including New Low Price on 512GB Model</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apples-m2-mac-mini-new-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-149-off-apples-m2-mac-mini-including-new-low-price-on-512gb-model.2417205/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:13:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apples-m2-mac-mini-new-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has Apple's M2 Mac mini on sale in all three configurations, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGHGXR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> for the 256GB model, down from &#36;599.00. You'll need to clip an on-page coupon for all of these deals, and after you do you'll find the final discounted prices at the checkout screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/mac-mini-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905646" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple updated the Mac mini one year ago this month, introducing the M2 and M2 Pro chips to the lineup. Unless you have Prime, delivery estimates have begun slipping into late January for these computers, but all models still have plenty of stock available on Amazon at these discounted prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGHGXR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>M2 Mac mini (256GB) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 512GB M2 Mac mini on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGTPMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;675.99</strong></a> with the on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00. This is a new all-time low price on this model of the Mac mini, and there's an estimated January 30 delivery date if ordered today.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGTPMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;123 OFF</div>M2 Mac mini (512GB) for &#36;675.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Amazon has the higher-end M2 Pro Mac mini for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHFS6XX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,149.99</strong></a> with the on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,299.00. This model doesn't go on sale as often as the M2 models, and this is a solid second-best price on the computer.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHFS6XX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>M2 Pro Mac mini (512GB) for &#36;1,149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apples-m2-mac-mini-new-low-price/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;149 Off Apple&#039;s M2 Mac Mini, Including New Low Price on 512GB Model</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-149-off-apples-m2-mac-mini-including-new-low-price-on-512gb-model.2417205/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Accessory Discounts Include &#36;15 Off AirTag 4-Pack, &#36;30 Off MagSafe Duo Charger, and Up to &#36;36 Off Official iPhone Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/iphone-accessory-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-accessory-discounts-include-15-off-airtag-4-pack-30-off-magsafe-duo-charger-and-up-to-36-off-official-iphone-cases.2417201/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:37:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/iphone-accessory-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a couple of deals on iPhone accessories that you can find on Amazon, including low prices on official iPhone cases, AirTags, and the MagSafe Duo Charger.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/airtag-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903337" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the AirTag 4-Pack, Amazon has this accessory for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"><strong>&#36;84.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. This isn't as low as we saw over the holiday season, but it's a solid second-best price on the Bluetooth trackers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;15 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;84.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/magsafe-duo-perspective-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1332" height="750" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-770700" /><br/>
Amazon also has the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB08MWR2NXZ"><strong>&#36;98.50</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is about &#36;1 higher than the previous all-time low price for the accessory on Amazon, so it's still a great deal. The MagSafe Duo Charger can simultaneously charge an iPhone via MagSafe and an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB08MWR2NXZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;98.50</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Amazon has a collection of Apple's FineWoven and Silicone Cases for the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max. You can find these for as low as &#36;21.70 right now on Amazon, and no coupon codes are required to get these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;22.90, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1652P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Silicone Case</a> - &#36;21.70, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9FJTK%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;33.09, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX47H6D%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus Silicone Case</a> - &#36;21.17, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWV4V75%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Silicone Case</a> - &#36;34.36, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1HZST%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Max FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;51.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWVCV1Y%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Max Silicone Case</a> - &#36;34.23, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/iphone-accessory-discounts/">iPhone Accessory Discounts Include &#36;15 Off AirTag 4-Pack, &#36;30 Off MagSafe Duo Charger, and Up to &#36;36 Off Official iPhone Cases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-accessory-discounts-include-15-off-airtag-4-pack-30-off-magsafe-duo-charger-and-up-to-36-off-official-iphone-cases.2417201/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Coming Soon as iPhone App Sideloading Deadline in EU Nears</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/ios-17-4-coming-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-coming-soon-as-iphone-app-sideloading-deadline-in-eu-nears.2417196/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:11:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/ios-17-4-coming-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has until March 6 to fully comply with the EU's Digital Markets Act, which among other things will require the company to allow iPhone users to install apps outside of the App Store. With the deadline for this regulation fast approaching, it is likely that Apple will begin preparing for these changes with iOS 17.4.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
The first iOS 17.4 beta is expected to be released as early as this week, although it is unclear if the app-related changes will be rolled out for testing immediately, or held for later beta versions. Apple is expected to add support for both third-party app stores and app sideloading on the iPhone for users in <a href="https://european-union.europa.eu/principles-countries-history/country-profiles_en">EU countries</a>, including Austria, Belgium, Italy, France, Germany, the Netherlands, Spain, Sweden, and others.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/10/13/apple-says-sideloading-makes-android-less-safe/">strongly</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-files-legal-challenge-against-eu/">opposed</a> the Digital Markets Act and app sideloading over the past few years, citing privacy and security risks for customers. At a tech conference in 2021, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/06/16/tim-cook-vivatech-conference-interview/">Apple CEO Tim Cook said</a> app sideloading "would destroy the security of the iPhone and a lot of the privacy initiatives that we've built into the App Store."<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely do the minimum required to comply with the Digital Markets Act, which may lead to several limitations and guardrails surrounding third-party app stores and app sideloading on the iPhone. We've seen Apple do similar with legal compliance in the U.S., where it recently allowed developers to direct customers to payment methods outside of the ‌App Store‌, but is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">still collecting up to a 27% commission</a> and has several rules.<br/>
<br/>
There are other changes coming to the iPhone in Europe as a result of regulatory pressures. Earlier this week, the European Commission announced that Apple has promised to give third-party payment apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-in-europe/">access to the iPhone's NFC chip in the EU, Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway</a>, which should result in more competition for Apple Pay. It's unclear when Apple will implement this change, but it is likely further away than app sideloading.<br/>
<br/>
We will be digging into iOS 17.4 as soon as it is released, so stay tuned for a closer look at any new features and code changes.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/ios-17-4-coming-soon/">iOS 17.4 Coming Soon as iPhone App Sideloading Deadline in EU Nears</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-coming-soon-as-iphone-app-sideloading-deadline-in-eu-nears.2417196/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Racing to Beat Apple to Non-Invasive Blood Glucose Monitoring Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/samsung-racing-to-beat-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-racing-to-beat-apple-to-non-invasive-blood-glucose-monitoring-technology.2417191/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 06:34:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/samsung-racing-to-beat-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Health Technologies</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung is striving to beat Apple to launch non-invasive blood glucose monitoring technology, as well as continuous blood pressure tracking features, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-22/samsung-races-apple-on-noninvasive-glucose-checks-blood-pressure-monitoring?"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/galaxy-watch6-models.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-904451" /><br/>
The efforts are part of the company's wider push to offer more health capabilities, embodied by the recent announcement of the Galaxy Ring, which touts activity and sleep tracking, with more health features set to arrive later. In a new interview, Samsung's mobile digital health chief Hon Pak said:<blockquote>If we can do continuous blood pressure and glucose, we're in a whole different ballgame. I think that's where everyone is trying to get to. We're putting significant investment toward that.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
We are looking at everything from miniaturization to the various different technology platforms that can do some type of glucose monitoring or anything in between.</blockquote>Pak declined to comment on a time frame for launching either of the features in specific Samsung devices, but believes that non-invasive glucose monitoring technology could come to market in some form within five years. Current blood glucose monitoring systems usually requires pricking the skin, but Apple has reportedly been working on a unique non-invasive approach for over a decade. The company is believed to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/22/apple-blood-glucose-monitoring-technology/">made major progress with the technology</a>, increasing pressure on rivals to provide competing features.<br/>
<br/>
While Samsung smartwatches already offer the ability to determine a user's blood pressure, the capability is not constant and requires specific calibration with a separate blood pressure monitor. Apple is purportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/2024-apple-watch-blood-pressure-sleep-apnea/">planning to add hypertension detection</a> to the Apple Watch later this year with no calibration requirement, but it will not provide exact readings, instead simply informing users that they may have elevated blood pressure. <br/>
<br/>
Like Apple, Samsung is also reportedly exploring adding health sensors to future versions of its earbuds, such as body temperature and heart rate monitoring, since the ear is a closer pathway to the heart than the wrist. Health information from the ear could be combined with data already collected from the wrist for even greater accuracy.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/health-technologies/">Health Technologies</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/samsung-racing-to-beat-apple/">Samsung Racing to Beat Apple to Non-Invasive Blood Glucose Monitoring Technology</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-racing-to-beat-apple-to-non-invasive-blood-glucose-monitoring-technology.2417191/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music to Pay Artists Up to 10% More Royalties for Spatial Audio Content</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-music-more-royalties-spatial-audio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-to-pay-artists-up-to-10-more-royalties-for-spatial-audio-content.2417177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 02:05:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-music-more-royalties-spatial-audio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has introduced royalty incentives to encourage music artists and record labels to publish tracks in Spatial Audio.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/apple-music-spatial-audio-ad.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-804348" /><br/>
In an update sent to partners on Monday seen by <em><a href="https://www.musicbusinessworldwide.com/apple-music-to-pay-artists-up-to-10-higher-royalties-for-music-available-in-spatial-audio/">Music Business Worldwide</a></em>, Apple said it will pay up to 10% more in royalties for Spatial Audio. <br/>
<br/>
The news follows a <em>Bloomberg</em> report in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-to-incentivize-spatial-audio/">December</a> that Apple would this year begin prioritizing streams of songs mixed in Dolby Atmos technology in its streaming calculations.<br/>
<br/>
Listeners do not have to listen to the Spatial Audio version of a song for artists to be eligible for the added benefits, with the availability of tracks in Dolby Atmos being sufficient.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/22/apple-music-spatial-audio-bonus/">9to5Mac</a></em>, Apple says the 10% bonus is a reward for artists delivering the content, and also compensation to recognize the additional time and effort required to mix in Dolby Atmos.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>‌ began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/17/apple-music-spatial-audio-announced/">hosting</a> Spatial Audio tracks in 2021, using Dolby Atmos technology to replicate an in-person music experience with sound coming from various directions around the listener when using compatible speakers or headphones. In February 2022, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/16/apple-music-spatial-audio-lossless-interview/">announced</a> that over half of the service's subscribers used the feature. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-music-more-royalties-spatial-audio/">Apple Music to Pay Artists Up to 10% More Royalties for Spatial Audio Content</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-to-pay-artists-up-to-10-more-royalties-for-spatial-audio-content.2417177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Philips Hue Line Gains New Wall Light, Pendant Cord and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/philips-hue-january-2024-new-lights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-line-gains-new-wall-light-pendant-cord-and-more.2417173/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/philips-hue-january-2024-new-lights/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Philips Hue</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.philips-hue.com/en-us">Philips Hue parent company Signify</a> is announcing several product updates today, with new products, colorways, and U.S. availability for some devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/philips-hue-dymara.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932253" /><br/>
A new wall light, the Philips Hue Dymera, offers two beams of light that shine both up and down. The light, which supports both white shades and color, can illuminate large surfaces and is able to be used both indoors and out.<br/>
<br/>
The Philips Hue Pendant Cord can be used with Hue Filament bulbs or the Hue Ellipse. 3D printed from 55 percent bio-circular material, the pendant cord comes in either black and white and can be purchased in two sizes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/hue-pendant.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932254" /><br/>
For those with the Hue Perifo track lighting, there are new connector options. The T Connector allows rails to run in three directions, while the Flexible Connector allows rails to run in any direction and beyond 90-degree angles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/hue-perifo-flexible-track.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932255" /><br/>
The Hue Being Ceiling Light is now available in black and white, rather than just the aluminum color. The Hue Being supports 50,000 shades of warm-to-cool white light.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/hue-being-light.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932256" /><br/>
Signify is selling the Hue Go Portable Table Lamp in updated colors that include black with an orange grip and white with a teal grip. The silicone grips are designed to make it easier to move the lamp from place to place. The lamp is able to charge in three to four hours with the included charging stand, and the battery lasts for up to 48 hours.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/hue-go-lamp-orange-grip.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932259" /><br/>
The Hue line now includes the Philips Hue Secure Floodlight Camera (U.S. availability is new) and the Hue Secure Camera Starter Kit. The indoor/outdoor Starter Kit has a wired camera, two Philips Hue bulbs, a Hue Bridge, and two Philips Hue Secure contact sensors that let users know when a door is opened or closed. The Floodlight Camera is meant to be used outdoors, and it offers both recording functionality and colored/white Hue light.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/hue-secure-starter-kit.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932261" /><br/>
New app updates are expected for the Security Center of the Hue app in the first half of 2024. Signify is improving security push notifications and the event timeline, as well as options for automatic light and sound alarms when motion is detected.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/hue-floodlight-camera.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932260" /><br/>
The Hue Dymera light is priced at &#36;220 in the U.S. and will be available on February 27. The Hue Perifio connectors will be coming in February and April and will be priced at &#36;35, while the updated Hue Being lights will be available on March 26 and are priced at &#36;220.<br/>
<br/>
The Hue Go table lamps with colored grips are available now <a href="https://www.philips-hue.com/en-us">from the Hue website</a> and are priced at &#36;160. The Hue Pendant Cord is priced starting at 60 euros and will launch in the EU in February.<br/>
<br/>
The Hue Secure Floodlight Camera will be available on February 27 and is priced at &#36;350, and the Hue Secure Starter Kit is priced at &#36;400 and is <a href="https://www.philips-hue.com/en-us">available today</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/philips-hue/">Philips Hue</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/philips-hue-january-2024-new-lights/">Philips Hue Line Gains New Wall Light, Pendant Cord and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-line-gains-new-wall-light-pendant-cord-and-more.2417173/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s What Apple Vision Pro&#039;s Huge Box Looks Like</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/heres-what-apple-vision-pros-box-looks-like/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-what-apple-vision-pros-huge-box-looks-like.2417144/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:05:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/heres-what-apple-vision-pros-box-looks-like/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset comes in a very large box that uses the company's typically distinctive design language, <em>MacRumors</em> has seen. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Box-and-Ref-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-932237" /><em>Render of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> box based on official materials.</em></div><br/>
The packaging, seen by <em>MacRumors</em> in an Apple employee training video, mirrors the design used across many of its other devices that come in boxes that slide open from the top. Those hoping for an exciting new packaging design for the new product line will be disappointed; the top of the cuboid box features a front view of the Vision Pro headset, while each of the longer sides is simply emblazoned with gray Apple "Vision Pro" text.<br/>
<br/>
While the design itself may be fairly unremarkable, the box's size is immense, almost filling the entire lap of a customer. This is because it contains a Solo Knit Band, a Dual Loop Band, a Light Seal, two Light Seal cushions, a cover, an external battery pack, a USB-C charging cable, a power adapter, a polishing cloth, and the Vision Pro headset itself, necessitating an extremely large receptacle. Until now, the size and design of the box has been unknown.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who purchase a Vision Pro in-store are set to have their device's various sized parts boxed up with the headset itself by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> employees. The device is arranged lengthways in the oblong box and comes pre-attached to the Solo Knit Band. Even though the Vision Pro's box is much larger than that of devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, which have a fabric handle on the top to help transport it, there is no grab-handle on the top of Vision Pro's box.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro headset is set to launch on Friday, February 2. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1749199540723535949?s=20">yesterday said</a> that the Vision Pro, like the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, will be accompanied by a commemorative shopping bag for those who buy or pick-up the device in-store. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/heres-what-apple-vision-pros-box-looks-like/">Here&#039;s What Apple Vision Pro&#039;s Huge Box Looks Like</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-what-apple-vision-pros-huge-box-looks-like.2417144/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.3 Features: What&#039;s New in iOS 17.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-features-whats-new-in-ios-17-3.2417139/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 14:09:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-features&#038;post_date=1705972175/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.3, a major update to the iOS operating system that adds Stolen Device Protection, collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists, and a handful of other interesting features.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xUIzfDkQqqo" title="iOS 17.3 Out Now - Everything New!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
In this guide, we've rounded up everything new in the iOS 17.3 update.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stolen_device_protection">Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
Earlier this year, there were news reports about a series of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> thefts where the thief spied on a victim to learn an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s passcode before going on to steal the device, leading to drained bank accounts, stolen passwords, and an untraceable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926120" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ios-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
As a solution, Apple included Stolen Device Protection in iOS 17.3 to add extra security. Should a thief get their hands on both your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and your passcode, Stolen Device Protection prevents total catastrophe. With Stolen Device Protection enabled, accessing passwords in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, turning off Lost Mode, erasing content, and making purchases in Safari requires biometric authentication with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Actions like changing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> password require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; <em>and</em> have a one-hour security delay. So if you (or someone else) tried to change your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; login information, you would need to authenticate with &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; and then wait an hour before the password could be updated. These wait periods are not required when you are in a trusted location like home or work.<br/>
<br/>
Here are actions that require biometric authentication when Stolen Device Protection is activated:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Viewing/using passwords or passkeys saved in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain</li><br/>
 <li>Applying for a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></li><br/>
 <li>Viewing an &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; virtual card</li><br/>
 <li>Turning off Lost Mode</li><br/>
 <li>Erasing all content and settings</li><br/>
 <li>Taking certain Apple Cash and Savings actions in Wallet</li><br/>
 <li>Using payment methods saved in Safari</li><br/>
 <li>Using your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to set up a new device</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Note that these actions do not have a passcode backup, so you can't use a passcode to skirt &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;. Actions that require biometric authentication and have a one-hour security delay include the following:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Changing your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; password</li><br/>
 <li>Updating select &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; account security settings, including adding or removing a trusted device, trusted phone number, Recovery Key, or Recovery Contact</li><br/>
 <li>Changing your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; passcode</li><br/>
 <li>Adding or removing &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>Turning off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a></li><br/>
 <li>Turning off Stolen Device Protection</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Stolen Device Protection is available on all iPhones that are able to run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, which includes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS and newer. It is an opt-in feature that can be turned on in the Settings app by going to &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; &amp; Passcode and toggling on Stolen Device Protection.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="collaborative_apple_music_playlists">Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</h2><br/>
Apple introduced collaborative &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Playlists in iOS 17.3. With this feature, you can take any of your existing playlists or create a new one and then invite others to join in to add songs and listen to the playlist. You can invite friends, family members, and others who share your musical preferences, and there doesn't appear to be a limit on how many people can contribute.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-collaborative-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="5484" height="3085" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918890" /><br/>
We have a <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/pl.u-kaJH7JG97e?a=join&amp;it=zr6IZVEGZ6tVoblq">MacRumors collaborative music playlist</a> available for those who want to join in and share music with other MacRumors readers.<br/>
<br/>
To use the collaboration feature, go to a playlist in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app and then tap on the person icon. You will be able to generate a link that you can send to others, and everyone who is invited can access the playlist. There is an option to approve each person that joins, and leaving this off just opens it up to anyone with the link.<br/>
<br/>
The person who created the playlist can remove people, remove songs, and turn off collaboration at any time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="collaborative_playlist_emoji_reactions">Collaborative Playlist Emoji Reactions</h2><br/>
Apple in iOS 17.3 also added a neat emoji reaction feature that allows listeners to add an emoji to any song that's playing to express their feelings about it. There are standard quick access emoji options like a heart and thumbs up, but with the "+" button, any emoji can be added.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926541" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/apple-music-collaborative-playlist-emoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
When you're listening to a song in the playlist that has emoji reactions added by people who have collaborated on a playlist, those emoji animate as the song begins to play.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="airplay_2_in_hotels">AirPlay 2 in Hotels</h2><br/>
Select hotels now support streaming content from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac directly to an AirPlay-compatible hotel. The feature is designed to allow you to watch content on streaming services without having to log in to a hotel TV with your credentials.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airplay-hotels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898340" /><br/>
<h2 id="applecare">AppleCare</h2><br/>
In the Settings app under General, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> and Warranty section displays the &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj; coverage for all devices signed in with your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="crash_detection">Crash Detection</h2><br/>
Apple has further optimized the Crash Detection feature that is available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models. Apple has been continually tweaking Crash Detection to prevent it from activating during activities that cause movement similar to a car crash.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="tv_show_and_movie_wishlists">TV Show and Movie Wishlists</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2, Apple stopped allowing TV shows and movies to be purchased with the iTunes Store app. iTunes Store wishlists were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/apple-removes-tv-show-movie-wishlists/">an unfortunate casualty</a> of the transition, and they became accessible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/itunes-movies-wishlist-ios-17-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931842" /><br/>
Users who were upset about losing carefully curated wishlists can now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/itunes-movies-tv-show-wishlists-ios-17-3/">access that information</a> again in the iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 updates. Apple has added a new "Go to Wish List" option so users can copy down their movie and TV show watch lists.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For details on all of the features that are included in the &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; update, we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">have a dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-features/">iOS 17.3 Features: What&#039;s New in iOS 17.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-features-whats-new-in-ios-17-3.2417139/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.3 and macOS Sonoma 14.3 Patch WebKit Vulnerability That May Have Been Exploited</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/ios-17-3-webkit-vulnerability-patch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-and-macos-sonoma-14-3-patch-webkit-vulnerability-that-may-have-been-exploited.2417120/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:41:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/ios-17-3-webkit-vulnerability-patch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>macOS Ventura</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.3, iPadOS 17.3, tvOS 17.3, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3, and it's a good idea to update as soon as possible to the new operating systems because the software patches an actively exploited vulnerability.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.3-Buggy-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928685" /><br/>
The updates fix a bug in WebKit that could allow maliciously crafted content to lead to arbitrary code execution. Apple says on its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214059">security support page</a> that it is aware of a report that the issue may have been exploited.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's software releases also address several other security vulnerabilities that were not known to have been used in the wild. iOS 17.3, for example, fixes bugs with the Neural Engine, kernel, Mail, Safari, Shortcuts, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Details on all of the security fixes for each update can be found on Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201222">security support site</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-ventura.239">macOS Ventura</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/ios-17-3-webkit-vulnerability-patch/">iOS 17.3 and macOS Sonoma 14.3 Patch WebKit Vulnerability That May Have Been Exploited</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-and-macos-sonoma-14-3-patch-webkit-vulnerability-that-may-have-been-exploited.2417120/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 With Stolen Device Protection, Collaborative Apple Music Playlists and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-with-stolen-device-protection-collaborative-apple-music-playlists-and-more.2417108/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:04:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, the third major updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> operating system updates that initially came out in September 2023. The software comes more than a month after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-releases-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2/">released iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2</a> with the Journal app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xUIzfDkQqqo" title="iOS 17.3 Out Now - Everything New!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update. Apple has also released iOS 15.8.1 and iOS 16.7.5 for those running older versions of iOS.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.3, Apple is adding Stolen Device Protection to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, limiting access to private information just in case someone gets ahold of both your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and your passcode. It requires biometric authentication to do things like access passwords, turn off Lost Mode, make purchases in Safari, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The update also includes support for AirPlaying content directly to some hotel room TVs, creating collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists with friends and family, and more. Apple's full release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote><b>Stolen Device Protection</b><br/>
- Stolen Device Protection increases security of iPhone and Apple ID by requiring Face ID or Touch ID with no passcode fallback to perform certain actions<br/>
- Security Delay requires Face ID or Touch ID, an hour wait, and then an additional successful biometric authentication before sensitive operations like changing device passcode or Apple ID password can be performed<br/>
<br/>
<b>Lock Screen</b><br/>
- New Unity wallpaper honors Black history and culture in celebration of Black History Month<br/>
<br/>
<b>Music</b><br/>
- Collaborate on playlists allows you to invite friends to join your playlist and everyone can add, reorder, and remove songs<br/>
- Emoji reactions can be added to any track in a collaborative playlist<br/>
<br/>
<b>This update also includes the following improvements:</b><br/>
- AirPlay hotel support lets you stream content directly to the TV in your room in select hotels<br/>
- AppleCare &amp; Warranty in Settings shows your coverage for all devices signed in with your Apple ID<br/>
- Crash detection optimizations (all iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 models)</blockquote><br/>
More details on all of the features that Apple has introduced so far in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">found in our dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/">Apple Releases iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 With Stolen Device Protection, Collaborative Apple Music Playlists and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-with-stolen-device-protection-collaborative-apple-music-playlists-and-more.2417108/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.3 With Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-with-collaborative-apple-music-playlists.2417109/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:03:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3, the third major update to the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that came out last September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 comes over a month after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-2/">release of macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
The ‌‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌ 14.3‌ update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings. There's also a macOS 13.6.4 release for those who are still running macOS Ventura and a macOS 12.7.3 release for those who have macOS Monterey installed. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 brings collaborative playlists in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, so that &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscribers can create playlists with friends and family members. The software also has an updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> & Warranty section in Settings that shows coverage for all devices signed in with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's full release notes for &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 are below:<br/>
<blockquote>macOS Sonoma 14.3 introduces enhancements to Apple Music, as well as other features, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Collaborate on playlists in Apple Music allows you to invite friends to join your playlist and everyone can add, reorder, and remove songs</li><br/>
 	<li>Emoji reactions can be added to any track in a collaborative playlist in Apple Music</li><br/>
 	<li>AppleCare & Warranty in Settings shows your coverage for all devices signed in with your Apple ID</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
</blockquote><br/>
More information on the features that have been introduced in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; to date can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">found in our macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.3 With Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-with-collaborative-apple-music-playlists.2417109/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 10.3 With New Watch Face</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-watchos-10-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-with-new-watch-face.2417115/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:02:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-watchos-10-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.3, the third major update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-watchos-10/">released in September</a>. watchOS 10.3 comes over a month after watchOS 10.2, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-releases-watchos-10-2/">a major update</a> that brought Health data access to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌‌.3 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later by opening it up and going to General & Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
The watchOS 10.3 update includes a new Unity Bloom watch face to celebrate Black History Month.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's release notes also say that the update includes unspecified improvements and bug fixes.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-watchos-10-3/">Apple Releases watchOS 10.3 With New Watch Face</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-with-new-watch-face.2417115/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases tvOS 17.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-tvos-17-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-tvos-17-3.2417114/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:01:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-tvos-17-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released tvOS 17.3, the third major update to the tvOS 17 operating system that came out last September. tvOS 17.3 comes over a month after tvOS 17.2, an update that brought the revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-tv-4k-yellow-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870258" /><br/>
tvOS 17.3 can be downloaded using the Settings app on the ‌&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;‌. Go to System &gt; Software Update to get the new software. ‌&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;‌ owners who have automatic software updates activated will be upgraded to tvOS 17.3 automatically.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are typically minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes. No new features were found in the tvOS 17.3 beta testing process.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares release notes for tvOS <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106336">in its tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each new version of tvOS comes out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-tvos-17-3/">Apple Releases tvOS 17.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-tvos-17-3.2417114/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
