<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 09:01:04 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 18 Public Beta, HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta-homepod-mini-in-new-midnight-color-and-more.2431808/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The public betas of iOS 18 and other upcoming major operating system updates are finally here! Apple has spent the past month refining the betas through developer testing, and it's now time to open them up for broader access ahead of a full public launch several months from now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/top-stories-20jul2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959414" /><br/>
We also got a surprise hardware update this week, but it was one of the most minor updates imaginable – swapping out the Space Gray color of the HomePod mini for a new version in an extremely similar Midnight color. This week also saw us taking a look ahead at the upcoming iPhone 16 and Apple Watch lineups that should now be less than two months way, while we went hands-on with Samsung's new earbuds that have some striking similarities to Apple's AirPods Pro, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases First iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 Public Betas</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/">first public beta of iOS 18 is now available for the iPhone</a>, allowing anyone to test the update for free. We recommend installing the beta on a secondary iPhone, rather than the one that you use daily, as there are often bugs and other issues with pre-release software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Public-Beta-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957836" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">How to Install the iOS 18 Public Beta</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 features more Home Screen and Control Center customization options, a completely redesigned Photos app, the ability to use any emoji as a Tapback in the Messages app, an option to lock apps behind Face ID or Touch ID, and much more. The tentpole feature of iOS 18 is Apple Intelligence, which is Apple's new suite of generative AI features coming to iPhone 15 Pro models and newer later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color</h2><br/>
Apple this week announced that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/">HomePod mini is now available in a new Midnight color</a>, which replaces the Space Gray color previously offered.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/HomePod-Mini-Midnight-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958753" /><br/>
There does not appear to be any other changes to the HomePod mini, which continues to start at &#36;99 in the United States. In fact, Midnight looks nearly identical to Space Gray, so there is little reason for any existing HomePod mini owners to purchase the new color option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Series Is Just Two Months Away: Everything We Know</h2><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">next-generation iPhone 16 series</a> is just two months away from being unveiled, and there are already many rumors for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
Earlier this week, we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">listed everything that we know about the iPhone 16 series</a> based on leaked information, with one key change expected to be larger displays on the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max. Plenty of other new features are expected, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">check out the full list</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2024 Apple Watch Lineup: Key Changes We're Expecting</h2><br/>
Alongside the iPhone 16 series later this year, we can expect the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/">next-generation Apple Watch lineup</a>, including so-called Apple Watch Series 10, Apple Watch Ultra 3, and Apple Watch SE 3 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
Earlier this week, we rounded up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/">key changes to expect from the next Apple Watch lineup</a>, including larger display sizes for some models. As is often the case, new health features like sleep apnea detection have also been rumored.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 Passwords App: All the Features</h2><br/>
iOS 18 features a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/">standalone Passwords app</a> from Apple that surfaces some of the iCloud Keychain functionality built into the Settings app on previous versions of iOS for more convenient access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Passwords-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959050" /><br/>
We recently shared a guide that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/">highlights all of the features built into the Passwords app</a>, which features a simpler layout compared to the previous iCloud Keychain section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple's AirPods Pro 2 vs. Samsung's Galaxy Buds3 Pro</h2><br/>
Samsung last week introduced its latest earbuds, the Galaxy Buds3 Pro, which look quite a bit like Apple's AirPods Pro 2. Given the similarities, we thought we'd <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">compare Samsung's new earbuds to the ‌AirPods Pro‌</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/AirPods-Pro-vs-Galaxy-Buds3-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2298" height="1292" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958664" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">Check out our hands-on video</a> that goes through the design similarities and differences, performance comparisons, and other features to get an idea of how they match head-to-head. Apple users will almost certainly want to stick with AirPods Pro while Android users would want to opt for the Galaxy Buds, but it's always good to see what the competition is up to.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jul-18-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/20/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta/">Top Stories: iOS 18 Public Beta, HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18-public-beta-homepod-mini-in-new-midnight-color-and-more.2431808/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Mirroring in macOS Sequoia and iOS 18: Everything You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-mirroring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-mirroring-in-macos-sequoia-and-ios-18-everything-you-need-to-know.2431770/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:27:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-mirroring&#038;post_date=1721424459/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expanding how its cross-platform Continuity features work in 2024, introducing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring option in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. As the name suggests, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring lets you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with your Mac by mirroring your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s display to your Mac's display. You can manage your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, using your mouse, keyboard, and trackpad with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, notifications, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fBxHMuDhvd4" title="This is Apple&#39;s BEST New Feature &#x1f92f;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
This guide walks through all of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring features and explains how it works.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_basics">iPhone Mirroring Basics</h2><br/>
After upgrading to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, there's a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app in the Dock, and that's how you start an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-interface.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959426" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>From your Mac's Dock, click on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app.</li><br/>
 <li>Click on Continue at the pop-up informational screen.</li><br/>
 <li>Select the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that you want to use if you have more than one &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>Unlock your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a passcode to allow the connection.</li><br/>
 <li>Click on Get Started.</li><br/>
 <li>Use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> on the Mac to authenticate (alternatively, enter your password).</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
When you start up &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring for the first time, you can opt to have it require authentication with every connection or to allow a connection automatically. If you choose automatic authentication, you will not need to authenticate with &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; or a password to use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring when your Mac is unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-settings.jpg" alt="" width="1221" height="555" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959433" /><br/>
Otherwise, you will need to authenticate on your Mac each time you want to use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring. Note that an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; needs to be locked while an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session is in progress, so you can't use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; while it's being mirrored to your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
If your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is not locked and you attempt to initiate &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring from your Mac, you will get a warning that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is in use.<br/>
<br/>
There is no option for launching an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; -- it needs to be done from a Mac. While the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app icon should be in the Dock, if it's not there, you can get to it from the Launchpad or the Applications folder, because it is treated as a standard app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_interface">iPhone Mirroring Interface</h2><br/>
Your full &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; interface is shown as a dedicated app on the Mac, with your wallpaper and app icons all visible and accessible. You can click in to any of your apps and use it on the Mac just like you would on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-mac-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959427" /><br/>
You can get to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> by clicking on the bottom bar, and swap between pages with the trackpad or with a click and drag gesture using a mouse. There are menu options for getting to the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; and for bringing up the app switching interface, but most control is done within the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring window.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-menu-options.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="638" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959432" /><br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_requirements">iPhone Mirroring Requirements</h2><br/>
To use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, you need a Mac that runs &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; and that has an Apple silicon chip (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or later) or a T2 security chip. Macs with T2 security chips are Intel-based and include the following machines:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>2018 and later MacBook Pro</li><br/>
 <li>2018 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></li><br/>
 <li>2020 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro</li><br/>
 <li>2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></li><br/>
 <li>2019 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
These Macs have Apple silicon chips:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>2020 and later &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>2020 and later &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>2021 and later &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>2021 and later MacBook Pro (14 and 16 inch)</li><br/>
 <li>2020 13-inch MacBook Pro</li><br/>
 <li>2022 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a></li><br/>
 <li>2023 &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj;</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Any &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that runs &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; works with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models</li><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models</li><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> models</li><br/>
 <li>All &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models</li><br/>
 <li>All &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 models</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS and XS Max</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> (2nd and 3rd gen)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac need to be signed into the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, and two-factor authentication must be enabled for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring feature to work. You will also need to turn on Bluetooth and Wi-Fi, and the two devices will need to be near each other.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-app-switcher.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1352" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959434" /><br/>
During an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring session, your Mac and your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; need to be close to one another, essentially in the same room.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="privacy_and_security">Privacy and Security</h2><br/>
You need to be signed into the same &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and your Mac for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring to work. While &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring is active, your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; does not need to be unlocked. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-in-use-notification.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="1323" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959428" /><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can remain tucked away in a pocket or a bag while you control it from your Mac, so no one can access it or see what you're doing with it. You do need to have your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; close enough to your Mac for there to be a Bluetooth connection, likely for security purposes. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="using_a_mouse_and_keyboard_with_iphone">Using a Mouse and Keyboard with iPhone</h2><br/>
Your Mac's keyboard, trackpad, and mouse can be used with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which is useful if you need to type something lengthy in an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-ring-app.jpg" alt="" width="2415" height="1454" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959429" /><br/>
<h2 id="audio_camera_and_microphone">Audio, Camera, and Microphone</h2><br/>
If you play a video on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; while &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring is enabled, the audio comes through your Mac. You can't turn on the Camera app or use the microphone, though.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_notifications_on_mac">iPhone Notifications on Mac</h2><br/>
With &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring turned on, incoming &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications show up right alongside your Mac notifications in the Notification Center at the upper right hand corner of the Mac's display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-notifications.jpg" alt="" width="759" height="871" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959431" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications are denoted with a small &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; icon, but they otherwise look like native Mac notifications.<br/>
<br/>
You can click on a notification and open up the app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, interacting with it directly from the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="standby">StandBy</h2><br/>
While your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is being mirrored to your Mac, it can be on a charger and in StandBy mode, displaying the time and other information.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="drag_and_drop">Drag and Drop</h2><br/>
Later this year, Apple plans to add &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring's best feature, file transfers. You will be able to transfer files, photos, and videos from your Mac to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and vice versa using drag and drop gestures.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that it will work just like dragging files from one Mac app to another.<br/>
<br/>
While drag and drop has yet to be implemented, you can sort of work around this by using AirDrop to move photos and files from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to your Mac, initiating AirDrop from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; without having to unlock it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_mirroring_limitations">iPhone Mirroring Limitations</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring will not work if the Mac is using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> to stream music or video content to another device, or if <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sidecar/">Sidecar</a> is enabled with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. Continuity Camera cannot be enabled either, so if you're using your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a webcam for your Mac, you can't use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring at the same time.<br/>
<br/>
Attempting to watch movies and TV shows from some apps like Hulu and Netflix does not work, with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app showing just a blank black screen, likely due to DRM restrictions.<br/>
<br/>
There is no option to resize the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring window, and you can't manually move it into landscape orientation. If an app or a game is displayed in landscape orientation, the window will shift into landscape.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-landscape-mode.jpg" alt="" width="1926" height="1083" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959435" /><br/>
You can delete apps when using &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring by going to the Settings app, but apps cannot be deleted from the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;. You also can't rearrange apps because there's no option to get into the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; (or Lock Screen) editing interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-mirroring-safari.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1250" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959436" /><br/>
Control Center and Notification Center are also inaccessible.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For more on the new features that Apple is adding in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">we have a dedicated iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-mirroring/">iPhone Mirroring in macOS Sequoia and iOS 18: Everything You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-mirroring-in-macos-sequoia-and-ios-18-everything-you-need-to-know.2431770/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Prepares for 2024 Summer Olympics With Updates to Maps, TV Coverage, Featured Apps and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/summer-olympics-apple-maps-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-prepares-for-2024-summer-olympics-with-updates-to-maps-tv-coverage-featured-apps-and-more.2431769/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:56:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/summer-olympics-apple-maps-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week updated the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> app in Paris in preparation for the 2024 Summer Olympics, which are set to begin on Friday, July 26. All permanent venues, such as the Parc de Princes and Centre Aquatique Olympique, are displayed as custom, hand-built 3D landmarks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/2024-summer-olympics-maps-update.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959419" /><br/>
Iconic sites like Gare de l'Est, Pont d'Iéna, and Place de la Madeleine are also rendered with more detail, and for the first time, the Maps app is displaying pop up locations that include temporary venues, souvenir shops, and public gathering sites. support for pop up locations will help attendees find important places for the summer games.<br/>
<br/>
All game locations and ceremony sites have special icons to help visitors find where they need to be, and Apple says that Maps displays all of the latest updates on road closures and advisories due to the games to help users navigate the city. There are curated Maps Guides for restaurants, hotels, and shopping, with dozens of new Guides from Le Bonbon, Le Fooding, Radio France, Madame Figaro, and My Little Paris.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the Maps updates, Apple plans to feature stories spotlighting popular events like gymnastics and swimming in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and it recommends that people download the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/paris-2024-olympics/id808794344">official Paris 2024 Olympics app</a> to follow along. Sports-themed mobile games and health and fitness apps will be highlighted as well.<br/>
<br/>
Full coverage of Olympic events will be available through the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/peacock-tv-stream-tv-movies/id1508186374">Peacock</a> and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nbc-sports/id542511686">NBC Sports apps</a>, which can be downloaded from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. A daily Olympic recap will be available on Peacock for fans in the U.S., offering customized playlists of highlights from relevant events from the prior day.<br/>
<br/>
There is a dedicated NBC Olympics Hub in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app for quick access to NBC coverage.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> will feature shows and episodes celebrating sports and the power of gathering together in Paris, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a> <a href="https://apple.news/TKLrmq8dkSgOQOchItCi2FA">will have curated coverage</a> of the events and the stars of the games along with a <a href="https://apple.news/2024_olympics_event_schedule">schedule of events</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> also plans to publish a Guide to French Music, which is an in-depth editorial feature of all the musical genres in France. It will go live later this week.<br/>
<br/>
The Summer Olympics will begin next Friday with an Opening Ceremony that begins at 1:30 p.m. Eastern Time or 7:30 p.m. Paris time. Soccer games will begin on July 24, with badminton, handball, rowing, volleyball, fencing, field hockey, shooting, diving, and gymnastics set to begin on July 27. Events will continue until August 11.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/summer-olympics-apple-maps-update/">Apple Prepares for 2024 Summer Olympics With Updates to Maps, TV Coverage, Featured Apps and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-prepares-for-2024-summer-olympics-with-updates-to-maps-tv-coverage-featured-apps-and-more.2431769/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Talking Vision Pro and iOS 18 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro-and-ios-18-beta.2431763/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:59:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/revisiting-apple-vision-pro-ios-18-public-beta-impressions/id1602394741?i=1000662756752">The MacRumors Show</a>, we revisit the experience of using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> and talk through our first impressions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> public beta. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fMftJc2guqw?si=hdalsHnMQdTxrKZe" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple's Vision Pro headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/12/apple-vision-pro-launched-uk-canada-france-germany/">now available</a> in the UK, Canada, France, Germany, Australia, China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore, prompting renewed interest in the spatial computing device. We discuss our thoughts on the best aspects of the Vision Pro, such as immersive video, spatial photos and video, gestures, and UI design, as well as its shortcomings, such as weight and comfort, video passthrough in dark environments, limited content, and general usefulness.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/">first public beta of iOS 18</a>, bringing the new software to the general public for the first time since the Worldwide Developers Conference in June. Apple has seeded three developer betas so far, and the first public beta includes the same content that's in the third developer beta. We talk over our thoughts on &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;'s new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> and Control Center customization features, the redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Let us know what you think about the experience of using the Vision Pro headset and the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta in the comments. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/12/the-macrumors-show-samsung-challenge-to-apple/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about all of the major new device announcements from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6/">Samsung's 2024 Galaxy Unpacked event</a> and how they compare to Apple's offerings.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro/">The MacRumors Show: Talking Vision Pro and iOS 18 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-talking-vision-pro-and-ios-18-beta.2431763/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods Pro and Max Get New Low Prices, Plus Big Discounts on iPads and MacBooks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-7-19-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-pro-and-max-get-new-low-prices-plus-big-discounts-on-ipads-and-macbooks.2431760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:37:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-7-19-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day took place earlier this week, and it introduced huge discounts on a wide variety of Apple products, including AirPods Max, MacBook Pro, and iPad Pro. Even though Prime Day has ended, we're still tracking quite a few of these record low prices as we head into the weekend, so if you missed out be sure to check out the deals below before they're gone for good.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-hero-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959384" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/airpods-max-pro-2-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959389" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;154 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;154 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
As is usual during big discount events, some of the best deals this week could be found on Apple's AirPods, and most of them are still available right now on Amazon. You'll find the AirPods Pro 2 and AirPods Max at all-time low prices today on Amazon, and the AirPods 2 at a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/pencil-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959387" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;19 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;109.99, down from the regular price of &#36;129.00. This is a new record low price for the accessory, beating the previous sale price by &#36;10. The Apple Pencil 2 is also at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/macbook-pro-m3-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959391" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;700 off MacBook Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>16-inch M3 Max MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;2,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's and Amazon's deals include all-time low prices on the 14-inch and 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro, and the best discounts will be found on the larger screen computers. The 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro is currently discounted by &#36;500 for all customers on Best Buy, but if you have a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, you can add up to an extra &#36;200 off select models.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,399.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">only at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,899.00 (&#36;600 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,299.00 (&#36;600 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,799.00 (&#36;700 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;3,299.00 (&#36;700 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">only at Best Buy for members</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m2-macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959392" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;200 off MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmHz6LU8QC4">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmHz6LU8QC4"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmHz8wfGa0G"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon and Best Buy are taking &#36;200 off the previous generation M2 MacBook Air this week, starting at &#36;799.00 for 256GB and rising to &#36;999.00 for 512GB. Both of these are all-time low prices for the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ipad-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959393" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;385 off the new M4 iPad Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>11-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;919.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week had all-time low prices on a few models of the 11-inch and 13-inch M4 iPad Pro, and most are still available. Prices start at &#36;919.00 for the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and also include multiple cellular tablets. Our original post has the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">full list of tablets on sale</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ipad-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959394" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking &#36;50 off the Wi-Fi models of the 2022 iPad, starting at &#36;299.00 for 64GB Wi-Fi. You'll also find both cellular devices on sale this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-7-19-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods Pro and Max Get New Low Prices, Plus Big Discounts on iPads and MacBooks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-pro-and-max-get-new-low-prices-plus-big-discounts-on-ipads-and-macbooks.2431760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Rumored to Use Same Rear Chassis as iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-use-same-rear-chassis-as-iphone-16.2431751/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:16:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will adopt the same rear chassis manufacturing process for the iPhone SE 4 that it is using for the upcoming standard iPhone 16, claims a new rumor coming out of China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iPhone-SE-4-Vertical-Camera-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959379" /><br/>
According to the Weibo-based leaker "<a href="https://weibo.com/5821279480/Oof995QJj">Fixed Focus Digital</a>," the backplate manufacturing process for the iPhone SE 4 is "exactly the same" as the standard model in Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 lineup, which is expected to be released in September. The iPhone SE 4, meanwhile, is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/when-to-expect-the-next-iphone-se/">expected</a> to arrive in the spring.<br/>
<br/>
The latest claim casts doubt on a previous rumor suggesting Apple would use a modified iPhone 14 chassis as the basis for a fourth-generation iPhone SE. In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-se-4-iphone-14-chassis/">November 2023</a>, <em>MacRumors</em> learned from a source close to Apple's manufacturing process that the dimensions of the ‌iPhone SE‌ 4 "perfectly matched" those of the base model ‌iPhone 14 <em>in its current stage</em>‌. <br/>
<br/>
While it's still unclear what may have led to the change, it's possible that Apple chose to adopt its newer rear chassis process for the more affordable SE model to achieve economy of scale at the point of production as the manufacture of iPhone 14 models winds down towards retirement. <br/>
<br/>
However, it could also indicate a change to the camera system on the fourth-generation iPhone SE. Unlike the ‌iPhone 14‌, the ‌iPhone SE‌ 4 was previously rumored to include a single 48-megapixel rear camera with a custom backplate for the device to account for the design change. <br/>
<br/>
In contrast, for the iPhone 16 models, Apple is planning a new vertical camera lens arrangement that is a departure from the diagonal lens setup found on iPhone 15 models. The new orientation will presumably allow the standard iPhone 16 models to capture Spatial Video for the Vision Pro headset. Adopting the same backplate for the iPhone SE 4 would seem to suggest it will feature the same dual camera setup, although we haven't heard any rumors specifically claiming that this is in Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to be targeting a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/iphone-se-4-face-id-price-rumor/">sub-&#36;500 starting price</a> for its fourth-generation iPhone SE model, despite a raft of rumored upgrades coming to the more affordable device. Touch ID and the Home button will be replaced by Face ID and a display notch, while the display size will increase from 4.7 inches to 6.1 inches. Other features expected for the next iPhone SE include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/">USB-C port and an Action button</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The third-generation iPhone SE was released in March 2022, so there is likely pent-up demand for a new model that includes some of the latest features of Apple's flagship iPhone models. For everything else we know about the iPhone SE 4, be sure to check our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/iphone-se-4-likely-to-use-iphone-16-chassis/">iPhone SE 4 Rumored to Use Same Rear Chassis as iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-use-same-rear-chassis-as-iphone-16.2431751/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Crowdstrike Says Global IT Outage Impacting Windows PCs, But Mac and Linux Hosts Not Affected</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/crowdstrike-says-global-it-outage-impacting-windows-pcs-but-mac-and-linux-hosts-not-affected.2431738/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 03:12:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Windows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A widespread system failure is currently affecting numerous Windows devices globally, causing critical boot failures across various industries, including banks, rail networks, airlines, retailers, broadcasters, healthcare, and many more sectors. The issue, manifesting as a Blue Screen of Death (BSOD), is preventing computers from starting up properly and forcing them into continuous recovery cycles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bsod.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959336" /><br/>
The cause of the failure has been identified as an update to Crowdstrike Falcon antivirus software installed on Windows 10 PCs, but Mac and Linux machines running the same cybersecurity software have been spared. <a href="https://www.crowdstrike.com">Crowdstrike</a>, which specializes in endpoint security protection for corporate networks, has just <a href="https://x.com/George_Kurtz/status/1814235001745027317">released the following statement</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>"Crowdstrike is actively working with customers impacted by a defect found in a single content update for Windows hosts.<br/>
<br/>
"Mac and Linux hosts are not impacted. This is not a security incident or cyberattack.<br/>
<br/>
"The issue has been identified, isolated and a fix has been deployed.<br/>
<br/>
"We refer customers to the support portal for the latest updates and will continue to provide complete and continuous updates on our website.<br/>
<br/>
"We further recommend organisations ensure they're communicating with Crowdstrike representatives through official channels.<br/>
<br/>
"Our team is fully mobilized to ensure the security and stability of Crowdstrike customers."</blockquote>Unfortunately, the nature of the problem means that fixing it isn't as simple as installing a patch. The workaround to break the infinite boot cycle on affected Windows machines involves manually booting into safe mode, navigating to the CrowdStrike directory, and deleting the system file that caused the problem. As such, it could be a while before all services impacted by the content update are back up and running. <br/>
<br/>
For those who have a Windows machine that has succumbed to the botched update (now rolled back), Crowdstrike has outlined the following steps system admins need to take to get back up and running: <br/>
<ol><li>Boot Windows into Safe Mode or the Windows Recovery Environment.</li><br/>
<li>Navigate to the C:\Windows\System32\drivers\CrowdStrike directory.</li><br/>
<li>Locate the file matching 'C-00000291*.sys', and delete it.</li><br/>
<li>Boot the host normally.</li></ol><br/>
As expected, Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">system status webpage</a> shows no issues with its services, however there have been scattered reports of problems with contactless payments across some businesses, which could prevent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> transactions from being processed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/windows/">Windows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/19/global-it-outage-limited-to-windows-pcs/">Crowdstrike Says Global IT Outage Impacting Windows PCs, But Mac and Linux Hosts Not Affected</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/crowdstrike-says-global-it-outage-impacting-windows-pcs-but-mac-and-linux-hosts-not-affected.2431738/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Eve Launches Matter-Enabled Eve Weather Smart Station</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/eve-weather-matter-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eve-launches-matter-enabled-eve-weather-smart-station.2431717/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:47:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/eve-weather-matter-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		<category>Matter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Smart home company Eve Systems today announced the launch of a new version of the Eve Weather that offers Matter support. With Matter, the new Eve Weather can be added to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> or smart home setups from other companies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/eve-weather.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959321" /><br/>
Eve Weather is a small cube-shaped accessory that is designed to provide outdoor weather temperature, humidity, and the local 12-hour weather trend. A display at the front allows you to see temperature and humidity at a glance, but the data also syncs to the Eve app.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; integration, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> can be used to provide details on the outdoor weather conditions, and the data can be used to trigger &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; automations. Eve Weather offers IPX4 water resistance so it can be kept outdoors year-round and displayed anywhere.<br/>
<br/>
Eve Weather can be purchased <a href="https://www.evehome.com/en-us">from the Eve website</a> or <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FEve-Weather-Matter-temperature-resistance%2Fdp%2FB0D81BVH6P">from Amazon.com</a> for &#36;80. Eve is continuing to sell the &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; version of the device as well for those who do not have a Matter-enabled hub, which includes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/matter/">Matter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/eve-weather-matter-support/">Eve Launches Matter-Enabled Eve Weather Smart Station</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eve-launches-matter-enabled-eve-weather-smart-station.2431717/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Gains 8 Million Global Subscribers Amid Price Hikes and Push to Ad-Supported Streaming</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/netflix-global-subscriber-increase-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-gains-8-million-global-subscribers-amid-price-hikes-and-push-to-ad-supported-streaming.2431710/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:59:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/netflix-global-subscriber-increase-ads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix has gained more than 8 million global paid subscribers since April, according to new subscriber information included in the company's second quarter earnings results [<a href="https://s22.q4cdn.com/959853165/files/doc_financials/2024/q2/FINAL-Q2-24-Shareholder-Letter.pdf">PDF</a>]. With the jump in paid subscriptions, Netflix now has a total of 277.65 million paid subscribers around the world, marking 16.5 percent year-over-year growth.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884791" /><br/>
Ad tier memberships increased 34 percent quarter-over-quarter, thanks to Netflix pushing its ad-supported tier. Netflix eliminated its cheapest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/netflix-removes-basic-plan/">ad-free "Basic" subscription tier</a> last year, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/03/netflix-phasing-out-basic-ads-free-plan/">earlier in July</a>, the company began warning customers in the UK and Canada that they would need to move to a new plan.<br/>
<br/>
In the United States, the Basic plan was priced at &#36;9.99 per month, but the cheapest ad-free Netflix plan is now priced at &#36;15.49 a month. Netflix had been allowing customers that were already on the Basic plan to continue using it, but that is being phased out. Ad tier memberships grew 34 percent from the first quarter to the second quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix with ads is priced at &#36;6.99 per month, and it includes between four and five minutes of ads per hour. Ads vary in length from 15 to 30 seconds and play before and during TV shows and movies. The company says that it will soon test an in-house ad tech platform in Canada, with plans to launch it broadly in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix saw 17 percent growth in revenue year-over-year, and it is expecting overall 2024 growth to be at 14 to 15 percent. Netflix is expecting ad memberships to increase in 2025 and beyond, with ad revenue becoming a more meaningful contributor to its business.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/netflix-global-subscriber-increase-ads/">Netflix Gains 8 Million Global Subscribers Amid Price Hikes and Push to Ad-Supported Streaming</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-gains-8-million-global-subscribers-amid-price-hikes-and-push-to-ad-supported-streaming.2431710/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Bird Buddy is a Fun iPhone-Connected Smart Bird Feeder</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/bird-buddy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bird-buddy-is-a-fun-iphone-connected-smart-bird-feeder.2431702/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 13:32:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/bird-buddy&#038;post_date=1721345527/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Most iPhone-connected smart home products are more for convenience than fun, but Bird Buddy, a bird feeder that sends pictures to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, is definitely in the latter category. When I first came across the Bird Buddy, I thought it would be an interesting novelty product to give as a gift, but it turned out to be one of my all-time favorite smart devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-main-image.jpg" alt="" width="1630" height="917" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959300" /><br/>
<h2>Design and Components</h2><br/>
Made from a sturdy plastic material, the Bird Buddy comes in either blue or yellow. The housing is designed around a camera, which is placed front and center to capture images of birds that come by to eat from the feeder. A tray holds the seed, and there's a small perch for birds to stand on to eat. There's a seed reservoir at the back to replenish what's in the tray as it's consumed, and a roof protects the seed from the elements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-components.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959301" /><br/>
There are two versions of the Bird Buddy, one with a solar roof for charging the camera and one with a standard plastic roof. If you have a semi-sunny spot for the Bird Buddy, I recommend the solar roof. I have my feeder in a spot that gets several hours of sun per day, and I've never had to take the camera out to charge it. A family member also has the solar model (that I gifted), and it is in a much shadier spot. With the shade cover, the Bird Buddy needs to be charged every month to every other month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-image-examples.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="880" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959442" /><br/>
Both of these feeders see multiple visits per day, though the one located in the shade that needs charging more often has an almost constant stream of bird visitors. Without a solar roof, Bird Buddy says that the battery lasts for 5 to 15 days, so the solar roof does eliminate the hassle of frequent charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-camera.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959302" /><br/>
The Bird Buddy disassembles into its component pieces for charging and cleaning. You can remove the camera module and bring it into the house, but doing so requires taking the feeder down, opening up the back, and pulling the camera out. It charges with USB-C, and takes two to four hours to charge to full. With the solar roof, you connect the USB-C port on the Bird Buddy to the USB-C port on the solar charger, so you could do the same thing with a DIY setup, adding your own solar panel. Alternatively, you could use an extension cord and keep it plugged in all the time, though Bird Buddy only recommends this for protected areas like a balcony.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-assembly.jpg" alt="" width="1800" height="1914" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959309" /><br/>
Setup wasn't difficult, but the lights on the Bird Buddy are super hard to see, so when you need a blinking red light to pair, it's hard to tell that it's blinking. I didn't have issues other than that, and with the solar version, it's a little tricky getting the camera plugged in. You need to connect the USB-C cable from the solar panel to the Bird Buddy camera, routing the cable through a small spot a the top of the feed bin. I was worried about this set up, but it's held up to heavy rain and the cabling has not gotten wet.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-setup-process.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1071" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959303" /><br/>
Along with the solar roof, camera module, and feeder housing, the Bird Buddy comes with a seed scoop for adding bird seed, a hanger, and a pole mount, so there are multiple options for mounting. I bought a pole from Wild Birds Unlimited that I read on the internet was compatible with the mount, but it was not, so I hung it up. If you want to mount the Bird Buddy on a pole, you will need a pole with a 0.97-inch inner diameter (a common size).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959304" /><br/>
Size wise, the Bird Buddy is comparable to smaller bird feeders on the market, and it holds about four cups of seed in the reservoir and tray. In my experience, that's about a pound of bird seed. Adding and refilling seed can be done by opening up the back hatch and using the seed scoop to pour it in. I only need to refill around once every two weeks or so because I have other bird feeders, but that will vary based on how many visitors you're getting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-solar-roof.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959307" /><br/>
You need to make sure the Bird Buddy is in range of your Wi-Fi router because it does need a constant Wi-Fi connection and a 2.4GHz band.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Add-Ons</h2><br/>
The size of the seed tray and the small size of the included perch will likely limit most visits to smaller birds like finches and sparrows, but Bird Buddy sells a perch extender for &#36;24. I did go ahead and pick this up, and I like it because it gives the birds more space to perch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-add-ons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1516" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959305" /><br/>
There's also a 3-in-1 nutrition set for &#36;29, but I wasn't a fan of it. It includes an add-on seed/water dish that you can use for seeds or jelly, or attach to an included water bottle. There's also a set of prongs where you can add an orange or another fruit if you want to attract orioles. You can only use one of these at a time, and while the tray itself was fine, the water bottle took up too much perch space and blocked the camera.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-seed-pourer.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959306" /><br/>
For &#36;14, you can get a suet ball holder too, which can attract more types of birds. The suet ball also blocks the camera somewhat, so it's a bit of a tradeoff. If you want to mount the Bird Buddy to the wall, you'll need the &#36;24 Wall Mount, which is not included with the base purchase.<br/>
<br/>
If you have access to a 3D printer, I have seen several Bird Buddy STLs for add-on perches and seed holders, plus neat options like a fence to keep birds from perching and eating out of view.<br/>
<br/>
There is no built-in protection from squirrels, raccoons, and other critters on the Bird Buddy, which is a downside. You either need to have a setup that puts the feeder out of range of these creatures or you need to accept them as visitors. The pole that I use has a baffle that blocks squirrels from climbing it, and it seems to be far enough away from nearby surfaces so the squirrels can't leap to the feeder. Bird Buddy does not sell poles or baffles at this time, though it looks like there's going to be a pole setup released later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-bird-feeder.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959312" /><br/>
While Bird Buddy sells birdseed, any kind of bird food can go in the device. There are some limitations, like full-sized in-shell peanuts likely wouldn't fit because of the opening size, but any kind of bird seed or meal worm mix should work. I have not tried the Bird Buddy bird seed, as I've just bought seed locally from a nearby bird store.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bird Visits</h2><br/>
It took a good two weeks for birds to start visiting my Bird Buddy after I set it up, and there are placement considerations to take into account. Bird Buddy's website has <a href="https://mybirdbuddy.com/ultimate-guide/">instructions and tips</a> on attracting birds. In addition to being positioned to keep squirrels and similar critters away, the Bird Buddy will be more successful near a water source like a bird bath and with trees and bushes that birds can hide in to escape predators.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="495" height="880" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/t8ATklej98s" title="Bird Buddy Demo Video" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
I don't have the Bird Buddy in the most ideal location because I wanted it near a window where my cat can watch it, but it's still attracting birds, so there's some wiggle room. I have a cohort of house finches that dominate my bird feeders right now, but I have seen a goldfinch a few times and a wren. There are robins and a ton of other birds around, but the combination of nearness to my windows, a nearby resident hawk, and the finches are keeping them away.<br/>
<br/>
A family member who has a Bird Buddy much further than the house near a forested area gets frequent cardinal, dove, and sparrow visits, plus we've seen bluebirds, nuthatches, chickadees, and towhees.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-on-pole.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959308" /><br/>
You could probably put it anywhere and have good luck on bird visits, though the most variety will come with offering the best conditions and food options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bird Buddy App</h2><br/>
The Bird Buddy is just a bird feeder with a camera, and there are many on the market, but it's the app that elevates the experience and sets it apart. Bird Buddy is able to recognize the birds that are visiting your feeder, letting you know what kind of bird you're getting, so it becomes a fun game trying to attract new birds. I was <em>thrilled</em> when I recently had visits from a pair of goldfinches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-postcards.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1434" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959313" /><br/>
It's a lot of fun to get an alert about a new type of bird, and you can collect snapshots of your favorites so you can keep a log of the species that you've seen.<br/>
<br/>
While you can view a livestream of the Bird Buddy, it's mostly set up to take snapshots when birds visit and then send "postcards" for you to view at various times throughout the day. Postcards include several photos and a video of the visit, and they are limited to the best images captured so that Bird Buddy doesn't send an excessive number of notifications.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-livestream.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="2152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959314" /><br/>
I get between two and four notifications a day, usually a couple visit notifications and then a wrap-up notification at the end of the day. Bird Buddy will also sometimes send notifications for a feeding frenzy so you can tune in and watch live. In the app, there are notification customization settings. Smart push notifications (the default) alert you to only the most "essential and intriguing updates" with an end-of-day recap, but there is an option to get all push notifications.<br/>
<br/>
There are separate battery preserving options that change how many postcards you get, so at max, you'll see more recordings. You can also ignore mystery visitors (where a bird can't be identified), or ignore a certain type of bird if you see the same thing over and over again. Notifications can also be paused for a set period of time, so there's a lot of control over what the app is sending.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to viewing your own Bird Buddy, you can be invited to receive postcards from other Bird Buddy owners, and you can invite people to see yours. You can invite three people to view your Bird Buddy feed in total. You can also choose to join popular bird feeders for a 72-hour period, where you receive postcards from that feeder. Pictures that you get from the Bird Buddy app can be saved to your smartphone, shared with other people, and shared on social media.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-snapshots.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1317" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959311" /><br/>
Bird Buddy has a "BB TV" feed where you can see videos from all around the world, swiping through them to swap to a new video, sort of like birdie TikTok. It's a fun way to see different birds, and to get a look at what kinds of birds might be in your own area that you can attract. You can save postcards, and tap into the Collection section of the app to see your images.<br/>
<br/>
Viewing an image in the Collection provides information on that bird species, such as their favorite foods, where they're found, fun facts, personality traits, and lifespan. There are even recordings of their songs and calls.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-collection.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1434" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959315" /><br/>
You do not need a subscription to use the Bird Buddy app, and viewing pictures of your own visits and birds from around the world is entirely free. There are, however, some "Pro" app features that are available as an upgrade. I bought a Pro subscription, but I'm not sure if it's something that I'll keep using.<br/>
<br/>
Pro lets you invite more people to your own feeder, view more remote feeders, ignore select bird species (possibly one of the most useful options), see higher-resolution video recordings, and get more postcards with frenzy mode. There are also new AI options that are still in the early stages of development. Bird Buddy can alert you to sick birds and hide their images, but since turning it on, it's been telling me every bird with a messy food beak is ill, which is inaccurate. I ultimately had to turn it off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-feeds.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1432" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959316" /><br/>
There's also a feature for "naming" frequent visitors, which I've been testing. I've named several of the house finches that come by, but Bird Buddy can't really tell them apart, which is not surprising because I'm not sure I can either. It will send a notification asking if a bird is a certain one that you've named, but it's up to you to confirm by comparing photographs. I have three female finches that I've named, but it only ever asks about one, so it's not a feature I've found particularly useful. You can get alerts about non-bird spottings like squirrels and lizards with Pro, and connect to Amazon Alexa devices to see images and hear bird sounds to bring the outdoors inside.<br/>
<br/>
Other standard app features include notifications for cleaning and charging, assembly and maintenance documents, and Bird Buddy support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/bird-buddy-ai-features.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="2121" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959310" /><br/>
Note that you need the Bird Buddy app to use the feeder and view the feed. It is not available for viewing on the web, and there is no Mac/PC version of the app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
The Bird Buddy is a lot of fun. I initially got one as a gift for someone who is hard to shop for, and it turned out to be a hit. We have regular conversations about bird visits, bird food, and thwarting squirrels. I'd definitely recommend it for that kind of situation, and any nature lover or gardener would likely be thrilled with it.<br/>
<br/>
I enjoy my daily postcard recap and checking out the birds that have visited over the course of the day, even when it's a bird I've seen dozens of times (aka house finches). There are bird squabbles, messy eating videos, acrobatics, and other activity to get into. I've found myself searching for the optimal bird food, adding additional bird feeders, and researching birds nearby, so it can get a little involved.<br/>
<br/>
On the downside, the Bird Buddy is expensive (definitely wait for a sale), and there are no size options if you want to attract bigger birds or use other kinds of feeders with the camera. The subscription features are a little hit or miss, and some of the new AI additions are very much in the early stages of development.<br/>
<br/>
There are a lot of bundle options, but I'd recommended the solar roof model and the add-on extended perch over the other add-ons.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Bird Buddy can be purchased from <a href="https://mybirdbuddy.com/shop/">the Bird Buddy website</a> or <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBird-Feeder-Resolution-Beautiful-Experience%2Fdp%2FB0C8TJTBMR">from Amazon</a>. It is priced at &#36;239 for the standard model and &#36;299 for the model with a solar roof, though there are often sales.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Bird Buddy provided MacRumors with a Smart Bird Feeder with Solar Roof for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/bird-buddy/">Bird Buddy is a Fun iPhone-Connected Smart Bird Feeder</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bird-buddy-is-a-fun-iphone-connected-smart-bird-feeder.2431702/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launching New Apple Immersive Videos, Films and Concerts for Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-immersive-videos-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launching-new-apple-immersive-videos-films-and-concerts-for-vision-pro.2431680/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:32:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-immersive-videos-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/new-apple-immersive-video-series-and-films-premiere-on-vision-pro/">today announced</a> the upcoming debut of multiple new immersive video experiences designed for the Vision Pro headset, which are available starting this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-immersive-video-boundless.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1224" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959296" /><br/>
"Boundless," which premieres tonight at 6:00 p.m. Pacific Time, features "once-in-a-lifetime trips," starting with a hot air balloon ride episode. Viewers will be able to see the landscape of Cappadocia, Türkiye. A second episode, "Arctic Surfing," will come out this fall.<br/>
<br/>
In August, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> will get a new installment of "Wild Life," a nature documentary series that brings viewers up close to "some of the most charismatic creatures on the planet." The new episode will feature Kenya's Sheldrick Wildlife Trust, where keepers look after orphaned elephants. An episode later in the year will feature a group of divers in the Bahamas.<br/>
<br/>
In September, Apple will debut the first episode of "Elevated," an aerial travel series that "whisks viewers around iconic vistas from staggering heights" that include volcanoes, waterfalls, and more in Hawaii. A second episode will feature an autumn scene in New England.<br/>
<br/>
Later in 2024, Apple also plans to introduce a new immersive performance from The Weeknd, as well as a scripted Apple Immersive short film called "Submerged." The short film is set during World War II, featuring sailors struggling to survive a deadly torpedo attack. There will also be a behind-the-scenes view of the 2024 NBA All-Star Weekend, and a new sports series called Big-Wave Surfing.<br/>
<blockquote>"Apple Immersive Video is a groundbreaking leap forward for storytelling, offering Apple Vision Pro users remarkable experiences with an unparalleled sense of realism and immersion," said Tor Myhren, Apple's vice president of Marketing Communications. "From soaring over volcanoes in Hawaii and surfing huge waves in Tahiti, to enjoying performances by the world's biggest artists and athletes from all-new perspectives, Apple Immersive Video revolutionizes the way people experience places, stories, sports, and more by making viewers feel like they're truly there. It's the next generation of visual storytelling, and we're excited to bring it to more people around the world."</blockquote><br/>
The new Apple Immersive video content is available from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app in Australia, Canada, Hong Kong, France, Germany, Japan, Singapore, the U.K., and the U.S. Users in China can watch the content through the Migu Video and Tencent Video apps.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-immersive-videos-vision-pro/">Apple Launching New Apple Immersive Videos, Films and Concerts for Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launching-new-apple-immersive-videos-films-and-concerts-for-vision-pro.2431680/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Expectation That Apple Intelligence Will Drive iPhone 16 Sales &#039;May Be Too Optimistic&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/kuo-no-iphone-16-ai-demand-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-expectation-that-apple-intelligence-will-drive-iphone-16-sales-may-be-too-optimistic.2431677/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:14:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/kuo-no-iphone-16-ai-demand-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple does not appear to have increased <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> orders despite reports to the contrary, according to <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/although-there-have-been-rumors-of-increased-orders-for-iphone-16-orders-from-time-to-time-after-4281627f2536">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. Kuo cites recent earnings reports from Apple suppliers TSMC and Largan as evidence.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935159" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" /><br/>
TSMC recently said that it did not see an increase in unit growth, while Largan said that orders for high-end models in 2024 are similar to last year. Kuo believes that Apple's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; orders for the second half of 2024 are around 87 million units, which is lower than the 91 million <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> units that Apple ordered in 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said that certain suppliers may have been asked to increase production, but that may be related to "specific reasons within individual industries or components."<br/>
<br/>
He suggests that expectations that Apple Intelligence will drive &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; sales "may be too optimistic" as the feature is available in U.S. English only.<br/>
<blockquote>The launch of Apple Intelligence is generally considered to be the reason for the increase in iPhone 16 orders. However, Apple Intelligence will only be available in Beta for US users in 2H24, and Apple Intelligence Siri only supports English. Regardless of whether Apple Intelligence alone can drive replacement demand (which is another big topic), the expectation that consumers will buy the new iPhone 16 for the Beta version of Apple Intelligence in 2H24 may be too optimistic.</blockquote><br/>
Earlier this month, <em>Bloomberg</em> suggested that Apple was counting on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> AI features to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-ai-iphone-16-shipment-boost/">boost iPhone shipments</a> by 10 percent in 2024. Apple Intelligence requires an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or later, so customers with an older <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will need to upgrade to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; to get the technology.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence includes a long list of new capabilities, including Writing Tools for proofreading, polishing, and summarizing text, Image Playground for generating images, and Genmoji for creating custom emoji. Apple Intelligence will also be used to overhaul <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, but the new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality isn't slated to launch until 2025.<br/>
<br/>
So far, Apple has not established an AI deal for Chinese consumers, and Apple Intelligence will also not be coming to the European Union when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; launches.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/kuo-no-iphone-16-ai-demand-increase/">Kuo: Expectation That Apple Intelligence Will Drive iPhone 16 Sales &#039;May Be Too Optimistic&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-expectation-that-apple-intelligence-will-drive-iphone-16-sales-may-be-too-optimistic.2431677/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Missed Amazon Prime Day? You Can Still Get M2 iPad Air, AirTag, and More for Record Low Prices Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/missed-amazon-prime-day-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/missed-amazon-prime-day-you-can-still-get-m2-ipad-air-airtag-and-more-for-record-low-prices-today.2431674/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:19:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/missed-amazon-prime-day-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Now that Amazon Prime Day has ended, many of the week's best deals have expired. However, today we are still tracking a few Apple products that remain at their best-ever prices even after the end of Prime Day, including iPads, MacBooks, AirTags, and a few Jackery accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/missed-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959279" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
The year's best prices on AirTag remain available on Amazon today, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;23.99</strong></a> for the 1 Pack and increasing to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;74.98</strong></a> for the 4 Pack.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;5 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;23.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;24 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;74.98</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
Amazon still has lowest prices ever on the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch SE, starting at just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2F5NJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;169.99</strong></a> for the 40mm GPS SE, down from &#36;249.00. The cheapest Series 9 model is the 41mm GPS model at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-Smartwatch-Aluminum-Fitness-Resistant%2Fdp%2FB0CSVB8BP1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;279.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;399.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2F5NJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTJ2Y5F%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us1%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;279.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX779JN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 iPad Air</h2><br/>
The cheapest model is the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7W33Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;549.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.00. You'll also find deals on the 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB models below, all of which are in stock on Amazon with delivery dates as soon as this weekend for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7W33Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J59856%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;729.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
Apple's iPad mini 6 hit &#36;119 off this week, a match for its all-time low price on both the 64GB Wi-Fi and 256GB Wi-Fi options, and both are still on sale today. You'll also find the cellular models at a discount right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9LPNLG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;529.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> today have Apple's 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"><strong>&#36;799.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. You'll find all four colors on sale at this price, including Midnight, Silver, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Studio Display</h2><br/>
Amazon has &#36;299 off the Apple Studio Display, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a> for the standard glass option. For this model, this is a match of the all-time low price. You'll need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see this discount.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Apple Studio Display (standard glass) for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
Jackery's Prime Day deals covered a large selection of portable power stations at big discounts, and they're all still on sale today.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.36ACZNP9NFZXM_1720797135027">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;169.00, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.RBRZCEOCA88O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.RBRZCEOCA88O_1720797474320">Solar Generator 240 with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1XYRT4EQJET79%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1XYRT4EQJET79_1720797554886">Solar Generator 300 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;398.98, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETFENZHJJVP7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ETFENZHJJVP7_1720797190458">Expansion Battery Pack 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;479.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34M7T7T7RIMAV%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34M7T7T7RIMAV_1720797593312">Solar Generator Explorer 500</a> - &#36;479.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D7PPG25F%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3N2AT8FS2RCU5%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3N2AT8FS2RCU5_1720797246445">Explorer 1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;599.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS_1720797331085">Expansion Battery Pack 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NIEM436WQUAO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NIEM436WQUAO_1720797439732">Explorer 2000 PRO Power Station</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LSGRBPNX6NQS_1720799483508">Explorer 2000 Plus + Expandable Battery + Solar Panel</a> - &#36;2,599.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/missed-amazon-prime-day-2/">Missed Amazon Prime Day? You Can Still Get M2 iPad Air, AirTag, and More for Record Low Prices Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/missed-amazon-prime-day-you-can-still-get-m2-ipad-air-airtag-and-more-for-record-low-prices-today.2431674/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Watch Never-Before-Seen Footage of Steve Jobs Discussing the Future of Computers in 1983</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/steve-jobs-archive-1983-speech/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watch-never-before-seen-footage-of-steve-jobs-discussing-the-future-of-computers-in-1983.2431668/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:07:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/steve-jobs-archive-1983-speech/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Steve Jobs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Steve Jobs Archive today <a href="https://stevejobsarchive.com/exhibits/objects-of-our-life">shared never-before-seen footage</a> of 28-year-old Steve Jobs speaking at the 1983 International Design Conference in Aspen, Colorado. His speech was focused on the future of computers and how they would change daily life.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Steve-Jobs-Younger.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959273" /><br/>
The Steve Jobs Archive was launched in 2022 by Laurene Powell Jobs, Tim Cook, and Jony Ive. The website features a collection of quotes, photos, videos, and emails from Jobs, and offers fellowships to young creators looking to follow in his footsteps.<br/>
<br/>
The new page features an introduction from Ive, who led design at Apple for over two decades and was a close friend of Jobs:<blockquote>Steve rarely attended design conferences. This was 1983, before the launch of the Mac, and still relatively early days of Apple. I find it breathtaking how profound his understanding was of the dramatic changes that were about to happen as the computer became broadly accessible. Of course, beyond just being prophetic, he was fundamental in defining products that would change our culture and our lives forever. <br/>
<br/>
On the eve of launching the first truly personal computer, Steve is not solely preoccupied with the founding technology and functionality of the product’s design. This is extraordinarily unusual, as in the early stages of dramatic innovation, it is normally the primary technology that benefits from all of the attention and focus.<br/>
<br/>
Steve points out that the design effort in the U.S. at the time had been focused on the automobile, with little consideration or effort given to consumer electronics. While it is not unusual to hear leaders talk about the national responsibility to manufacture, I thought it was interesting that he talked about a nation’s responsibility to design.<br/>
<br/>
In the talk, Steve predicts that by 1986 sales of the PC would exceed sales of cars, and that in the following ten years, people would be spending more time with a PC than in a car. These were absurd claims for the early 1980s. Describing what he sees as the inevitability that this would be a pervasive new category, he asks the designers in the audience for help. He asks that they start to think about the design of these products, because designed well or designed poorly, they still would be made.<br/>
<br/>
Steve remains one of the best educators I’ve ever met in my life. He had that ability to explain incredibly abstract, complex technologies in terms that were accessible, tangible and relevant. You hear him describe the computer as doing nothing more than completing fairly mundane tasks, but doing so very quickly. He gives the example of running out to grab a bunch of flowers and returning by the time you could snap your fingers – speed rendering the task magical.<br/>
<br/>
When I look back on our work, what I remember most fondly are not the products but the process. Part of Steve’s brilliance was how he learned to support the creative process, encouraging and developing ideas even in large groups of people. He treated the process of creating with a rare and wonderful reverence.<br/>
<br/>
The revolution Steve described over 40 years ago did of course happen, partly because of his profound commitment to a kind of civic responsibility. He cared, way beyond any sort of functional imperative. His was a victory for beauty, for purity and, as he would say, for giving a damn. He truly believed that by making something useful, empowering and beautiful, we express our love for humanity.</blockquote>Head to <a href="https://stevejobsarchive.com/exhibits/objects-of-our-life">"The Objects of Our Life" page</a> to learn more about the speech that Jobs gave, and to view some related photos and exhibits from that time.<br/>
<br/>
The full video of Jobs speaking can be found towards the bottom of the page.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/steve-jobs/">Steve Jobs</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/steve-jobs-archive-1983-speech/">Watch Never-Before-Seen Footage of Steve Jobs Discussing the Future of Computers in 1983</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watch-never-before-seen-footage-of-steve-jobs-discussing-the-future-of-computers-in-1983.2431668/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Looking to License More Movies to Expand Apple TV+ Library</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies-to-expand-apple-tv-library.2431664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:37:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is in active talks to license more films from major Hollywood studios as it seeks to bolster <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-07-18/apple-is-in-talks-to-license-more-films-from-hollywood"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-TV-Plus-Feature-2-Dark-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959287" /><br/>
Apple has traditionally focused on original productions for its streaming platform, but it is increasingly looking to expand its offerings by acquiring programming from the extensive libraries of established studios, sources familiar with the matter claim. While &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; has seen some success with original series such as "Ted Lasso" and "The Morning Show," these hits have been relatively few and far between, and the service has struggled to match the extensive catalogs of competitors like Netflix and Disney+.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; launched in November 2019, positioning itself as a premium service with a slate of high-quality, original content. Despite receiving critical acclaim and numerous awards, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/">72 Emmy nominations this year</a>, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; has not garnered the same subscriber base as its competitors. According to the research firm MoffettNathanson, only 11% of U.S. households use &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, compared to 55% for Netflix. The limited scope of content available on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; is apparently seen as a significant factor contributing to its slower growth. Data from Antenna indicates that streaming services with larger content libraries, like Netflix, experience lower cancellation rates. <br/>
<br/>
In an effort to address this, Apple has already begun experimenting with licensing. Earlier this year, the company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-tv-gains-over-50-movies-for-a-limited-time/">licensed approximately 50 movies</a> from Hollywood studios for its service in the United States, adding popular titles such as "Mean Girls" and "Titanic" to its catalog. The positive reception to this initial batch of licensed films is said to have encouraged Apple to pursue additional deals. These discussions aim to license even more titles, potentially expanding the service's offerings internationally as well as domestically. Simultaneously, major studios such as Warner Bros., Discovery, and Disney are increasingly open to selling their content to rivals to boost revenue.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies/">Apple Looking to License More Movies to Expand Apple TV+ Library</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-looking-to-license-more-movies-to-expand-apple-tv-library.2431664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max Are Still on Sale at Their Ultra-Low Prime Day Prices Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-3-airpods-pro-2-and-airpods-max-are-still-on-sale-at-their-ultra-low-prime-day-prices-today.2431662/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:05:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Even though Prime Day has ended, there are a few AirPods models that are still seeing <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">record low prices today on Amazon</a>. We don't know how long these deals will last at this point, so if you're interested be sure to lock in these steep discounts on the AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max as soon as possible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Combo-Discount-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895386" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the AirPods 3 with the Lightning Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00, which is a new record low price introduced for Prime Day and beats the previous low price by about &#36;10. The AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;168.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00, and is another new all-time low Prime Day price that has stuck around after the event ended.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;119.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Amazon has the AirPods Max for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;394.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;549.00. This is the overall steepest AirPods-related discount still available on Amazon, and it beats the previous low price from before Prime Day by about &#36;55. Every color is available at this low price as well, including Green, Silver, Pink, Sky Blue, and Space Gray.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZHYWJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;154 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/airpods-still-on-sale/">AirPods 3, AirPods Pro 2, and AirPods Max Are Still on Sale at Their Ultra-Low Prime Day Prices Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-3-airpods-pro-2-and-airpods-max-are-still-on-sale-at-their-ultra-low-prime-day-prices-today.2431662/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Dyson&#039;s New OnTrac Headphones Rival AirPods Max With 55-Hour Battery Life and Customization Options</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/dyson-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dysons-new-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max-with-55-hour-battery-life-and-customization-options.2431660/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:35:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/dyson-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Dyson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Dyson <a href="https://www.dyson.com/sign-up/wearables">today introduced</a> its second pair of headphones, the OnTrac, focusing on customization and premium features to directly compete with the likes of Apple and Bose.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dyson-ontrack-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959226" /><br/>
The new headphones represent a significant shift from Dyson's previous attempt, the Dyson Zone, which combined noise-canceling headphones with an air purifying mask. Priced at &#36;499.99, the OnTrac headphones are designed with a modular approach that allows users to replace the ear cushions and outer caps, enabling over 2,000 potential color combinations. <br/>
<br/>
One of the standout features of the OnTrac is its active noise cancellation (ANC). Dyson employs an eight-microphone system that samples external noise 384,000 times per second, aiming to provide what it claims is best-in-class noise cancellation. This system is comparable to Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, which also uses multiple microphones for ANC, although the exact sampling rate of the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; is not known. The OnTrac's ANC is designed to block up to 40 decibels of noise, enhancing the listening experience in noisy environments.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dyson-ontrac-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959224" /><br/>
<br/>
In terms of battery life, the OnTrac headphones offer 55 hours of continuous listening on a single charge with ANC enabled. This surpasses the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;, which provides up to 20 hours of battery life with ANC and spatial audio enabled. Dyson achieves this extended battery life by housing two high-capacity lithium-ion cells in the headband, which also helps distribute weight evenly for comfort. Charging is facilitated via a USB-C port, and a 10-minute quick charge can provide up to 2.5 hours of playback.<br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac headphones are equipped with 40mm drivers that reproduce frequencies from as low as 6Hz to as high as 21kHz. This wide frequency range aims to deliver deep bass and clear highs, with the drivers angled towards the ears for more direct audio delivery. In comparison, the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; feature custom-built 40mm dynamic drivers and support a frequency range from 20Hz to 20kHz. While both sets of headphones aim to provide high-fidelity sound, the OnTrac's extended frequency range may offer more detailed audio, particularly in the low-end frequencies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dyson-ontrac-3.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-959225" /><br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac headphones also feature a unique control system, including a joystick for playback control and touch-sensitive ear cups for toggling ANC. The MyDyson app allows users to monitor noise exposure levels and customize the EQ settings with presets like Bass Boost, Enhanced, and Natural.<br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac includes replaceable ear cushions and outer caps, available in various colors and finishes, allowing users to deeply customize the look of their headphones. The headphones come in four main colorways at launch: CNC Aluminum with bright yellow ear cushions, CNC Copper with purple headband and copper ear cups, Ceramic Cinnabar with a light red headband and matte ear cups, and CNC Black Nickel with an all-black design.<br/>
<br/>
The OnTrac headphones will be available from Dyson's website starting on August 1, with additional customization options sold separately. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dyson/">Dyson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/dyson-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max/">Dyson&#039;s New OnTrac Headphones Rival AirPods Max With 55-Hour Battery Life and Customization Options</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dysons-new-ontrac-headphones-rival-airpods-max-with-55-hour-battery-life-and-customization-options.2431660/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Earns Record 72 Emmy Award Nominations for &#039;Lessons in Chemistry,&#039; &#039;Slow Horses,&#039; &#039;The Morning Show,&#039; and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations-for-lessons-in-chemistry-slow-horses-the-morning-show-and-more.2431659/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:21:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple TV+ has earned a record <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/apple-scores-record-72-emmy-award-nominations-and-sweeps-across-top-categories/">72 Emmy nominations</a> across 16 Apple Originals, including its first-ever nominations Outstanding Limited Series for "Lessons in Chemistry," Outstanding Drama Series for "The Morning Show" and "Slow Horses," and Outstanding Comedy Series for "Palm Royale."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-TV-Plus-Black-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952746" /><br/>
You can read the full list of Emmy nominations on the <a href="https://www.emmys.com/sites/default/files/Downloads/76thnominations-list-v1.pdf?q=2024&q1=">Television Academy's website</a>. We've gathered all of Apple's nominations in the list below.<br/>
<h2>The Morning Show (16)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Drama Series: Jennifer Aniston</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Drama Series: Reese Witherspoon</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Nicole Beharie</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Greta Lee</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Karen Pittman</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series: Holland Taylor</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Billy Crudup</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Jon Hamm</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Mark Duplass</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Guest Actress in a Drama Series: Marcia Gay Harden</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Drama Series: Mimi Leder</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Casting for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Production Design for a Narrative Contemporary Program (One Hour or More)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Contemporary Hairstyling</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Contemporary Makeup (Non-Prosthetic)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Palm Royale (11)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Comedy Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Comedy Series: Kristen Wiig</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Comedy Series: Carol Burnett</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period Costumes for a Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Choreography for Scripted Programming</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Production Design for a Narrative Period or Fantasy Program (One Hour or More)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period or Fantasy/Sci-Fi Hairstyling</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period or Fantasy/Sci-Fi Makeup (Non-Prosthetic)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Series (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Main Title Design</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Original Main Title Theme Music</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Lessons in Chemistry (10)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Limited or Anthology Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Brie Larson</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Aja Naomi King</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Lewis Pullman</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Limited or Anthology Series, Movie, or Special (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie: Millicent Shelton</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period Costumes for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Main Title Design</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Original Main Title Theme Music</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Slow Horses (9)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series: Gary Oldman</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series: Jack Lowden</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Guest Actor in a Drama Series: Jonathan Pryce</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Casting for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Writing for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Drama Series: Saul Metzstein</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Picture Editing for a Drama Series</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Series (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Loot (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actress in a Comedy Series: Maya Rudolph</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hijack (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series: Idris Elba</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>The New Look (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Period Costumes for a Series</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Masters of the Air (3)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Original Main Title Theme Music</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Editing for a Limited or Anthology Series, Movie, or Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Mixing for a Limited or Anthology Series or Movie</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Physical (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Single-Camera Series (Half-Hour)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Choreography for Scripted Programming</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Silo (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Music Composition for a Series (Original Dramatic Score)</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Main Title Design</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Girls State (3)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Documentary or Nonfiction Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Documentary/Nonfiction Program: Amanda McBaine and Jesse Moss</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sugar (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Cinematography for a Single-Camera Series (Half-Hour)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hannah Waddingham: Home for Christmas (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Production Design for a Variety Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Technical Direction and Camerawork for a Special</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Reluctant Traveler With Eugene Levy (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Hosted Nonfiction Series or Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Writing for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>STEVE! (martin) a documentary in 2 pieces (5)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Documentary or Nonfiction Special</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Directing for a Documentary/Nonfiction Program: Morgan Neville</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Picture Editing for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Editing for a Nonfiction or Reality Program</li><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Sound Mixing for a Nonfiction Program</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Carpool Karaoke: The Series (1)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Outstanding Short Form Comedy, Drama, or Variety Series</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Nominees for Outstanding Commercial (2)</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>"Album Cover" — Apple iPhone 15</li><br/>
  <li>"Fuzzy Feelings" — iPhone + Mac</li><br/>
</ul>Apple Original films, documentaries, and series have earned 499 wins and 2,262 award nominations so far, including multi-Emmy Award-winning comedy "Ted Lasso" and Oscar Best Picture winner "CODA." The final winners of the 76nd Emmy Awards will be revealed on Sunday, September 15, on ABC.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations/">Apple Earns Record 72 Emmy Award Nominations for &#039;Lessons in Chemistry,&#039; &#039;Slow Horses,&#039; &#039;The Morning Show,&#039; and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-earns-record-72-emmy-award-nominations-for-lessons-in-chemistry-slow-horses-the-morning-show-and-more.2431659/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pencil Pro Drops to &#36;109.99 on Amazon Alongside Record Low Prices for M4 iPad Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-109-99-on-amazon-alongside-record-low-prices-for-m4-ipad-pro.2431658/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:09:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Pencil Pro has dropped to a new record low price today on Amazon, and we're also tracking a big collection of discounts on the M4 iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956283" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon today has the Apple Pencil Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;109.99</strong></a>, down from the regular price of &#36;129.00. This is a new record low price for the accessory, beating the previous sale price by &#36;10. The Apple Pencil 2 is also at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Pencil Pro launched in May alongside the new 2024 iPad lineup, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/09/apple-pencil-pro-features/">new gestures and capabilities</a> into the stylus. The Apple Pencil Pro is compatible with the M4 iPad Pro and the M2 iPad Air, and marks the first update to the Apple Pencil since the Apple Pencil 2 in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
Moving to the iPads, Amazon has all-time low prices on a few models of the 11-inch M4 iPad Pro. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;919.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and also include multiple cellular tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;919.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,328.99, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9KW87%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8GYMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,299.00, down from &#36;1,399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6WQCK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,699.00, down from &#36;1,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB59ZT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Cellular (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,099.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<br/>
</ul><h3>13-inch</h3><br/>
Prices for the larger models start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet. Overall, nearly every 13-inch M4 iPad Pro is on sale right now on Amazon, all at all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,389.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6S6LS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,839.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,099.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7ZX58%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,389.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6W9TW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,574.00, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J98VKZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,939.00, down from &#36;2,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8TSQN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Cellular (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;2,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9H49F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Cellular</a> - &#36;2,304.00, down from &#36;2,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9KW8F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Cellular (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,214.00, down from &#36;2,599.00</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-pencil-pro-to-109/">Apple Pencil Pro Drops to &#36;109.99 on Amazon Alongside Record Low Prices for M4 iPad Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-109-99-on-amazon-alongside-record-low-prices-for-m4-ipad-pro.2431658/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Humorous &#039;The Underdogs&#039; Video Featuring iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-humorous-the-underdogs-video-featuring-iphone-ipad-mac-and-apple-vision-pro.2431657/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:52:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a humorous <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SbYckRAt5os">new video on its YouTube channel</a> that dramatizes many of the uses of Apple devices, including its Apple Vision Pro spatial computing device.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SbYckRAt5os?si=KavZs80xSDHHOxt7" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Titled "OOO (Out of Office)," the 10-minute video follows design team "The Underdogs" as they travel to Thailand in a last-ditch attempt fulfill a client's wishes. In order to do so, they must find a new packaging factory, solve last-minute design changes, create prototypes, break down language barriers, and more. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has shared longer ads in the past featuring "The Underdogs" design team racing against time to fulfill the needs of a client, but this is the first one to feature one of the characters using an Apple Vision Pro headset to multi-task across several open windows in virtual space.<br/>
<br/>
The short comes after similar "Apple at Work" videos that Apple published in 2019, 2020, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/apple-security-at-work-video-short/">2023</a> using the same actors. Other highlighted products, apps, and features in the video include Live Voicemail, Translate, AirDrop, NameDrop, Apple Wallet, Standby Mode, Animoji, FaceTime, Ringtones, AR, Object Capture, Mac Virtual Display, and more.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/apple-shares-underdogs-video-vision-pro/">Apple Shares Humorous &#039;The Underdogs&#039; Video Featuring iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-humorous-the-underdogs-video-featuring-iphone-ipad-mac-and-apple-vision-pro.2431657/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
