<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 09:04:11 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 4 Drop to &#36;119 on Amazon, Plus Record Low Prices on iPhone 16 Cases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/airpods-4-drop-to-119/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-4-drop-to-119-on-amazon-plus-record-low-prices-on-iphone-16-cases.2440773/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 07:48:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/airpods-4-drop-to-119/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking two separate sales across Amazon and Woot, with big discounts on AirPods 4 and Apple's MagSafe cases for iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/02/airpods-4-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964768" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with AirPods, Amazon has the AirPods 4 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is the base model without Active Noise Cancellation, and Amazon's price today is just &#36;1 off from the all-time low price on this model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;168.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;179.00. Similar to the previous model, this is just about &#36;1 away from the record low price on this version of the AirPods 4, making today's sale a solid second-best price for anyone shopping for AirPods this week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Cases</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-cases-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968483" /><br/>
<br/>
Over at Woot, you can get <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases">all-time low prices on Silicone and Clear Cases</a> for the iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max. Woot has a large selection of these down to &#36;34.99 right now, and you can take an additional &#36;10 off with the coupon code APPLEWELCOME through Friday, October 25.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;24 OFF</div>iPhone 16 Cases at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
These cases are in new condition and come with a one year Apple manufacturer limited warranty. There are multiple colors on sale for each model, including Denim, Black, Lake Green, Fuchsia, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/airpods-4-drop-to-119/">AirPods 4 Drop to &#36;119 on Amazon, Plus Record Low Prices on iPhone 16 Cases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-4-drop-to-119-on-amazon-plus-record-low-prices-on-iphone-16-cases.2440773/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>5 Reasons to Get Excited About the New Mac Mini</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/5-reasons-get-excited-upcoming-mac-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-reasons-to-get-excited-about-the-new-mac-mini.2440770/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 06:55:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/5-reasons-get-excited-upcoming-mac-mini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Mac mini has long been a powerhouse in a compact form, offering impressive performance in a small package. With rumors swirling about a completely overhauled new model that is likely just days away from being announced, anticipation is building for what Apple has in store. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Silver-Perspective.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961276" /><br/>
From enhanced connectivity to major hardware upgrades, the upcoming Mac mini promises to bring significant improvements that make it more compelling than ever. Here are five reasons to get excited about the next generation of this beloved small form-factor desktop. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Major Redesign</h2><br/>
Apple is planning to debut completely redesigned Mac mini models, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. The new ‌Mac mini‌ will be the first major design change to the machine since 2010, and is expected to become Apple's smallest ever desktop computer. The slimmed down machine will retain its aluminum casing and be comparable in size to the Apple TV, though it is expected to be taller. Individuals working on the new device reportedly say that it is "essentially an iPad Pro in a small box."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>5 USB-C Ports</h2><br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/02/new-m4-mac-mini-5-usb-c-ports/">Mark Gurman</a> and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/mac-mini-5-usb-c-ports-leak/">leaked Apple report</a>, the next Mac mini is expected to come with five USB-C ports. Similar to the Mac Studio, two of these ports are anticipated to be positioned on the front. It's likely that some of these will support Thunderbolt 4, utilizing the same USB-C interface. However, the full set of five ports might only be available on the M4 Pro versions of the Mac mini.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Chip</h2><br/>
The next Mac mini will come in both M4 and M4 Pro configurations, a significant step up from the current M2 and M2 Pro models. Like the M3, the M4 is built on a 3nm process, but with enhancements from Apple supplier TSMC for improved performance and power efficiency. The M4 also includes an improved Neural Engine that fuels accelerated AI workloads. Apple says it is the company's most powerful Neural Engine ever, capable of 38 trillion operations per second, so there's plenty of scope for faster compute speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>16GB Base RAM</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-08-23/when-is-apple-announcing-the-iphone-16-apple-planning-event-on-sept-10-2024"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> reported in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-new-macs-16gb-ram-standard/">August</a> that Apple has tested four new Mac models equipped with an M4 chip, and all of them have either 16GB or 32GB of unified memory. The adequacy of 8GB of RAM in Macs has been a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/is-8gb-of-ram-enough-for-macbook-pro/#:~:text=8GB%20or%20More%20RAM%3F,run%20smoothly%20even%20during%20multitasking.">contentious issue</a> for over a decade. That has left Apple open to criticism from users who believe that 8GB is not a sufficient amount of RAM for most creative professional workflows, so the news that 16GB is likely to be the new minimum will surely be a welcome development.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
Apple is expected to emphasize the artificial intelligence capabilities of the M4 chip series, and the first Apple Intelligence features are expected to arrive with the release of macOS Sequoia 15.1 on October 28, which is right around the time we are expecting a Mac mini announcement. The initial release will focus on new Siri features, Smart Replies in Mail and Messages, Priority messages in the Mail app, Memory Movie and Clean Up in Photos, and more, with additional features coming in phased updates over the next several months.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Release Timing</h3><br/>
The new-look Mac mini is expected to be announced by Apple before the end of October, with a launch to follow in early November. In his latest word on the subject, Gurman said an "M4 Mac launch" is on Apple's schedule for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/">next week</a>, but he did not mention a specific day. What are you looking forward to about the overhauled model? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/5-reasons-get-excited-upcoming-mac-mini/">5 Reasons to Get Excited About the New Mac Mini</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-reasons-to-get-excited-about-the-new-mac-mini.2440770/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple May Stop Producing Vision Pro by the End of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-may-stop-producing-vision-pro-by-end-of-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-may-stop-producing-vision-pro-by-the-end-of-2024.2440767/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 06:11:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-may-stop-producing-vision-pro-by-end-of-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Luxshare</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has abruptly reduced production of the Vision Pro headset and could stop making the current version of the device completely by the end of 2024, <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-sharply-scales-back-production-of-vision-pro"><em>The Information</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-944159" /><br/>
Citing multiple people "directly involved" in making components for the headset, the report says that the scaling back of production began in the early summer. This indicates that Apple now has a sufficient number of Vision Pro units in its inventory to meet demand for the device's remaining lifespan through to next year.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro is widely reported to have seen weak demand due to insufficient content and its high price point. <em>The Information</em> says that Vision Pro suppliers have now produced enough components for between 500,000 to 600,000 headsets. Some factories suspended production of Vision Pro components as early as May based on Apple's weak sales forecasts, and warehouses remain filled with tens of thousands of undelivered parts.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to have recently told Luxshare, a Chinese company that serves as the Vision Pro's assembler, that it may need to wind down production in November. Luxshare is currently making around 1,000 Vision Pro headsets per day, which is half that being produced at its peak. Apple will still be able to resume Vision Pro production if sales pick up since the production lines are not yet due to be dismantled.<br/>
<br/>
Moreover, Apple has apparently suspended work on the second-generation Vision Pro for at least a year to focus on developing a lower-cost headset. Interestingly, Apple has told suppliers to prepare to build four million low-cost headsets over the entire lifespan of the future product. This is half the total number of Vision Pros that Apple told suppliers to produce, suggesting that sales expectations are even lower for the cheaper headset.<br/>
<br/>
Although Apple's work on the second-generation Vision Pro has apparently stalled, there are some indications that the company could release "an incremental update to the product with limited changes to its physical design," such as a chip upgrade. This would allow Apple to use up the considerable number of excess components in its supply chain.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/luxshare/">Luxshare</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-may-stop-producing-vision-pro-by-end-of-2024/">Report: Apple May Stop Producing Vision Pro by the End of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-may-stop-producing-vision-pro-by-the-end-of-2024.2440767/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Shares Another Teaser Trailer for &#039;Severance&#039; Season 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-two-teaser/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-shares-another-teaser-trailer-for-severance-season-2.2440766/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 06:05:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-two-teaser/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple TV+ today <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/10/apple-tv-unveils-severance-season-two-teaser-ahead-of-the-highly-anticipated-return-of-the-emmy-and-peabody-award-winning-phenomenon/">shared</a> another teaser trailer for the second season of the critically-acclaimed workplace thriller "Severance."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-TV-Plus-Severance-Season-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1104" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958238" /><br/>
Apple previously announced that the 10-episode second season of "Severance" will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-2-date/">premiere on Friday, January 17</a>, and then one episode will follow every Friday through March 21. The first season ended in April 2022, so fans have waited a long time for the show to return, partly due to the Writers Guild of America going on strike last year.<br/>
<br/>
The sci-fi series revolves around the mysterious company Lumon Industries, whose employees cannot recall any memories about their personal lives while they are at work. Similarly, the employees cannot remember anything about the workplace when they are out of the office. In the second season, Apple says the employees "learn the dire consequences of trifling with the severance barrier, leading them further down a path of woe."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VwP6M9zS_pQ?si=oLj7HVqSAD9SWTG0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
"Severance" was created by Dan Erickson, and Ben Stiller serves as an executive producer. The series has an ensemble cast, including Adam Scott, Britt Lower, Tramell Tillman, Zach Cherry, Christopher Walken, and others.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple TV+ costs &#36;9.99 per month or &#36;99 per year, and the service is included in all Apple One subscription bundles. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-two-teaser/">Apple TV+ Shares Another Teaser Trailer for &#039;Severance&#039; Season 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-shares-another-teaser-trailer-for-severance-season-2.2440766/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 With Apple Intelligence Available Today for Same-Day Pickup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/ipad-mini-7-now-available-same-day-pickup/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-with-apple-intelligence-available-today-for-same-day-pickup.2440762/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 04:16:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/ipad-mini-7-now-available-same-day-pickup/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting today, Apple's new iPad mini 7 with A17 Pro chip is available for same-day or next-day pickup at Apple Stores, with no pre-order required. Online orders are also beginning to arrive to customers today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972160" /><br/>
Customers across Europe, Asia, and other regions can now place an order on Apple's website or in the Apple Store app and arrange for in-store pickup at a local retail location. Apple has yet to update its online store for customers in the United States and Canada, but that will change in the next couple of hours.<br/>
<br/>
To order a product with ‌Apple Store‌ pickup, add the product to your bag on Apple.com, proceed to checkout, select the "I'll pick it up" option, enter your ZIP code, choose an available ‌Apple Store‌ location, and select a pickup date. Payment is completed online, and a valid government-issued photo ID and the order number may be required upon pickup.<br/>
<br/>
The iPad mini is Apple's smallest tablet device and the latest model features a slim-bezeled design, an A17 Pro chip with support for Apple Intelligence features that are coming in iPadOS 18.1, a USB-C port, and Apple Pencil Pro support. Base storage has been doubled, so the entry-level iPad mini starts with 128GB of storage, up from 64GB. 256GB and 512GB options are available as upgrades.<br/>
<br/>
The 12MP wide back camera on the new iPad mini now supports Smart HDR 4 and uses machine learning to detect and scan documents right in the Camera app, while the USB-C port delivers 2x faster wired connections than the previous generation, with data transfers up to 10Gbps. The iPad mini 7's cellular version supports sub-6GHz 5G, and now includes Wi-Fi 6E for faster 6GHz connections. Bluetooth is improved to version 5.3, and Apple has replaced the nano-SIM slot with eSIM-only connectivity worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
Note that iPad mini models sold in Europe <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/whats-in-the-ipad-mini-7-box/">do not come with a power adapter</a> in the box, whereas models sold in the US do include a 20W USB-C adapter.<br/>
<br/>
The iPad mini comes in four colors, including Blue, Starlight, Purple, and Space Gray. It starts at &#36;499 for the 128GB Wi-Fi-only model, going up to &#36;799 for the 512GB model. Cellular models are available for &#36;150 more over the base price of each configuration. Apple is also selling new &#36;59 Smart Folio cases for the iPad mini in matching colors, while the Apple Pencil Pro that works with the iPad mini is available for &#36;129. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/ipad-mini-7-now-available-same-day-pickup/">iPad Mini 7 With Apple Intelligence Available Today for Same-Day Pickup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-with-apple-intelligence-available-today-for-same-day-pickup.2440762/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Supports Over-the-Air Recovery Using Another iOS Device</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/ipad-mini-7-ota-recovery-ios-device/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-supports-over-the-air-recovery-using-another-ios-device.2440760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 03:29:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/ipad-mini-7-ota-recovery-ios-device/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, Apple includes a new over-the-air recovery feature designed to revive bricked iPhone 16 devices using another iPhone or an iPad, and it appears that the same feature can be used to recover the new iPad mini 7, too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972027" /><br/>
In iOS 18, placing an iPhone 16 next to another iPhone or iPad can start an over-the-air firmware recovery – the other device downloads a new iOS firmware and transfers it to the bricked device, removing the need to connect it to a computer. ‌This contrasts with iPhone 15 and earlier models, which require connection to a Mac or PC to restore the firmware.<br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-restored-wirelessly/">9to5Mac</a></em> today reports that the firmware shipped with the iPad mini 7, which is powered by an A17 Pro chip, includes the same RecoveryOS partition that was added to the iPhone 16 models. The finding puts to bed the earlier theory that the RecoveryOS partition was something exclusive to the A18 chip in the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
Evidence that Apple has been working on an over-the-air recovery method for iOS devices first appeared <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/02/26/ios-13-4-over-the-air-recovery-feature/">way back in iOS 13.4</a>. Whether Apple intends to add the functionality to other iPhone or iPad models via a software update remains unclear. Apple introduced the iPad mini 7 on October 15, and the first pre-orders are arriving in the hands of customers today.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/ipad-mini-7-ota-recovery-ios-device/">iPad Mini 7 Supports Over-the-Air Recovery Using Another iOS Device</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-supports-over-the-air-recovery-using-another-ios-device.2440760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Craig Federighi Explains Phased Release of Apple Intelligence Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/craig-federighi-phased-release-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/craig-federighi-explains-phased-release-of-apple-intelligence-features.2440759/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 02:59:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/craig-federighi-phased-release-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Craig Federighi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a new interview with <em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr8ALcEiYAk">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>, Apple's head of software Craig Federighi has highlighted the company's measured, multi-phase approach to introducing Apple Intelligence features, with the initial iOS 18.1 release next week marking just the beginning of a staggered rollout over several months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
"This is a big lift," Federighi told <em>WSJ</em>'s Joanna Stern, explaining Apple's cautious strategy of integrating AI into its devices. "You could put something out there and have it be sort of a mess. Apple's point of view is more like, 'Let's try to get each piece right and release it when it's ready.'"<br/>
<br/>
The initial release will focus on basic features including Writing Tools for text summarization, notification summaries, and a Clean Up tool in Photos for removing unwanted objects. While most processing occurs on-device, Apple's Private Cloud Compute system handles more intensive tasks through encrypted servers. In other words, user data isn't stored or accessed for AI training. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's approach differs significantly from other large language models, which typically process all user input on cloud servers. According to Federighi, the company's personally oriented, privacy-first approach is also why Siri won't offer the sort of answers that one might get from something like ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
"There's a trade-off across capabilities," he explained. "Those other chatbots are great if you want to ask a question about quantum mechanics, and then have them write a poem about it, but they won't open your garage or send a text message. Will these worlds converge? Of course."<br/>
<br/>
Several anticipated features showcased by Apple at WWDC in June won't appear until later updates: iOS 18.2 is expected before the end of the year, and will introduce Image Playground for generating cartoon-style images and Genmoji for creating custom emoji. The update will also add ChatGPT integration for handling complex Siri queries.<br/>
<br/>
The most significant Siri enhancements are scheduled for iOS 18.4 around March 2025. These include onscreen awareness for contextual commands, personal context for better understanding of user data, and expanded app control capabilities. Initially, Apple Intelligence will only support U.S. English, with additional languages planned for next year.<br/>
<br/>
In contrast to its rivals, Apple is taking a particularly measured approach to image manipulation. The new Clean Up tool in Photos allows users to remove unwanted objects or people from images, but avoids more complex AI-generated alterations like changing the background. "People view photographic content as something they can rely on as indicative of reality," explained Federighi. "It's important to us that we help purvey accurate information, not fantasy."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fr8ALcEiYAk?si=YlwIgNHfXvfUiGWb" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Speaking more broadly about the rollout of Apple Intelligence features, Federighi said: "This is a many-year, honestly, even decades-long arc of this technology playing out, and so we're going to do it responsibly." The new Apple Intelligence features will be available on iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 16 models, as well as Apple silicon-powered iPads and Macs, when iOS 18.1 launches on October 28.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/craig-federighi/">Craig Federighi</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/craig-federighi-phased-release-apple-intelligence/">Craig Federighi Explains Phased Release of Apple Intelligence Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/craig-federighi-explains-phased-release-of-apple-intelligence-features.2440759/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Game Studio Shutdown Suggests Gaming May Not Be Working Out for Netflix</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/netflix-game-studio-shutdown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-studio-shutdown-suggests-gaming-may-not-be-working-out-for-netflix.2440744/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:57:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/netflix-game-studio-shutdown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix recently shut down its "Team Blue" gaming studio in Southern California, according to <em><a href="https://www.gamefile.news/p/netflix-team-blue-socal-studio">Game File</a></em>. The studio included industry veterans that worked on titles like Halo, Overwatch, and God of War.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-824171" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/netflix-games-launch.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
There have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/11/09/netflix-games-ios-launch/">mobile gaming titles</a> available through Netflix since 2021, but Team Blue was supposedly working on a big budget AAA gaming title that would have represented an expansion of Netflix's gaming efforts.<br/>
<br/>
The decision to shutter the studio developing an original multi-platform AAA title suggests that gaming might not be going so well for Netflix. Back in 2022, a report suggested that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/08/netflix-games-note-engaging-subscribers/">less than one percent</a> of Netflix subscribers were engaging in games, but Netflix has made an effort to introduce more premium titles since then.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix's mobile gaming catalog includes several Grand Theft Auto titles, popular roguelike Hades, Cozy Grove, Farming Simulator, Spiritfarer, Rollercoaster Tycoon, and more. The games are included with a Netflix subscription, and no additional fees are required to play them.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix games can be downloaded as standalone games on Apple devices, and are available to play after logging in with an active Netflix account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/netflix-game-studio-shutdown/">Game Studio Shutdown Suggests Gaming May Not Be Working Out for Netflix</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-studio-shutdown-suggests-gaming-may-not-be-working-out-for-netflix.2440744/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Mini 7 Models Begin Arriving to Customers in Australia and New Zealand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-australia-new-zealand/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-mini-7-models-begin-arriving-to-customers-in-australia-and-new-zealand.2440736/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 15:12:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-australia-new-zealand/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's Wednesday, October 23 in Australia and New Zealand, which means that customers who pre-ordered one of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a> devices are starting to receive their orders.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-red-and-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972028" /><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/apple-unveils-new-ipad-mini-apple-intelligence/">introduced the iPad mini 7</a> on October 15, which is also when the company began accepting pre-orders. While the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; has the same design as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> 6, it is equipped with an A17 Pro chip and 8GB RAM in order to support the Apple Intelligence features that are coming in iPadOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; also offers Wi-Fi 6E, faster USB-C data transfer speeds, Bluetooth 5.3, and support for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro. It now offers a minimum of 128GB of storage with an option to upgrade to 256GB or 512GB, and Apple also unveiled new colors.<br/>
<br/>
There are no Apple retail stores in New Zealand, but Apple Stores in Australia will have the new &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; available for walk-in purchases. We are not expecting any shortages of the new tablet.<br/>
<br/>
Following New Zealand and Australia, sales of the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; will begin in Asia, the Middle East, Europe, and finally, North America.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;499, and it continues to be Apple's smallest tablet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-australia-new-zealand/">New iPad Mini 7 Models Begin Arriving to Customers in Australia and New Zealand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-mini-7-models-begin-arriving-to-customers-in-australia-and-new-zealand.2440736/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Dropped iPhone Causes Woman to Be Trapped Upside Down in Rock Crevice for Hours</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/dropped-iphone-rock-crevice-accident/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dropped-iphone-causes-woman-to-be-trapped-upside-down-in-rock-crevice-for-hours.2440733/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 14:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/dropped-iphone-rock-crevice-accident/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Australian woman Matilda Campbell ended up trapped in a tight rock crevice upside down after she fell trying to retrieve an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that she dropped, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2024-10-22/images-of-hunter-valley-rescue-after-woman-falls-rock-crevice/104500728">ABC Newcastle</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iphone-trapped-crevice.jpg" alt="" width="1536" height="862" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972106" /><br/>
The 23-year-old was taking images in the New South Wales Hunter Valley when she lost hold of her phone. She tried to get it, but slipped and fell three meters and became stuck between two large boulders, hanging upside down by her feet. While the news report does not make specific mention of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Campbell's social media accounts indicate she was an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user.<br/>
<br/>
It took an hour for rescuers to get to Campbell, and several more hours to free her. NSW Ambulance rescue paramedic Peter Watts told <em>ABC Newcastle</em> that Campbell was calm and collected, despite the situation. He said it was a difficult, "out-of-the-box rescue" that was unlike anything he'd previously experienced. NSW Ambulance shared images of the rescue <a href="https://www.facebook.com/NSWAmbulance">on Facebook</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Rescue crews had to remove seven boulders weighing between 80 and 500 kilograms to free Campbell, plus a wooden frame had to be constructed in case any boulders cracked and fell. Campbell was trapped for approximately seven hours, and she ended up with scrapes, bruises, and a cracked vertebra. She was not able to retrieve her &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/dropped-iphone-rock-crevice-accident/">Dropped iPhone Causes Woman to Be Trapped Upside Down in Rock Crevice for Hours</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dropped-iphone-causes-woman-to-be-trapped-upside-down-in-rock-crevice-for-hours.2440733/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Said to Be Working on New Gaming App for iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-gaming-app-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-said-to-be-working-on-new-gaming-app-for-ios.2440726/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:17:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-gaming-app-ios/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		<category>Game Center</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on an App Store-style app designed for gaming, according to a report from <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/10/22/apple-new-app-store-like-app-games/">9to5Mac</a></em>. It would merge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> gaming content, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, and Game Center into a central location.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/apple-arcade-orange-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-748620" /><br/>
The app is said to feature a Play Now tab with gaming content and suggestions, plus a Game Center tab for tracking game progress and games that friends are playing. Game Center features like achievements and leaderboards will be highlighted.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to offer both &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games and &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; games in the app, and the company will promote gaming events and details about important updates. It is possible that there will be integration with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and Messages for remote play with friends, as well as App Clip mini game demos.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word on when Apple might release this dedicated gaming app.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/game-center/">Game Center</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-gaming-app-ios/">Apple Said to Be Working on New Gaming App for iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-said-to-be-working-on-new-gaming-app-for-ios.2440726/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second visionOS 2.1 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate.2440725/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:11:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded a second release candidate version of an upcoming visionOS 2.1 update to developers for testing purposes. The new software comes a day after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate/">first release candidate version</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955607" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.1 can be installed by going to the Software Update section of the Settings app on the Vision Pro and opting into Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
So far, no major new features have been discovered in the update, and it likely focuses on bug fixes and other small feature improvements. Apple's release notes say that the second visionOS 2.1 RC fixes an issue that could cause <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> songs and music videos to fail to play.<br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.1 is expected to see a release next Monday alongside iOS 18.1.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds Second visionOS 2.1 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate.2440725/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro, AirPods, and AirPods Max Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-airpods-and-airpods-max-firmware.2440718/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 11:39:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, the AirPods 2, the AirPods 3, and the Lightning version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> headphones. The new firmware is version 6F21, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-all-airpods-new-firmware/">prior 6A326 firmware</a> that these devices were previously running.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
There is no word on what's included in the firmware, but given that these are all older models, it is likely that the new firmware includes bug fixes and other minor improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't have a way to manually upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air when the AirPods are in a charging case and connected to an iOS device or Mac.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro, AirPods, and AirPods Max Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-airpods-and-airpods-max-firmware.2440718/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Now Try AT&amp;T&#039;s Network for Free</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/att-free-network-trial/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-try-at-ts-network-for-free.2440716/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 11:19:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/att-free-network-trial/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AT&amp;amp;T</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AT&T today <a href="https://about.att.com/blogs/2024/try-att.html">announced a new promotion</a> that allows potential new customers to try out the AT&T network for 30 days for free.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ATT-Banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937556" /><br/>
Customers with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that has an eSIM can download the myAT&T app or visit the AT&T <a href="http://www.att.com/wireless/free-trial/">free trial website</a> to sign up for temporary access to the AT&T network. No credit card is required for the AT&T trial, which includes 5G access.<br/>
<br/>
Compatible iPhones with eSIM capabilities include the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 2020 and all later models, but note that devices must be unlocked. Testing AT&T's network through the Try AT&T feature does not require transferring a phone number or canceling current service. It instead operates as a second line on a compatible &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, with options to switch between the AT&T test and another carrier plan.<br/>
<br/>
AT&T is providing unlimited talk and text, 100GB of data, 25GB of personal hotspot data, AT&T 5G access, and unlimited texting from the United States to more than 230 countries. After the 30-day trial ends, service will be canceled automatically, but customers will have the option to sign up for AT&T service.<br/>
<br/>
Both Verizon and T-Mobile have previously rolled out programs that allow customers to test their networks for free, but AT&T is offering 25GB of hotspot data, which neither Verizon or T-Mobile support.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/att/">AT&amp;T</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/att-free-network-trial/">You Can Now Try AT&amp;T&#039;s Network for Free</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-try-at-ts-network-for-free.2440716/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iPadOS 18.0.1 for iPad Mini 7 Ahead of Tomorrow&#039;s Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-for-ipad-mini-7-ahead-of-tomorrows-launch.2440711/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:55:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-ipad-mini-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new version of iPadOS 18.0.1 that's designed specifically for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a> that will be available as of tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-blue-and-orange.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972026" /><br/>
The iPadOS 18.0.1 update features the same content as the iPadOS 18.0.1 update that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/apple-releases-ios-18-0-1/">released in early October</a>, but it has a 22A8380 build number. The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; isn't out just yet, but customers in Australia and New Zealand who pre-ordered will be getting their shipments in just a few hours, and they'll be able to update during the setup process.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 18.0.1 includes a fix for an issue that could cause the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> to unexpectedly quit when replying to a message with a shared Apple Watch face, plus it has a security fix to address a vulnerability with the Passwords app.<br/>
<br/>
Launch versions of the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; have a version of iOS 18.0 installed rather than iPadOS 18.0.1, which is why there's an out-of-the-box update. Next week, &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; owners can also upgrade to iPadOS 18.1, an update that includes the first Apple Intelligence features.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-ipad-mini-7/">Apple Releases iPadOS 18.0.1 for iPad Mini 7 Ahead of Tomorrow&#039;s Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-for-ipad-mini-7-ahead-of-tomorrows-launch.2440711/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: &#039;M4 Mac Launch&#039; is &#039;Next Week&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-m4-mac-launch-is-next-week.2440707/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:29:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a few hours after claiming that the first Macs with M4 chips are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/gurman-says-m4-macs-launch-very-soon/">launching "very soon,"</a> <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has followed up with a slightly more specific timeframe. In his latest <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1848762199675965773">social media post</a> today, he said an "M4 Mac launch" is on Apple's schedule for next week, but he did not mention a specific day.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/M4-Mac-mini-Ortho-Black-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972058" /><em>A concept of a smaller Mac mini with front-facing USB-C ports</em></div><br/>
"Busy week for Apple next week: Apple Intelligence on Monday, then M4 Mac launch, then earnings results on Thursday," he posted.<br/>
<br/>
In <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1848748246799429753">another social media post</a> today, Gurman said that Apple is inviting journalists and content creators to a hands-on experience in Los Angeles next Wednesday, and he believes this means the new Macs would need to be announced before then.<br/>
<br/>
In another twist, leaker Sonny Dickson today claimed that he heard the new Mac mini with five USB-C ports <a href="https://x.com/SonnyDickson/status/1848596156302971278">might launch this week</a> instead. Dickson has revealed some accurate details about upcoming Apple products through leaked cases and dummy models, but some of his hardware-related claims have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/06/09/imac-redesign-wwdc/">proven to be inaccurate</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, it looks like Apple will announce the first Macs with M4 chips in around a week from now at the latest, based on these latest claims. It's still not entirely clear if the announcements will be part of an online event, like the "Scary Fast" event on October 30 last year, or if the products will be announced in press releases on the Apple Newsroom website only. There is still time left in October for Apple to invite the media to watch an online event, but the window for that is gradually coming to a close. We'll see!<br/>
<br/>
Here is everything that Apple is likely to announce in the coming days:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>An entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4 chip, and an additional Thunderbolt port compared to the current model</li><br/>
<li>14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4 Pro and M4 Max chip options</li><br/>
<li>An updated iMac with the M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>A new Mac mini with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/mac-mini-redesign-rumor/">smaller Apple TV-like design, two front-facing USB-C ports, and M4 and M4 Pro chip options</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/apple-new-magic-mouse-trackpad-keyboard/">USB-C versions of the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard accessories</a></li></ul>The entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4 chip <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-potentially-facing-worst-leak-since-iphone-4/">allegedly leaked in a few unboxing videos</a> earlier this month, and it was shown to be a November 2024 model in those videos. If the videos are legitimate, that means the first Macs with M4 chips might not arrive to customers until next month, even if they are announced within the next week or so.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/">Gurman: &#039;M4 Mac Launch&#039; is &#039;Next Week&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-m4-mac-launch-is-next-week.2440707/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds watchOS 11.1 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate-now-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-11-1-release-candidate.2440706/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:15:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate-now-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming watchOS 11.1 update to developers and public beta testers for testing purposes. The new software comes approximately week after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/14/apple-seeds-fifth-beta-watchos-11-1/">fifth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Feature-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955937" /><br/>
watchOS 11.1 can be installed by going to the Apple Watch app and selecting the Software Update section under "General" in Settings. <br/>
<br/>
So far, no major new features have been discovered in the watchOS 11.1 update, though Apple's release notes indicate that there is a fix for an issue that could cause problems writing breathing disturbance data to the Health app. <br/>
<br/>
watchOS 11.1 is expected to see a release alongside iOS 18.1 next Monday.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate-now-available/">Apple Seeds watchOS 11.1 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-11-1-release-candidate.2440706/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Launches Tomorrow: Here Are 12 Changes to Know About</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-all-new-features-and-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-launches-tomorrow-here-are-12-changes-to-know-about.2440699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 08:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-all-new-features-and-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this month, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/apple-unveils-new-ipad-mini-apple-intelligence/">announced a new iPad mini</a> for the first time in three years. Ahead of the device launching this Wednesday, we have outlined 12 new features and changes with the seventh-generation iPad mini compared to the previous model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-apple-intelligence-a17-pro-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970909" /><br/>
Here's everything new with the iPad mini 7:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>A17 Pro chip:</strong> Introduced in the iPhone 15 Pro models last year, the A17 Pro chip is now available in the iPad mini 7, although it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/">has a 5-core GPU</a> instead of a 6-core GPU. Apple says the iPad mini 7 offers up to 30% faster CPU performance compared to the previous iPad mini with the A15 Bionic chip.</li><br/>
<li><strong>8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence support:</strong> The new iPad mini is compatible with Apple Intelligence, which will be available <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/airpods-pro-hearing-features-launching-in-ios-18-1/">starting with iPadOS 18.1 next week</a>. Geekbench results confirmed that the device is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/">equipped with 8GB of RAM</a>, the minimum requirement for Apple Intelligence. That's up from 4GB of RAM in the iPad mini 6.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Pencil Pro support:</strong> The new iPad mini is compatible with the Apple Pencil Pro.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Pencil hover:</strong> This feature lets you preview the Apple Pencil's stroke on the canvas before the accessory touches the screen.</li><br/>
<li><strong>"Jelly scrolling" fixed?</strong> Most reviews said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/does-ipad-mini-7-fix-jelly-scrolling/">"jelly scrolling" is much less noticeable or fully absent on the new iPad mini</a>, but one prominent technology website disagreed, so we await teardowns for further confirmation.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Faster USB-C port:</strong> The USB-C port on the iPad mini 7 supports data transfer speeds of up to 10 Gbps, compared to 5 Gbps for the iPad mini 6.</li><br/>
<li><strong>eSIM only:</strong> All cellular models of the iPad mini 7 lack a nano-SIM card slot worldwide and instead rely solely on digital eSIM technology.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Wi-Fi 6E support:</strong> The new iPad mini supports the faster Wi-Fi 6E standard, which extends the capabilities of regular Wi-Fi 6 to the 6 GHz band. You will also need a router with Wi-Fi 6E support.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Double the base storage:</strong> iPad mini now starts with 128GB of storage, compared to 64GB for the previous model.</li> <br/>
<li><strong>Final Cut Pro support:</strong> Final Cut Pro is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-compatible-with-final-cut-pro/">compatible with the new iPad mini</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Improved HDR photos:</strong> The new iPad mini supports "Smart HDR 4," whereas the previous model supports "Smart HDR 3." Apple says Smart HDR 4 makes photos look "even more detailed and vivid."</li><br/>
<li><strong>"iPad mini" inscription:</strong> The new iPad mini has an "iPad mini" inscription on the back of device. Previous models of the device are inscribed with "iPad."</li></ul><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-all-new-features-and-changes/">iPad Mini 7 Launches Tomorrow: Here Are 12 Changes to Know About</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-launches-tomorrow-here-are-12-changes-to-know-about.2440699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: 15 Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide-15-differences-compared.2337402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 08:16:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1729620960/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently introduced the seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, offering the A17 Pro chip, Apple Intelligence support, 8GB of memory, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover support, and more. Earlier this year, Apple debuted the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, featuring the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro support, and a larger display size option. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/ipad-mini-vs-air-early-2022.jpg" alt="" width="2498" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839261" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; effectively shares the design of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, with both devices possessing many of the same features such as an all-screen design with no Home button, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> in the top button, and stereo speakers. Despite theoretically being different product lines, the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; are almost identical in terms of specifications and are even available in the same color options. There are still some minor differences between the devices, such as their display sizes and chips, that set the devices apart.<br/>
<br/>
Should you buy the more expensive, larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, or opt for the smaller and more affordable &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;? Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two iPads is best for you. All of the differences between the two devices are listed below:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; (seventh generation, 2024)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; (sixth generation, 2024)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>8.3-inch display with 326 ppi</td><br/>
 <td>11-inch or 13-inch display with 264 ppi</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>500 nits max SDR brightness</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-inch</strong>: 500 nits max SDR brightness<br/>
<strong>13-inch</strong>: 600 nits max SDR brightness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smaller, compact design for maximum portability</td><br/>
 <td>Larger design, better for productivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 0.66 pounds (297 grams)</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-inch</strong>: Weighs 1.02 pounds (462 grams)<br/>
<strong>13-inch</strong>: Weighs 1.36 pounds (617 grams)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A17 Pro chip (introduced with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro in 2023, made with TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> N3 process)</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip (introduced with redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> in 2022, made with TSMC's enhanced 5nm N5P process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>8-core CPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>9-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated media Engine<br/>
Hardware-accelerated H.264 and HEVC<br/>
Video decode engine<br/>
Video encode engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a> support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Volume buttons on top</td><br/>
 <td>Volume buttons on right side</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12MP Ultra Wide front camera</td><br/>
 <td>Landscape 12MP Ultra Wide front camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>True Tone flash</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Compatible with Bluetooth keyboards only</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-connector/">Smart Connector</a> to support Apple's Magic Keyboard and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-keyboard/">Smart Keyboard</a> Folio</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, or 512GB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, or 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;499</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;599<br/>
<strong>13-inch</strong>: Start at &#36;799</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is the best all-around option for the majority of users, providing a large screen for productivity and consuming entertainment in a slim, portable design. The additional &#36;100 needed to buy the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; over the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is more than justified for the benefits that come with its larger display and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, not least the ability to practically use it as a laptop replacement with the Magic Keyboard and &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Yet, most customers who choose the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will do so because of its screen size rather than in spite of it. The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is ideal for comfortably reading ebooks, playing handheld games, and easy transport and storage. Those who buy the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will likely have a specific use case in mind for how they will use the device, such as for note-taking on the go with the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, throwing into a small bag to use on public transport, or giving it to a kid as their first tablet.<br/>
<br/>
If you do not see the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s smaller display, easy one-handed grip, lightweight design, and portable form factor as an advantage for your use case and are focused on a more versatile display size, you will likely prefer the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, especially as it is now available with a 13-inch size option. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is more of an all-around device that works as a potential laptop replacement with support for &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj;, with the added bonuses that come with a bigger screen for productivity and entertainment.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air/">iPad Mini vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: 15 Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide-15-differences-compared.2337402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook and COO Jeff Williams Visiting China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/cook-and-williams-visiting-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-and-coo-jeff-williams-visiting-china.2440693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:59:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/cook-and-williams-visiting-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Jeff Williams</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and COO Jeff Williams are in China this week to promote Apple's products and initiatives in the region. Throughout their trip, Cook has been <a href="https://m.weibo.cn/u/5524254784?luicode=20000061&lfid=4883088750673991">active on Weibo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/tim-cook-jeff-williams-china.jpg" alt="" width="6300" height="4235" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-972030" /><br/>
Cook and Williams met students from China Agricultural University and Zhejiang University, exploring how they use iPhones and iPads to improve sustainable agricultural practices. Cook thanked the China Rural Development Fund (CFRD) and everyone involved in the Science and Technology Backyards initiative for their work in promoting efficiency and sustainability in farming.<br/>
<br/>
They also met renowned Chinese fashion photographer Chen Man, who captured images of Cook using the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max. Cook spent time with musician Lexie Liu, who shared insights into her creative process and how she uses Apple products, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Mac. Cook and Williams also visited developers at Gala Sports, where they witnessed a demonstration of the game NBA Rivals on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<br/>
A significant aspect of Cook's trip was the announcement of Apple's support for a national parks initiative in China through a partnership with the China Green Carbon Foundation (CGCF). The visit marks Cook's second trip to China in 2024, following a visit in March, which included the opening of Apple's 57th store in the Greater China region and meetings with key suppliers. <br/>
<br/>
Simultaneously, Apple's Senior Vice President Worldwide Marketing Greg Jozwiak is <a href="https://x.com/gregjoz/status/1848372693923504398">visiting Europe</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-williams/">Jeff Williams</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/cook-and-williams-visiting-china/">Apple CEO Tim Cook and COO Jeff Williams Visiting China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-and-coo-jeff-williams-visiting-china.2440693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
