<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:03:46 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Fold: New Leak Corroborates Camera Setup on Outer Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/iphone-fold-camera-setup-outer-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-fold-new-leak-corroborates-camera-setup-on-outer-display.2455408/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 02:45:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/iphone-fold-camera-setup-outer-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Further details have emerged about the camera system on Apple's upcoming foldable iPhone, informally dubbed the "iPhone Fold."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Iridescent-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995555" /><br/>
Expected to launch next year, Apple's book-style foldable is rumored to feature a 7.8-inch crease-free internal display and a 5.5-inch external screen. According to industry analyst <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, the device will include a dual-lens rear camera along with front-facing cameras usable in both folded and unfolded states, ensuring comprehensive camera functionality in any configuration.<br/>
<br/>
While previous reports noted that the unfolded state will utilize an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/iphone-fold-display-resolutions-cameras/">under-screen camera (USC)</a>, there was less information about the front camera in the folded state – until now.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223835009454&navType=by">Korean news aggregator yeux1122</a>, citing an unknown Weibo-based source, Apple has opted for a punch-hole front-facing camera on the outer display. The design is said to be "almost identical to current foldables" on the market, such as Google's Pixel 9 Pro Fold (pictured below). The blog also cited previously revealed information on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/kuo-apple-foldable-iphone-book-style-2000/">display sizes</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/iphone-fold-display-resolutions-cameras/">screen resolutions</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It remains unclear whether the punch-hole will be visible during active use or encased in a smaller Dynamic Island, but Face ID is not expected to be part of the equation. Instead, Apple is believed to have <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">integrated Touch ID into the side button</a>, in order to conserve internal space for other components.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/google-pixel-9-fold.jpg" alt="pixel" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998892" /><br/>
Kuo says final hardware specifications will be locked in during the second quarter of this year (April 1 - June 30), suggesting some elements are still subject to change. However, analyst Jeff Pu claims the device has already entered the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/apple-foldables-mass-production-2026/">New Product Introduction (NPI) phase</a> at Foxconn – a critical stage in Apple's product development cycle – indicating that key specs may already be finalized.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/foldable-iphone-expected-2026-rumored-features/">Foldable iPhone Expected Next Year: All the Rumored Features So Far</a></li></ul><br/>
Mass production is reportedly scheduled for the fourth quarter of 2026, with a release expected late next year. The first-generation foldable iPhone is expected to carry a price tag between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/foldable-iphone-to-launch-next-year/">&#36;2,000</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/">&#36;2,300</a>. A second-generation model is reportedly already in the pipeline, with mass production planned for the second half of 2027.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/iphone-fold-camera-setup-outer-display/">iPhone Fold: New Leak Corroborates Camera Setup on Outer Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-fold-new-leak-corroborates-camera-setup-on-outer-display.2455408/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What&#039;s On Your iOS 19 Wishlist?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-wishlist/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-on-your-ios-19-wishlist.2455397/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:12:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-wishlist/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of when new versions of iOS come out, <em>MacRumors</em> forum members and readers often create wishlists for features they're hoping to see, and this year is no exception. Over on our forums, there are a <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-speculation-thread.2449565/?post=33741752#post-33741752">couple wishlists</a> of features that users have been contributing to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-wishlist.2428729/">since last June</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-19-Mock-WWDC25-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996726" /><br/>
We've rounded up a few of the features that have been suggested. Feel free to add your own suggestions in the comments here or <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-wishlist.2428729/">go visit the wishlist thread</a>.<br/>
<h2>Apps</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Custom password for locking Passwords app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to add attachments in the Passwords app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to snooze emails.</li><br/>
 	<li>Swipe gesture to delete iMessage attachments.</li><br/>
 	<li>Account balance and transaction history for all cards in Wallet app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Food logging in the Health app.</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a> icons for web apps.</li><br/>
 	<li>Toggle to force camera to use Ultrawide or Telephoto lens in low light.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Home Screen/Lock Screen</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Weather wallpaper for Lock Screen, Dynamic Wallpaper for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to pick an icon for an app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Support for split screen apps.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to turn off or speed up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> animations.</li><br/>
 	<li>Universal notification center that syncs between multiple devices.</li><br/>
 	<li>Opacity setting for widgets.</li><br/>
 	<li>More rows of icons on larger phones.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Other</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Separate volume toggles for music, system sounds, and phone calls.</li><br/>
 	<li>Custom Focus mode status options.</li><br/>
 	<li>Lock rotation options on a per-app basis.</li><br/>
 	<li>Battery status widget for all devices signed into an Apple Account.</li><br/>
 	<li>Sandboxed kids mode with apps for kids.</li><br/>
 	<li>One combined user interface for Spotlight and Type to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Number row for stock keyboard.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Read More</h2><br/>
Check out our <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-wishlist.2428729/">full iOS 19 wishlist thread</a> over on the forums for more suggestions that users have made.<br/>
<h2>What's Rumored for iOS 19</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> is rumored to be getting a major design update with visuals inspired by visionOS. It could have a floating, glossy look with a focus on transparency, along with simplified navigation and a reimagining of icons, buttons, and menu bars.<br/>
<br/>
More <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features are in the works, including the updates to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; that we were supposed to get in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. We have a list of all the &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; rumors so far <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">in our iOS 19 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-wishlist/">What&#039;s On Your iOS 19 Wishlist?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-on-your-ios-19-wishlist.2455397/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nanoleaf Launches Multi-Functional Desk Lights for Your Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/nanoleaf-pegboard-desk-dock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-multi-functional-desk-lights-for-your-mac.2455396/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:13:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/nanoleaf-pegboard-desk-dock/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nanoleaf today announced the launch of the <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/pegboard-desk-dock/?size=1">Pegboard Desk Dock</a>, a desktop light that's also able to hold accessories and serve as a dock for peripherals like a keyboard and a mouse thanks to added USB-A and USB-C ports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/nanoleaf-pegboard-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998712" /><br/>
The Pegboard Desk Dock works with the Nanoleaf Desktop app, so it is able to change the color of the light to match the content on your Mac's display, making it ideal for gaming, watching movies, and similar activities. Like other Nanoleaf products, the Pegboard Desk Dock supports millions of colors, and can be set to different scenes, including those that respond to music.<br/>
<br/>
Because the Pegboard Desk Dock is meant to work specifically with a Mac or PC using a physical connection, it does not connect to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> like other Nanoleaf products, nor does it work with the Nanoleaf mobile app. Instead, it connects to a computer over USB-C. There's a built-in USB-C cable that needs to connect to a USB-C port on a Mac or a Mac's attached display, like the Studio Display.<br/>
<br/>
Once connected, the Pegboard Desk Dock can be paired to the Nanoleaf Desktop app. More than one Dock can be paired to a Mac at once, but both need to be plugged into separate USB-C ports, or, alternatively, one can plug into the other. To power two, the host Dock's PD port needs to be connected to a power adapter via a USB-C cable, neither of which are included. You'll also need to plug in for higher powered peripherals like webcams and keyboards with RGB lighting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/nanoleaf-pegboard-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998713" /><br/>
The Nanoleaf Desktop app can be used to set colors and animated scenes where the lights will cycle through different colors using patterns. There is also the option to have the lights change based on what's on the display of your computer, which is a neat effect. Turning on this option requires Screen Mirroring to be enabled, and for that, the Nanoleaf app requires Screen and System Audio Recording capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
While the Nanoleaf Desktop app itself is slow and somewhat laggy, the Screen Mirroring feature that actually displays the colors on the Pegboard Desk Dock works well with no latency. The Screen Mirroring option matches the color of the main window that you have active, so it's best for full screen games and entertainment. It's similar to light strips that change color based on what's on a display, but it is more versatile. Because the lights aren't designed to illuminate behind a display, the Pegboard Desk Dock works for setups where your desk is not in front of a wall.<br/>
<br/>
An Orchestrator section of the app changes the light based on the audio of an app that's selected like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, and a Scenescapes feature plays sound and light for an immersive experience. There are scenes like aquarium, beach, at sea, fireplace, and rainfall. Orchestrator and Scenescapes are only available with one option without a Nanoleaf Desktop subscription.<br/>
<br/>
The Nanoleaf Desktop app costs &#36;1.99 per month or &#36;19.99 per year. It's not needed to play scenes, change colors, or use Screen Mirroring, but it is needed for full Orchestrator and Scenescape access. When Screen Mirroring isn't on, there are user-created scenes to choose from, and these scenes provide one-click access to tons of color and motion options. There's plenty to access without a subscription.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
The Pegboard Desk Dock is two-sided, so the light can be seen from either side. One side has the "pegboard" of the name, while the other is a plain, diffused LED. There are four hooks that can be attached to the pegboard side of the dock, and the size is ideal for game controllers or other similar objects.<br/>
<br/>
There are two USB-C ports at the back of the Pegboard Desk Dock, another USB-C port on the side, and a USB-A port on the opposite side, so multiple peripherals can be connected. Aside from the built-in cable, there's a cable extender if extra length is needed to reach a Mac. The light portion of the dock pops out of the base, which makes it easy to swap designs.<br/>
<br/>
Each light is 50 lumens, and the dock side is not too bright when it's next to a display, but the other side can be a little hard to look at if the colors aren't muted down somewhat. Given that these aren't super bright, they're best used for ambient lighting in a dim room.<br/>
<br/>
The Pegboard Desk Dock can be <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/pegboard-desk-dock/?size=1">purchased from the Nanoleaf website</a> for &#36;60, with a two-pack available for &#36;100.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/nanoleaf-pegboard-desk-dock/">Nanoleaf Launches Multi-Functional Desk Lights for Your Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-multi-functional-desk-lights-for-your-mac.2455396/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Working on Social Network With Image Generation Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/openai-social-network/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-working-on-social-network-with-image-generation-features.2455388/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:33:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/openai-social-network/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI is developing a social network that's focused on ChatGPT's image generation features, reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/openai/648130/openai-social-network-x-competitor">The Verge</a></em>. OpenAI is reportedly testing a prototype version of an image generator with a social feed, and OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has been asking people for feedback on the project.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
It's not clear if OpenAI will integrate its social network into ChatGPT or launch it as a standalone app, and there's also a chance that the app doesn't make it out of the prototyping phase.<br/>
<br/>
Facebook parent company Meta is also planning for a social feed for its standalone AI assistant app, which would pit OpenAI's social AI app against Meta's social AI app. OpenAI would also need to compete with X (formerly Twitter), as X already integrates with the Grok chatbot. Grok's integration with X apparently has "made everyone jealous," especially the way that "people create viral tweets by getting it to say something stupid."<br/>
<br/>
By developing a social network, OpenAI would have access to real-time data to further train its models. Meta and X both already have real-time social feeds to use for training purposes and for surfacing real-time information to answer queries.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/openai-social-network/">OpenAI Working on Social Network With Image Generation Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-working-on-social-network-with-image-generation-features.2455388/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Alogic&#039;s Roam Power Bank Charges Up All of Your Devices on the Go</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-roam-power-bank/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-roam-power-bank-charges-up-all-of-your-devices-on-the-go.2455387/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:28:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-roam-power-bank&#038;post_date=1744756099/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Portable multi-device chargers are popular accessories for frequent travelers, offering the ability to keep your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, AirPods, and in some cases other devices charged up while away from home. Alogic's recently launched <a href="https://alogic.co/products/roam-21-000mah-universal-power-bank-with-100w-usb-c-laptop-charging-and-3-in-1-wireless-charging?ref=y2uwzwu">Roam 21,000mAh 6-in-1 Power Bank</a> takes things a step further, pairing all of these chargers with an integrated battery to help charge your devices even while away from fixed power.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-devices-portrait.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998846" /><br/>
I've been testing out the Roam for a few weeks, including on a week-long multi-stop trip around the U.S., and I've found it to be a handy travel companion that gets the job done with a few sacrifices.<br/>
<br/>
The Roam is essentially a fairly large 21,000 mAh (77 Wh) power bank equipped with a variety of charging surfaces, ports, and even an integrated USB-C cable to help charge whatever devices you're bringing with you on the road.<br/>
<br/>
The whole thing folds down to a relatively compact rectangular body, but when you're ready to use it, the Qi2 magnetic phone charging pad and the Apple Watch charging puck swing up for optimal positioning while also revealing a recessed Qi charging surface for charging your AirPods. If you need to charge more devices like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and/or a Mac, there's a short integrated USB-C cable that tucks in along the side of the Roam, plus a pair of USB-C ports on the rear.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-collapsed-side.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998847" /><br/>
The body of the Roam is primarily a matte black plastic that does pick up a few fingerprints over time, with a band of aluminum around the edges.<br/>
<br/>
As noted, the phone charger on the Roam is a MagSafe-compatible Qi2 charger, and it supports up to 15 watts of charging power for most of Apple's recent iPhones. That's not quite as fast as the 25-watt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> support introduced on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series, but it's plenty sufficient. In my testing, the Roam was able to boost an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max battery by 50% in under an hour, similar to what I've seen with other Qi2 chargers. The folding pad works at any angle from completely flat against the body of the Roam to up to almost 90 degrees, and it remains solidly in position thanks to hinge tension, making it convenient to set up your phone to charge in either vertical or horizontal orientation, with StandBy mode supported.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-open.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998848" /><br/>
The AirPods charging surface is revealed once the Qi2 pad is raised, and it's a simple 5-watt Qi charging pad without magnetic alignment, but it works fine for keeping wireless charging-capable AirPods cases charged up.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch charging puck swings up at the rear of the Roam, and it's a matte black color that blends in nicely with the rest of the Roam's surface, a pleasant deviation from the typical white Apple Watch charging pucks that tend to stand out visually. The puck's design supports Nightstand mode for the Apple Watch, but its placement behind the Qi2 charger means you probably won't be able to see it while charging multiple devices. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s larger-screen StandBy functionality is better for nighttime use anyway.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-devices-landscape.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998853" /><br/>
One potentially significant drawback for the Apple Watch charger is that it is NOT a fast charger and offers only 2-watt charging. As a result, my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>'s battery only increased by around 25% in an hour on the charger, when a fast charger should be able to deliver around 80% charge in that amount of time. It's a non-issue if you want to leave your watch on the charger overnight, but if you're someone like me who likes to wear their watch overnight and usually tries to get a a quick charge in before bedtime, the Roam won't be able to deliver on that front.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-cable.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998849" /><br/>
For charging other devices, the Roam features an integrated ~5-inch USB-C cable supporting up to 100 watts of charging power, as well as two USB-C ports on the rear, one of which supports up to 100 watts and the other supporting up to 18 watts. It's worth noting that the Roam can deliver a maximum of 100 watts of simultaneous output, so you'll only be able to max out those 100-watt USB-C options if you have nothing else connected to the power bank, but you can still get a decent amount of power out of them even with other devices charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-ports.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="899" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998850" /><br/>
The Roam supports up to 65 watts of input charging through either the integrated cable or the 100-watt USB-C port, and it took about 90 minutes to recharge the Roam from 25% to 90% before things slowed a bit as it approached a full charge, reaching 97% after 120 minutes. Passthrough charging of other devices is supported if you are charging the Roam through the 100-watt USB-C port, but not if you're using the integrated cable.<br/>
<br/>
To help you keep tabs on charging state, the Roam features a small LCD on the side that shows the current level of the Roam's internal battery, as well as some small green icons to provide information about charging input and output. There is also a power button on the rear of the Roam to help you turn it on and off and activate passthrough charging, but the bank also turns off automatically after a period of non-use to help limit battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-flat-phone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998851" /><br/>
With its 21,000 mAh battery that checks in at 77 Wh, the Roam is comfortably under the limit for carrying it on an airplane, though that internal battery does still bring some heft with it. The Roam checks in at 606 grams or around 1.3 pounds.<br/>
<br/>
That's a decent amount of weight, but not unreasonably so to toss in a bag, backpack, or carry-on suitcase. Alongside everything else I was carrying in my backpack on my trip, the Roam's weight wasn't noticeable, but if I'd been traveling lighter it certainly would have made a difference. It measures in at 158 mm (6.2 inches) x 82 mm (3.2 inches) x 35 mm (1.4 inches), so it's roughly the footprint of a Pro Max phone but substantially thicker and nearly three times as heavy.<br/>
<br/>
That bulk and weight is the price you pay to be able to have a fair amount of battery power with you, but just how much does that 21,000 mAh actually get you? Alogic says you should be able to charge an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; four times from the Roam, and that seems pretty much in line with my observation of around three times for an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max's battery is only 4,685 mAh, so in theory you should be able to charge it four times from the Roam, but due to inefficiencies in power storage and transfer you won't get quite that much out of it. An Apple Watch and AirPods obviously don't require much juice to recharge, but if you're looking to charge bigger items like an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or MacBook from the Roam, you're going to start running out of power pretty quickly.<br/>
<br/>
You might be able to get a full charge of a 13-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> out of it, but a 15-inch model would definitely be pushing it and any <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> would come up short, and that doesn't even account for charging your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and any other devices from the Roam.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-watch-airpods.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998854" /><br/>
So while the Roam would be plenty adequate for a weekend trip off the grid with your smaller devices, it's not going to be sufficient to keep an entire set of Apple portable products up and running for more than a single additional charge, if that. While it would be great to be able to keep an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, MacBook, Apple Watch, and AirPods charged up for days' worth of use, the shortfall is simply the reality of how much power our devices need and the calculated tradeoffs of size and weight required to carry extra juice for them. As long as you're aware of the limitations and keep your expectations in line, the Roam can be a solid travel companion to keep your devices going when you don't have ready access to fixed power.<br/>
<br/>
The other consideration worth keeping in mind is that the handy features of the Roam do add bulk, weight, and cost to the overall package. If you want a barebones power bank in the same capacity range, you can certainly find options that are much cheaper, a bit smaller, and on the order of half the weight, but you will need cables for each of your devices and potentially not be able to charge as many devices simultaneously as you can with the Roam. The Roam is a premium product offering convenience and travel simplicity, but if you're willing to pay a bit more and carry some additional weight around, it may be worth the tradeoffs.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://alogic.co/products/roam-21-000mah-universal-power-bank-with-100w-usb-c-laptop-charging-and-3-in-1-wireless-charging?ref=y2uwzwu">Roam 21,000mAh 6-in-1 Power Bank</a> is available from Alogic's website and is normally priced at &#36;197.99, but an Easter sale currently knocks 20% off, bringing it down to &#36;158.39.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Alogic provided MacRumors with the Roam power bank for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Alogic. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-roam-power-bank/">Review: Alogic&#039;s Roam Power Bank Charges Up All of Your Devices on the Go</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-roam-power-bank-charges-up-all-of-your-devices-on-the-go.2455387/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Celebrating Earth Day With Apple Watch Activity Challenge</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-watch-activity-challenge-earth-day-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-earth-day-with-apple-watch-activity-challenge.2455384/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:27:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-watch-activity-challenge-earth-day-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will launch its next Apple Watch activity challenge on Tuesday, April 22 in celebration of Earth Day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth-day-2025-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="825" height="464" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998860" /><br/>
To complete the challenge, Apple Watch owners will be required to complete a workout that lasts for 30 minutes or longer, with the activity recorded through the Workout app or an app that adds information to the Health app.<br/>
<blockquote>On April 22, celebrate Earth Day and win this award with any workout of 30 minutes or more. Try to get outside for it!</blockquote><br/>
Apple Watch owners who earn the award will unlock an award in the Fitness app, plus they will get a series of animated stickers that can be used in the Messages and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998861" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998862" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998863" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998864" /><br/>
The April Earth Day challenge comes just before Apple's special Close Your Rings Day award on April 24, which is being offered to celebrate the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch users who close all three of their Activity rings on April 24 will earn 10 animated stickers and a digital award, plus Apple retail locations are offering a special physical pin while supplies last. The special Close Your Rings Day stickers are below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_9.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998866" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_8.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998867" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_10.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998868" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_11.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998869" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998870" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998871" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998872" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_6.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998873" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_7.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998874" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_5.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998875" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998876" /><br/>
The pin will be available at Apple Stores on April 24 on a first come, first serve basis. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-watch-activity-challenge-earth-day-2/">Apple Celebrating Earth Day With Apple Watch Activity Challenge</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-earth-day-with-apple-watch-activity-challenge.2455384/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 18.5 and macOS Sequoia 15.5 Public Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-releases-ios-18-5-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-18-5-and-macos-sequoia-15-5-public-betas.2455378/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:10:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-releases-ios-18-5-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first public betas of upcoming iOS 18.5, iPadOS 18.5, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.5 updates, allowing the public to test the updates ahead of when they see an official launch. The public betas come a day after Apple provided the second betas to developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iOS-18.5-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997322" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download the updates from the Settings app on each device after opting into the beta through Apple's public beta testing website. <br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.5 and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.5 are relatively minor updates, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-5-beta-features/">few new features</a> have been discovered. The iOS Mail app has options for toggling off Contact <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> and Group by Sender for a look that's more like the iOS 17 Mail app, and there are some minor changes to how <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> info is displayed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also released public betas of watchOS 11.5 and tvOS 18.5.<br/>
<br/>
The software likely focuses on bug fixes and security improvements that are not outward facing. We're expecting Apple to release iOS 18.5, iPadOS 18.5, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.5, and the other software updates sometime in May.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-releases-ios-18-5-public-beta/">Apple Releases iOS 18.5 and macOS Sequoia 15.5 Public Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-18-5-and-macos-sequoia-15-5-public-betas.2455378/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says These Products Are Now Vintage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-vintage-list-mac-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-these-products-are-now-vintage.2455376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:53:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-vintage-list-mac-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage products list</a> to add the 2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6s, devices that will get more limited service and repairs now that they are considered vintage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-6s-MacRumors-YouTube.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929156" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6s initially launched in 2015, but Apple kept it around as a low-cost device until 2018, which is why it is only now being added to the vintage list. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6s had Apple's A9 chip, and it was equipped with a strengthened aluminum chassis to fix the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 "bendgate" design flaw. It was also the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3d-touch/">3D Touch</a>, and the last flagship &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a headphone jack. <br/>
<br/>
The 2018 &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; came out before Apple transitioned to Apple silicon, and it was actually the last &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; that had Intel chips inside. It was equipped with Intel's "Coffee Lake" chipset with 4-core and 6-core options, plus it had Intel UHD Graphics 630.<br/>
<br/>
A device is considered "vintage" five years after it was last distributed for sale. For vintage products, Apple's retail stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers (AASPs) are still able to offer repairs, but only if the required parts are available.<br/>
<br/>
At the seven year mark after a device's last date of sale, it is considered "obsolete." Apple Stores and AASPs generally do not repair products that are obsolete, and parts are no longer provided by Apple.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-vintage-list-mac-iphone/">Apple Says These Products Are Now Vintage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-these-products-are-now-vintage.2455376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Foldable iPhone to Cost ~&#36;1,000 More Than Today&#039;s Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1-000-more-than-todays-pro-max.2455366/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:10:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will likely cost around 10% more than Samsung's rival device, according to a known Weibo leaker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-995556" /><br/>
According to a new post from the Weibo user known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a>," Apple's first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will likely cost between &#36;2,100 and &#36;2,300—just a little more than Samsung's high-end foldable.<br/>
<br/>
The Samsung Galaxy Z Fold6 starts at &#36;1,899.99, while the Galaxy Z Flip6 starts at &#36;1,219.99. Apple's first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is expected to have a book-like design that folds horizontally, just like the Z Fold. The rumored pricing would make Apple's foldable around &#36;200–&#36;400 more expensive than Samsung's equivalent offering.<br/>
<br/>
For comparison, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max starts at &#36;1,199, but when configured with 1TB of storage that increases to &#36;1,599. This means that Apple's first foldable will still be around &#36;1,000 more expensive than the current flagship &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There are a growing number of insightful reports about Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">long-rumored foldable iPhone</a>; it is now expected to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/foldable-iphone-to-launch-next-year/">as soon as next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Instant Digital has a mixed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">track record for Apple rumors</a>, but has provided some strikingly accurate information, such as the imminent launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">2023's Yellow iPhone 14</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted back glass</a> of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, the Apple Watch Series 9 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/04/apple-watch-series-9-basically-unchanged/">as a minor refresh</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/future-iphone-could-capture-spatial-photos-videos/">spatial video capture</a> on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro, the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape front-facing camera</a>, the M4 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-to-gain-matte-option/">nano-texture display option</a>, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-16-pro-battery-capacities/">battery capacities</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-may-introduce-redesigned-milanese-loop/">continued Apple Watch band compatibility</a> through the Apple Watch Series 10. As a result, their reports are worth taking seriously.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/">Foldable iPhone to Cost ~&#36;1,000 More Than Today&#039;s Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1-000-more-than-todays-pro-max.2455366/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stores to Offer 10% Off Accessories When You Recycle Electronics</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-to-launch-recycling-promotion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-to-offer-10-off-accessories-when-you-recycle-electronics.2455365/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:02:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-to-launch-recycling-promotion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Earth Day</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of Earth Day on April 22, Apple plans to launch an in-store promotion that offers customers 10% off select Apple accessories when they bring in old electronics for free recycling, according to <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1912155413639807112"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Trade-in-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1770" height="996" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985655" /><br/>
Apple has long <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in#recycle">offered to recycle</a> older devices, cables, cases, and accessories for free, as part of its environmental initiatives. Starting this Wednesday, customers who recycle electronics that are not eligible for trade-in credit at an Apple Store will temporarily qualify for up to &#36;20 off select Apple accessories, including the AirTag, AirPods, Apple Pencil, Apple Watch bands, iPhone cases, and the Magic Mouse/Trackpad/Keyboard trio for Macs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple even accepts certain electronics from other brands for free recycling, so it will be interesting to see what qualifies for this promotion.<br/>
<br/>
The promotion will run for one month, according to Gurman. It is unclear if the offer will be available in the U.S. only, or in multiple countries.<br/>
<br/>
While a 10% discount is not significant, Apple rarely offers direct savings on its products beyond its annual Back to School and Black Friday events.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earth-day/">Earth Day</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-to-launch-recycling-promotion/">Apple Stores to Offer 10% Off Accessories When You Recycle Electronics</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-to-offer-10-off-accessories-when-you-recycle-electronics.2455365/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s Spring Sale Includes Big Discounts on iPad Pro, TVs, Headphones, and Much More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/best-buys-spring-sale-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-spring-sale-includes-big-discounts-on-ipad-pro-tvs-headphones-and-much-more.2455361/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:01:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/best-buys-spring-sale-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy this week kicked off a new <a href="https://howl.link/yjzc069clxmav">Spring Sale</a>, including major discounts on computers, TVs, headphones, smartphones, video games, LEGO sets, and much more. This also includes a collection of Apple product discounts on MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, and iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Best-Buy-Spring-Sale-25-Hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998776" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In terms of Apple products, Best Buy is offering a huge collection of <a href="https://howl.link/s27s8sh1uavii">discounts on the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro</a>. You'll find nearly every Wi-Fi and cellular model on sale at Best Buy during this event, with as much as &#36;200 off these tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/yjzc069clxmav"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DISCOUNTS</div>Best Buy Spring Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Most of the deals shared below are available to all shoppers, but some do require a <a href="https://howl.link/449banpw821ef">My Best Buy Plus/Total membership</a>. These start at &#36;49.99/year for My Best Buy Plus, and grant access to exclusive discounts and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/8s9puy9as9t57">Apple</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/ipad-pro-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998782" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/gwm0qvogh2hw6">13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> - &#36;799.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/k5fhilgqqnq86">11-inch M4 iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi)</a> - &#36;899.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/u7ngje1gdphs8">13-inch M4 iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi)</a> - &#36;1,099.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/yngcuyewg1qoy">15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> - &#36;1,049.00 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/vpqgtca6p0r6r">14-inch M4 Pro MacBook Pro (24GB/512GB)</a> - &#36;1,749.00 for members (&#36;250 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/mk5eci3v9ujy8">TVs</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/samsung-frame-tv-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998785" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/lyvqkqe5offa2">65-inch LG LED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;349.99 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/d38sn911qusra">75-inch Insignia LED 4K Smart Fire TV</a> - &#36;399.99 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/i0iwj1f396o5h">85-inch Samsung QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;999.99 (&#36;700 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ziekygnaqo5be">55-inch Samsung The Frame QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/cl7h4h3x9wyft">75-inch Sony Bravia LED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;500 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/hlk96vt9cp2p4">65-inch LG OLED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,399.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/y29y6rtsjutkc">65-inch Sony Bravia OLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,799.99 (&#36;500 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/xio9zjpyhdx6w">Headphones</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/headphones-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998786" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/4y34wo97fkz19">Skullcandy Crusher Over-the-Ear Noise Cancelling Headphones</a> - &#36;129.99 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ydvq7ubyyvyp1">Sony WF1000XM5 Wireless Noise Cancelling Earbuds</a> - &#36;179.99 for members (&#36;120 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ah6jqjuk2pujs">Samsung Galaxy Buds3 Pro Wireless Earbuds</a> - &#36;209.99 (&#36;40 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/voifnet1b5cmm">Bose Ultra Open-Ear Wireless Earbuds</a> - &#36;229.00 (&#36;70 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9iiroeth7hpet">Sony WH1000XM4 Noise-Cancelling Headphones</a> - &#36;249.99 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/itib9edw405ah">Sony WH1000XM5 Wireless Noise-Cancelling Headphones</a> - &#36;329.99 (&#36;70 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/h9ql56szjle44">Laptops</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alienware-laptop-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998787" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/1umygfqmdpkf8">HP Touch Screen Laptop</a> - &#36;349.99 (&#36;230 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/voaszu4snw929">Lenovo IdeaPad Slim</a> - &#36;499.99 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/lngthxoifot9l">Alienware x16 Gaming Laptop</a> - &#36;1,799.99 (&#36;900 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/xf30g2go9bfqd">LEGO</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lego-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998788" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/7sb751mujcl2x">Lotus Flowers</a> - &#36;10.49 (&#36;4.50 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/vj9swux9zctyh">Roses Botanical Collection</a> - &#36;11.99 (&#36;3 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/exw5gem8fjg55">Creator 3-in-1 Retro Camera</a> - &#36;15.99 (&#36;4 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/q6witjujld9yz">Animal Crossing Bunnie's Outdoor Activities</a> - &#36;15.99 (&#36;4 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/7htoithgact36">Creator 3-in-1 Flatbed Truck with Helicopter</a> - &#36;15.99 (&#36;4 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/b4o3eq6w2wpev">Creator 3-in-1 Flowers in Water Can</a> - &#36;23.99 (&#36;6 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/er2kjbvcudhg1">Creator 3-in-1 Space Astronaut</a> - &#36;43.99 (&#36;11 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/best-buys-spring-sale-2025/">Best Buy&#039;s Spring Sale Includes Big Discounts on iPad Pro, TVs, Headphones, and Much More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-spring-sale-includes-big-discounts-on-ipad-pro-tvs-headphones-and-much-more.2455361/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Will Add These New Features to Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features-to-your-iphone.2455358/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:37:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first iOS 19 beta is less than two months away, and there are already a handful of new features that are expected with the update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iOS-19-Roundup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979789" /><br/>
Apple should release the first iOS 19 beta to developers immediately following the WWDC 2025 keynote, which is scheduled for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">Monday, June 9</a>. Following beta testing, the update should be released to the general public in September.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we recap the key iOS 19 rumors so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Design With Floating Tab Bar</h2><br/>
iOS 19 is expected to introduce a new design that looks more like the visionOS operating system on the Apple Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Alleged-iOS-19-Tab-Bar-Front-Page-Tech.jpg" alt="" width="3010" height="1506" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997907" /><br/>
According to Front Page Tech's Jon Prosser, iOS 19 will have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/ios-19-visionos-like-design-rumors/">glass-like appearance</a>, with added translucency for menus, buttons, and other user interface elements. He also expects <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/ios-19-rounder-app-icons-video/">rounder app icons, and a new floating tab bar</a> in Apple apps.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman also expects iOS 19 to have a visionOS-like design, and he believes the design changes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/ios-19-macos-16-major-design-update/">will be the biggest since iOS 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>End-to-End Encryption for RCS</h2><br/>
Last month, Apple said that it plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/14/apple-encrypted-rcs-messaging-software-update/">add support for end-to-end encrypted RCS messages</a> to the Messages app in future iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and watchOS software updates. That likely means iOS 19, macOS 16, and other corresponding updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/RCS-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994897" /><br/>
Apple promising end-to-end encryption for RCS messages indirectly confirms that it will be adopting the RCS Universal Profile 3.0 specification, which also includes several iMessage-like enhancements that were originally introduced in version 2.7 of the specification. iOS 18 supports RCS Universal Profile 2.4.<br/>
<br/>
Here are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/15/ios-19-rcs-upgrades/">five new capabilities</a> to expect for RCS conversations on iOS 19:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>End-to-end encryption, which will prevent Apple and any other third party from being able to read messages and attachments while they are being sent between devices</li><br/>
<li>In-line replies</li><br/>
<li>Edit messages</li><br/>
<li>Unsend messages</li><br/>
<li>Full-fledged Tapback support for RCS messages, ensuring they always work</li></ul>iMessage conversations with blue bubbles have supported end-to-end encryption by default since iOS 5. In addition, iMessage has supported in-line replies since iOS 14, while the options to edit and unsend iMessages were introduced with iOS 16.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not indicated which iOS version will upgrade RCS, but iOS 19 or a follow-up update like iOS 19.1 or iOS 19.2 seems like a safe bet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Live Translate With AirPods</h2><br/>
At least some AirPods models will be getting a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/13/airpods-live-translation-ios-19/">new live translation feature</a> with iOS 19 and an accompanying firmware update, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/10/airpods-pro-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866123" /><br/>
Here is how that feature will work, according to his report last month:<blockquote>The capability will work like this: If an English speaker is hearing someone talk in Spanish, the iPhone will translate the speech and relay it to the user's AirPods in English. The English speaker's words, meanwhile, will be translated into Spanish and played back by the iPhone.</blockquote>Google already offers a similar Live Translate feature.<br/>
<br/>
He also said iOS 19 will have bolstered translation capabilities, which likely means improvements are coming to the Apple Translate app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Revamped Health App With Coaching Feature</h2><br/>
A revamped Health app is expected to debut <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/ios-19-4-revamped-health-app-rumor/">as early as iOS 19.4 next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Apple-Health-Icon.png" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998771" /><br/>
Apple plans to offer a new AI-powered health coaching feature that offers personalized health recommendations, according to Gurman. The information provided by the coaching feature would be accompanied by videos from health experts that inform users about various health conditions and ways to make lifestyle improvements. For example, if the Apple Watch tracks poor heart-rate trends, a video could explain the risks of heart disease.<br/>
<br/>
Food tracking will be another big part of the revamped Health app, which could compete with the MyFitnessPal app, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Personalized Siri</h2><br/>
Apple recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delayed the more personalized version of Siri</a> that it previewed at WWDC last year. The company said it anticipates rolling out the Siri upgrades at some point "in the coming year," so the features could launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/">as part of iOS 19 later this year</a>, although they could also arrive as part of a later update, such as iOS 19.1 through iOS 19.4.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
Whenever they launch, the Siri upgrades will include understanding of a user's personal context, on-screen awareness, and deeper per-app controls. For example, during its WWDC 2024 keynote, Apple showed an iPhone user asking Siri about their mother's flight and lunch reservation plans based on info from the Mail and Messages apps.<br/>
<br/>
The more personalized Siri features will require an iPhone model that supports Apple Intelligence, so you will need an iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, any iPhone 16 model, or any iPhone 17 model launching later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>EU Changes</h2><br/>
The European Commission last month announced a <a href="https://digital-markets-act.ec.europa.eu/questions-and-answers/interoperability_en">long list of changes</a> that Apple is legally required to implement in future iOS 19 and iOS 20 updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iOS-19-Roundup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979789" /><br/>
The announcement clarifies interoperability requirements that Apple is required to adhere to in the EU, under the Digital Markets Act, which has been fully enforced since March 2024. The changes will further open up the iPhone and its technologies to competing companies and devices, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/19/apple-eu-interoperability-bad-for-products-users/">Apple is not happy about it</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Here are some of the key requirements:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Third-party smartwatches must be able to display and interact with iOS notifications by the end of 2025, which likely means iOS 19.2 or earlier.</li><br/>
<li>Apple must make its automatic audio switching feature available to third-party headphones by June 1, 2026, which likely means iOS 19.4 or earlier. This is the feature that allows most AirPods and select Beats to automatically switch connection between Apple devices, such as a Mac and an iPhone.</li><br/>
<li>Apple must make changes to iOS that allow for third parties to offer equivalent AirDrop alternatives by June 1, 2026.</li><br/>
<li>Apple must make changes to iOS that allow for third parties to offer equivalent AirPlay alternatives by iOS 20, or the end of 2026. iOS 20 is expected to be released to the general public in September 2026.</ul>The entire list of changes can be found <a href="https://digital-markets-act.ec.europa.eu/questions-and-answers/interoperability_en">on the European Commission's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatibility</h2><br/>
According to a reliable source of iOS-related information, iOS 19 will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones/">compatible with the iPhone 11 series and newer</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More</h2><br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19 roundup</a> for more details about the upcoming software update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features/">iOS 19 Will Add These New Features to Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features-to-your-iphone.2455358/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Launches New Collection of Charging Cables</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/beats-charging-cables/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-launches-new-collection-of-charging-cables.2455355/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/beats-charging-cables/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In line with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/26/new-beats-charging-cable-listings/">reseller leaks from last month</a>, Apple's Beats brand is launching its <a href="https://www.beatsbydre.com/products/charging-cables">first-ever set of charging cables</a> today. Available in up to four color options, the new cables include USB-C to USB-C, USB-A to USB-C, and USB-C to Lightning options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Beats-Color-Matched-Charging-Cables-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998656" /><br/>
All three cable types are available in 1.5-meter (5-foot) and 20-centimeter (8-inch) lengths and both lengths are priced at &#36;18.99 for a single cable. The 1.5-meter versions of USB-C to USB-C and USB-A to USB-C are also available in 2-packs for &#36;34.99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/beats-cable-red-pill.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998622" /><br/>
The 1-pack versions of the 1.5-meter cables are available in Bolt Black, Surge Stone, and Rapid Red, though the Rapid Red versions of the USB-A to USB-C and USB-C to Lightning won't be available until summer. The USB-C to USB-C cable is also available in a Nitro Navy color.<br/>
<br/>
The 2-pack versions of the 1.5-meter USB-C to USB-C and USB-A to USB-C cables, as well as the three 20-centimeter cables, are available only in Bolt Black.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/beats-cable-stone-desk.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998623" /><br/>
The new Beats cables are made with a woven design for increased durability and to prevent tangles, with the USB-C to USB-C cables supporting charging at up to 60 watts while the USB-A to USB-C cables support charging at up to 15 watts. Data speeds on both are limited to USB 2.0 rates. The USB-C to Lightning cables support fast charging on select <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> models, though Beats did not specify an exact wattage limit.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/W5TbUlxv3t0?si=wuTqAyUIS2DQrYWS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
To promote the launch, the Beats "Pill People" have returned in a brief ad spot voiced by comedians Ben Marshall, Desi Banks and Megan Stalter.<br/>
<br/>
The new cables are <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/accessories/all/new-arrivals?page=1&s=newest">available to order starting today</a> at apple.com in the United States, with on-shelf availability starting this Thursday, April 17.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/beats-cable-navy-phone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998625" /><br/>
The debut of the new cables from Beats follows the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-beats-iphone-16-cases/">cases for the iPhone 16 series</a> back in September <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/beats-iphone-16-cases-pink-blue/">and December</a> as the brand has worked to expand its product portfolio into new accessory categories.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/beats-charging-cables/">Beats Launches New Collection of Charging Cables</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-launches-new-collection-of-charging-cables.2455355/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 20th Anniversary iPhone May Finally Go All Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/20th-anniversary-iphone-truly-all-screen-model/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-20th-anniversary-iphone-may-finally-go-all-screen.2455353/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 06:31:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/20th-anniversary-iphone-truly-all-screen-model/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing a "bold" new iPhone Pro model for the iPhone's 20th anniversary in 2027, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2025-04-06/will-apple-raise-iphone-prices-in-the-us-after-trump-tariffs-iphone-17-details"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. As part of what's being described as a "major shake-up," Apple is said to be developing a design that makes more extensive use of glass – and this could point directly to the display itself.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/Beyond-iPhone-13-Better-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793994" /><br/>
Here's the case for Apple releasing a truly all-screen iPhone with no display cutout for its premium 20th anniversary model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Road to All-Screens</h2><br/>
Gurman recently reported that the Pro models are expected to gain a smaller Dynamic Island in 2026 or 2027, as Apple moves more of its front-facing components beneath the display. While it's not yet clear whether the selfie camera or the TrueDepth system behind Face ID will make the move first, display analyst Ross Young has said under-screen Face ID is currently slated to <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1786098652420911128">arrive in 2026</a>.<br/>
<br/>
That would mean under-display Face ID could debut as early as next year, in the iPhone 18 Pro and iPhone 18 Pro Max. In that scenario, the Dynamic Island would shrink but remain, housing a front-facing camera via a small cutout. The next logical step – for 2027's flagship – would be to move that camera under the display as well, finally achieving the full-screen design that has long been rumored. That progression aligns with <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1642942985976578049">Young's display roadmap</a>, which has predicted this shift since 2023.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/Beyond-iPhone-13-Better-Blue-Face-ID-Single-Camera-Hole.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891051" /><br/>
Backing this up, Weibo-based leaker Digital Chat Station recently claimed the next two iPhone generations – iPhone 17 and iPhone 18 – will both retain the Dynamic Island. But for the 2027 model, Apple may be on track to complete its transition to a seamless display.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Foldable Innovations</h2><br/>
Apple is reportedly already testing the technologies that could make this possible. The company is developing an 18.8-inch foldable device, and one prototype is said to feature a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/foldable-ipad-pro-under-display-face-id/">metal superstructure lens</a>" that integrates the transmitter and receiver components used for Face ID, enabling facial recognition under the display.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the long-rumored foldable iPhone, which could launch as soon as next year, reportedly uses an under-display front-facing camera and forgoes Face ID entirely, instead <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">relying on Touch ID built into the side button</a>. If accurate, that would signal Apple is actively experimenting with multiple under-display camera systems across its product lines – some with Face ID, some without.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995556" /><br/>
Together, these developments suggest Apple may already have the foundational technologies in place to hide both the TrueDepth system and selfie camera beneath the screen – key requirements for a truly all-screen iPhone. That would set the stage for a major design milestone in 2027, in line with what former design chief Jony Ive long envisioned.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Engineering Advances</h2><br/>
Of course, this all depends on Apple overcoming some significant engineering hurdles. For Face ID to work under the display, its sensors – especially those that use infrared light – need to operate without interference from the display layers above them. That's difficult with current OLED and LCD technology, which tend to scatter or absorb infrared signals.<br/>
<br/>
There are, however, several emerging display solutions that might enable this. Transparent OLED panels can allow infrared light to pass through specific areas of the screen, though current implementations suffer from reduced brightness and clarity. LTPO displays with subpixels that can temporarily deactivate may also allow sensors to "see" through the panel during authentication. <br/>
<br/>
Another possibility involves integrating optical waveguide layers into the display to channel infrared signals to and from the sensors with minimal distortion. Apple could also incorporate advanced IR-pass materials to create invisible sensor zones that preserve display quality while enabling accurate facial recognition.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2017/09/faceidscaniphonex.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="493" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-588776" /><br/>
It's likely that a future under-display Face ID system would require a combination of these technologies to meet Apple's high standards for privacy, performance, and visual consistency.<br/>
<br/>
As for the front camera, industry progress is further along. Several Android phones already feature under-display selfie cameras, and Apple has reportedly been working on its own solution for some time. According to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/">April 2024 report</a>, LG Innotek – one of Apple's Korean suppliers – is developing under-display cameras that leave no visible hole when inactive. These systems use a "freeform optic" multiple lens array designed to reduce image distortion and improve brightness, compensating for the light loss that typically occurs when a camera sits behind a display.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>20th Anniversary iPhone</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iphone-x-front-back-feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="868" height="488" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997833" /><br/>
If Apple intends to mark the iPhone's 20th anniversary with a hardware leap on the scale of 2017's iPhone X – which removed the Home button and introduced Face ID in a top-screen notch – then a true all-screen design would certainly make a splash.<br/>
<br/>
As for naming, it's unclear whether Apple will stick with its annual numbering pattern, which would put us at iPhone 19 in 2027, or choose a commemorative name like "iPhone 20" to align with the milestone year – just as it introduced the iPhone 8 and the radically redesigned iPhone X side by side in 2017.<br/>
<br/>
Either way, a full-screen, all-glass iPhone would be a fitting way to celebrate two decades of Apple's most iconic product.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/20th-anniversary-iphone-truly-all-screen-model/">Apple&#039;s 20th Anniversary iPhone May Finally Go All Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-20th-anniversary-iphone-may-finally-go-all-screen.2455353/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Feature for Tracking Lost Baggage Expands to 2 More Airlines</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/iphone-tracking-lost-baggage-china-airlines/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-feature-for-tracking-lost-baggage-expands-to-2-more-airlines.2455348/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 04:06:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/iphone-tracking-lost-baggage-china-airlines/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		<category>Find My</category>
		<category>Taiwan</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Taiwan's China Airlines and Air India now support Apple's iPhone feature that makes it easier to share the location of AirTag-equipped baggage at airports, according to <a href="https://news.ltn.com.tw/news/life/breakingnews/5012598">local</a> <a href="https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-news-technology/air-india-apple-airtag-support-how-to-track-9930422/">media</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/AirTag-on-Baggage.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-977065" /><br/>
With iOS 18.2, Apple introduced a new Find My feature that lets you temporarily share the location of an AirTag-equipped item – such as a bag – with others, including participating airline staff, to help track it if it's lost or delayed.<br/>
<br/>
Users running iOS 18.2, iPadOS 18.2, or macOS Sequoia 15.2 and later can generate a "Share Item Location" link in the Find My app. Recipients can view the item's location on a live-updating web map.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iOS-18-2-Share-Item-Location.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-976718" /><br/>
Apple says it collaborated with airlines to enable private and secure access to these links. Only a small number of people can view each link, and airline staff must authenticate using an Apple ID or a verified partner email to gain access.<br/>
<br/>
China Airlines said that as soon as customers find their item, location sharing is disabled. The owner can also stop sharing their location at any time, and the sharing link automatically expires after 7 days to ensure the privacy of passengers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Apple-Share-Item-Location-iPhone-iPad-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-976679" /><br/>
American Airlines rolled out support for the feature in February. Other airlines that also offer the feature include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/16/united-delta-air-canada-find-my-luggage/">Delta, United, Air Canada</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/airtag-lost-baggage-feature-more-airlines/">Virgin Atlantic, Lufthansa</a>, and more. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/taiwan/">Taiwan</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/iphone-tracking-lost-baggage-china-airlines/">iPhone Feature for Tracking Lost Baggage Expands to 2 More Airlines</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-feature-for-tracking-lost-baggage-expands-to-2-more-airlines.2455348/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Foldable iPhone Set to Use Exclusively Samsung OLED Panels</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-samsung-oled-panels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphone-set-to-use-exclusively-samsung-oled-panels.2455347/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:38:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-samsung-oled-panels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming foldable iPhone (aka "iPhone Fold") will use OLED panels exclusively supplied by Samsung Display, reports <em><a href="https://www.businesskorea.co.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=239775">Business Korea</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-Fold-Vertical-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988570" /><br/>
Apple's decision to rely exclusively on Samsung Display is noteworthy, as it marks a departure from Apple's usual strategy of sourcing components from multiple suppliers to reduce costs and ensure consistent quality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's decision to use Samsung as the sole supplier of the OLED panels, leaving out LG Display and China's BOE, was reportedly down to Samsung's "technological edge in minimizing screen creases." <br/>
<br/>
"For Apple, which prioritizes quality over price when selecting component suppliers, Samsung was the only viable choice," stated an industry insider quoted in the report.<br/>
<br/>
Based on previous reports, when the device is folded, users will interact with a 5.5-inch outer display that is similar to a typical iPhone screen, while unfolding it will reveal a larger 7.8-inch iPad-style screen with a punch-hole camera. The inner display is said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-2026-foldable-phone-has-no-crease/">virtually crease-free</a>, and the screen dimensions have been corroborated by two <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/kuo-apple-foldable-iphone-book-style-2000/">reputable</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/alleged-display-sizes-apple-foldable-iphone/">sources</a>. Instead of Face ID, Apple is said to be using <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">Touch ID integrated into the side button</a> to save internal space. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/foldable-iphone-expected-2026-rumored-features/">Foldable iPhone Expected Next Year: All the Rumored Features So Far</a></li></ul><br/>
According to Business Korea, the supply volume for Apple's foldable iPhone, expected to launch late next year, has not yet been finalised. However, industry expectations suggest it could exceed its initially projected annual level of 9 million units, and potentially reach over 15 million units.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-samsung-oled-panels/">Foldable iPhone Set to Use Exclusively Samsung OLED Panels</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphone-set-to-use-exclusively-samsung-oled-panels.2455347/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Foldable iPhone&#039;s Under-Screen Camera Likely Won&#039;t Include Face ID</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-under-screen-camera-no-face-id/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphones-under-screen-camera-likely-wont-include-face-id.2455343/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:43:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-under-screen-camera-no-face-id/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's rumored foldable iPhone currently in development features an under-screen camera integrated into the folding display, but the module is unlikely to include TrueDepth components that make up Face ID. That's according to Weibo-based leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PnngRFfih">Digital Chat Station</a> who has sources within the Chinese supply chain. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Iridescent-Search.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995557" /><br/>
On Monday, the leaker revealed the alleged <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/iphone-fold-display-resolutions-cameras/">screen resolutions</a> for the 7.76-inch inner display and the 5.49-inch outer display of Apple's book-style foldable device, and they also claimed that the inner display uses "under-screen camera technology." However, it was not clear whether this meant the TrueDepth system that underlies Face ID would be integrated beneath the screen along with the selfie camera.<br/>
<br/>
The latest tidbit of information clears this up, and suggests that the display will have a single punch-hole camera. It also aligns with industry analyst Ming-Chi Kuo's claim that Apple's foldable iPhone will <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">forgo Face ID authentication</a>, instead using a Touch ID side button as a means to save precious internal space. Apple already integrates Touch ID into the side button on some iPads, so there's precedent for this.<br/>
<br/>
Integrating Face ID under the screen is difficult because the core components that make up the TrueDepth camera system – like the dot projector and infrared camera – need a clear, unobstructed view to accurately scan your face. Current display layers block or distort infrared light, which degrades the system's ability to create a secure 3D facial map. Fully under-display Face ID will remain a technical hurdle until displays can transmit infrared light cleanly.<br/>
<br/>
That said, it's possible that Apple has already made advances toward achieving such a feat. Apple is also developing a larger 18.8-inch foldable device, and according to Digital Chat Station, one of Apple's engineering prototypes features a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/foldable-ipad-pro-under-display-face-id/">metal superstructure lens</a>" that integrates the receiver and transmitter components of Face ID for under-display facial recognition. <br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has suggested the "giant" foldable tablet will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/16/foldable-ipad-likely-set-for-2028-launch/">launch in 2028</a>. Whether the new Face ID technology makes it into the finished device is unknown. <br/>
<br/>
Apple will launch its long-rumored foldable iPhone late next year with a ~&#36;2,000 premium price tag attached, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/foldable-iphone-to-launch-next-year/">according to Gurman</a>. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-under-screen-camera-no-face-id/">Foldable iPhone&#039;s Under-Screen Camera Likely Won&#039;t Include Face ID</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphones-under-screen-camera-likely-wont-include-face-id.2455343/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Comedy &#039;Mythic Quest&#039; Canceled</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/mythic-quest-canceled/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-comedy-mythic-quest-canceled.2455325/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:54:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/mythic-quest-canceled/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is canceling popular comedy series Mythic Quest after a four season run, with the show to wrap up after a re-released season 4 finale that's coming later this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/mythic-quest-season-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998666" /><br/>
Mythic Quest starred Rob McElhenney, Charlotte Nicdao, Danny Pudi, and David Hornsby, all of whom played characters that worked at the fictional Mythic Quest Studios creating, designing, and running a massively multiplayer online roleplaying game. The show provided a satirical and humorous look at the inner workings of video game development.<br/>
<br/>
Season four was not initially meant to be the show's final season, so the season four finale has been updated with a new ending that will provide Mythic Quest fans with closure. In a statement to <em><a href="https://deadline.com/2025/04/mythic-quest-canceled-apple-no-season-5-finale-updated-1236367033/">Deadline</a></em>, series producers Megan Ganz, David Hornsby and Rob McElhenney said they wanted to be able to say goodbye.<br/>
<blockquote>Endings are hard. But after four incredible seasons, Mythic Quest is coming to a close. We're so proud of the show and the world we got to build -- and deeply grateful to every cast and crew member who poured their heart into it. To all our fans, thank you for playing with us. To our partners at Apple, thank you for believing in the vision from the very beginning. Because endings are hard, with Apple's blessing we made one final update to our last episode -- so we could say goodbye, instead of just game over.</blockquote><br/>
Mythic Quest was one of the first shows that launched on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+, debuting in February 2020. There have been four seasons and two special episodes, including one that was filmed remotely on iPhones during the COVID-19 pandemic.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's decision to cancel Mythic Quest follows reports of &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ losses. &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ is losing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/20/report-tv-losing-1-billion-annually/">as much as &#36;1 billion per year</a> as Apple works to lure subscribers and add more content to the streaming service.  <br/>
<br/>
Mythic Quest has spawned a spinoff show called Side Quest, a four episode miniseries that explores the lives of Mythic Quest employees and players. The final episode of season four aired on March 26 and ended with a cliffhanger. The re-edited final episode with a new ending will be available this week.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/mythic-quest-canceled/">Apple TV+ Comedy &#039;Mythic Quest&#039; Canceled</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-comedy-mythic-quest-canceled.2455325/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Trump Planning Semiconductor Tariffs That Will Impact Apple, No One &#039;Getting Off the Hook&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/trump-semiconductor-tariffs-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/trump-planning-semiconductor-tariffs-that-will-impact-apple-no-one-getting-off-the-hook.2455322/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/trump-semiconductor-tariffs-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will not be exempt from tariffs after all, with U.S. President Donald Trump working on new semiconductor levies that will likely impact Apple devices, chips from companies like Nvidia, and other electronics.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/m2-macbook-air-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-987864" /><br/>
Over the weekend, the U.S. Customers and Border Protection agency <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/apple-tariff-exemptions/">shared a long list of electronic devices</a> excluded from the current tariffs, including iPhones, iPads, Macs, the Apple Watch, and more. Apple scored a reprieve from the 145 percent tariff impacting goods imported from China and the 10 percent tariff on goods imported from other countries, but it doesn't sound like it's going to last.<br/>
<br/>
On his <a href="https://truthsocial.com/@realDonaldTrump/posts/114332337028519855">Truth Social</a> network, Trump said that no one is "getting off the hook" and there "was no tariff exception." Apple and other tech companies are "just moving to a different tariff bucket," with the 20 percent "Fentanyl Tariffs" still in place, and additional tariffs coming.<br/>
<br/>
Trump said that his administration will be "taking a look" at semiconductors and the electronics supply chain in the National Security Tariff Investigations. He also reiterated that "we need to make products in the United States." Trump is expected to announce some kind of semiconductor tariff in the coming days.<br/>
<br/>
Trump has suggested that Apple could manufacture the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and other products <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/trump-apple-us-iphone-manufacturing/">in the United States</a>, but even if such a move were not wildly expensive, Apple would not be able to find enough people with the necessary skillset to assemble devices in the quantities needed. U.S. manufacturing would also drive the cost of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; up significantly.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/trump-semiconductor-tariffs-apple/">Trump Planning Semiconductor Tariffs That Will Impact Apple, No One &#039;Getting Off the Hook&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/trump-planning-semiconductor-tariffs-that-will-impact-apple-no-one-getting-off-the-hook.2455322/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Chipolo Launches Colorful New &#039;Pop&#039; Trackers Compatible With Find My</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/chipolo-pop-tracker/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chipolo-launches-colorful-new-pop-trackers-compatible-with-find-my.2455321/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:53:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/chipolo-pop-tracker/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Chipolo today introduced a series of new Bluetooth-enabled item trackers that are compatible with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> network. Called <a href="https://chipolo.net/en-us/products/chipolo-pop">the Pop</a>, these trackers come in a range of bright colors, including blue, yellow, red, and green, along with black and white.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/chipolo-pop-tracker.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="787" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998705" /><br/>
The Chipolo Pop item trackers work with Apple &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, so you can use them just like AirTags. The Pop can be added to your Items tab in the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app, and once added, it is trackable over Bluetooth and can be placed on an item like a bag or a suitcase for tracking purposes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/chipolo-pop-tracker-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1350" height="758" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998707" /><br/>
When the item is out of range, the Pop is able to connect to the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; network to leverage the iPhones of other people to locate your item and relay its location.<br/>
<br/>
Like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a>, the Chipolo Pop is equipped with a CR2032 battery that lasts for up to a year before it needs to be replaced. The Pop is 6.6mm thick (so a little thinner than an &zwnj;AirTag&zwnj;) and it has a 300 ft range, plus it comes with a loop at the top for attaching a keyring or strap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/chipolo-pop-tracker-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="1228" height="691" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998708" /><br/>
Compared to prior-generation Chipolo trackers, the Pop has a louder sound when the Play Sound option is selected in &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, a longer range, and IP55 dust and water resistance.<br/>
<br/>
Chipolo is selling the Pop for &#36;29, and it can be purchased from the Chipolo website. Four Pops are priced at &#36;89, and six Pops are priced at &#36;121, or a little over &#36;20 per tracker.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/chipolo-pop-tracker/">Chipolo Launches Colorful New &#039;Pop&#039; Trackers Compatible With Find My</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chipolo-launches-colorful-new-pop-trackers-compatible-with-find-my.2455321/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
