<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 17:11:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Threatens to Ban Apple Devices Over ChatGPT Integration</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/elon-musk-threatens-to-ban-apple-devices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/elon-musk-threatens-to-ban-apple-devices-over-chatgpt-integration.2428757/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:29:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/elon-musk-threatens-to-ban-apple-devices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Elon Musk</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk has threatened to ban Apple devices from his companies over Apple’s newly announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/">ChatGPT integration</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/elon-musk.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-842835" /><br/>
Apple Intelligence in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia allows <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> to utilize ChatGPT to handle complex queries, but only when explicit user permission is provided. The feature is designed to provide users with richer, more contextual responses without requiring them to open the ChatGPT app.<br/>
<br/>
During Apple's keynote event, Senior Vice President of Software Engineering, Craig Federighi, emphasized that users will have full control over when ChatGPT is used and that data shared with OpenAI would not be logged or stored. "You are in control over when ChatGPT is used and will be asked before any of your information is shared," Federighi said.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these assurances, <a href="https://x.com/elonmusk">Musk expressed</a> strong opposition to the integration on his social media platform, X (formerly Twitter). Musk said, "If Apple integrates OpenAI at the OS level, then Apple devices will be banned at my companies. That is an unacceptable security violation." He continued, "Visitors will have to check their Apple devices at the door, where they will be stored in a Faraday cage." He also repeatedly questioned Apple's ability to ensure data security, stating, "Apple has no clue what's actually going on once they hand your data over to OpenAI. They're selling you down the river."<br/>
<br/>
Apple and OpenAI have both emphasized that user data will only be shared with explicit consent and that these interactions are designed to be secure. OpenAI noted in a new <a href="https://openai.com/index/openai-and-apple-announce-partnership/">blog post</a> that "requests are not stored by OpenAI, and users' IP addresses are obscured." Users can also choose to connect their ChatGPT accounts to access paid features, but this is an opt-in feature.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been clear in its messaging that the new AI capabilities are designed with user privacy at the core. Apple's approach leverages a combination of on-device processing and cloud computing, ensuring that data is not stored in the cloud. Apple's integration of ChatGPT into its operating systems is part of a broader strategy to enhance the AI capabilities of iOS, iPadOS, and macOS. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/elon-musk-threatens-to-ban-apple-devices/">Elon Musk Threatens to Ban Apple Devices Over ChatGPT Integration</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/elon-musk-threatens-to-ban-apple-devices-over-chatgpt-integration.2428757/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 and macOS Sequoia Add &#039;Rotate Wi-Fi Address&#039; Option to Cut Down on Tracking</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-rotate-wifi-address/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-and-macos-sequoia-add-rotate-wi-fi-address-option-to-cut-down-on-tracking.2428755/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:21:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-rotate-wifi-address/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, Apple has replaced the Private Wi-Fi Address option for Wi-Fi networks with a new Rotate Wi-Fi Address option that's aimed at better minimizing tracking.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/rotate-wifi-address-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="2553" height="1436" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954724" /><br/>
Available when accessing the settings of any Wi-Fi network, Apple says the opt-in Rotate Wi-Fi Address feature changes your Wi-Fi address at random times.<br/>
<blockquote>A rotating Wi-Fi address helps reduce tracking by changing your Wi-Fi address at various times. Tracking can happen when your address always appears the same to other devices and people using the same network as you.</blockquote><br/>
The prior Private Wi-Fi Address setting assigned a different MAC address to a device for each Wi-Fi network it connected to.<br/>
<br/>
Rotate Wi-Fi Address, like Private Wi-Fi Address, is separate from the additional Limit IP Address Tracking option that can be turned on for Mail and Safari.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-rotate-wifi-address/">iOS 18 and macOS Sequoia Add &#039;Rotate Wi-Fi Address&#039; Option to Cut Down on Tracking</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-and-macos-sequoia-add-rotate-wi-fi-address-option-to-cut-down-on-tracking.2428755/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia and iPadOS 18 Drop Support for These Macs and iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/macos-sequoia-and-ipados-18-compatibility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-and-ipados-18-drop-support-for-these-macs-and-ipads.2428754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:13:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/macos-sequoia-and-ipados-18-compatibility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[macOS Sequoia is still compatible with several Intel-based Macs, but it does drop support for 2018 and 2019 models of the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/sequoia.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954485" /><br/>
macOS Sequoia is compatible with the following Macs, according to Apple:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>MacBook Pro:</strong> 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>MacBook Air:</strong> 2020 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac mini:</strong> 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>iMac:</strong> 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>iMac Pro:</strong> 2017</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac Studio:</strong> 2022 and later</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mac Pro:</strong> 2019 and later</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">"Apple Intelligence" suite of AI features</a> will require an Apple silicon Mac with an M1 chip or newer. The new AI features can help you write faster, categorize mail, prioritize notifications, and more. A smarter version of Siri powered by Apple Intelligence will also be limited to Macs with an M1 chip or newer.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/">iPhone Mirroring</a> will be available on both Apple silicon Macs and Intel-based Macs with the T2 security chip, letting you control your iPhone from your Mac's screen:<blockquote>A user's custom wallpaper and icons appear just like on their iPhone, and they can swipe between pages on their Home Screen, or launch and browse any of their favorite apps. The keyboard, trackpad, and mouse on Mac also let a user interact with their iPhone, and audio even comes through. Users can seamlessly drag and drop between iPhone and Mac, and a user's iPhone remains locked, so nobody else can access or see what the user is doing. It also works great with StandBy, which stays visible, so users can get information at a glance. Additionally, users can review and respond to iPhone notifications directly from their Mac.</blockquote>As for iPadOS 18, the update drops support for the first-generation 10.5-inch iPad Pro, second-generation 12.9-inch iPad Pro, and the sixth-generation low-end iPad.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 18 is compatible with the following iPads, according to Apple:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iPad Pro: 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad Air: 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad mini: 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad: 2019 and later</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
macOS Sequoia and iPadOS 18 are now available in beta for Apple Developer Program members, and the updates should be released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/macos-sequoia-and-ipados-18-compatibility/">macOS Sequoia and iPadOS 18 Drop Support for These Macs and iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-and-ipados-18-drop-support-for-these-macs-and-ipads.2428754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Lets You Lock and Hide Your Apps for Added Privacy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-hide-lock-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-lets-you-lock-and-hide-your-apps-for-added-privacy.2428745/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:11:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-hide-lock-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is improving privacy in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, introducing a feature that allows apps to be locked or hidden, which makes them inaccessible without a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> scan.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-lock-apps.jpg" alt="" width="5560" height="3128" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954703" /><br/>
If someone is using your phone and you've locked an app, when they try to open that app, they'll see a popup that says it can't be accessed without secondary authentication. Locking an app can be done by long pressing on it and selecting the Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; option (or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>).<br/>
<br/>
Not all apps can be locked, with Apple not providing an option for innocuous apps like Maps, Clock, Calculator, and Stocks, but almost every other app can be locked, including third-party apps. When you lock an app, you have the option to hide it as well, which moves it into a locked, hidden apps folder that requires authentication to open.<br/>
<br/>
Locked or hidden apps are not only unable to be opened, but also hidden from search, notifications, and other places across the operating system. Enabling a lock on an app also shows the apps that have access to it, such as apps that are able to write images to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app. Hiding an app means that you will not receive incoming notifications or calls from it, and it will only be available from a "Hidden" folder in the App Library.<br/>
<br/>
If you want to turn off the locking feature, you can long press on an app icon and choose the "Don't Require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;" option. Turning the lock on and off requires a &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; scan, so it can't be turned off without your knowledge. Locking and hiding apps is also a feature that works on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-hide-lock-apps/">iOS 18 Lets You Lock and Hide Your Apps for Added Privacy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-lets-you-lock-and-hide-your-apps-for-added-privacy.2428745/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Can Record and Transcribe Your Phone Calls</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-record-phone-calls/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-can-record-and-transcribe-your-phone-calls.2428741/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:54:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-record-phone-calls/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of the interesting new features coming in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> will let you automatically record and transcribe your live phone calls through the Phone app. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Phone-App-Icon-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954687" /><br/>
After answering a call or placing a call, you can enable recording. All call participants are notified that the call is being recorded, so there are no surprises and everyone is aware of the recording from the start. As the call is recorded, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is also able to provide a transcript. <br/>
<br/>
The upcoming Apple Intelligence features can generate a summary of key points that were included in the call, so you can look back at what was important at a glance. <br/>
<br/>
Phone call transcription will be available in English (U.S., UK, Australia, Canada, India, Ireland, New Zealand, Singapore), Spanish (U.S., Mexico, Spain), French (France), German (Germany), Japanese (Japan), Mandarin Chinese (China mainland, Taiwan), Cantonese (China mainland, Hong Kong), and Portuguese (Brazil).<br/>
<br/>
Other new features for the Phone app include a search interface for call history, autofill for a number when you start typing in digits, and the option to seamlessly switch SIM cards. <br/>
<br/>
Apple also plans to bring the same audio and transcription features to the Notes app, so you can record audio and get a live transcript on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 and later. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-record-phone-calls/">iOS 18 Can Record and Transcribe Your Phone Calls</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-can-record-and-transcribe-your-phone-calls.2428741/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Brings New Insights, Widgets, and Health Integration to Apple&#039;s Journal App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-brings-new-insights-to-journal-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-brings-new-insights-widgets-and-health-integration-to-apples-journal-app.2428736/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:46:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-brings-new-insights-to-journal-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> introduces a host of new features for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>’s Journal app, including an all-new insights view, advanced search and sort functionalities, and integration with the Health app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-journal-app.jpg" alt="" width="4800" height="2700" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954669" /><br/>
The all-new insights view offers a comprehensive overview of journaling activities. This includes tracking writing streaks, displaying a calendar with existing entries, and providing fun statistics that encourage users to write more frequently. <br/>
<br/>
The updated Journal app now includes advanced search and sort functionalities. Users can easily locate specific entries and organize their journal for easier accessibility. <br/>
<br/>
Time spent journaling can now be recorded as mindful minutes and users can log their state of mind directly within the Journal app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has introduced new widgets for the Journal app, available on both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> and Lock Screen. These widgets allow users to quickly start a new entry, view their current streaks, and receive writing prompts throughout the day. <br/>
<br/>
The Journal app also gains automatic transcription for audio recordings, allowing users to capture their thoughts and ideas verbally, with the app converting spoken words into text entries. <br/>
<br/>
The app now supports exporting of journal entries, allowing users to save entries offline or share them in printed form.<br/>
<br/>
The Journal app made its debut on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in December 2023, but it remains unavailable in iPadOS 18 and macOS Sequoia.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-brings-new-insights-to-journal-app/">iOS 18 Brings New Insights, Widgets, and Health Integration to Apple&#039;s Journal App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-brings-new-insights-widgets-and-health-integration-to-apples-journal-app.2428736/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Introduces More Charging Limit Options on iPhone 15 Models: 85%, 90%, and 95%</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-introduces-more-charging-limits/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-introduces-more-charging-limit-options-on-iphone-15-models-85-90-and-95.2428718/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:45:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-introduces-more-charging-limits/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[All four iPhone 15 models feature a setting that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/iphone-15-80-percent-battery-limit-option/">prevents the devices from charging beyond 80%</a> while toggled on, which can potentially improve an iPhone battery's lifespan by reducing the time that the battery is fully charged. And with iOS 18, Apple has taken this feature a step further by adding new 85%, 90%, and 95% charging limit options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Custom-Emoji-Tapback-Feature-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954637" /><em>Screenshot: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a></em></div><br/>
The feature can be found in the Settings app under Battery → Charging.<br/>
<br/>
The charging limit feature remains exclusive to the iPhone 15 lineup on the first iOS 18 beta, with the option not found on the iPhone 14 Pro or older.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/">first iOS 18 beta</a> is now available for Apple Developer Program members, and a public beta will follow in July. Following beta testing, the update should be widely released to all users with an iPhone XS or newer in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-introduces-more-charging-limits/">iOS 18 Introduces More Charging Limit Options on iPhone 15 Models: 85%, 90%, and 95%</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-introduces-more-charging-limit-options-on-iphone-15-models-85-90-and-95.2428718/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Lets You Swap Out Lock Screen Camera and Flashlight Buttons</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-swap-out-lock-screen-buttons/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-lets-you-swap-out-lock-screen-camera-and-flashlight-buttons.2428710/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:22:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-swap-out-lock-screen-buttons/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> allows users to change the two shortcut buttons on the Lock Screen to an action of their choice for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-lock-screen-buttons.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954622" /><br/>
Users can now swap out the two controls at the bottom of the Lock Screen for a different action of their choosing. Shortcuts to functions like Translate, Notes, and music recognition in Shazam, and more are available. The full list of actions is as follows:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here are all the options to replace the camera and flashlight buttons on the Lock Screen on iOS 18 <a href="https://t.co/ZS6j5xWQzF">pic.twitter.com/ZS6j5xWQzF</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1800257722673181161?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 10, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
These new controls can also be accessed via the Action Button on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
The ability to change these Lock Screen controls is part of a wave of new customization features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, which includes app icon color-changing capabilities and more. The first developer beta of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is now available, with the public beta set to follow in July and the official release scheduled for the fall. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-swap-out-lock-screen-buttons/">iOS 18 Lets You Swap Out Lock Screen Camera and Flashlight Buttons</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-lets-you-swap-out-lock-screen-camera-and-flashlight-buttons.2428710/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 18 Compatible With Apple TV HD Released Nearly Nine Years Ago</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-18-compatible-apple-tv-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-compatible-with-apple-tv-hd-released-nearly-nine-years-ago.2428705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:08:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-18-compatible-apple-tv-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Here is something that Apple TV HD owners probably didn't expect when they purchased the device all the way back in 2015: it continues to receive software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-tv-4k-yellow-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870258" /><br/>
Apple's developer website confirms that the tvOS 18 update unveiled today is compatible with all Apple TV HD and Apple TV 4K models.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 compatibility list:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Apple TV HD (2015)</li><br/>
<li>Apple TV 4K (2017)</li><br/>
<li>Apple TV 4K (2nd Generation) (2021)</li><br/>
<li>Apple TV 4K (3rd Generation) (2022)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 introduces a new InSight feature, includes updates to Enhance Dialogue and subtitles, adds new screen savers, supports 21:9 video playback for playing movies and shows on projectors, and more, as outlined in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-gaining-insight-feature/">our coverage of the update</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The first tvOS 18 developer beta is available for Apple Developer Program members starting today, and Apple said that a public beta will follow in July. The update should be widely released to all users with a compatible Apple TV in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-18-compatible-apple-tv-models/">tvOS 18 Compatible With Apple TV HD Released Nearly Nine Years Ago</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-compatible-with-apple-tv-hd-released-nearly-nine-years-ago.2428705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Send Texts via Satellite in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/you-can-send-texts-via-satellite-in-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-send-texts-via-satellite-in-ios-18.2428704/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:08:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/you-can-send-texts-via-satellite-in-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple is expanding the Emergency SOS via satellite feature to introduce Messages via satellite, a feature that will let you send texts even when you don't have a Wi-Fi or cellular connection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/messages-via-satellite.jpg" alt="" width="2226" height="1252" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954617" /><br/>
Available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> or later, you can send and receive iMessages or SMS messages using a satellite connection. The feature works with all iMessage features such as emoji and Tapbacks, plus with iMessage, conversations are end-to-end encrypted.<br/>
<br/>
Messages via satellite will work on the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and later, aka the same devices that support Emergency SOS via satellite. Apple did not specify whether there will be a cost for Messages via satellite, but Emergency SOS via satellite is still free for all &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; users for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/emergency-sos-extra-year-iphone-14/">total of three years</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has said it eventually plans to charge for satellite services, but no pricing has been unveiled. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models also came with two free years of satellite access.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/you-can-send-texts-via-satellite-in-ios-18/">You Can Send Texts via Satellite in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-send-texts-via-satellite-in-ios-18.2428704/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>RCS Coming to Messages in iOS 18 for Improved Texts With Android Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18-for-improved-texts-with-android-users.2428700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:56:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>RCS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today confirmed that it plans to implement support for Rich Communication Services, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>, in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> this fall. Apple software chief Craig Federighi confirmed &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support when introducing new features for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at the WWDC keynote event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-rcs-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2776" height="1562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923042" /><br/>
We've known about Apple's plans to adopt &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; since last November, but Apple only gave a vague "later in 2024" timeline for adoption so it was unclear exactly when the feature might roll out. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; replaces SMS/MMS as the default communication protocol on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; has already been adopted by Google, U.S. smartphone carriers, and other companies, so Apple is a little late to the party. It doesn't change much for iMessage, but it does overhaul the way iPhones interact with Android devices. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; improves texting with Android users, adding support for features that have previously been limited to iMessage. Some of the additions: <br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Support for higher resolution photos and videos.</li><br/>
 <li>Support for larger file sizes and file sharing.</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages.</li><br/>
 <li>Cross-platform emoji reactions.</li><br/>
 <li>Real-time typing indicators.</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts.</li><br/>
 <li>Ability to send messages over cellular or Wi-Fi (SMS is cellular only). There is no cost to send an &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; message over Wi-Fi.</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
It is not clear if Apple will introduce &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support during the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta testing period or hold the feature until the fall public launch of the update, but we do know that it is indeed tied to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; at this point. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18/">RCS Coming to Messages in iOS 18 for Improved Texts With Android Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18-for-improved-texts-with-android-users.2428700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Introduces Standalone &#039;Passwords&#039; App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app.2428694/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:45:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iCloud Keychain</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia feature a new, dedicated Passwords app for faster access to important credentials.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954590" /><br/>
The Passwords app replaces <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, which is currently only accessible via a menu in Settings. Now, passwords are available directly via a standalone app for markedly quicker access, bringing it more in line with rival services.<br/>
<br/>
The Passwords app consolidates various credentials, including passwords, passkeys, and Wi-Fi passwords, into a single, easily accessible location. Users can filter and sort their accounts based on various criteria, such as recently created accounts, credential type, or membership in shared groups. <br/>
<br/>
Passwords is also compatible with Windows via the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; for Windows app, extending its utility to users who operate across different platforms. <br/>
<br/>
The developer beta versions of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia are available today with official release to the public scheduled for the fall, providing an early look at the Passwords app.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-keychain/">iCloud Keychain</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/">Apple Introduces Standalone &#039;Passwords&#039; App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app.2428694/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2428693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:43:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new beta firmware for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, including both the Lightning and USB-C versions. The updated firmware has a build number of 7A5220e, and it is available to developers at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/AirPods-Pro-Beta-Firmware.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1081" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803705" /><br/>
At today's keynote event, Apple introduced several new features that are coming to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, including head gestures, and these features may be included in the firmware update.<br/>
<br/>
With head gestures, users can control <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with a shake or a nod of the head. If you get a phone call, for example, you can shake your head no if you don't want to answer it, or nod to accept the call. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interactions can be used for responding to incoming messages, calls, and notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is adding Voice Isolation to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to cut down on loud background sounds to make you easier to hear, and there is a new Personalized Spatial Audio feature specific to gaming. Game developers will be able to incorporate spatial audio into their games for a more immersive audio experience.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2428693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 11 Drops Support for These Apple Watch Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-11-drops-support-for-these-apple-watch-models.2428692/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:41:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatibility-rumor/">rumored</a>, watchOS 11 drops support for the Apple Watch Series 4, Apple Watch Series 5, and first-generation Apple Watch SE, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/watchos/watchos-preview/">Apple's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/09/apple-watch-series-4-flames.jpg" alt="" width="1130" height="634" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-655494" /><br/>
The update is compatible with all other models, including the Apple Watch Series 6 and beyond:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Apple Watch SE (2nd generation)<br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 6</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 7</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 8</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 9</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Ultra</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Ultra 2</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Even though the Series 5 has an S5 chip, it has the same processor as the S4 chip in the Series 4, so it is not too surprising that Apple dropped support for these models simultaneously. Key changes with the Series 5 compared to the Series 4 included an always-on display option, increased storage, and a compass.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 11 continues to work with a paired iPhone XS or newer. A developer beta is available starting today, and a public beta will follow in July.<br/>
<br/>
The general public can expect watchOS 11 to be released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/">watchOS 11 Drops Support for These Apple Watch Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-11-drops-support-for-these-apple-watch-models.2428692/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Features Coming to iOS 18 Beta Testers This Summer</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-ios-18-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-features-coming-to-ios-18-beta-testers-this-summer.2428691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:36:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-ios-18-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a>, Apple introduced an onslaught of <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence features</a> that integrate AI into everything from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> to built-in apps like Mail, Messages, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>. Apple Intelligence is still under development, and it won't immediately be available to developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954498" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Apple plans to debut Apple Intelligence in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia betas this summer. When Apple Intelligence officially launches to the public this fall, it will be available in a beta capacity. Some of the Apple Intelligence additions might take even longer to launch, with Apple suggesting that "some features, additional languages, and platforms" will be coming over the course of the next year.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple Intelligence, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is much smarter, and there are tools for generating custom emoji and images, refining your writing, summarizing content, cutting down on unimportant notifications, and way more. Apple is also partnering with OpenAI to bring ChatGPT 4o to its platforms, with ChatGPT set to be integrated into &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and Writing Tools. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to tap into ChatGPT for some tasks, asking user permission to share information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence is free to use, but it is limited to devices with the A17 Pro chip or any M-series chip. That means to use these features, you need an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, but the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup will support Apple Intelligence too.<br/>
<br/>
On the Mac side, you need a Mac with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or later, and for iPads, you need an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> with an &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip or later.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-ios-18-beta/">Apple Intelligence Features Coming to iOS 18 Beta Testers This Summer</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-features-coming-to-ios-18-beta-testers-this-summer.2428691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Betas of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and visionOS 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-18-ipados-18-macos-sequoia-tvos-18-watchos-11-and-visionos-2.2428680/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:16:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following today's WWDC keynote event that saw the unveiling of new software, Apple has provided the first betas of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2 to developers for testing purposes. Developers have access to the software so they can begin incorporating all of the new features into their apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-tile-summary.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954455" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app on their device, going to the Software Update Section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta, but Apple allows even free developer accounts to install beta software.<br/>
<br/>
It is a bad idea to install early betas on a main device, and we recommend having a secondary device if you want to try out the software. There are often significant bugs in early versions of iOS and macOS, so if you do install on a main device, make sure to create a backup beforehand.<br/>
<br/>
Over the course of the next several months, Apple will refine the features available in all of its new software, and we will go through several betas before the updates see a public release around September.<br/>
<br/>
While the betas are limited to developers right now, Apple typically provides a public beta in July, which is usually much more stable than the early developer betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/">Apple Releases First Betas of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and visionOS 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-18-ipados-18-macos-sequoia-tvos-18-watchos-11-and-visionos-2.2428680/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases visionOS 1.2 With Persona, Eyesight and Virtual Keyboard Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-2-with-persona-eyesight-and-virtual-keyboard-improvements.2428678/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:10:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.2, the second major update to the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; operating system that launched alongside the Vision Pro in February. &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2 comes three months after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-visionos-1-1/">the launch of visionOS 1.1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929937" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Orange-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;‌ updates can be installed by going to the Settings app on the Vision Pro, selecting the General section, and choosing Software Update. The Vision Pro headset will need to be removed to install new software, with a progress bar available on the front EyeSight display.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2 adds Persona improvements such as improved hair and makeup appearance, as well as better rendering for Eyesight. Messages supports Contact Key Verification, and Apple made improvements to both the Virtual Keyboard and the Mac Virtual Display. Apple's full release notes are below.<br/>
<blockquote><strong>Mobile Device Management</strong><br/>
- Enables account-driven device and user enrollment using Managed Apple IDs<br/>
- Support for device configuration (Wi-Fi, VPN, email accounts, single sign-on, and more)<br/>
- Support for deploying apps in volume including iPhone and iPad compatible apps, visionOS apps included in a Universal purchase, and proprietary in-house visionOS apps<br/>
- Support for remote erase via MDM and device inventory data<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Messages</strong><br/>
- Adds support for iMessage Contact Key Verification<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>
- Closed captions can be anchored to the playback control while viewing Apple Immersive Video<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Persona (beta) and EyeSight</strong><br/>
- Adds an option to enroll your Persona hands-free<br/>
- Improves hair and makeup appearance<br/>
- Improves neck and mouth representation<br/>
- Improves rendering of the eyes for EyeSight<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Virtual keyboard</strong><br/>
- Cursor positioning for text input is now more accurate<br/>
- Resolves some instances where the virtual keyboard placement obscures the text input field<br/>
- Fixes an issue where in some cases, the text preview on the virtual keyboard may appear out of sync with the text field in the app<br/>
- Fixes an issue where the edit menu may appear unexpectedly<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Mac Virtual Display</strong><br/>
- Improves the reliability of discovering and connecting to a Mac using Mac Virtual Display<br/>
- Resolves an issue where Universal Control may stop working<br/>
- Addresses a connectivity issue that occurs when a previously paired Bluetooth device cannot be found<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Captive Network Support</strong><br/>
- Ability to set up your device while using a captive WiFi network such as those found at hotels, cafes and airports<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website:<br/>
https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>The first year of the Vision Pro will see plenty of feature refinements, and Apple has already announced &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 2 with even more new additions.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/">Apple Releases visionOS 1.2 With Persona, Eyesight and Virtual Keyboard Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-2-with-persona-eyesight-and-virtual-keyboard-improvements.2428678/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Recaps 18 Key Announcements From WWDC 2024 Keynote in Short Video</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-wwdc-2024-recap-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-recaps-18-key-announcements-from-wwdc-2024-keynote-in-short-video.2428675/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:03:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-wwdc-2024-recap-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple promised that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/wwdc-2024-live-coverage/">WWDC 2024 keynote</a> would be action-packed, and it absolutely was. With new updates like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-ios-18-with-new-customization-features-and-more/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, along with a whole new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence suite of AI features</a>, there were a ton of announcements.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LtIWE4CCX5M?si=osB0dzjF9CXloPjM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
To help out, Apple has shared the nearly three-minute video above highlighting 18 key things that it unveiled during the keynote.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, we'll have our own in-depth coverage of Apple's announcements here at <em>MacRumors</em>, so be sure to follow along to learn more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-wwdc-2024-recap-video/">Apple Recaps 18 Key Announcements From WWDC 2024 Keynote in Short Video</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-recaps-18-key-announcements-from-wwdc-2024-keynote-in-short-video.2428675/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and More Available in Public Beta in July</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-macos-sequoia-and-more-available-in-public-beta-in-july.2428671/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:52:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that public betas of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, and HomePod software version 18 will be available in July.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
Apple did not provide a specific release date for the public betas, nor did it say that visionOS 2 will be available as a public beta.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Developer Program members can test all of the new updates starting today, including visionOS 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/">iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and More Available in Public Beta in July</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-macos-sequoia-and-more-available-in-public-beta-in-july.2428671/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Siri Can Access ChatGPT Directly With iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-can-access-chatgpt-directly-with-ios-18.2428665/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:42:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/introducing-apple-intelligence-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">announced</a> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> will be able to access ChatGPT directly in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia to provide better responses in relevant situations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/chatgpt-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954523" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will determine if queries may be useful to forward to ChatGPT, and asks the user for permission to share. This enables &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to leverage ChatGPT's image- and text-understanding capabilities with no need to jump between tools. Users can ask questions related to text, documents, photos, PDFs, and more. <br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT will also be available in Apple's new systemwide Writing Tools to help users generate content for anything they're writing about. With Compose, users can similarly access ChatGPT image tools to generate images in a range of styles to compliment their writing.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will leverage GPT-4o for free, with no need to create an account. Requests are not logged and IP addresses are obscured. ChatGPT subscribers will also be able to access paid features within the experiences.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/">Siri Can Access ChatGPT Directly With iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-can-access-chatgpt-directly-with-ios-18.2428665/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
