<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 09:04:34 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Reveal Hidden Folder Sizes in macOS Finder With These Tricks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/reveal-finder-folder-sizes-macos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/reveal-hidden-folder-sizes-in-macos-finder-with-these-tricks.2455433/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 08:28:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/reveal-finder-folder-sizes-macos&#038;post_date=1744828090/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When using macOS Finder in List view, you'll see the sizes of individual files – but not folders.<br/>
Instead, folders show a pair of dashes (--) in the Size column. macOS skips calculating folder sizes by default to keep List view performance fast, especially in directories with many nested files. But if you want to keep an eye on folder sizes in certain locations, or even globally, there are a few ways to do it. Here's how.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/finder-window-list-view-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998961" /><br/>
What if you want to use List view and still keep an eye on the size of a handful of folders in a specific location – in Documents, for instance, or in a directory synced to a cloud storage service? Or what if you have a super-fast SSD that can handle the pressure of calculating the size of lots of folders on the fly? Thankfully, there are several ways to make Finder show folder sizes, even in List view.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Enable Calculate All Sizes</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/calculate-folder-sizes.jpg" alt="finder" width="2650" height="1742" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998962" /><br/>
Open the folder in question, select <strong>View ➝ Show View Options</strong> from the menu bar or press the keys <strong>Command+J</strong>, and check <strong>Calculate All Sizes</strong>. Finder will now remember your viewing preference for that particular location only.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Turn On Preview Panel</h2> <br/>
If you're looking for a more global solution for keeping tabs on folder sizes that will work in any Finder view mode, you might consider enabling the Preview panel. To do this, open a Finder window and select the menu bar option <strong>View ➝ Show Preview</strong>, or press the keys <strong>Shift+Command+P</strong>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/finder-folder-preview.jpg" alt="finder" width="2502" height="1178" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998964" /><br/>
In the Preview panel, the size of the selected folder always appears immediately below the folder name. If this is the only folder information you want to see in the Preview panel, you can select the menu bar option <strong>View ➝ Show Preview Options</strong> and uncheck all other metadata options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Use Get Info</h2><br/>
Of course, you may find that relying on the Preview panel to keep a check on individual folder sizes isn't an ideal use of Finder window space. This is where the menu bar option <strong>File ➝ Get Info</strong> (or key combo <strong>Command+I</strong>) can come in helpful. Opening a separate Get Info panel lets you see the size of the item in question, regardless of whether it's a file or a folder. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/get-info-windows.jpg" alt="finder" width="2622" height="1890" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998965" /><br/>
The downside? Each Get Info panel is static and specific to the item selected. Opening several at once can clutter your desktop, since each new window stays open until manually closed.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Use Inspector for Live Folder Info</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/finder-inspector.jpg" alt="finder" width="2304" height="1616" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998967" /><br/>
Fortunately, this inconvenience can be easily solved: Click <strong>File</strong> in the menu bar and hold the <strong>Option</strong> key, and <strong>Get Info</strong> will turn into <strong>Show Inspector</strong>. Unlike a Get Info panel, the Inspector panel is dynamically updated and will always display information for the active Finder window's currently selected file or folder – including, of course, its size.<br/>
<br/>
In summary, for casual folder-size checking, use the Preview panel. For detailed or multiple folders, enable Calculate All Sizes in View Options. And if you need real-time updates without clutter, use Show Inspector.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/reveal-finder-folder-sizes-macos/">Reveal Hidden Folder Sizes in macOS Finder With These Tricks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/reveal-hidden-folder-sizes-in-macos-finder-with-these-tricks.2455433/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple &#039;Vision Air&#039; Headset Rumored to Feature Thinner, Lighter Design With &#039;Midnight&#039; Finish</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-vision-air-rumored-with-new-design/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-air-headset-rumored-to-feature-thinner-lighter-design-with-midnight-finish.2455430/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 08:14:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-vision-air-rumored-with-new-design/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An all new Apple "Vision Air" headset featuring a thinner, lighter design and a "Midnight" blue finish is in the works, according to the prototype collector and leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-expanded.jpg" alt="" width="2949" height="1659" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898909" /><br/>
In a new <a href="https://x.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1912515498480193846">post on X</a>, the leaker explained that the "Vision Air" will feature a thinner design and switch the battery enclosure and several of its internal structures to titanium to reduce the device's overall weight. Most of the exterior of the device will continue to be aluminum, except with a "Midnight" bluish-black finish. Today's Vision Pro is only available in silver.<br/>
<br/>
The leaker also recently shared a series of images of a new, Lightning-style connector in Midnight purportedly for the next-generation Vision device.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Our next Vision <a href="https://t.co/VGAK9rNsrU">pic.twitter.com/VGAK9rNsrU</a></p>&mdash; Kosutami (@Kosutami_Ito) <a href="https://twitter.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1911069453170999702?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 12, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro uses a similar connector, except with 12 pins instead of eight, suggesting that the new cable is part of a more substantial redesign.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/vision-pro-2-now-in-production/">second-generation Vision Pro headset</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/03/apple-vision-pro-with-m5-chip-rumor/">M5 chip</a> between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/vision-pro-2-now-in-production/">fall 2025 and spring 2026</a>, but the company's work on a lower-cost headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/03/apple-vision-pro-with-m5-chip-rumor/">widely rumored</a>. The latter could be the "Vision Air" device Kosutami is today referring to.<br/>
<br/>
Kosutami has a mixed track record for Apple rumors, but they were the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/09/new-apple-watch-magnetic-band/">first to say</a> that Apple would replace its leather Modern Buckle band with a FineWoven version in 2023. They also went on to provide the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/exclusive-first-look-finewoven-apple-watch-band/">first real-world images</a> of the FineWoven Apple Watch bands prior to their official unveiling, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/iphone-15-pro-usb-c-thunderbolt-cable/">new Thunderbolt 4 cable</a> released alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/">improved thermal design</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">redesigned battery</a>, and more. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-vision-air-rumored-with-new-design/">Apple &#039;Vision Air&#039; Headset Rumored to Feature Thinner, Lighter Design With &#039;Midnight&#039; Finish</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-air-headset-rumored-to-feature-thinner-lighter-design-with-midnight-finish.2455430/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces Major Reduction in Greenhouse Gas Emissions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-announces-major-reduction-in-gas-emissions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-major-reduction-in-greenhouse-gas-emissions.2455426/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 07:28:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-announces-major-reduction-in-gas-emissions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Environment</category>
		<category>Environment</category>
		<category>Environmental Responsibility</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/04/apple-surpasses-60-percent-reduction-in-global-greenhouse-gas-emissions/">announced</a> that it has now reduced its global greenhouse gas emissions by more than 60 percent compared to 2015 levels, as part of its commitment to achieving full carbon neutrality across its entire business footprint by 2030.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/apple-park-sunset.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-844498" /><br/>
The update was shared ahead of Earth Day as part of the company's <a href="https://www.apple.com/environment/">2025 Environmental Progress Report</a>. The 60% milestone includes emissions from corporate operations, manufacturing, and the full product life cycle. The company aims to cut its emissions by 75% overall by 2030, with the remaining 25% to be offset through what it describes as "high-quality carbon credits." According to Apple, its efforts in 2024 alone prevented around 41 million metric tons of greenhouse gas emissions.<br/>
<br/>
The report outlines several areas of recent progress, particularly in clean energy adoption across its supply chain and the use of recycled materials in Apple-designed components. As of this year, Apple has achieved the use of 99% recycled rare earth elements in all magnets across its product lines, including in the Taptic Engine found in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch. The company also reports 99% recycled cobalt usage in batteries that are designed in-house, which it says accounts for over 97% of its total cobalt consumption. The goal is to reach 100% for both materials during 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said that there are now 17.8 gigawatts of renewable electricity in use across its supply chain–a significant increase from previous years. In 2024, the renewable energy used by suppliers helped avoid 21.8 million metric tons of emissions, an increase of more than 17% compared to 2023. Suppliers are also working with Apple to improve energy efficiency, avoiding almost two million metric tons of emissions.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has additionally focused on reducing emissions from the manufacturing of semiconductors and displays, processes that release potent fluorinated greenhouse gases. The company said that 26 of its semiconductor suppliers, as well as all of its direct display suppliers, have now committed to abate at least 90% of fluorinated emissions related to Apple production by 2030.<br/>
<br/>
Since the launch of its Supplier Clean Water Program in 2013, Apple and its suppliers have apparently saved more than 90 billion gallons of fresh water. The company reports that 14 billion gallons were saved in 2024 alone, and that participating suppliers achieved an average reuse rate of 42%. Apple has set a target to replenish 100% of freshwater used in high-stress areas by 2030 and has now initiated partnerships expected to account for over 40% of that goal.<br/>
<br/>
The company's "Zero Waste" program continued to expand last year. Suppliers involved in the program redirected roughly 600,000 metric tons of waste from landfills in 2024, bringing the total to 3.6 million metric tons since the program began in 2015. Moreover, the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> is produced using more than 55 percent recycled content—the highest proportion yet in any Apple device. <br/>
<br/>
As part of its Earth Day initiatives, Apple is encouraging users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-earth-day-recycling-promotion/">recycle eligible devices</a> by offering 10% off a new Apple accessory when recycling in-store before May 16. It is also launching a range of themed content and challenges; Apple Watch users will be able to earn a limited-edition award on April 22 by completing a 30-minute workout.<br/>
<br/>
A new episode of Time to Walk featuring actress and environmental advocate Shailene Woodley will be available from April 21 in Apple Fitness+. Additional episodes of Time to Run explore locations such as Lake Tahoe, Zion National Park, and Yellowstone. These are accompanied by a guided ocean breathing meditation.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ is also promoting a selection of nature-themed content for Earth Day, including original series such as <em>Prehistoric Planet</em>, <em>Tiny World</em>, <em>Earth at Night in Color</em>, and <em>The Secret Lives of Animals</em> in a curated collection titled "The Future Is Up to Us." The Tips app now includes a dedicated Earth Day collection that suggests ways &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users can reduce environmental impact, such as identifying plants in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app or using downloadable Maps for offline outdoor exploration.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-environment/">Apple Environment</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/environment/">Environment</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/environmental-responsibility/">Environmental Responsibility</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-announces-major-reduction-in-gas-emissions/">Apple Announces Major Reduction in Greenhouse Gas Emissions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-major-reduction-in-greenhouse-gas-emissions.2455426/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;79 Off Apple Watch SE and Apple Watch Series 10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/amazon-apple-watch-se-series-10/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-79-off-apple-watch-se-and-apple-watch-series-10.2455425/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 07:01:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/amazon-apple-watch-se-series-10/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today is discounting <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">numerous models</a> of the Apple Watch Series 10 and Apple Watch SE, including both GPS and cellular models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/apple-watch-series-10-new-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984049" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the 42mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;329.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;399.00, as well as the 46mm GPS model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;359.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;429.00. Both of these are solid second-best prices on the Apple Watch Series 10, and they're available in numerous case colors and band styles, all of which you can find in the lists below.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<h3>42mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Black Sport Band (S/M)</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJBRKHV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Ink Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHV8NLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Rose Gold Aluminum Case with Plum Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYQ1VJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Rose Gold Aluminum Case with Light Blush Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ2C3YR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Blue Cloud Sport Loop</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;399.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>46mm GPS Apple Watch Series 10</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Black Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHNXP5Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Jet Black Aluminum Case with Ink Sport Loop</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3WKR6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Rose Gold Aluminum Case with Light Blush Sport Band (M/L)</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHVB7QS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Silver Aluminum Case with Blue Cloud Sport Loop</a> - &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-watch-se-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944157" /><br/>
<br/>
In addition to Series 10 deals, Amazon is discounting the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.97</strong></a> today, down from &#36;249.00. This is the best price we've tracked so far in 2025, and it's available in Starlight, Silver, and Midnight Aluminum color options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, you can get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHRBF1J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.97</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This one is also available in Midnight, Silver, and Starlight Aluminum colors, and multiple band sizes.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHRBF1J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/amazon-apple-watch-se-series-10/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;79 Off Apple Watch SE and Apple Watch Series 10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-79-off-apple-watch-se-and-apple-watch-series-10.2455425/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches 2025 Earth Day Promotion With Discounted Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-earth-day-recycling-promotion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-2025-earth-day-promotion-with-discounted-accessories.2455421/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 06:00:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-earth-day-recycling-promotion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Earth Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today launched an <a href="http://apple.com/promo">Earth Day promotion</a> that offers customers 10% off eligible Apple accessories when they recycle eligible devices at participating Apple Stores. The offer is available from today through May 16 in many countries, including the U.S., Canada, U.K., Australia, France, Germany, Italy, Spain, China, Japan, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Trade-in-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="1770" height="996" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985656" /><br/>
Keep in mind that this promotion seems to be geared towards devices that are not eligible for trade-in credit at Apple Stores. The idea is that you can help the planet by bringing in old electronics to Apple for free recycling, as has long been possible, but now with the added bonus of receiving 10% off an accessory for a limited time.<br/>
<br/>
The offer is available at physical Apple Store locations only. Each customer may recycle up to five eligible devices for a promotional discount on eligible accessories. Recycling of the eligible device and purchase of an eligible accessory must be completed in the same transaction. Full terms and conditions <a href="http://apple.com/promo">can be found on Apple's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Eligible devices for recycling, according to Apple:<ul><li>AirPods</li><br/>
  <li>AirPort</li><br/>
  <li>AirTag</li><br/>
  <li>Apple TV</li><br/>
  <li>Computers</li><br/>
  <li>Displays</li><br/>
  <li>Hard Drives & Storage</li><br/>
  <li>Headphones & Speakers</li><br/>
  <li>HomePod</li><br/>
  <li>Mice & Keyboards</li><br/>
  <li>Networking</li><br/>
  <li>Printers & Scanners</li><br/>
  <li>Smartphones</li><br/>
  <li>Tablets</li><br/>
  <li>Watches</li><br/>
  <li>iPod</li></ul>Accessories eligible for the 10% discount:<ul><li>AirPods 4</li><br/>
  <li>AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation</li><br/>
  <li>AirTag (1-pack)</li><br/>
  <li>AirTag (4-pack)</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Pencil</li><br/>
  <li>Apple TV 4K</li><br/>
  <li>HomePod mini</li><br/>
  <li>Apple Watch bands</li><br/>
  <li>Apple-branded adapters, cables, and chargers</li><br/>
  <li>Apple-branded iPhone and iPad cases</li><br/>
  <li>Magic Mouse</li><br/>
  <li>Magic Trackpad</li><br/>
  <li>Magic Keyboard (excluding the iPad version)</li></ul>While a 10% discount is not massive, Apple rarely offers direct savings on its products beyond its annual Back to School and Black Friday events.<br/>
<br/>
Earth Day is on Tuesday, April 22.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earth-day/">Earth Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-earth-day-recycling-promotion/">Apple Launches 2025 Earth Day Promotion With Discounted Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-2025-earth-day-promotion-with-discounted-accessories.2455421/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Abruptly Changes Product Marketing Materials Amid Apple Intelligence Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-abruptly-changes-marketing-materials/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-abruptly-changes-product-marketing-materials-amid-apple-intelligence-controversy.2455417/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 05:18:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-abruptly-changes-marketing-materials/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has seemingly changed the marketing strategy for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup and other products amid the delay in releasing key <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-964666" /><br/>
The global marketing campaign for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> centered around the tagline "Hello, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;." The company now seems to have universally changed this to "Built for &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;," often in a smaller font. The alteration seems to be a subtle acknowledgment that &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; isn't ready, moving emphasis from &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; in the present to support in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple has updated its slogan from “Hello, Apple Intelligence” to “Built for Apple Intelligence” across its entire product lineup. <a href="https://t.co/jO3qzbrKT1">pic.twitter.com/jO3qzbrKT1</a></p>&mdash; Basic Apple Guy (@BasicAppleGuy) <a href="https://twitter.com/BasicAppleGuy/status/1912163132245725361?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 15, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
The change also extends to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Mac, which also carried the "Hello, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;" tagline. They too now simply say "Built for &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;." Meanwhile, some people have noticed a growing number of &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; marketing materials such as billboards with <a href="https://x.com/ParkerOrtolani/status/1912258868148858923">no reference to Apple Intelligence</a> at all.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been hit with multiple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/">class action lawsuits</a> over its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delayed Apple Intelligence features</a>. They allege that Apple violated false advertising and unfair competition laws by marketing features that are still not available. Plaintiffs claim they never would have purchased or been willing to pay as much for an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; had they known that Apple's marketing surrounding the features was false and misleading.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first previewed &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; during its WWDC 2024 keynote last June, including personalized <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, which it said would be rolling out over the course of the following year. That gave Apple until <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a> this June to roll out the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features, but last month the company announced that it needed more time and anticipated rolling out the features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">at some point "in the coming year"</a> from then. The debacle has become the subject of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/gruber-says-something-is-rotten-at-apple/">intense criticism</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The features were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-powered-siri/">initially expected to launch in iOS 18.4</a>, but they are now expected to arrive at some point during the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> cycle. Many well-connected Apple reporters and observers believe the features will not be available until 2026. The <em>New York Times</em> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-ai-struggles-2023-chip-budget-dispute/">still believes</a> that they will be released in the fall. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/apple-abruptly-changes-marketing-materials/">Apple Abruptly Changes Product Marketing Materials Amid Apple Intelligence Controversy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-abruptly-changes-product-marketing-materials-amid-apple-intelligence-controversy.2455417/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Security Database Used by Apple Goes Independent After Funding Cut [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/security-database-used-apple-goes-independent/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/security-database-used-by-apple-goes-independent-after-funding-cut-updated.2455415/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 05:10:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/security-database-used-apple-goes-independent/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Cybersecurity</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update</strong>: Following the CVE Foundation's announcement (below), CISA has said the U.S. government is extending funding to ensure no continuity issues with the critical Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) program (via <em><a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-extends-funding-to-ensure-no-lapse-in-critical-cve-services/">Bleeping Computer</a></em>). Original story follows.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<br/>
Apple, along with other tech companies, relies on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) program to identify and track security flaws in its software. This critical cybersecurity resource now faces an uncertain future, after federal funding was today abruptly cut off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
In response to the crisis, a coalition of longtime CVE Board members announced today the formation of the <a href="https://www.thecvefoundation.org">CVE Foundation</a>, a non-profit organization dedicated to ensuring the continued operation of the vulnerability identification system.<br/>
<blockquote>"CVE, as a cornerstone of the global cybersecurity ecosystem, is too important to be vulnerable itself," said Kent Landfield, an officer of the newly formed Foundation. "Cybersecurity professionals around the globe rely on CVE identifiers and data as part of their daily work—from security tools and advisories to threat intelligence and response. Without CVE, defenders are at a massive disadvantage against global cyber threats."</blockquote>The CVE program provides a standardized system for identifying and cataloging security vulnerabilities across all software and hardware, including Apple's macOS, iOS, iPadOS, and other products. When security researchers discover flaws, they're assigned unique CVE identifiers that allow companies like Apple to coordinate patches and updates.<br/>
<br/>
MITRE Corporation, which has managed the program under contract with the U.S. Department of Homeland Security, confirmed that government funding expired on April 16. <em>Reuters</em> <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-funding-running-out-critical-cyber-vulnerability-database-manager-says-2025-04-15/">reports</a> that the expiry may be linked to the federal government undergoing a radical downsizing driven in part by the Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE). The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), which is exposed to the downsizing, stated it is "urgently working to mitigate impact," as the sudden funding gap threatened to disrupt vulnerability management worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
Security experts warned that without CVE, cybersecurity efforts would face "total chaos" as the common language used to communicate about vulnerabilities would effectively disappear. One researcher compared it to "suddenly deleting all dictionaries."<br/>
<br/>
The newly established CVE Foundation aims to transition the program to a dedicated non-profit model that isn't dependent on a single government sponsor. The Foundation's organizers revealed they had been preparing for this possibility for the past year.<br/>
<br/>
"For the international cybersecurity community, this move represents an opportunity to establish governance that reflects the global nature of today's threat landscape," the Foundation stated in its <a href="https://www.thecvefoundation.org">announcement</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The funding cut also affects the related Common Weakness Enumeration (CWE) program, which helps companies like Apple identify potential security issues before they become vulnerabilities.<br/>
<br/>
The CVE Foundation is expected to release more details about its structure and funding plans in the coming days. Apple and other major tech companies will likely play a significant role in supporting it as a critical part of cybersecurity infrastructure.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cybersecurity/">Cybersecurity</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/security-database-used-apple-goes-independent/">Security Database Used by Apple Goes Independent After Funding Cut [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/security-database-used-by-apple-goes-independent-after-funding-cut-updated.2455415/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anthropic&#039;s Claude AI Chatbot Expected to Gain &#039;Voice Mode&#039; This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/anthropics-claude-ai-voice-mode-this-month/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anthropics-claude-ai-chatbot-expected-to-gain-voice-mode-this-month.2455412/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:34:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/anthropics-claude-ai-voice-mode-this-month/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.anthropic.com">Anthropic</a>, makers of the <a href="https://claude.ai/login?returnTo=%2F%3F">Claude AI chatbot</a>, are close to launching a new voice assistant to rival OpenAI's similar option for interacting with ChatGPT, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-04-15/anthropic-is-readying-a-voice-assistant-feature-to-rival-openai">Bloomberg</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/claude-ios-app.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948971" /><br/>
Unless plans change, the new "voice mode" feature could be released as soon as this month – nearly a year after OpenAI began rolling out its own equivalent to users.<br/>
<br/>
The feature, which will be available in the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/claude/id6473753684">Claude iOS app</a> and likely elsehwhere, reportedly includes three voices named Airy, Mellow, and British-accented Buttery. <br/>
<br/>
Anthropic has previously said it is working on a voice mode for Claude, but it has not officially revealed a planned launch window or any other details. The feature was discovered in Anthropic's code by app researcher M1Astra.<br/>
<br/>
Anthropic recently launched a new feature for its Claude AI assistant called "Research," aimed at providing thorough, citation-supported answers by drawing from online sources and corporate customer data. The tool is Anthropic's answer to OpenAI's Deep Research, which debuted earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, Claude is gaining support for Gmail, Google Calendar, and Google Docs, enabling users to query and interact with their Google Workspace content for more efficient task and information management.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/anthropics-claude-ai-voice-mode-this-month/">Anthropic&#039;s Claude AI Chatbot Expected to Gain &#039;Voice Mode&#039; This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anthropics-claude-ai-chatbot-expected-to-gain-voice-mode-this-month.2455412/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Fold: New Leak Corroborates Camera Setup on Outer Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/iphone-fold-camera-setup-outer-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-fold-new-leak-corroborates-camera-setup-on-outer-display.2455408/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 02:45:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/iphone-fold-camera-setup-outer-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Further details have emerged about the camera system on Apple's upcoming foldable iPhone, informally dubbed the "iPhone Fold."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Iridescent-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995555" /><br/>
Expected to launch next year, Apple's book-style foldable is rumored to feature a 7.8-inch crease-free internal display and a 5.5-inch external screen. According to industry analyst <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, the device will include a dual-lens rear camera along with front-facing cameras usable in both folded and unfolded states, ensuring comprehensive camera functionality in any configuration.<br/>
<br/>
While previous reports noted that the unfolded state will utilize an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/iphone-fold-display-resolutions-cameras/">under-screen camera (USC)</a>, there was less information about the front camera in the folded state – until now.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223835009454&navType=by">Korean news aggregator yeux1122</a>, citing an unknown Weibo-based source, Apple has opted for a hole-punch front-facing camera on the outer display. The design is said to be "almost identical to current foldables" on the market, such as Google's Pixel 9 Pro Fold (pictured below). The blog also cited previously revealed information on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/kuo-apple-foldable-iphone-book-style-2000/">display sizes</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/14/iphone-fold-display-resolutions-cameras/">screen resolutions</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It remains unclear whether the hole-punch will be visible during active use or encased in a smaller Dynamic Island, but Face ID is not expected to be part of the equation. Instead, Apple is believed to have <a href="https://mingchikuo.craft.me/84AOn3Ll8Zah6f">integrated Touch ID into the side button</a>, in order to conserve internal space for other components.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/google-pixel-9-fold.jpg" alt="pixel" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998892" /><br/>
Kuo says final hardware specifications will be locked in during the second quarter of this year (April 1 - June 30), suggesting some elements are still subject to change. However, analyst Jeff Pu claims the device has already entered the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/apple-foldables-mass-production-2026/">New Product Introduction (NPI) phase</a> at Foxconn – a critical stage in Apple's product development cycle – indicating that key specs may already be finalized.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/foldable-iphone-expected-2026-rumored-features/">Foldable iPhone Expected Next Year: All the Rumored Features So Far</a></li></ul><br/>
Mass production is reportedly scheduled for the fourth quarter of 2026, with a release expected late next year. The first-generation foldable iPhone is expected to carry a price tag between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/foldable-iphone-to-launch-next-year/">&#36;2,000</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/">&#36;2,300</a>. A second-generation model is reportedly already in the pipeline, with mass production planned for the second half of 2027.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/16/iphone-fold-camera-setup-outer-display/">iPhone Fold: New Leak Corroborates Camera Setup on Outer Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-fold-new-leak-corroborates-camera-setup-on-outer-display.2455408/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What&#039;s On Your iOS 19 Wishlist?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-wishlist/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-on-your-ios-19-wishlist.2455397/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:12:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-wishlist/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of when new versions of iOS come out, <em>MacRumors</em> forum members and readers often create wishlists for features they're hoping to see, and this year is no exception. Over on our forums, there are a <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-speculation-thread.2449565/?post=33741752#post-33741752">couple wishlists</a> of features that users have been contributing to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-wishlist.2428729/">since last June</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-19-Mock-WWDC25-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996726" /><br/>
We've rounded up a few of the features that have been suggested. Feel free to add your own suggestions in the comments here or <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-wishlist.2428729/">go visit the wishlist thread</a>.<br/>
<h2>Apps</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Custom password for locking Passwords app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to add attachments in the Passwords app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to snooze emails.</li><br/>
 	<li>Swipe gesture to delete iMessage attachments.</li><br/>
 	<li>Account balance and transaction history for all cards in Wallet app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Food logging in the Health app.</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a> icons for web apps.</li><br/>
 	<li>Toggle to force camera to use Ultrawide or Telephoto lens in low light.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Home Screen/Lock Screen</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Weather wallpaper for Lock Screen, Dynamic Wallpaper for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to pick an icon for an app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Support for split screen apps.</li><br/>
 	<li>Option to turn off or speed up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> animations.</li><br/>
 	<li>Universal notification center that syncs between multiple devices.</li><br/>
 	<li>Opacity setting for widgets.</li><br/>
 	<li>More rows of icons on larger phones.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Other</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Separate volume toggles for music, system sounds, and phone calls.</li><br/>
 	<li>Custom Focus mode status options.</li><br/>
 	<li>Lock rotation options on a per-app basis.</li><br/>
 	<li>Battery status widget for all devices signed into an Apple Account.</li><br/>
 	<li>Sandboxed kids mode with apps for kids.</li><br/>
 	<li>One combined user interface for Spotlight and Type to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Number row for stock keyboard.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Read More</h2><br/>
Check out our <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-wishlist.2428729/">full iOS 19 wishlist thread</a> over on the forums for more suggestions that users have made.<br/>
<h2>What's Rumored for iOS 19</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> is rumored to be getting a major design update with visuals inspired by visionOS. It could have a floating, glossy look with a focus on transparency, along with simplified navigation and a reimagining of icons, buttons, and menu bars.<br/>
<br/>
More <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features are in the works, including the updates to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; that we were supposed to get in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. We have a list of all the &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; rumors so far <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">in our iOS 19 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-wishlist/">What&#039;s On Your iOS 19 Wishlist?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whats-on-your-ios-19-wishlist.2455397/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nanoleaf Launches Multi-Functional Desk Lights for Your Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/nanoleaf-pegboard-desk-dock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-multi-functional-desk-lights-for-your-mac.2455396/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 15:13:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/nanoleaf-pegboard-desk-dock/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nanoleaf today announced the launch of the <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/pegboard-desk-dock/?size=1">Pegboard Desk Dock</a>, a desktop light that's also able to hold accessories and serve as a dock for peripherals like a keyboard and a mouse thanks to added USB-A and USB-C ports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/nanoleaf-pegboard-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998712" /><br/>
The Pegboard Desk Dock works with the Nanoleaf Desktop app, so it is able to change the color of the light to match the content on your Mac's display, making it ideal for gaming, watching movies, and similar activities. Like other Nanoleaf products, the Pegboard Desk Dock supports millions of colors, and can be set to different scenes, including those that respond to music.<br/>
<br/>
Because the Pegboard Desk Dock is meant to work specifically with a Mac or PC using a physical connection, it does not connect to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> like other Nanoleaf products, nor does it work with the Nanoleaf mobile app. Instead, it connects to a computer over USB-C. There's a built-in USB-C cable that needs to connect to a USB-C port on a Mac or a Mac's attached display, like the Studio Display.<br/>
<br/>
Once connected, the Pegboard Desk Dock can be paired to the Nanoleaf Desktop app. More than one Dock can be paired to a Mac at once, but both need to be plugged into separate USB-C ports, or, alternatively, one can plug into the other. To power two, the host Dock's PD port needs to be connected to a power adapter via a USB-C cable, neither of which are included. You'll also need to plug in for higher powered peripherals like webcams and keyboards with RGB lighting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/nanoleaf-pegboard-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998713" /><br/>
The Nanoleaf Desktop app can be used to set colors and animated scenes where the lights will cycle through different colors using patterns. There is also the option to have the lights change based on what's on the display of your computer, which is a neat effect. Turning on this option requires Screen Mirroring to be enabled, and for that, the Nanoleaf app requires Screen and System Audio Recording capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
While the Nanoleaf Desktop app itself is slow and somewhat laggy, the Screen Mirroring feature that actually displays the colors on the Pegboard Desk Dock works well with no latency. The Screen Mirroring option matches the color of the main window that you have active, so it's best for full screen games and entertainment. It's similar to light strips that change color based on what's on a display, but it is more versatile. Because the lights aren't designed to illuminate behind a display, the Pegboard Desk Dock works for setups where your desk is not in front of a wall.<br/>
<br/>
An Orchestrator section of the app changes the light based on the audio of an app that's selected like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, and a Scenescapes feature plays sound and light for an immersive experience. There are scenes like aquarium, beach, at sea, fireplace, and rainfall. Orchestrator and Scenescapes are only available with one option without a Nanoleaf Desktop subscription.<br/>
<br/>
The Nanoleaf Desktop app costs &#36;1.99 per month or &#36;19.99 per year. It's not needed to play scenes, change colors, or use Screen Mirroring, but it is needed for full Orchestrator and Scenescape access. When Screen Mirroring isn't on, there are user-created scenes to choose from, and these scenes provide one-click access to tons of color and motion options. There's plenty to access without a subscription.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
The Pegboard Desk Dock is two-sided, so the light can be seen from either side. One side has the "pegboard" of the name, while the other is a plain, diffused LED. There are four hooks that can be attached to the pegboard side of the dock, and the size is ideal for game controllers or other similar objects.<br/>
<br/>
There are two USB-C ports at the back of the Pegboard Desk Dock, another USB-C port on the side, and a USB-A port on the opposite side, so multiple peripherals can be connected. Aside from the built-in cable, there's a cable extender if extra length is needed to reach a Mac. The light portion of the dock pops out of the base, which makes it easy to swap designs.<br/>
<br/>
Each light is 50 lumens, and the dock side is not too bright when it's next to a display, but the other side can be a little hard to look at if the colors aren't muted down somewhat. Given that these aren't super bright, they're best used for ambient lighting in a dim room.<br/>
<br/>
The Pegboard Desk Dock can be <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/pegboard-desk-dock/?size=1">purchased from the Nanoleaf website</a> for &#36;60, with a two-pack available for &#36;100.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/nanoleaf-pegboard-desk-dock/">Nanoleaf Launches Multi-Functional Desk Lights for Your Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-multi-functional-desk-lights-for-your-mac.2455396/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Working on Social Network With Image Generation Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/openai-social-network/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-working-on-social-network-with-image-generation-features.2455388/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:33:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/openai-social-network/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI is developing a social network that's focused on ChatGPT's image generation features, reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/openai/648130/openai-social-network-x-competitor">The Verge</a></em>. OpenAI is reportedly testing a prototype version of an image generator with a social feed, and OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has been asking people for feedback on the project.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
It's not clear if OpenAI will integrate its social network into ChatGPT or launch it as a standalone app, and there's also a chance that the app doesn't make it out of the prototyping phase.<br/>
<br/>
Facebook parent company Meta is also planning for a social feed for its standalone AI assistant app, which would pit OpenAI's social AI app against Meta's social AI app. OpenAI would also need to compete with X (formerly Twitter), as X already integrates with the Grok chatbot. Grok's integration with X apparently has "made everyone jealous," especially the way that "people create viral tweets by getting it to say something stupid."<br/>
<br/>
By developing a social network, OpenAI would have access to real-time data to further train its models. Meta and X both already have real-time social feeds to use for training purposes and for surfacing real-time information to answer queries.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/openai-social-network/">OpenAI Working on Social Network With Image Generation Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-working-on-social-network-with-image-generation-features.2455388/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Alogic&#039;s Roam Power Bank Charges Up All of Your Devices on the Go</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-roam-power-bank/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-roam-power-bank-charges-up-all-of-your-devices-on-the-go.2455387/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 12:28:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-roam-power-bank&#038;post_date=1744756099/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Portable multi-device chargers are popular accessories for frequent travelers, offering the ability to keep your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, AirPods, and in some cases other devices charged up while away from home. Alogic's recently launched <a href="https://alogic.co/products/roam-21-000mah-universal-power-bank-with-100w-usb-c-laptop-charging-and-3-in-1-wireless-charging?ref=y2uwzwu">Roam 21,000mAh 6-in-1 Power Bank</a> takes things a step further, pairing all of these chargers with an integrated battery to help charge your devices even while away from fixed power.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-devices-portrait.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998846" /><br/>
I've been testing out the Roam for a few weeks, including on a week-long multi-stop trip around the U.S., and I've found it to be a handy travel companion that gets the job done with a few sacrifices.<br/>
<br/>
The Roam is essentially a fairly large 21,000 mAh (77 Wh) power bank equipped with a variety of charging surfaces, ports, and even an integrated USB-C cable to help charge whatever devices you're bringing with you on the road.<br/>
<br/>
The whole thing folds down to a relatively compact rectangular body, but when you're ready to use it, the Qi2 magnetic phone charging pad and the Apple Watch charging puck swing up for optimal positioning while also revealing a recessed Qi charging surface for charging your AirPods. If you need to charge more devices like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and/or a Mac, there's a short integrated USB-C cable that tucks in along the side of the Roam, plus a pair of USB-C ports on the rear.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-collapsed-side.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998847" /><br/>
The body of the Roam is primarily a matte black plastic that does pick up a few fingerprints over time, with a band of aluminum around the edges.<br/>
<br/>
As noted, the phone charger on the Roam is a MagSafe-compatible Qi2 charger, and it supports up to 15 watts of charging power for most of Apple's recent iPhones. That's not quite as fast as the 25-watt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> support introduced on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series, but it's plenty sufficient. In my testing, the Roam was able to boost an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max battery by 50% in under an hour, similar to what I've seen with other Qi2 chargers. The folding pad works at any angle from completely flat against the body of the Roam to up to almost 90 degrees, and it remains solidly in position thanks to hinge tension, making it convenient to set up your phone to charge in either vertical or horizontal orientation, with StandBy mode supported.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-open.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998848" /><br/>
The AirPods charging surface is revealed once the Qi2 pad is raised, and it's a simple 5-watt Qi charging pad without magnetic alignment, but it works fine for keeping wireless charging-capable AirPods cases charged up.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch charging puck swings up at the rear of the Roam, and it's a matte black color that blends in nicely with the rest of the Roam's surface, a pleasant deviation from the typical white Apple Watch charging pucks that tend to stand out visually. The puck's design supports Nightstand mode for the Apple Watch, but its placement behind the Qi2 charger means you probably won't be able to see it while charging multiple devices. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s larger-screen StandBy functionality is better for nighttime use anyway.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-devices-landscape.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998853" /><br/>
One potentially significant drawback for the Apple Watch charger is that it is NOT a fast charger and offers only 2-watt charging. As a result, my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>'s battery only increased by around 25% in an hour on the charger, when a fast charger should be able to deliver around 80% charge in that amount of time. It's a non-issue if you want to leave your watch on the charger overnight, but if you're someone like me who likes to wear their watch overnight and usually tries to get a a quick charge in before bedtime, the Roam won't be able to deliver on that front.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-cable.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998849" /><br/>
For charging other devices, the Roam features an integrated ~5-inch USB-C cable supporting up to 100 watts of charging power, as well as two USB-C ports on the rear, one of which supports up to 100 watts and the other supporting up to 18 watts. It's worth noting that the Roam can deliver a maximum of 100 watts of simultaneous output, so you'll only be able to max out those 100-watt USB-C options if you have nothing else connected to the power bank, but you can still get a decent amount of power out of them even with other devices charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-ports.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="899" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998850" /><br/>
The Roam supports up to 65 watts of input charging through either the integrated cable or the 100-watt USB-C port, and it took about 90 minutes to recharge the Roam from 25% to 90% before things slowed a bit as it approached a full charge, reaching 97% after 120 minutes. Passthrough charging of other devices is supported if you are charging the Roam through the 100-watt USB-C port, but not if you're using the integrated cable.<br/>
<br/>
To help you keep tabs on charging state, the Roam features a small LCD on the side that shows the current level of the Roam's internal battery, as well as some small green icons to provide information about charging input and output. There is also a power button on the rear of the Roam to help you turn it on and off and activate passthrough charging, but the bank also turns off automatically after a period of non-use to help limit battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-flat-phone.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998851" /><br/>
With its 21,000 mAh battery that checks in at 77 Wh, the Roam is comfortably under the limit for carrying it on an airplane, though that internal battery does still bring some heft with it. The Roam checks in at 606 grams or around 1.3 pounds.<br/>
<br/>
That's a decent amount of weight, but not unreasonably so to toss in a bag, backpack, or carry-on suitcase. Alongside everything else I was carrying in my backpack on my trip, the Roam's weight wasn't noticeable, but if I'd been traveling lighter it certainly would have made a difference. It measures in at 158 mm (6.2 inches) x 82 mm (3.2 inches) x 35 mm (1.4 inches), so it's roughly the footprint of a Pro Max phone but substantially thicker and nearly three times as heavy.<br/>
<br/>
That bulk and weight is the price you pay to be able to have a fair amount of battery power with you, but just how much does that 21,000 mAh actually get you? Alogic says you should be able to charge an &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; four times from the Roam, and that seems pretty much in line with my observation of around three times for an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max's battery is only 4,685 mAh, so in theory you should be able to charge it four times from the Roam, but due to inefficiencies in power storage and transfer you won't get quite that much out of it. An Apple Watch and AirPods obviously don't require much juice to recharge, but if you're looking to charge bigger items like an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or MacBook from the Roam, you're going to start running out of power pretty quickly.<br/>
<br/>
You might be able to get a full charge of a 13-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> out of it, but a 15-inch model would definitely be pushing it and any <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> would come up short, and that doesn't even account for charging your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and any other devices from the Roam.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alogic-roam-watch-airpods.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998854" /><br/>
So while the Roam would be plenty adequate for a weekend trip off the grid with your smaller devices, it's not going to be sufficient to keep an entire set of Apple portable products up and running for more than a single additional charge, if that. While it would be great to be able to keep an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, MacBook, Apple Watch, and AirPods charged up for days' worth of use, the shortfall is simply the reality of how much power our devices need and the calculated tradeoffs of size and weight required to carry extra juice for them. As long as you're aware of the limitations and keep your expectations in line, the Roam can be a solid travel companion to keep your devices going when you don't have ready access to fixed power.<br/>
<br/>
The other consideration worth keeping in mind is that the handy features of the Roam do add bulk, weight, and cost to the overall package. If you want a barebones power bank in the same capacity range, you can certainly find options that are much cheaper, a bit smaller, and on the order of half the weight, but you will need cables for each of your devices and potentially not be able to charge as many devices simultaneously as you can with the Roam. The Roam is a premium product offering convenience and travel simplicity, but if you're willing to pay a bit more and carry some additional weight around, it may be worth the tradeoffs.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://alogic.co/products/roam-21-000mah-universal-power-bank-with-100w-usb-c-laptop-charging-and-3-in-1-wireless-charging?ref=y2uwzwu">Roam 21,000mAh 6-in-1 Power Bank</a> is available from Alogic's website and is normally priced at &#36;197.99, but an Easter sale currently knocks 20% off, bringing it down to &#36;158.39.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Alogic provided MacRumors with the Roam power bank for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Alogic. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-roam-power-bank/">Review: Alogic&#039;s Roam Power Bank Charges Up All of Your Devices on the Go</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-roam-power-bank-charges-up-all-of-your-devices-on-the-go.2455387/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Celebrating Earth Day With Apple Watch Activity Challenge</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-watch-activity-challenge-earth-day-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-earth-day-with-apple-watch-activity-challenge.2455384/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:27:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-watch-activity-challenge-earth-day-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will launch its next Apple Watch activity challenge on Tuesday, April 22 in celebration of Earth Day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth-day-2025-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="825" height="464" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998860" /><br/>
To complete the challenge, Apple Watch owners will be required to complete a workout that lasts for 30 minutes or longer, with the activity recorded through the Workout app or an app that adds information to the Health app.<br/>
<blockquote>On April 22, celebrate Earth Day and win this award with any workout of 30 minutes or more. Try to get outside for it!</blockquote><br/>
Apple Watch owners who earn the award will unlock an award in the Fitness app, plus they will get a series of animated stickers that can be used in the Messages and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998861" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998862" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998863" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/earth_day_2025_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998864" /><br/>
The April Earth Day challenge comes just before Apple's special Close Your Rings Day award on April 24, which is being offered to celebrate the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch users who close all three of their Activity rings on April 24 will earn 10 animated stickers and a digital award, plus Apple retail locations are offering a special physical pin while supplies last. The special Close Your Rings Day stickers are below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_9.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998866" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_8.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998867" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_10.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998868" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_11.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998869" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998870" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998871" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998872" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_6.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998873" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_7.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998874" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_5.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998875" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Close_Your_Rings_2025_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998876" /><br/>
The pin will be available at Apple Stores on April 24 on a first come, first serve basis. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-watch-activity-challenge-earth-day-2/">Apple Celebrating Earth Day With Apple Watch Activity Challenge</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-earth-day-with-apple-watch-activity-challenge.2455384/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 18.5 and macOS Sequoia 15.5 Public Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-releases-ios-18-5-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-18-5-and-macos-sequoia-15-5-public-betas.2455378/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:10:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-releases-ios-18-5-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first public betas of upcoming iOS 18.5, iPadOS 18.5, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.5 updates, allowing the public to test the updates ahead of when they see an official launch. The public betas come a day after Apple provided the second betas to developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iOS-18.5-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997322" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download the updates from the Settings app on each device after opting into the beta through Apple's public beta testing website. <br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.5 and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.5 are relatively minor updates, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-5-beta-features/">few new features</a> have been discovered. The iOS Mail app has options for toggling off Contact <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> and Group by Sender for a look that's more like the iOS 17 Mail app, and there are some minor changes to how <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> info is displayed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also released public betas of watchOS 11.5 and tvOS 18.5.<br/>
<br/>
The software likely focuses on bug fixes and security improvements that are not outward facing. We're expecting Apple to release iOS 18.5, iPadOS 18.5, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.5, and the other software updates sometime in May.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-releases-ios-18-5-public-beta/">Apple Releases iOS 18.5 and macOS Sequoia 15.5 Public Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-18-5-and-macos-sequoia-15-5-public-betas.2455378/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says These Products Are Now Vintage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-vintage-list-mac-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-these-products-are-now-vintage.2455376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:53:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-vintage-list-mac-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage products list</a> to add the 2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6s, devices that will get more limited service and repairs now that they are considered vintage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-6s-MacRumors-YouTube.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929156" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6s initially launched in 2015, but Apple kept it around as a low-cost device until 2018, which is why it is only now being added to the vintage list. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6s had Apple's A9 chip, and it was equipped with a strengthened aluminum chassis to fix the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 "bendgate" design flaw. It was also the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3d-touch/">3D Touch</a>, and the last flagship &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a headphone jack. <br/>
<br/>
The 2018 &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; came out before Apple transitioned to Apple silicon, and it was actually the last &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; that had Intel chips inside. It was equipped with Intel's "Coffee Lake" chipset with 4-core and 6-core options, plus it had Intel UHD Graphics 630.<br/>
<br/>
A device is considered "vintage" five years after it was last distributed for sale. For vintage products, Apple's retail stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers (AASPs) are still able to offer repairs, but only if the required parts are available.<br/>
<br/>
At the seven year mark after a device's last date of sale, it is considered "obsolete." Apple Stores and AASPs generally do not repair products that are obsolete, and parts are no longer provided by Apple.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-vintage-list-mac-iphone/">Apple Says These Products Are Now Vintage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-these-products-are-now-vintage.2455376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Foldable iPhone to Cost ~&#36;1,000 More Than Today&#039;s Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1-000-more-than-todays-pro-max.2455366/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:10:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will likely cost around 10% more than Samsung's rival device, according to a known Weibo leaker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-995556" /><br/>
According to a new post from the Weibo user known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a>," Apple's first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will likely cost between &#36;2,100 and &#36;2,300—just a little more than Samsung's high-end foldable.<br/>
<br/>
The Samsung Galaxy Z Fold6 starts at &#36;1,899.99, while the Galaxy Z Flip6 starts at &#36;1,219.99. Apple's first foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is expected to have a book-like design that folds horizontally, just like the Z Fold. The rumored pricing would make Apple's foldable around &#36;200–&#36;400 more expensive than Samsung's equivalent offering.<br/>
<br/>
For comparison, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max starts at &#36;1,199, but when configured with 1TB of storage that increases to &#36;1,599. This means that Apple's first foldable will still be around &#36;1,000 more expensive than the current flagship &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There are a growing number of insightful reports about Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">long-rumored foldable iPhone</a>; it is now expected to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/24/foldable-iphone-to-launch-next-year/">as soon as next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Instant Digital has a mixed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">track record for Apple rumors</a>, but has provided some strikingly accurate information, such as the imminent launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">2023's Yellow iPhone 14</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted back glass</a> of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, the Apple Watch Series 9 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/04/apple-watch-series-9-basically-unchanged/">as a minor refresh</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/future-iphone-could-capture-spatial-photos-videos/">spatial video capture</a> on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro, the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape front-facing camera</a>, the M4 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-to-gain-matte-option/">nano-texture display option</a>, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-16-pro-battery-capacities/">battery capacities</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-may-introduce-redesigned-milanese-loop/">continued Apple Watch band compatibility</a> through the Apple Watch Series 10. As a result, their reports are worth taking seriously.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1000-more-than-pro-max/">Foldable iPhone to Cost ~&#36;1,000 More Than Today&#039;s Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-iphone-to-cost-1-000-more-than-todays-pro-max.2455366/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stores to Offer 10% Off Accessories When You Recycle Electronics</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-to-launch-recycling-promotion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-to-offer-10-off-accessories-when-you-recycle-electronics.2455365/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 09:02:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-to-launch-recycling-promotion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		<category>Earth Day</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of Earth Day on April 22, Apple plans to launch an in-store promotion that offers customers 10% off select Apple accessories when they bring in old electronics for free recycling, according to <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1912155413639807112"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Trade-in-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1770" height="996" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985655" /><br/>
Apple has long <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in#recycle">offered to recycle</a> older devices, cables, cases, and accessories for free, as part of its environmental initiatives. Starting this Wednesday, customers who recycle electronics that are not eligible for trade-in credit at an Apple Store will temporarily qualify for up to &#36;20 off select Apple accessories, including the AirTag, AirPods, Apple Pencil, Apple Watch bands, iPhone cases, and the Magic Mouse/Trackpad/Keyboard trio for Macs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple even accepts certain electronics from other brands for free recycling, so it will be interesting to see what qualifies for this promotion.<br/>
<br/>
The promotion will run for one month, according to Gurman. It is unclear if the offer will be available in the U.S. only, or in multiple countries.<br/>
<br/>
While a 10% discount is not significant, Apple rarely offers direct savings on its products beyond its annual Back to School and Black Friday events.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earth-day/">Earth Day</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/apple-to-launch-recycling-promotion/">Apple Stores to Offer 10% Off Accessories When You Recycle Electronics</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-to-offer-10-off-accessories-when-you-recycle-electronics.2455365/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s Spring Sale Includes Big Discounts on iPad Pro, TVs, Headphones, and Much More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/best-buys-spring-sale-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-spring-sale-includes-big-discounts-on-ipad-pro-tvs-headphones-and-much-more.2455361/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 08:01:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/best-buys-spring-sale-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy this week kicked off a new <a href="https://howl.link/yjzc069clxmav">Spring Sale</a>, including major discounts on computers, TVs, headphones, smartphones, video games, LEGO sets, and much more. This also includes a collection of Apple product discounts on MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, and iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Best-Buy-Spring-Sale-25-Hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998776" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In terms of Apple products, Best Buy is offering a huge collection of <a href="https://howl.link/s27s8sh1uavii">discounts on the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro</a>. You'll find nearly every Wi-Fi and cellular model on sale at Best Buy during this event, with as much as &#36;200 off these tablets.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/yjzc069clxmav"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DISCOUNTS</div>Best Buy Spring Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Most of the deals shared below are available to all shoppers, but some do require a <a href="https://howl.link/449banpw821ef">My Best Buy Plus/Total membership</a>. These start at &#36;49.99/year for My Best Buy Plus, and grant access to exclusive discounts and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/8s9puy9as9t57">Apple</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/ipad-pro-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998782" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/gwm0qvogh2hw6">13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> - &#36;799.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/k5fhilgqqnq86">11-inch M4 iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi)</a> - &#36;899.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/u7ngje1gdphs8">13-inch M4 iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi)</a> - &#36;1,099.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/yngcuyewg1qoy">15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> - &#36;1,049.00 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/vpqgtca6p0r6r">14-inch M4 Pro MacBook Pro (24GB/512GB)</a> - &#36;1,749.00 for members (&#36;250 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/mk5eci3v9ujy8">TVs</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/samsung-frame-tv-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998785" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/lyvqkqe5offa2">65-inch LG LED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;349.99 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/d38sn911qusra">75-inch Insignia LED 4K Smart Fire TV</a> - &#36;399.99 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/i0iwj1f396o5h">85-inch Samsung QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;999.99 (&#36;700 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ziekygnaqo5be">55-inch Samsung The Frame QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/cl7h4h3x9wyft">75-inch Sony Bravia LED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;500 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/hlk96vt9cp2p4">65-inch LG OLED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,399.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/y29y6rtsjutkc">65-inch Sony Bravia OLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,799.99 (&#36;500 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/xio9zjpyhdx6w">Headphones</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/headphones-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998786" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/4y34wo97fkz19">Skullcandy Crusher Over-the-Ear Noise Cancelling Headphones</a> - &#36;129.99 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ydvq7ubyyvyp1">Sony WF1000XM5 Wireless Noise Cancelling Earbuds</a> - &#36;179.99 for members (&#36;120 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ah6jqjuk2pujs">Samsung Galaxy Buds3 Pro Wireless Earbuds</a> - &#36;209.99 (&#36;40 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/voifnet1b5cmm">Bose Ultra Open-Ear Wireless Earbuds</a> - &#36;229.00 (&#36;70 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9iiroeth7hpet">Sony WH1000XM4 Noise-Cancelling Headphones</a> - &#36;249.99 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/itib9edw405ah">Sony WH1000XM5 Wireless Noise-Cancelling Headphones</a> - &#36;329.99 (&#36;70 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/h9ql56szjle44">Laptops</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/alienware-laptop-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998787" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/1umygfqmdpkf8">HP Touch Screen Laptop</a> - &#36;349.99 (&#36;230 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/voaszu4snw929">Lenovo IdeaPad Slim</a> - &#36;499.99 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/lngthxoifot9l">Alienware x16 Gaming Laptop</a> - &#36;1,799.99 (&#36;900 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/xf30g2go9bfqd">LEGO</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/lego-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998788" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/7sb751mujcl2x">Lotus Flowers</a> - &#36;10.49 (&#36;4.50 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/vj9swux9zctyh">Roses Botanical Collection</a> - &#36;11.99 (&#36;3 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/exw5gem8fjg55">Creator 3-in-1 Retro Camera</a> - &#36;15.99 (&#36;4 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/q6witjujld9yz">Animal Crossing Bunnie's Outdoor Activities</a> - &#36;15.99 (&#36;4 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/7htoithgact36">Creator 3-in-1 Flatbed Truck with Helicopter</a> - &#36;15.99 (&#36;4 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/b4o3eq6w2wpev">Creator 3-in-1 Flowers in Water Can</a> - &#36;23.99 (&#36;6 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/er2kjbvcudhg1">Creator 3-in-1 Space Astronaut</a> - &#36;43.99 (&#36;11 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/best-buys-spring-sale-2025/">Best Buy&#039;s Spring Sale Includes Big Discounts on iPad Pro, TVs, Headphones, and Much More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-spring-sale-includes-big-discounts-on-ipad-pro-tvs-headphones-and-much-more.2455361/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Will Add These New Features to Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features-to-your-iphone.2455358/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 07:37:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first iOS 19 beta is less than two months away, and there are already a handful of new features that are expected with the update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iOS-19-Roundup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979789" /><br/>
Apple should release the first iOS 19 beta to developers immediately following the WWDC 2025 keynote, which is scheduled for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">Monday, June 9</a>. Following beta testing, the update should be released to the general public in September.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we recap the key iOS 19 rumors so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Design With Floating Tab Bar</h2><br/>
iOS 19 is expected to introduce a new design that looks more like the visionOS operating system on the Apple Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Alleged-iOS-19-Tab-Bar-Front-Page-Tech.jpg" alt="" width="3010" height="1506" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997907" /><br/>
According to Front Page Tech's Jon Prosser, iOS 19 will have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/ios-19-visionos-like-design-rumors/">glass-like appearance</a>, with added translucency for menus, buttons, and other user interface elements. He also expects <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/ios-19-rounder-app-icons-video/">rounder app icons, and a new floating tab bar</a> in Apple apps.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman also expects iOS 19 to have a visionOS-like design, and he believes the design changes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/ios-19-macos-16-major-design-update/">will be the biggest since iOS 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>End-to-End Encryption for RCS</h2><br/>
Last month, Apple said that it plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/14/apple-encrypted-rcs-messaging-software-update/">add support for end-to-end encrypted RCS messages</a> to the Messages app in future iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and watchOS software updates. That likely means iOS 19, macOS 16, and other corresponding updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/RCS-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994897" /><br/>
Apple promising end-to-end encryption for RCS messages indirectly confirms that it will be adopting the RCS Universal Profile 3.0 specification, which also includes several iMessage-like enhancements that were originally introduced in version 2.7 of the specification. iOS 18 supports RCS Universal Profile 2.4.<br/>
<br/>
Here are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/15/ios-19-rcs-upgrades/">five new capabilities</a> to expect for RCS conversations on iOS 19:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>End-to-end encryption, which will prevent Apple and any other third party from being able to read messages and attachments while they are being sent between devices</li><br/>
<li>In-line replies</li><br/>
<li>Edit messages</li><br/>
<li>Unsend messages</li><br/>
<li>Full-fledged Tapback support for RCS messages, ensuring they always work</li></ul>iMessage conversations with blue bubbles have supported end-to-end encryption by default since iOS 5. In addition, iMessage has supported in-line replies since iOS 14, while the options to edit and unsend iMessages were introduced with iOS 16.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not indicated which iOS version will upgrade RCS, but iOS 19 or a follow-up update like iOS 19.1 or iOS 19.2 seems like a safe bet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Live Translate With AirPods</h2><br/>
At least some AirPods models will be getting a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/13/airpods-live-translation-ios-19/">new live translation feature</a> with iOS 19 and an accompanying firmware update, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/10/airpods-pro-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866123" /><br/>
Here is how that feature will work, according to his report last month:<blockquote>The capability will work like this: If an English speaker is hearing someone talk in Spanish, the iPhone will translate the speech and relay it to the user's AirPods in English. The English speaker's words, meanwhile, will be translated into Spanish and played back by the iPhone.</blockquote>Google already offers a similar Live Translate feature.<br/>
<br/>
He also said iOS 19 will have bolstered translation capabilities, which likely means improvements are coming to the Apple Translate app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Revamped Health App With Coaching Feature</h2><br/>
A revamped Health app is expected to debut <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/ios-19-4-revamped-health-app-rumor/">as early as iOS 19.4 next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Apple-Health-Icon.png" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998771" /><br/>
Apple plans to offer a new AI-powered health coaching feature that offers personalized health recommendations, according to Gurman. The information provided by the coaching feature would be accompanied by videos from health experts that inform users about various health conditions and ways to make lifestyle improvements. For example, if the Apple Watch tracks poor heart-rate trends, a video could explain the risks of heart disease.<br/>
<br/>
Food tracking will be another big part of the revamped Health app, which could compete with the MyFitnessPal app, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Personalized Siri</h2><br/>
Apple recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delayed the more personalized version of Siri</a> that it previewed at WWDC last year. The company said it anticipates rolling out the Siri upgrades at some point "in the coming year," so the features could launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/">as part of iOS 19 later this year</a>, although they could also arrive as part of a later update, such as iOS 19.1 through iOS 19.4.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
Whenever they launch, the Siri upgrades will include understanding of a user's personal context, on-screen awareness, and deeper per-app controls. For example, during its WWDC 2024 keynote, Apple showed an iPhone user asking Siri about their mother's flight and lunch reservation plans based on info from the Mail and Messages apps.<br/>
<br/>
The more personalized Siri features will require an iPhone model that supports Apple Intelligence, so you will need an iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, any iPhone 16 model, or any iPhone 17 model launching later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>EU Changes</h2><br/>
The European Commission last month announced a <a href="https://digital-markets-act.ec.europa.eu/questions-and-answers/interoperability_en">long list of changes</a> that Apple is legally required to implement in future iOS 19 and iOS 20 updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iOS-19-Roundup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979789" /><br/>
The announcement clarifies interoperability requirements that Apple is required to adhere to in the EU, under the Digital Markets Act, which has been fully enforced since March 2024. The changes will further open up the iPhone and its technologies to competing companies and devices, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/19/apple-eu-interoperability-bad-for-products-users/">Apple is not happy about it</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Here are some of the key requirements:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Third-party smartwatches must be able to display and interact with iOS notifications by the end of 2025, which likely means iOS 19.2 or earlier.</li><br/>
<li>Apple must make its automatic audio switching feature available to third-party headphones by June 1, 2026, which likely means iOS 19.4 or earlier. This is the feature that allows most AirPods and select Beats to automatically switch connection between Apple devices, such as a Mac and an iPhone.</li><br/>
<li>Apple must make changes to iOS that allow for third parties to offer equivalent AirDrop alternatives by June 1, 2026.</li><br/>
<li>Apple must make changes to iOS that allow for third parties to offer equivalent AirPlay alternatives by iOS 20, or the end of 2026. iOS 20 is expected to be released to the general public in September 2026.</ul>The entire list of changes can be found <a href="https://digital-markets-act.ec.europa.eu/questions-and-answers/interoperability_en">on the European Commission's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatibility</h2><br/>
According to a reliable source of iOS-related information, iOS 19 will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/31/ios-19-expected-to-run-on-these-iphones/">compatible with the iPhone 11 series and newer</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More</h2><br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19 roundup</a> for more details about the upcoming software update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/15/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features/">iOS 19 Will Add These New Features to Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-add-these-new-features-to-your-iphone.2455358/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
