<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:02:40 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>RCS Coming to Messages in iOS 18 for Improved Texts With Android Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18-for-improved-texts-with-android-users.2428700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:56:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>RCS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today confirmed that it plans to implement support for Rich Communication Services, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>, in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> this fall. Apple software chief Craig Federighi confirmed &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support when introducing new features for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at the WWDC keynote event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-rcs-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2776" height="1562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923042" /><br/>
We've known about Apple's plans to adopt &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; since last November, but Apple only gave a vague "later in 2024" timeline for adoption so it was unclear exactly when the feature might roll out. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; replaces SMS/MMS as the default communication protocol on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; has already been adopted by Google, U.S. smartphone carriers, and other companies, so Apple is a little late to the party. It doesn't change much for iMessage, but it does overhaul the way iPhones interact with Android devices. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; improves texting with Android users, adding support for features that have previously been limited to iMessage. Some of the additions: <br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Support for higher resolution photos and videos.</li><br/>
 <li>Support for larger file sizes and file sharing.</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages.</li><br/>
 <li>Cross-platform emoji reactions.</li><br/>
 <li>Real-time typing indicators.</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts.</li><br/>
 <li>Ability to send messages over cellular or Wi-Fi (SMS is cellular only). There is no cost to send an &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; message over Wi-Fi.</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
It is not clear if Apple will introduce &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support during the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta testing period or hold the feature until the fall public launch of the update, but we do know that it is indeed tied to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; at this point. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18/">RCS Coming to Messages in iOS 18 for Improved Texts With Android Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rcs-coming-to-messages-in-ios-18-for-improved-texts-with-android-users.2428700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Introduces Standalone &#039;Passwords&#039; App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app.2428694/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:45:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iCloud Keychain</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia feature a new, dedicated Passwords app for faster access to important credentials.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954590" /><br/>
The Passwords app replaces <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, which is currently only accessible via a menu in Settings. Now, passwords are available directly via a standalone app for markedly quicker access, bringing it more in line with rival services.<br/>
<br/>
The Passwords app consolidates various credentials, including passwords, passkeys, and Wi-Fi passwords, into a single, easily accessible location. Users can filter and sort their accounts based on various criteria, such as recently created accounts, credential type, or membership in shared groups. <br/>
<br/>
Passwords is also compatible with Windows via the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; for Windows app, extending its utility to users who operate across different platforms. <br/>
<br/>
The developer beta versions of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia are available today with official release to the public scheduled for the fall, providing an early look at the Passwords app.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-keychain/">iCloud Keychain</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app/">Apple Introduces Standalone &#039;Passwords&#039; App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-introduces-standalone-passwords-app.2428694/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2428693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:43:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new beta firmware for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, including both the Lightning and USB-C versions. The updated firmware has a build number of 7A5220e, and it is available to developers at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/AirPods-Pro-Beta-Firmware.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1081" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803705" /><br/>
At today's keynote event, Apple introduced several new features that are coming to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, including head gestures, and these features may be included in the firmware update.<br/>
<br/>
With head gestures, users can control <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with a shake or a nod of the head. If you get a phone call, for example, you can shake your head no if you don't want to answer it, or nod to accept the call. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interactions can be used for responding to incoming messages, calls, and notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is adding Voice Isolation to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to cut down on loud background sounds to make you easier to hear, and there is a new Personalized Spatial Audio feature specific to gaming. Game developers will be able to incorporate spatial audio into their games for a more immersive audio experience.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2428693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 11 Drops Support for These Apple Watch Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-11-drops-support-for-these-apple-watch-models.2428692/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:41:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatibility-rumor/">rumored</a>, watchOS 11 drops support for the Apple Watch Series 4, Apple Watch Series 5, and first-generation Apple Watch SE, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/watchos/watchos-preview/">Apple's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/09/apple-watch-series-4-flames.jpg" alt="" width="1130" height="634" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-655494" /><br/>
The update is compatible with all other models, including the Apple Watch Series 6 and beyond:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Apple Watch SE (2nd generation)<br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 6</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 7</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 8</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Series 9</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Ultra</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Ultra 2</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Even though the Series 5 has an S5 chip, it has the same processor as the S4 chip in the Series 4, so it is not too surprising that Apple dropped support for these models simultaneously. Key changes with the Series 5 compared to the Series 4 included an always-on display option, increased storage, and a compass.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 11 continues to work with a paired iPhone XS or newer. A developer beta is available starting today, and a public beta will follow in July.<br/>
<br/>
The general public can expect watchOS 11 to be released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/watchos-11-compatible-apple-watch-models/">watchOS 11 Drops Support for These Apple Watch Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-11-drops-support-for-these-apple-watch-models.2428692/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Features Coming to iOS 18 Beta Testers This Summer</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-ios-18-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-features-coming-to-ios-18-beta-testers-this-summer.2428691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:36:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-ios-18-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a>, Apple introduced an onslaught of <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence features</a> that integrate AI into everything from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> to built-in apps like Mail, Messages, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>. Apple Intelligence is still under development, and it won't immediately be available to developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954498" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Apple plans to debut Apple Intelligence in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia betas this summer. When Apple Intelligence officially launches to the public this fall, it will be available in a beta capacity. Some of the Apple Intelligence additions might take even longer to launch, with Apple suggesting that "some features, additional languages, and platforms" will be coming over the course of the next year.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple Intelligence, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is much smarter, and there are tools for generating custom emoji and images, refining your writing, summarizing content, cutting down on unimportant notifications, and way more. Apple is also partnering with OpenAI to bring ChatGPT 4o to its platforms, with ChatGPT set to be integrated into &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and Writing Tools. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to tap into ChatGPT for some tasks, asking user permission to share information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence is free to use, but it is limited to devices with the A17 Pro chip or any M-series chip. That means to use these features, you need an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, but the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup will support Apple Intelligence too.<br/>
<br/>
On the Mac side, you need a Mac with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or later, and for iPads, you need an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> with an &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip or later.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-ios-18-beta/">Apple Intelligence Features Coming to iOS 18 Beta Testers This Summer</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-features-coming-to-ios-18-beta-testers-this-summer.2428691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Betas of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and visionOS 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-18-ipados-18-macos-sequoia-tvos-18-watchos-11-and-visionos-2.2428680/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:16:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following today's WWDC keynote event that saw the unveiling of new software, Apple has provided the first betas of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2 to developers for testing purposes. Developers have access to the software so they can begin incorporating all of the new features into their apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-tile-summary.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954455" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app on their device, going to the Software Update Section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta, but Apple allows even free developer accounts to install beta software.<br/>
<br/>
It is a bad idea to install early betas on a main device, and we recommend having a secondary device if you want to try out the software. There are often significant bugs in early versions of iOS and macOS, so if you do install on a main device, make sure to create a backup beforehand.<br/>
<br/>
Over the course of the next several months, Apple will refine the features available in all of its new software, and we will go through several betas before the updates see a public release around September.<br/>
<br/>
While the betas are limited to developers right now, Apple typically provides a public beta in July, which is usually much more stable than the early developer betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-first-developer-betas-new-software/">Apple Releases First Betas of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and visionOS 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-18-ipados-18-macos-sequoia-tvos-18-watchos-11-and-visionos-2.2428680/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases visionOS 1.2 With Persona, Eyesight and Virtual Keyboard Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-2-with-persona-eyesight-and-virtual-keyboard-improvements.2428678/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:10:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.2, the second major update to the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; operating system that launched alongside the Vision Pro in February. &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2 comes three months after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-visionos-1-1/">the launch of visionOS 1.1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929937" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Orange-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;‌ updates can be installed by going to the Settings app on the Vision Pro, selecting the General section, and choosing Software Update. The Vision Pro headset will need to be removed to install new software, with a progress bar available on the front EyeSight display.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2 adds Persona improvements such as improved hair and makeup appearance, as well as better rendering for Eyesight. Messages supports Contact Key Verification, and Apple made improvements to both the Virtual Keyboard and the Mac Virtual Display. Apple's full release notes are below.<br/>
<blockquote><strong>Mobile Device Management</strong><br/>
- Enables account-driven device and user enrollment using Managed Apple IDs<br/>
- Support for device configuration (Wi-Fi, VPN, email accounts, single sign-on, and more)<br/>
- Support for deploying apps in volume including iPhone and iPad compatible apps, visionOS apps included in a Universal purchase, and proprietary in-house visionOS apps<br/>
- Support for remote erase via MDM and device inventory data<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Messages</strong><br/>
- Adds support for iMessage Contact Key Verification<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>
- Closed captions can be anchored to the playback control while viewing Apple Immersive Video<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Persona (beta) and EyeSight</strong><br/>
- Adds an option to enroll your Persona hands-free<br/>
- Improves hair and makeup appearance<br/>
- Improves neck and mouth representation<br/>
- Improves rendering of the eyes for EyeSight<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Virtual keyboard</strong><br/>
- Cursor positioning for text input is now more accurate<br/>
- Resolves some instances where the virtual keyboard placement obscures the text input field<br/>
- Fixes an issue where in some cases, the text preview on the virtual keyboard may appear out of sync with the text field in the app<br/>
- Fixes an issue where the edit menu may appear unexpectedly<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Mac Virtual Display</strong><br/>
- Improves the reliability of discovering and connecting to a Mac using Mac Virtual Display<br/>
- Resolves an issue where Universal Control may stop working<br/>
- Addresses a connectivity issue that occurs when a previously paired Bluetooth device cannot be found<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Captive Network Support</strong><br/>
- Ability to set up your device while using a captive WiFi network such as those found at hotels, cafes and airports<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website:<br/>
https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>The first year of the Vision Pro will see plenty of feature refinements, and Apple has already announced &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 2 with even more new additions.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-visionos-1-2/">Apple Releases visionOS 1.2 With Persona, Eyesight and Virtual Keyboard Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-1-2-with-persona-eyesight-and-virtual-keyboard-improvements.2428678/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Recaps 18 Key Announcements From WWDC 2024 Keynote in Short Video</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-wwdc-2024-recap-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-recaps-18-key-announcements-from-wwdc-2024-keynote-in-short-video.2428675/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:03:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-wwdc-2024-recap-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple promised that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/wwdc-2024-live-coverage/">WWDC 2024 keynote</a> would be action-packed, and it absolutely was. With new updates like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-ios-18-with-new-customization-features-and-more/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, along with a whole new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence suite of AI features</a>, there were a ton of announcements.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LtIWE4CCX5M?si=osB0dzjF9CXloPjM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
To help out, Apple has shared the nearly three-minute video above highlighting 18 key things that it unveiled during the keynote.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, we'll have our own in-depth coverage of Apple's announcements here at <em>MacRumors</em>, so be sure to follow along to learn more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-wwdc-2024-recap-video/">Apple Recaps 18 Key Announcements From WWDC 2024 Keynote in Short Video</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-recaps-18-key-announcements-from-wwdc-2024-keynote-in-short-video.2428675/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and More Available in Public Beta in July</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-macos-sequoia-and-more-available-in-public-beta-in-july.2428671/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:52:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that public betas of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, and HomePod software version 18 will be available in July.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
Apple did not provide a specific release date for the public betas, nor did it say that visionOS 2 will be available as a public beta.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Developer Program members can test all of the new updates starting today, including visionOS 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/">iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and More Available in Public Beta in July</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-macos-sequoia-and-more-available-in-public-beta-in-july.2428671/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Siri Can Access ChatGPT Directly With iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-can-access-chatgpt-directly-with-ios-18.2428665/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:42:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/introducing-apple-intelligence-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">announced</a> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> will be able to access ChatGPT directly in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia to provide better responses in relevant situations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/chatgpt-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954523" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will determine if queries may be useful to forward to ChatGPT, and asks the user for permission to share. This enables &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to leverage ChatGPT's image- and text-understanding capabilities with no need to jump between tools. Users can ask questions related to text, documents, photos, PDFs, and more. <br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT will also be available in Apple's new systemwide Writing Tools to help users generate content for anything they're writing about. With Compose, users can similarly access ChatGPT image tools to generate images in a range of styles to compliment their writing.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will leverage GPT-4o for free, with no need to create an account. Requests are not logged and IP addresses are obscured. ChatGPT subscribers will also be able to access paid features within the experiences.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/siri-can-access-chatgpt-with-ios-18/">Siri Can Access ChatGPT Directly With iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-can-access-chatgpt-directly-with-ios-18.2428665/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Unveils &#039;Image Playground&#039; On-Device AI Image Generator</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-unveils-image-playground-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-image-playground-on-device-ai-image-generator.2428662/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:38:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-unveils-image-playground-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of Apple Intelligence, Apple has unveiled a new Image Playground feature that allows you to create generative images on the fly using a range of concepts like themes, costumes, accessories, places, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-Apple-Intelligence-Image-Playground-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954533" /><br/>
You can type a description, and choose from Animation, Illustration, or Sketch, and Image Playground will create the image tailored to your preferences. Previews are created on-device, and your generative images are accessible in Messages, Pages, Freeform, and even a dedicated Image Playground app.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2024/">WWDC 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-unveils-image-playground-ai/">Apple Unveils &#039;Image Playground&#039; On-Device AI Image Generator</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-image-playground-on-device-ai-image-generator.2428662/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18&#039;s New &#039;Genmoji&#039; Feature Lets You Create Your Own Emoji</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-genmoji/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-new-genmoji-feature-lets-you-create-your-own-emoji.2428660/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:36:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-genmoji/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		<category>Genmoji</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of the new Apple Intelligence features coming to the iPhone with iOS 18 is Genmoji, which allows you to instantly create your own custom emoji.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Genmoji-iOS-18.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954516" /><br/>
The emoji can be created with text prompts like "t-rex wearing a tutu on a surfboard."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Genmoji-iOS-18-Two.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954517" /><br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">full coverage of Apple Intelligence</a> to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
Genmoji will be able to be used in the Messages app.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-genmoji/">iOS 18&#039;s New &#039;Genmoji&#039; Feature Lets You Create Your Own Emoji</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-new-genmoji-feature-lets-you-create-your-own-emoji.2428660/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iMessage on iOS 18: Bold, Underline, Italics, Emoji Tapbacks, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-imessage-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imessage-on-ios-18-bold-underline-italics-emoji-tapbacks-and-more.2428656/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:17:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-imessage-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today previewed iOS 18 with several new features for the Messages app, including text effects, emoji tapbacks, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-1.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954499" /><br/>
iMessage is finally getting bold, italics, underline, and strikeout options, along with all-new text effects that allow you to animate individual words in a message.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954501" /><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-3.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954500" /><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-iOS-18-4.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954505" /><br/>
Apple has redesigned the Tapback icons like the heart, thumbs up, thumbs down, and exclamation marks to be more colorful on iOS 18, and the Tapback system now works with any emoji too.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-imessage-features/">iMessage on iOS 18: Bold, Underline, Italics, Emoji Tapbacks, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imessage-on-ios-18-bold-underline-italics-emoji-tapbacks-and-more.2428656/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Apple Intelligence&#039; Personal AI Unveiled for iPhone, iPad, and Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac.2428655/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:13:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>WWDC 2024</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple at WWDC today announced Apple Intelligence, a deeply integrated, personalized AI experience for Apple devices that uses cutting-edge generative artificial intelligence to enhance user experiences across <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-Apple-Intelligence-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954530" /><br/>
Apple says that Apple Intelligence "combines the power of generative models with personal context to deliver intelligence that's incredibly useful and relevant." Baked into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, it can create language and images, take action across apps, and draw from personal context to simplify and accelerate everyday tasks. And with Private Cloud Compute, Apple is focused on delivering AI based on privacy, with the ability to flex and scale computational capacity between on-device processing and larger, server-based models that run on dedicated Apple silicon servers.<br/>
<blockquote>"We're thrilled to introduce a new chapter in Apple innovation. Apple Intelligence will transform what users can do with our products — and what our products can do for our users," said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. "Our unique approach combines generative AI with a user's personal context to deliver truly helpful intelligence. And it can access that information in a completely private and secure way to help users do the things that matter most to them. This is AI as only Apple can deliver it, and we can't wait for users to experience what it can do."</blockquote>Top of the features list are new ways for users to enhance their writing and communicate more effectively. Apple says that with brand-new systemwide Writing Tools built into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, users can rewrite, proofread, and summarize text nearly everywhere they write, including Mail, Notes, Pages, and third-party apps.<br/>
<br/>
For example, with Rewrite, Apple Intelligence allows users to choose from different versions of what they have written, and then adjust the tone "to suit the audience and task at hand." According to Apple, the Rewrite feature helps users deliver the right words to meet the occasion, whether that's finessing a cover letter, or adding humor and creativity to a party invitation. A new Proofread option checks grammar, word choice, and sentence structure while also suggesting edits — along with explanations of the edits — that users can review or quickly accept. And with Summarize, users can select text and have it recapped in the form of a digestible paragraph, bulleted key points, a table, or a list.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-Apple-Intelligence-Writing-Tools-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954542" /><br/>
In Mail, a new section at the top of the inbox called Priority Messages shows your most urgent emails, like a same-day dinner invitation or boarding pass. But instead of previewing the first few lines of each email, you can see summaries without needing to open a message. Meanwhile, for long threads, you can view pertinent details with a tap. There's also a Smart Reply feature that offers suggestions for a quick response. The feature also identifiwa questions in an email to ensure everything is answered, according to Apple. <br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, a new Priority Notifications feature surfaces alerts at the top of the stack to show what's most important to you, and summaries help you scan long or stacked notifications to show key details right on the Lock Screen, such as when a group chat is particularly active. To help users stay present in what they are doing, there's also a new Focus called Reduce Interruptions that surfaces only the notifications that might need immediate attention, like a text about an early pickup from daycare.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/notification-summaries.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954554" /><br/>
In the Notes and Phone apps, Apple Intelligence allows users to record, transcribe, and summarize audio. When a recording is initiated while on a call, participants are automatically notified, and once the call ends, Apple Intelligence generates a summary to help recall key points. A new Image Playground feature also allows users to choose from a range of concepts from categories like themes, costumes, accessories, and places to create their own images for sharing in Messages, Notes, Keynote, Freeform, and Pages, and third-party apps that support the new Image Playground API.<br/>
<br/>
Taking emoji to new places, users can also create an original Genmoji to express themselves. By simply typing a description, their Genmoji appears, along with additional options. Users can also create Genmoji of friends and family based on their photos. Just like emoji, Genmoji can be added inline to messages, or shared as a sticker or reaction in a Tapback.<br/>
<br/>
Switching to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, natural language can be used to search for specific photos, such as "Maya skateboarding in a tie-dye shirt," or "Katie with stickers on her face." Search in videos also becomes more powerful with the ability to find specific moments in clips so users can go right to the relevant segment. Additionally, the new Clean Up tool can identify and remove distracting objects in the background of a photo, without accidentally altering the subject, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-Apple-Intelligence-Memory-movie-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954563" /><blockquote>With Memories, users can create the story they want to see by simply typing a description. Using language and image understanding, Apple Intelligence will pick out the best photos and videos based on the description, craft a storyline with chapters based on themes identified from the photos, and arrange them into a movie with its own narrative arc. Users will even get song suggestions to match their memory from Apple Music. As with all Apple Intelligence features, user photos and videos are kept private on device and are not shared with Apple or anyone else.</blockquote>Apple is also emphasizing cross-platform enhancements to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, which is said to be "more natural, more contextually relevant, and more personal, with the ability to simplify and accelerate everyday tasks." For example, it can follow along if users stumble over words and maintain context from one request to the next. Additionally, users can type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, and switch between text and voice to communicate with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; however they like. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; also has a brand-new design, suggestive of its new capabilities, with a glowing light that wraps around the edge of the screen when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is active.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can answer queries about how to do something on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and Mac, and with onscreen awareness, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to understand and take action with users' content in more apps over time, according to Apple. For example, if a friend texts a user their new address in Messages, the receiver can say, "Add this address to his contact card," and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will do just that. Similar actions will extend across Apple and third-party apps.<br/>
<blockquote>Siri will be able to deliver intelligence that’s tailored to the user and their on-device information. For example, a user can say, “Play that podcast that Jamie recommended,” and Siri will locate and play the episode, without the user having to remember whether it was mentioned in a text or an email. Or they could ask, “When is Mom’s flight landing?” and Siri will find the flight details and cross-reference them with real-time flight tracking to give an arrival time.</blockquote>Thanks to on-device processing, Apple says its AI features are aware of your personal data without collecting your data. And when it needs more compute capacity, it sends only the data needed to fulfill the request to Apple's Private Cloud Compute servers, which share the same privacy and security capabilities of your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, according to Apple. <br/>
<br/>
To verify privacy, Apple says that independent experts can inspect the code that runs on Apple silicon servers, and Private Cloud Compute cryptographically ensures that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and Mac do not talk to a server unless its software has been publicly logged for inspection. "Apple Intelligence with Private Cloud Compute sets a new standard for privacy in AI, unlocking intelligence users can trust," says Apple. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is integrating ChatGPT access into experiences within &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, allowing users to access its expertise — as well as its image- and document-understanding capabilities — without needing to jump between tools. Apple says users are asked before any questions are sent to ChatGPT, along with any documents or photos, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; then presents the answer directly.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-Apple-Intelligence-ChatGPT-Writing-Tools-Compose-prompt-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954569" /><br/>
Additionally, ChatGPT will be available in Apple's systemwide Writing Tools to help users generate content for anything they are writing about. For example, with Compose, users will also be able to access ChatGPT image tools to generate images in a variety of styles to complement what they are writing.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that ChatGPT will come to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia later this year, powered by GPT-4o. Users can access it for free without creating an account, and ChatGPT subscribers can connect their accounts and access paid features right from these experiences.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2024/">WWDC 2024</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">&#039;Apple Intelligence&#039; Personal AI Unveiled for iPhone, iPad, and Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac.2428655/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 18 Adds &#039;InSight&#039; to Identify Actors and Songs in Apple TV+ Shows, Plus &#039;Enhanced Dialogue&#039; Feature and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-gaining-insight-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-adds-insight-to-identify-actors-and-songs-in-apple-tv-shows-plus-enhanced-dialogue-feature-and-more.2428652/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:56:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-gaining-insight-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/updates-to-the-home-experience-elevate-entertainment-and-bring-more-convenience/">announced</a> that tvOS 18 is gaining a feature called "InSight," which helps you find more information about all of the actors and songs in the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> show or movie you're watching. InSight will only be available on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; content.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/f-c0756092e0ae6fd8d8add09562de18179d8bd899.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954478" /><br/>
Apple said that InSight is connected to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> account. This way, if you hear a song you like in an &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; show, you can use InSight to find out what it is, and immediately add it to your &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; library.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, tvOS 18 is getting a smarter "Enhance Dialogue" feature for TV speakers and receivers, AirPods, and other Bluetooth devices. This feature uses machine learning to give greater vocal clarity to voices in shows and movies.<br/>
<br/>
A few other new tvOS additions include:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Subtitles will automatically appear if you mute the volume or go back a few seconds</li><br/>
<li>Adding support for the 21:9 format for projectors on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></li><br/>
<li>Redesigned Apple Fitness+ experience</li><br/>
<li>New Portraits category for screen savers</li><br/>
<li>New TV+ shows and movies category for screen savers</li><br/>
<li>New Snoopy screen saver</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
These new features will be coming to tvOS 18 later in 2024.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2024/">WWDC 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/tvos-gaining-insight-feature/">tvOS 18 Adds &#039;InSight&#039; to Identify Actors and Songs in Apple TV+ Shows, Plus &#039;Enhanced Dialogue&#039; Feature and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-adds-insight-to-identify-actors-and-songs-in-apple-tv-shows-plus-enhanced-dialogue-feature-and-more.2428652/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Unveils macOS 15 Sequoia With iPhone Mirroring, Passwords App, More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-macos-15-sequoia-with-iphone-mirroring-passwords-app-more.2428651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:56:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		<category>WWDC 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple at WWDC today announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a> Sequoia, featuring several of the new capabilities introduced in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> in addition to a new Continuity feature called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/sequoia.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954485" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring allows you to view and control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac. Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be mirrored to your Mac, showing everything, including icons, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a>, apps, and more. Any app can be opened direct from the Mac, and your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s audio even comes through to Mac. All the while, your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can stay locked, so nobody else can access it. You can even drag and drop items and files from your Mac to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; seamlessly.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj; also brings &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications to Mac, where they appear alongside Mac notifications. In addition, macOS now automatically sizes windows to tile them and fill up the screen, utilizing maximum screen real estate. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj; also includes a new dedicated Passwords app, allowing you to manage Wi-Fi passwords, app and website passwords, verification codes, and more. Passwords sync across devices, and macOS uses autofill to populate passwords in the Passwords app. The Passwords app is also available on Windows, thanks to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> for Windows app. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2024/">WWDC 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-announces-macos-sequoia/">Apple Unveils macOS 15 Sequoia With iPhone Mirroring, Passwords App, More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-macos-15-sequoia-with-iphone-mirroring-passwords-app-more.2428651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Unveils Calculator App for iPad With Math Notes, Apple Pencil Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-calculator-ipad-apple-pencil/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-calculator-app-for-ipad-with-math-notes-apple-pencil-support.2428646/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:52:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-calculator-ipad-apple-pencil/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple at WWDC today announced a new Calculator app as part of iPadOS 18 that features special <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> support and a new Math Notes feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/calculator-app-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954479" /><br/>
Apple says the Math Notes calculator allows users to type or write out mathematical expressions and see them instantly solved in their own handwriting. It's also possible to assign values to variables when learning new concepts in class, calculating a budget, and more. <br/>
<br/>
With a new graphing feature, users can write or type an equation and insert a graph with just one tap, and can even add multiple equations on the same graph to see how they relate, according to Apple. Math Notes are also automatically accessible in the Notes app in a new Math Notes folder.<br/>
<br/>
Basic and scientific calculators are included in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> app that are designed to make it easy to view complete expressions before completing them. Meanwhile, a History feature helps users keep track of previous calculations, and unit conversions let users quickly convert length, weight, currencies, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ipados-18-math-notes.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954476" /><br/>
The first developer beta of iPadOS 18 is available starting today, with a public beta following in July, and official release to the public in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2024/">WWDC 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-calculator-ipad-apple-pencil/">Apple Unveils Calculator App for iPad With Math Notes, Apple Pencil Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-calculator-app-for-ipad-with-math-notes-apple-pencil-support.2428646/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Unveils iPadOS 18 With New Calculator App, Tab Bar, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-unveils-ipados-18-with-new-calculator-app-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-ipados-18-with-new-calculator-app-tab-bar-and-more.2428645/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:50:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-unveils-ipados-18-with-new-calculator-app-and-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/ipados-18-introduces-powerful-intelligence-features-and-apps-for-apple-pencil/">today previewed</a> iPadOS 18, a major update to the operating system for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> that introduces a new Calendar app, a redesigned systemwide tab bar, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ipados-18-math-notes.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954476" /><br/>
iPadOS 18 brings over many of the new features and improvements introduced in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; such as the redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app and new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> customization tools.<br/>
<br/>
In iPadOS 18, a new floating tab bar morphs into the navigation sidebar. The tab bar is also customizable to keep favourites within easy reach. It is available across the system. There is also a new document browser in Pages, Numbers, and Keynote.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 18 also brings the Calculator app to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; for the first time, with new features like history and unit conversions. Math notes allows users to solve expressions when writing with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Math notes enable users to hand-write expressions and automatically calculate the answer, displaying it in handwriting that's like their own. Users can use basic or scientific math, and notes can be saved for later. Variables are supported, allowing you to solve algebraic equations. They can be edited to see results change in real time, and even generate a graph.<br/>
<br/>
Notes has the same math capabilities from Calculator. Notes also gains new Smart Script capabilities that automatically improve your handwriting as you write.<br/>
<br/>
SharePlay now allows users to tap and draw on the screen when sharing, and you can remotely control someone else's &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 18 also includes refined animations across the UI, making them feel even more responsive. There are new APIs for developers to integrate these animations.<br/>
<br/>
The first developer beta of iPadOS 18 is available starting today, with a public beta following in July, and official release to the public in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-unveils-ipados-18-with-new-calculator-app-and-more/">Apple Unveils iPadOS 18 With New Calculator App, Tab Bar, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-ipados-18-with-new-calculator-app-tab-bar-and-more.2428645/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Previews watchOS 11 With New Health and Workout Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-previews-watchos-11-with-new-health-and-workout-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-previews-watchos-11-with-new-health-and-workout-features.2428643/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:43:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-previews-watchos-11-with-new-health-and-workout-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/watchos-11-brings-powerful-health-and-fitness-insights/">today previewed</a> watchOS 11, the next major software update for the Apple Watch that introduces several new health and workout features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-training-load.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954466" /><br/>
Activity Rings can now be adjusted by day of the week and paused for a rest day, allowing users to keep their award streak going. Users can set workouts to alert a friend that they have been safely completed, such as a late-night run.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 11 includes a new "training load" feature, helping users to track intensity over time. A new algorithm uses heart rate, altitude, workout duration, and age and weight data to give a calculation of your estimated effort rating and training load.<br/>
<br/>
A new Vitals app provides an overview of daily health, comparing daily health statistics to historical data and highlighting when health data is outside your typical range. If multiple metrics are out of range, you will receive a tailored message to see how they could be affecting you.<br/>
<br/>
Cycle tracking now shows estimates of gestational age, showing pregnancy across charts to review metrics like high heart rate notification thresholds.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a> will be automatically added to the Smart Stack. For example, the Translate app will show automatically when you go to a different country and the Weather app will show up when rain is imminent. watchOS 11 also brings Live Activities to the Apple Watch for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
An improved <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face gives users more control and uses machine learning to automatically crop photos. The update also brings the Translate app to the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
The first developer beta of watchOS 11 is available starting today, with a public beta following in July, and official release to the public in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-previews-watchos-11-with-new-health-and-workout-features/">Apple Previews watchOS 11 With New Health and Workout Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-previews-watchos-11-with-new-health-and-workout-features.2428643/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: New Control Center Features Multiple Customizable Screens</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-ios-18-control-center-multiple-screens/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-new-control-center-features-multiple-customizable-screens.2428642/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:42:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-ios-18-control-center-multiple-screens/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple at WWDC has announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, which includes an overhauled Control Center interface with new customization features and the ability to add multiple control screens.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-control-center.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954582" /><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, Control Center has been redesigned to provide easier access to many of the things users do every day, and it gets new levels of customization and flexibility. <br/>
<br/>
The redesign delivers quick access to new groups of a user's most-utilized controls, such as media playback, Home controls, and connectivity, as well as the ability to easily swipe between each.<br/>
<br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, when you invoke Control Center with a swipe down from the top-right of your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s screen, you can continuously swipe to get to more control center screens. There's a new controls gallery that lets you customize the controls you see, and you can change the size of buttons to emphasize priority. Additionally, developers can include controls from their own apps, enabling quick access to controls like remotely starting a car, for example.<br/>
<br/>
The new Controls API from Apple also allows you to switch up the controls on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s lock screen, so you can replace the traditional flashlight and camera buttons with something more convenient to you. And if you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, you can also assign Control Center buttons to the physical Action button.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wwdc-2024/">WWDC 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-ios-18-control-center-multiple-screens/">iOS 18: New Control Center Features Multiple Customizable Screens</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-new-control-center-features-multiple-customizable-screens.2428642/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
