<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 05:04:39 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch AFib History Feature Qualified by FDA to Evaluate Medical Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-watch-afib-history-evaluate-medical-devices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-afib-history-feature-qualified-by-fda-to-evaluate-medical-devices.2425302/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 04:27:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-watch-afib-history-evaluate-medical-devices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>FDA</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's atrial fibrillation (AFib) history feature on Apple Watch has been <a href="https://content.govdelivery.com/accounts/USFDA/bulletins/399d551">qualified</a> by the FDA under its Medical Device Development Tools (MDDT) program, the first digital health technology feature of its kind to do so.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/watchos-9-afib-history.jpg" alt="" width="2676" height="1502" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849842" /><br/>
Since 2022, Apple Watch has supported AFib History, which allows users diagnosed with atrial fibrillation to view an estimate of how frequently their heart is in this type of irregular rhythm. <br/>
<br/>
The feature analyzes pulse rate data collected by a photoplethysmography (PPG) sensor to identify episodes consistent with AFib and provides the user with a retrospective estimate of AFib burden (a measure of the amount of time spent in AFib during past Apple Watch wear). Apple says the feature is intended for individuals aged 22 years or older who have been diagnosed with atrial fibrillation.<br/>
<br/>
The AFib History feature received FDA clearance in the United States just prior to its announcement by Apple, after being validated in a clinical study. The MDDT program under which the feature was <a href="https://www.fda.gov/media/178230/download?attachment">approved</a> today is the FDA's method of qualifying tools that medical device sponsors can choose to use in the development and evaluation of medical devices.  <br/>
<br/>
According to the FDA, the Atrial Fibrillation History feature is:<br/>
<ul><li>The first digital health technology qualified under the MDDT program, providing a non-invasive way to check estimates of atrial fibrillation (AFib) burden within clinical studies.</li><br/>
<li>Designed to be used as a biomarker test to help evaluate estimates of AFib burden as a secondary effectiveness endpoint within clinical studies intended to evaluate the safety and effectiveness of cardiac ablation devices to treat.</li><br/>
<li>Designed to be used throughout the clinical study, both before and after cardiac ablation devices, to monitor a study participant’s weekly estimate of AFib burden.</li></ul><em>(Via <a href="https://www.myhealthyapple.com/fda-qualifies-afib-history-mddt/">MyHealthyApple.com</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fda/">FDA</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-watch-afib-history-evaluate-medical-devices/">Apple Watch AFib History Feature Qualified by FDA to Evaluate Medical Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-afib-history-feature-qualified-by-fda-to-evaluate-medical-devices.2425302/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Paid Apple &#36;20 Billion in 2022 to Be Default Safari Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/google-default-search-engine-safari-20-billion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-paid-apple-20-billion-in-2022-to-be-default-safari-search-engine.2425289/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:57:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/google-default-search-engine-safari-20-billion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google paid Apple &#36;20 billion in 2022 to be the default search engine for Safari on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-01/google-s-payments-to-apple-reached-20-billion-in-2022-cue-says">Bloomberg</a></em>. The information was revealed in court documents Google provided in its antitrust dispute with the United States Department of Justice.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916340" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/safari-google-search.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" /><br/>
The DoJ has accused Google of having a monopoly on search, and in the lawsuit against Google, the search engine deal with Apple has been a major focus. In November, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-google-safari-search-revenue/">lawsuit documents indicated</a> that Google was paying 36 percent of the total revenue that it earns from searches conducted on Safari, and now it turns out that equates to &#36;20 billion.<br/>
<br/>
Google has been the default search engine on Apple devices since 2002, though the deal has been renegotiated several times. Apple and Google have worked to keep the terms of the search engine agreement under wraps during the trial and before, but it has been well known that Google is paying Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/google-pays-apple-billions-default-search/">billions per year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Last October, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella testified that the agreement between Apple and Google has made it impossible for search engines like Bing to compete. Microsoft at one point wanted Apple to buy Bing, but Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/microsoft-bing-acquisition-talks/">was not interested</a>. Microsoft blamed Google, but Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a> said that Aplple was concerned that Bing could not compete in "quality and capabilities." Cue claimed that Apple uses Google as the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s default search engine because Apple has "always thought it was the best."<br/>
<br/>
Google is the default search engine on Apple devices in most countries, but users can opt to swap to Yahoo, Bing, DuckDuckGo, and Ecosia as alternatives. Changing browser engines requires opening up the Safari settings.<br/>
<br/>
In Europe, the Digital Markets Act has required Apple to make changes to how browsers work. Users are able to choose a default browser when setting up their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and there are more options than the handful of providers that Apple allows in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
If Google loses the antitrust lawsuit against it, the deal between Apple and Google could be dissolved. Closing arguments are expected on Thursday and Friday, with the judge's ruling set to come later in 2024.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/google-default-search-engine-safari-20-billion/">Google Paid Apple &#36;20 Billion in 2022 to Be Default Safari Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-paid-apple-20-billion-in-2022-to-be-default-safari-search-engine.2425289/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Check Out This Apple Watch iPad Demo Unit From 2014</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/apple-watch-ipad-demo-unit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-this-apple-watch-ipad-demo-unit-from-2014.2425283/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:46:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/apple-watch-ipad-demo-unit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch approaching, we thought it would be fun to take a look back at an interesting bit of Apple Watch history.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ipad-demo-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1337" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948938" /><br/>
After the Apple Watch was announced in 2014, and before it became available in 2015, Apple sent out custom Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> demo kiosks to retail stores. The Apple Watch and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; units used for these devices were specially designed, had custom software, and represent the first and only time that an Apple Watch was able to pair with an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://twitter.com/AppleDemoYT">AppleDemoYT</a>, known for sourcing rare prototypes, shared images and detailed information about the demo units with <em>MacRumors</em>, offering up detailed insight on the lengths Apple went to for this custom experience. AppleDemoYT was able to acquire one of these now-rare demo units.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ipad-demo-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948939" /><br/>
Jony Ive and his design team came up with the Apple Watch &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; Kiosks as a way for customers to try out an Apple Watch without needing help from an employee. Apple used a modified <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> 2 running iOS 8.2 paired with an original Apple Watch running watchOS 1.0, with the two devices fused in a custom housing.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; Apple used had multiple components removed, including the camera, microphone, and speakers, and the housing of the setup served as the body of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. The Apple Watch was heavily modified as well, featuring a groove along the diagnostic port for cable routing, holes to affix it to the demo unit, and a special Sport Band that was shorter than normal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ipad-demo-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948940" /><br/>
The Apple Watch was paired to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; using a wired connection. A lightning cable attached to the Apple Watch diagnostic port connected to a converter board inside the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, allowing the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to communicate with and charge the Apple Watch. A special app called Apple Watch Demo was used to allow the Apple Watch to interface with the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and a connection to Apple's server was required.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ipad-demo-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948941" /><br/>
The server that Apple used for the Apple Watch Demo app has long since gone offline, so the only way to see how the setup worked is through a demo unit that was paired in 2014 and not reset since then. With a functional unit, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is able to mirror the Apple Watch, offering up transition animations and providing tips on the actions that can be performed on the Apple Watch. This functionality is demoed in AppleDemoYT's video:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Watch Demo (2014) - Interactive Demonstration - The Forgotten Apple Device - Apple Demo" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9vidGNxCuIA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The custom &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; was not only the sole model able to connect with an Apple Watch, it was also the only &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; that could be charged using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> 2, originally designed for the Mac. A &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; connector charged the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Apple Watch, and extra batteries inside the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. A Lightning port is available as well, but Apple's documentation suggests that it is only meant to be used for data transfer.<br/>
<br/>
Apple discontinued the demo unit in 2016 because it was riddled with issues. Updates to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or Apple Watch would erase demo content, and the front glass was prone to cracking because of the design of the housing. Batteries degraded quickly due to the always-on charging, and overheating and failure were continual problems. Apple also had to deal with pairing and syncing issues, and that caused Apple to tweak the interactive part of the demo functionality in 2015. After that change, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; provided Apple Watch info, but no longer mirrored the content on the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ipad-demo-5.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948942" /><br/>
Demo units that were decommissioned were supposed to be destroyed, and so finding one that is still available, functional, and in good working condition is unusual. The Apple Watch &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; kiosk represents one of the most advanced custom devices that Apple had designed at the time, and it offers a neat look back at the Apple Watch's debut.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple has plans for the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch, and as soon as this year, we may see a redesigned "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>" with an updated magnetic band attachment system, new health features, and more.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/apple-watch-ipad-demo-unit/">Check Out This Apple Watch iPad Demo Unit From 2014</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-this-apple-watch-ipad-demo-unit-from-2014.2425283/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumor: Calendar App to Feature Integration With Reminders App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/ios-18-calendar-reminders-integration-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-calendar-app-to-feature-integration-with-reminders-app.2425275/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:39:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/ios-18-calendar-reminders-integration-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>AppleInsider</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with iOS 18, the Calendar app on the iPhone will feature integration with the Reminders app, according to information obtained <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/05/01/apples-ios-18-to-streamline-task-management-with-unified-events-and-reminders">by <em>AppleInsider</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Calendar-and-Reminders-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948925" /><br/>
The report claims that iPhone users will be able to schedule and organize reminders directly within the Calendars app, without needing to open the Reminders app. Reminders are expected to be visible within the Day, Week, and Month calendar views.<br/>
<br/>
The change will extend to the Mac with macOS 15, the report says.<br/>
<br/>
The same publication recently reported that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">Calculator and Notes app will also be integrated</a> on iOS 18, and said that the update will include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/safari-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">new Safari features such as "Intelligent Search" and "Web Eraser."</a> We recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/">recapped iOS 18 rumors on a per-app basis</a>, with new features also expected for Apple Music, Messages, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce iOS 18, macOS 15, and other software updates during its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>. The first betas of iOS 18 and macOS 15 will likely be made available to members of Apple's Developer Program immediately following the keynote, and the updates should be widely released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/appleinsider-com/">AppleInsider</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/ios-18-calendar-reminders-integration-rumor/">iOS 18 Rumor: Calendar App to Feature Integration With Reminders App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-calendar-app-to-feature-integration-with-reminders-app.2425275/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will the New iPad Pro Really Have the M4 Chip?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-the-m4-chip.2425260/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 08:30:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models have been expected to feature the M3 chip for over a year, recent reports have unexpectedly suggested that the new devices will instead feature the as-yet-unannounced M4 chip. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oUBArI37GvI" title="New iPad Pro with M4 LEAKED! AI-Focused iPad Coming Next Week?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Last week, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that he now believes there is a "strong possibility" that the upcoming &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/">equipped with Apple's next-generation M4 chip</a>, rather than the M3 chip that debuted in the MacBook Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> six months ago. He said a key new feature of the M4 chip will be an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">upgraded Neural Engine</a> that boosts performance for AI tasks, and he believes Apple will market the next &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; as an AI-powered device.<br/>
<br/>
Introducing the M4 chip in an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and only six months after the previous chip generation would be unprecedented moves. Yet this is not the first time that the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models have been rumored to feature the M4 chip. In March, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/chip-details-of-16-upcoming-apple-devices-revealed/">chip details of 16 new Apple devices</a> were revealed by a source with a proven track record of sharing accurate information about Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
The disclosed technical information contained four identifiers for an unreleased chip that relates to the upcoming 11- and 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models display sizes. This sequence of identifiers suggested that the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will contain the M4 chip, rather than the M3. With Gurman now supporting this possibility and the potential of an AI focus, it seems like an increasingly likely eventuality.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple does introduce the M4 chip in the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, its Apple silicon roadmap would appear to be moving faster than expected. It is possible that TSMC's N3E production volume remains low, making it more suitable for a device like the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; rather than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or Mac at this point in time. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models at its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">"Let Loose" event on May 7</a>. Do you think the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will contain the M4 chip and why? Let us know what you think in the comments.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/">Will the New iPad Pro Really Have the M4 Chip?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-the-m4-chip.2425260/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors 2024 Blood Drive</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/macrumors-2024-blood-drive/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-2024-blood-drive.2425257/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 08:15:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/macrumors-2024-blood-drive/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Doctor Q</dc:creator>
		<category>MacRumors Blood Drive</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[MacRumors is pleased to announce our <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2425233/">Fifteenth Annual MacRumors Blood Drive</a>, throughout the month of May 2024. Let's save lives together by encouraging donations of blood, platelets, and plasma. While most blood drives are specific to a geographic location, our blood drive is online and worldwide. Anyone can participate.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/blood_drive_2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="672" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948801" /><br/>
Over the past 14 years, MacRumors Blood Drives have recorded donations of <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/posts/32205640/">1,305 units of blood, platelets, and plasma</a>, cheered for donors, and celebrated new signups for the organ donor and bone marrow registries. We've heard from hundreds of forum members who donate or whose lives were saved by the donations of strangers.<br/>
<br/>
This year's featured donor is user Neil.gtis, a three-year forum member from England. Neil is a regular donor who has made 98 blood donations to date, and will reach his 100th donation this year. Whether you're a regular donor like Neil.gtis or someone overcoming apprehension to donate for the very first time, we congratulate you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/featured_donor_2024.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="701" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948802" /><br/>
<h3>How to participate in the MacRumors Blood Drive</h3><br/>
<ol><li>If you are an eligible donor (e.g., <a href="https://www.redcrossblood.org/donate-blood/how-to-donate/eligibility-requirements.html">U.S. eligibility rules</a>), schedule a blood, platelet, or plasma donation (<a href="https://macrumors.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/201729417-Blood-and-Platelet-Donation-">FAQ</a>) at any donation center near you. Post in the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2425233/">MacRumors 2024 Blood Drive!</a> thread to tell us about it. Also post if you register as an organ donor or register for the bone marrow registry (<a href="https://macrumors.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/201771053-Organ-Tissue-and-Bone-Marrow-Donation">FAQ</a>). We'll add all donors and registrants to our <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/posts/33101529/">Honor Roll</a>.</li><br/>
<li>If you aren't eligible to donate, such as for medical reasons, please encourage someone else to make a donation, and let us know. If they donate, you'll both be added to our <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/posts/33101529/">Honor Roll</a>. The FDA has changed the U.S. donor eligibility rules, by removing the blanket ban on MSM donors, so there are more eligible donors than ever before.</li><br/>
<li>Share our message with friends, relatives, and followers. Thank the forum members who post in the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2425233/">MacRumors 2024 Blood Drive!</a> thread.</li></ol><br/>
After the MacRumors Blood Drive ends on May 31, please record your blood, platelet, and plasma donations on our <a href="https://sleevesup.redcrossblood.org/campaign/macrumors-blood-drive-2024-2025">Team MacRumors 2024-2025</a> page (see <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/posts/33101531/">instructions</a>). We'll tally your donations and count them for the MacRumors 2025 Blood Drive next May.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macrumors-blood-drive/">MacRumors Blood Drive</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/macrumors-2024-blood-drive/">MacRumors 2024 Blood Drive</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-2024-blood-drive.2425257/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon&#039;s Apple Watch Sale Includes &#36;60 Off 2nd Gen SE and &#36;100 Off Series 9</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/amazon-apple-watch-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-apple-watch-sale-includes-60-off-2nd-gen-se-and-100-off-series-9.2425256/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:57:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/amazon-apple-watch-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This is just &#36;10 higher compared to the all-time low price on the wearable, and it's available in the Silver, Midnight, and Starlight Aluminum Case options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-gen-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-865510" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's available in Midnight and Starlight Aluminum options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, both cellular models have hit record low prices this week on Amazon. The 40mm cellular Apple Watch SE is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7PF7V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;239.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00, and the 44mm cellular model is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXB1D3Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;269.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. You can find these all-time low prices available in multiple colors right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
This model of the Apple Watch SE launched in September 2022 and remains Apple's most affordable Apple Watch. The Apple Watch SE lacks some of the upgraded features you'll find in some Series 9 or Ultra 2 models, like temperature sensing and ECG functionality, but it will otherwise provide you with all key Apple Watch features, and at the cheapest price possible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-series-9-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948907" /><br/>
If you're shopping for the Apple Watch Series 9, there are a few options on Amazon right now as well. You can get the 45mm GPS model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;329.00</strong></a> in (PRODUCT)RED, down from &#36;429.00. The 41mm cellular model is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXDRLMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a> and the 45mm cellular model is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9H4Q4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;429.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;100 off and all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXDRLMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9H4Q4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;429.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/amazon-apple-watch-sale/">Amazon&#039;s Apple Watch Sale Includes &#36;60 Off 2nd Gen SE and &#36;100 Off Series 9</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-apple-watch-sale-includes-60-off-2nd-gen-se-and-100-off-series-9.2425256/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>LG TVs Gain Support for Dolby Atmos With Apple Music</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/lg-tv-support-for-apple-music-dolby-atmos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lg-tvs-gain-support-for-dolby-atmos-with-apple-music.2425255/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:48:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/lg-tv-support-for-apple-music-dolby-atmos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>LG</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		<category>Dolby Atmos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LG has updated its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> app to support Dolby Atmos, making it the first smart TV manufacturer to do so (via <em><a href="https://www.flatpanelshd.com/news.php?subaction=showfull&id=1714539123">FlatpanelsHD</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-music-lg-tv.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-826014" /><br/>
The change allows users to experience immersive audio that enhances the spatial perception of sound, previously achievable only with external hardware. The feature was confirmed to be operational on the LG GX OLED TV from the 2020 lineup, with expectations that it will work on all LG TVs that are compatible with Dolby Atmos from 2020 onwards.<br/>
<br/>
While the TV's built-in speakers can utilize this new capability, LG suggests that the best audio experience is achieved with a compatible surround sound system, which can take advantage of the Dolby Atmos technology more effectively.<br/>
<br/>
The update to the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app on LG TVs circumvents the necessity for additional Apple hardware. Before this update, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;'s Dolby Atmos support was available on TVs singularly through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K, paired with either Apple's HomePods or Sonos speakers connected through the Sonos app. Other smart TV manufacturers are likely to follow suit and add support for Dolby Atmos in their own &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; apps. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg/">LG</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dolby-atmos/">Dolby Atmos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/lg-tv-support-for-apple-music-dolby-atmos/">LG TVs Gain Support for Dolby Atmos With Apple Music</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lg-tvs-gain-support-for-dolby-atmos-with-apple-music.2425255/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Turn Several Live Photos into a Single Video on iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-several-live-photos-into-video-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/turn-several-live-photos-into-a-single-video-on-iphone.2425253/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-several-live-photos-into-video-iphone&#038;post_date=1714584600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Photos</category>
		<category>Live Photos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Did you know it's possible to take multiple Live Photos from your iPhone's photo library and turn them into a single continuous video? Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/icloud-photos.jpg" alt="" width="836" height="470" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897381" /><br/>
On iPhone and iPad, Live Photos bring your pictures to life by adding a few seconds of video before and after the shot, creating a living memory rather than a static image. <br/>
<br/>
While Live Photos are great on their own, it's also possible to weave several together to create a video montage. This process transforms a collection of moments into a cohesive narrative, and offers an easier way to share and relive your memories. <br/>
<br/>
Whether it's a series of shots from a special event, a day out with friends, or a compilation of everyday moments, the following steps show you how to turn several Live Photos into a video that can encapsulate their essence in a way that a single photo or traditional video might not.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>In the Photos app, tap the <strong>Albums</strong> icon at the bottom of the screen.</li><br/>
  <li>Scroll down to "Media Types," and tap <strong>Live Photos</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Select</strong> in the top-right corner, then tap the Live Photos you want to include in your video so that a little checkmark appears on each one.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the circle icon containing three dots in the bottom-right corner.</li><br/>
  <li>Choose <strong>Save as Video</strong> in the pop-up menu.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/turn-live-photos-into-video.jpg" alt="photos" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942186" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. To watch your newly created video, return to the <strong>Albums</strong> view and select <strong>Videos</strong> under the "Media Types" section. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4szR1fs-4N/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:540px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4szR1fs-4N/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;">View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div></div></a><p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4szR1fs-4N/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank">A post shared by MacRumors (@macrumors)</a></p></div></blockquote> <script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"></script></div><br/>
Note that the video will be dated to when the Live Photos were originally taken, so they may not show as the latest video in your collection.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-photos/">Live Photos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/turn-several-live-photos-into-video-iphone/">Turn Several Live Photos into a Single Video on iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/turn-several-live-photos-into-a-single-video-on-iphone.2425253/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Watch Ultra to Get &#039;Almost No&#039; Hardware Upgrades This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/kuo-on-apple-watch-ultra-3-hardware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-to-get-almost-no-hardware-upgrades-this-year.2425251/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 06:53:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/kuo-on-apple-watch-ultra-3-hardware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just over six months ago, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said the likelihood of a new Apple Watch Ultra being released in 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-3-in-2024-odds-decreasing/">was "decreasing,"</a> but it now sounds like there will be an Apple Watch Ultra 3 this year after all.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-blorange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911679" /><br/>
In a direct message shared with <em>MacRumors</em> today, Kuo said that while the Apple Watch Ultra will be updated this year, the new model will have "almost no" hardware upgrades compared to the Apple Watch Ultra 2. Kuo did not reveal any specific changes planned for the Apple Watch Ultra 3, which will presumably launch in September.<br/>
<br/>
A third-generation Apple Watch SE is also a possibility this year if Apple sticks to a two-year upgrade cycle for that model, but the successor to the Apple Watch Series 9 is not entirely clear. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman previously reported about a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">redesigned "Apple Watch X"</a> with a thinner case and magnetic bands, but he said it would be released "in 2024 or 2025," so it is not clear if it will launch this year or next year.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, Gurman previously said the model that succeeds the Apple Watch Series 9 will offer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/2024-apple-watch-blood-pressure-sleep-apnea/">blood pressure sensing and sleep apnea detection</a>, and these features would almost certainly extend to the Apple Watch Ultra 3.<br/>
<br/>
The original Apple Watch was unveiled in September 2014, and launched in April 2015, so the device is approaching its tenth anniversary.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/kuo-on-apple-watch-ultra-3-hardware/">Kuo: Apple Watch Ultra to Get &#039;Almost No&#039; Hardware Upgrades This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-watch-ultra-to-get-almost-no-hardware-upgrades-this-year.2425251/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report Examines GM&#039;s Controversial Move to Abandon Apple CarPlay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/gm-controversial-move-to-abandon-carplay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-examines-gms-controversial-move-to-abandon-apple-carplay.2425248/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:53:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/gm-controversial-move-to-abandon-carplay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>GM</category>
		<category>General Motors</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An in-depth <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2024-05-01/will-gm-regret-kicking-apple-carplay-off-the-dashboard"><em>Bloomberg</em> report</a> today resurfaced General Motors' decision to replace Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> with its own software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-CarPlay-Dash.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-934995" /><br/>
Last year, GM <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/31/general-motors-to-phase-out-apple-carplay/">announced</a> that it planned to forgo Apple &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; in its new electric vehicles, starting with the 2024 Chevrolet Blazer EV. Instead, the automaker introduced a proprietary infotainment platform, aiming to control and customize the digital experience within its vehicles. This transition is part of GM's strategic pivot toward enhancing its software capabilities and establishing a stronger digital services revenue stream. However, the change has not been without its hurdles, with numerous customers and automotive reviewers reporting technical issues and a steep learning curve associated with the new system.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; has become a staple of most new vehicles, offering drivers a familiar interface that mirrors their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s functionality onto the vehicle's dashboard. Apple reported in 2022 that 79% of car buyers in the U.S. insisted on &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; support when considering a new vehicle purchase. <br/>
<br/>
GM's new in-house system, Ultifi, is envisioned as a comprehensive digital platform that offers a range of services such as navigation and media streaming, enhanced by subscription-based add-ons to drive revenue. Despite these aspirations, the rollout of Ultifi has encountered significant obstacles such as software malfunctions that dealerships have struggled to resolve. <br/>
<br/>
GM's move is driven by a wish to reclaim customer connections and data insights from third parties, but customer resistance to abandoning a familiar and popular system like &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; that directly integrates with their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; poses a significant challenge to GM's strategy.<br/>
<br/>
The outcome of GM's decision could influence future industry practices significantly. If GM can refine Ultifi into a robust, user-friendly platform that rivals or surpasses &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;'s functionality, it may set a precedent for other automakers to follow suit. Conversely, if consumers continue to prefer established systems like &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, automakers may find themselves in a difficult position, needing to balance their corporate interests with consumer preferences.<br/>
<br/>
See <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2024-05-01/will-gm-regret-kicking-apple-carplay-off-the-dashboard"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s full article</a> for more insights into GM's move to abandon Apple &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/gm/">GM</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/general-motors/">General Motors</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/gm-controversial-move-to-abandon-carplay/">Report Examines GM&#039;s Controversial Move to Abandon Apple CarPlay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-examines-gms-controversial-move-to-abandon-apple-carplay.2425248/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Remove Suggested Contacts From Your iPhone&#039;s Share Menu</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/remove-suggested-contacts-iphone-share-menu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/remove-suggested-contacts-from-your-iphones-share-menu.2425242/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 02:06:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/remove-suggested-contacts-iphone-share-menu&#038;post_date=1714565190/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When you go to share something on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, iOS tries to be helpful by displaying a row of suggested contacts at the top of the Share menu. Keep reading to learn how to get rid of them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/suggested-contacts.jpg" alt="share menu suggestions" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948831" /><br/>
Whenever you go to share something on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> using the Share button, iOS brings up a Share menu – often called the Share Sheet – at the top of which is a row of suggested contacts with whom you've interacted recently. Swiping along this row reveals more contacts, and the icon in the corner of each profile picture indicates the app that you often use to communicate with that person.<br/>
<br/>
These suggested contacts are useful if you share a lot of things with the same people, but there may be times when you'd prefer not to see specific contacts there, for example if someone is a duplicate suggestion over multiple apps, or if you don't want to draw attention to your regular comms with a certain someone. Whatever the reason, you can actually steer these sharing suggestions to appear less often, or not at all. Here's how.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Make Contacts Appear Less Often in the Share Menu</h2><ol><li>Tap the <strong>Share button</strong> (the box with an arrow pointing out) in any app to bring up the Share Sheet.</li><br/>
<li>Long press on the suggested contact that you want to see less often in the Share menu.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Suggest Less</strong> in the popover menu.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/1suggested-contacts-.jpg" alt="share menu" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948829" /><br/>
<br/>
Bear in mind, doing this won't guarantee that the contact doesn't appear in the Share Sheet again in future, but if you keep repeating it whenever they do show up, iOS will eventually get the message.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Remove All Contacts From iPhone Share Menu</h2><br/>
Short of deleting their contact in the Contacts app, the only way to guarantee that someone doesn't keep turning up on your Share Sheet is to disable the contact suggestions row completely.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap <strong>Siri & Search</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Under the "Suggestions From Apple" section, toggle off the switch next to <strong>Show When Sharing</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/2suggested-contacts-.jpg" alt="settings" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948830" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. Now the next time you invoke the Share Sheet, you won't see any contact profiles at the top. You can reverse the change just as easily by switching on the <strong>Show When Sharing</strong> toggle again.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/remove-suggested-contacts-iphone-share-menu/">Remove Suggested Contacts From Your iPhone&#039;s Share Menu</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/remove-suggested-contacts-from-your-iphones-share-menu.2425242/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discounts MLS Season Pass</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/apple-discounts-2024-mls-season-pass/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discounts-mls-season-pass.2425240/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:29:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/apple-discounts-2024-mls-season-pass/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today dropped the price of the MLS Season Pass for the rest of the 2024 Major League Soccer season, which is about a third of the way through.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/apple-tv-mls-season-pass.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-873748" /><br/>
MLS in the U.S. now costs &#36;69, down from &#36;99 when the season began in February. For <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> subscribers, the pass is now just &#36;59.<br/>
<br/>
The MLS Season Pass offers access to every live Major League Soccer match, including Leagues Cup, and All-Star games. Apple offered a similar discount last year, but it came later in the season in September.<br/>
<br/>
The 2024 Major League Soccer season will run through October 19, and the MLS Season Pass also includes live coverage of the playoffs that are expected to start in mid-October. The MLS Season Pass is available in the TV app on Apple devices and on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/apple-discounts-2024-mls-season-pass/">Apple Discounts MLS Season Pass</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discounts-mls-season-pass.2425240/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok May Be Breaking App Store Rules by Avoiding Commissions on Tips</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/tiktok-app-store-rules-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-may-be-breaking-app-store-rules-by-avoiding-commissions-on-tips.2425220/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:55:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/tiktok-app-store-rules-tips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[TikTok appears to be quietly showing some users an option to purchase "coins" on the web instead of through in-app purchases, circumventing the commission that Apple receives on digital purchases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/tiktok-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-752609" /><br/>
As noted by David Tesler (via <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/screenshots-suggest-tiktok-is-circumventing-apple-app-store-commissions/">TechCrunch</a></em>) TikTok has been offering a limited number of TikTok app users an option to purchase coins on TikTok.com instead of in the app. "Try recharging on tiktok.com to avoid in-app service fees," reads the text. "You can save the service fee and get access to popular payment methods."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">TikTok might get banned from the app store next week<br><br>Why? It looks like they’re circumventing apple fee by directing users to purchase coins via external payment methods <a href="https://t.co/VG8ihvsRmv">pic.twitter.com/VG8ihvsRmv</a></p>&mdash; David Tesler (@getdavenow) <a href="https://twitter.com/getdavenow/status/1785391788481786001?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 30, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Following through and opting to purchase from TikTok.com brings up an interface for using payment options such as PayPal or a credit/debit card. "Save around 25% with a lower third-party service fee," the app suggests. The purchase workflow can be completed entirely in the TikTok app with no requirement to use in-app purchase.<br/>
<br/>
TikTok's coins are used as a way for users to provide "Gifts" to creators. Users pay real money for a certain number of coins, and those coins are used for little gift emoji that can be provided to creators. TikTok says that gifts are used to determine the number of "diamonds" awarded to content creators, and diamonds can be redeemed for money. A TikTok coin is worth about half a diamond, and 100 diamonds is worth 50 cents, so TikTok is collecting quite a bit of money during the conversion.<br/>
<br/>
Apple requires in-app purchase to be used for digital goods and services, and TikTok's "coins" presumably count as a digital good. If TikTok is indeed offering customers a way to purchase coins without in-app purchase as suggested by the screenshots from Tesler, then TikTok is breaking Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules.<br/>
<br/>
TikTok coins would likely be considered tips, and Apple has forced other major social networks like Facebook to use in-app purchase for a creator tipping feature. What TikTok is doing is actually similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/fornite-adds-direct-payment-option-on-ios/">direct purchase options</a> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> added to the Fortnite app back in 2020, a move that ultimately led to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">banning of the Fortnite app</a> and a multi-year legal battle.<br/>
<br/>
Most TikTok users are only able to purchase coins through the in-app purchase interface, and the option to purchase direct from TikTok with a credit or debit card is allegedly a feature showing up only for a small number of users. The option is perhaps being limited to those who have spent a lot of money on coins in the past.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/tiktok-app-store-rules-tips/">TikTok May Be Breaking App Store Rules by Avoiding Commissions on Tips</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-may-be-breaking-app-store-rules-by-avoiding-commissions-on-tips.2425220/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.5 Includes &#039;Repair State&#039; Option That Doesn&#039;t Require Turning Off Find My for Service</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-17-5-repair-state/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-5-includes-repair-state-option-that-doesnt-require-turning-off-find-my-for-service.2425219/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:24:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-17-5-repair-state/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iOS 17.5, Apple is adding a "Repair State" feature that is designed to allow an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to be sent in for service without deactivating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> and Activation Lock. The fourth iOS 17.5 beta that came out today adds a "Remove This Device" option for all devices in &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, and using it with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; puts that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; into the new Repair State.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ios-17-5-repair-state.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948810" /><br/>
Right now, sending an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to Apple to be repaired <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109519">requires turning off Find My</a>, and Apple says that it "might not" be able to repair devices that have &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; activated. Turning off &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; disables Activation Lock, an important anti-theft security feature that prevents an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from being used with another <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple currently uses &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; and Activation Lock as a way to ensure that a person sending a device in for repair actually owns that device, and that it's not stolen. An &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sent in for repair with &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; disabled cannot be tracked, and it is not protected from theft, so if it is lost or stolen at some point in transit during the repair process, there is no recovery method available. Removing &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; also has a hitch with Stolen Device Protection, as there is an hour wait when turning off &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, which can be inconvenient for repair purposes.<br/>
<br/>
The new repair state leaves &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; turned on, so Activation Lock remains enabled, and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; continues to be trackable with the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app while it is being repaired. When enabled, the device in the repair state has a "Ready for Repair" label. "This device remains fully functional in the repair state," reads the text.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/ios-17-5-repair-state-icon.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948812" /><br/>
In the list of devices, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; put into a repair state has a small stethoscope icon, and it can be marked as lost. While in repair state, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is fully functional.<br/>
<br/>
As of right now, using the "Remove This Device" option in &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; to enable a repair state appears to be limited to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Using it on other devices like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, or Apple Watch shows a warning that the feature will remove the device from the &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; account, allowing it to be used by someone else. Note that an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; must be online and trackable through &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; for the repair state option to pop up. An &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that is offline will display the standard removal text. It is also worth noting that repair state cannot be disabled at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
Repair state is a feature that is still in development, so it might work with other devices when iOS 17.5 and its sister updates launch in May.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-17-5-repair-state/">iOS 17.5 Includes &#039;Repair State&#039; Option That Doesn&#039;t Require Turning Off Find My for Service</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-5-includes-repair-state-option-that-doesnt-require-turning-off-find-my-for-service.2425219/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for USB-C Apple Pencil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/apple-releases-usb-c-apple-pencil-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-usb-c-apple-pencil.2425217/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 12:41:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/apple-releases-usb-c-apple-pencil-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a firmware update for the USB-C <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> that came out last year. The new firmware has a version number of 10M6060, up from 10M5164. On device, the updated firmware version number will be 37377.37377.16.0.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917176" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" /><br/>
There is no word on what features, fixes, or updates might be included in the new firmware, and Apple does not offer release notes for &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; software releases.<br/>
<br/>
The USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is nearly identical in design to the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2, but it is shorter and has a hidden USB-C port for charging and pairing. It cannot wirelessly charge, and it lacks some of the features available with the more expensive &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; models such as pressure sensitivity.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not have an established procedure for updating &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hardware, but in the case of the USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, connecting it to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with a USB-C cable and powering on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; should be enough to spur the update to download.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/apple-releases-usb-c-apple-pencil-firmware/">Apple Releases New Firmware for USB-C Apple Pencil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-usb-c-apple-pencil.2425217/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple&#039;s Earnings Report This Week Following Vision Pro Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/apple-q2-2024-earnings-preview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-earnings-report-this-week-following-vision-pro-launch.2425216/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 12:39:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/apple-q2-2024-earnings-preview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will report its earnings results for the second quarter of its 2024 fiscal year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/apple-to-report-earnings-on-may-2/">on Thursday, May 2</a> at 1:30 p.m. Pacific Time. Apple's CEO Tim Cook and CFO Luca Maestri will discuss the results on a conference call with analysts a half hour later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Keep reading for some key things to know about the quarter, including a recap of new products announced, revenue expectations, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Products During Quarter</h2><br/>
The quarter ran from December 31, 2023 through March 30, 2024, according to Apple's fiscal calendar. The following products launched during this period:<ul><li>Apple Vision Pro</li><br/>
<li>13-inch MacBook Air with M3 chip</li><br/>
<li>15-inch MacBook Air with M3 chip</li></ul><h2>Revenue Expectations</h2><br/>
Apple has not provided formal revenue guidance since before the COVID-19 pandemic, but the average Wall Street estimate for Apple's second quarter revenue is &#36;90 billion, according to <a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2264410/should-you-buy-apple-aapl-stock-ahead-of-q2-earnings">Zacks Investment Research</a>. This would be around a 5% decline compared to the &#36;94.8 billion revenue the company reported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/04/apple-2q-2023-earnings/">in the year-ago quarter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Maestri provided the following commentary on Apple's earnings call last quarter:<blockquote>As a reminder, in the December quarter a year ago, we faced significant supply constraints on the iPhone 14 Pro and 14 Pro Max due to COVID-19 factory shutdowns. And in the March quarter a year ago, we were able to replenish channel inventory and fulfill significant pent-up demand from the constraints. We estimate that this impact added close to &#36;5 billion to the March quarter's total revenue last year. When we remove this impact from last year's revenue, we expect both our March quarter total company revenue and iPhone revenue to be similar to a year ago.</blockquote><h2>Conference Call</h2><br/>
Cook and Maestri will hold a conference call at 2:00 p.m. Pacific Time on Thursday to discuss the company's quarterly earnings results. The call should last around one hour, and it will include a Q&A segment with analysts.<br/>
<br/>
A live audio stream of the conference call will be available on <a href="https://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">Apple's Investor Relations page</a>, and a recording will be available later in the day for replay.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What's Next</h2><br/>
Apple's current quarter runs through June 29. Apple has yet to announce any new products during the quarter, but it is expected to unveil new versions of the iPad Pro, iPad Air, Apple Pencil, and Magic Keyboard at its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">"Let Loose" event on May 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
AAPL is trading above &#36;172 as of writing, down from a 52-week high of &#36;199.62.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/apple-q2-2024-earnings-preview/">What to Expect From Apple&#039;s Earnings Report This Week Following Vision Pro Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-earnings-report-this-week-following-vision-pro-launch.2425216/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumored to Add New Features to These 15 Apps on Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-add-new-features-to-these-15-apps-on-your-iphone.2425212/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:44:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to announce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> during its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>, and new features have already been rumored for many apps, including Apple Music, Apple Maps, Calculator, Messages, Notes, Safari, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Apple-Music-Messages-and-Notes-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948782" /><br/>
Below, we recap iOS 18 rumors on a per-app basis, based on reports from <em>MacRumors</em>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, and others:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Apple Maps:</strong> At least two new Apple Maps features are expected on iOS 18, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/">custom routes</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/27/ios-18-topographic-maps/">topographic maps</a>. Custom routes would allow users to choose specific roads to travel on while navigating, while topographic maps include details such as trails, contour lines, elevation, and points of interest for hiking. Topographic maps were added to the Apple Watch with watchOS 10.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Music:</strong> With iOS 18, Apple Music will reportedly be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">auto-generate playlists</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Calculator:</strong> iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS 15 are rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macos-15-revamped-calculator-app/">revamped Calculator app with several new features</a>, including a sidebar that lists recent calculations, an improved interface for converting units, integration with the Notes app, and more. That means the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">Calculator app will finally be available on iPads</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Freeform:</strong> iOS 18 is rumored to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/ios-18-macos-15-freeform-app-scenes/">add a new "Scenes" option to Apple's drawing app Freeform</a>. This feature would allow users to select specific sections ("scenes") on the canvas for easier navigation.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Health:</strong> Apple is reportedly planning new AI-powered features <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-15/apple-s-ai-plans-github-copilot-rival-for-developers-tool-for-testing-apps">for its Health app</a>, but no specific details are known yet.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Keynote, Numbers, and Pages:</strong> Alongside iOS 18, Apple reportedly plans to update its iWork suite of productivity apps with new generative AI features for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">auto-generating slides in Keynote, writing faster in Pages, and more</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mail, Photos, and Fitness:</strong> These apps will reportedly be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ios-18-notes-mail-photos-fitness-rumors/">"overhauled" with iOS 18</a>, but no specific details are known yet.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Messages:</strong> iOS 18 is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">add RCS support to the Messages app</a>, which will improve the messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices by allowing for higher-resolution photos and videos, audio messages, typing indicators, read receipts, Wi-Fi messaging, and more. It has also been rumored that the Messages app will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">use generative AI to auto-complete sentences</a> more effectively.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Notes:</strong> With iOS 18, the Notes app is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">be able to display mathematical notation</a>, allowing users to include more types of algebraic equations and formulas in notes. The app is also rumored to gain a built-in audio recording tool, eliminating the need to switch over to the Voice Memos app.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Safari:</strong> iOS 18 is likely to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-18-safari-browsing-assistant-rumor/">add a browsing assistant to Safari</a>, which could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/safari-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">summarize web pages and more</a>. A new "Web Eraser" feature that would allow users to remove certain elements from web pages has also been rumored.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Shortcuts:</strong> With iOS 18, users will reportedly be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">automate complex tasks more easily</a> with the Shortcuts app.</li></ul>While they are not dedicated apps, it has also been rumored that generative AI technology will allow the iPhone's virtual assistant Siri and built-in search tool Spotlight to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">respond to more complex questions and search queries</a>.<br/>
<br/>
For even more rumors, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/">iOS 18 Rumored to Add New Features to These 15 Apps on Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-add-new-features-to-these-15-apps-on-your-iphone.2425212/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-17-5-beta-4-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-ios-17-5-and-ipados-17-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2425207/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:18:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-17-5-beta-4-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth betas of upcoming iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/">released the third betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943813" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
Most of the features that Apple promised would be coming in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have now been released, but iOS 17.5 adds additional app ecosystem changes in the European Union. App developers can offer apps for download on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">directly from their websites</a>, in addition to through app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
There are also code changes that hint at new Apple Pencils and a Battery Health feature for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, with more information on what's new available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/everything-new-in-ios-17-5-beta-1/">iOS 17.5 beta features post</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-17-5-beta-4-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-ios-17-5-and-ipados-17-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2425207/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-4-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2425208/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:17:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-4-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.5 update to developers, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-3/">released the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what is included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.5, and no new features were found in the first three developer betas. Fresh release candidate versions of macOS Ventura 13.6.7 and macOS Monterey 12.7.5 have also been seeded to developers.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-4-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2425208/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
