<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 08:03:52 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Do-It-Yourself Repair Store Now Offering Parts for M4 Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/m4-macs-self-service-repairs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-do-it-yourself-repair-store-now-offering-parts-for-m4-macs.2448830/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 07:57:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/m4-macs-self-service-repairs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Self Service Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week added parts and tools for all M4 Macs to its <a href="https://selfservicerepair.com/en-US/order">self-service repair store</a> in the U.S. and many European countries. This includes parts for MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini models with M4, M4 Pro, and/or M4 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
Since launching in 2022, Apple's self-service repair program has given customers access to the same genuine Apple parts, tools, and manuals used by the Genius Bar at Apple Stores and at Apple Authorized Service Providers, allowing for do-it-yourself repairs. Repair manuals for M4 Macs are <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/docs/mac">available on Apple's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Depending on the model, repair parts that can be ordered for M4 Macs include displays, logic boards, speakers, trackpads, top cases with a keyboard and battery, SSD modules, USB-C ports, fans, Wi-Fi antennas, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The self-service repair store also offers parts for various iPhone models and the Studio Display, as well as replacement batteries for the Beats Pill speaker. Apple says the program is "intended for individuals who are experienced with the complexities of repairing electronic devices," and the repair manuals include important safety information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/m4-macs-self-service-repairs/">Apple&#039;s Do-It-Yourself Repair Store Now Offering Parts for M4 Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-do-it-yourself-repair-store-now-offering-parts-for-m4-macs.2448830/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M4 iMac (8-Core/256GB) Drops to &#36;1,149.99 on Amazon, More Models at Up to &#36;175 Off</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/m4-imac-drops-175-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-imac-8-core-256gb-drops-to-1-149-99-on-amazon-more-models-at-up-to-175-off.2448826/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 07:20:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/m4-imac-drops-175-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has up to &#36;175 off a collection of Apple's M4 iMac computers, and it's matching a few all-time low prices on multiple models. The cheapest M4 iMac available is the 8-core/16GB RAM/256GB 24-inch iMac at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL76BQ5N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,149.99</strong></a> with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,299.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-iMac-M4-hero-feature.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-973309" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You'll also find  the 512GB models on sale, and each configuration has multiple colors available at these discounts. For the steepest markdown, Amazon has the 10-core/24GB RAM/512GB 24-inch iMac for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL6X847C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;1,724.00</strong></a> in Blue, down from &#36;1,899.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL76BQ5N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>24-inch M4 iMac (8-core/16GB RAM/256GB) for &#36;1,149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Some of these deals will require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price at checkout. This is mainly regarding the entry-level 8-core/256GB iMac, but a few color options from the other configurations will also require a coupon to be clipped.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL76BQ5N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">8-core/16GB RAM/256GB</a> - &#36;1,149.99, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL71DPKQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">10-core/16GB RAM/256GB</a> - &#36;1,349.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL6NCGNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">10-core/16GB RAM/512GB</a> - &#36;1,549.99, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DL6X847C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">10-core/24GB RAM/512GB</a> - &#36;1,724.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/m4-imac-drops-175-off/">Apple&#039;s M4 iMac (8-Core/256GB) Drops to &#36;1,149.99 on Amazon, More Models at Up to &#36;175 Off</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-imac-8-core-256gb-drops-to-1-149-99-on-amazon-more-models-at-up-to-175-off.2448826/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia 15.3 Fixes SuperDuper Bootable Backups Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/macos-15-3-fixes-superduper-bootable-backups/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-15-3-fixes-superduper-bootable-backups-bug.2448823/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:56:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/macos-15-3-fixes-superduper-bootable-backups/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest macOS Sequoia 15.3 update appears to have resolved a bug that prevented popular backup utility <a href="https://www.shirt-pocket.com/SuperDuper/SuperDuperDescription.html">SuperDuper</a> from creating bootable backups, according to developer Dave Nanian.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/superduper-macos.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-982434" /><br/>
The fix addresses an issue introduced in macOS 15.2 that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/17/macos-15-2-breaks-superduper-bootable-backups/">caused SuperDuper to fail</a> during the final stages of creating bootable backups due to a "Resource Busy" error when attempting to copy system preboot or recovery files.<br/>
<br/>
Apple requires third-party apps to use Apple's own replication tools rather than directly copying the operating system. When these tools malfunctioned in macOS 15.2, it directly impacted SuperDuper's ability to create bootable backups.<br/>
<br/>
"macOS 15.3 is now out, and with it, a fix for the broken replicator," Nanian wrote on his <a href="https://www.shirtpocket.com/blog/index.php/shadedgrey/comments/happy_new_fix/">Shirt Pocket Watch blog</a>. "As such, macOS copying will work again with 'Erase, then copy' backups."<br/>
<br/>
However, Nanian cautions that while the specific replicator bug has been fixed, this doesn't guarantee that booting from backup copies will work in all situations. This is largely due to changes that Apple has made in macOS and recent Mac hardware in the name of enhanced security.<br/>
<br/>
For example, Apple Silicon Macs require that the internal SSD remains functional for external booting to work, meaning a Mac with a failed internal drive <a href="https://eclecticlight.co/2021/01/14/m1-macs-radically-change-boot-and-recovery/">won't boot</a> from a SuperDuper backup, even if the backup itself is perfectly intact. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/macos-15-3-fixes-superduper-bootable-backups/">macOS Sequoia 15.3 Fixes SuperDuper Bootable Backups Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-15-3-fixes-superduper-bootable-backups-bug.2448823/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M5 Apple Silicon Chip Reportedly Enters Mass Production</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-silicon-m5-chip-enters-mass-production/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m5-apple-silicon-chip-reportedly-enters-mass-production.2448820/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 04:51:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-silicon-m5-chip-enters-mass-production/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		<category>M5</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has begun mass production of its next-generation M5 chip, according to South Korean media, with the processor expected to arrive in devices potentially as soon as this year. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-2024-feature-purple-m5.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983351" /><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.etnews.com/20250205000198">ET News</a></em> reports that Apple began packaging the M5 chip last month. Packaging is the final step in semiconductor manufacturing after fabrication, and involves the process of protecting the chip and enabling electrical connections with other devices or components. <br/>
<br/>
Apple outsources to TSMC the front-end manufacturing phase of fabricating the chips on silicon wafers. Now that fabrication is underway, the packaging is being handled by OSAT (Outsourced Semiconductor Assembly and Test) companies including Taiwan's ASE Group, America's Amkor, and China's JCET. According to the report, ASE was the first to begin mass production, while Amkor and JCET are expected to follow sequentially.<br/>
<br/>
The initial production run is said to be for the base M5 model, rather than Apple's more advanced M5 Pro, M5 Max, and M5 Ultra processors. The OSAT companies mentioned above are said to be currently investing in additional facilities to support the mass production of the high-end models.<br/>
<br/>
The M5 series is expected to feature an enhanced ARM architecture and is reportedly being manufactured using TSMC's advanced 3-nanometer process technology. Apple's decision to forgo TSMC's more advanced 2nm process for the M5 chip is believed to be due to cost considerations. However, the high-end versions of the M5 will still feature significant advancements over their M4 equivalents, mainly through the adoption of TSMC's System on Integrated Chip (SoIC) technology.<br/>
<br/>
This 3D chip-stacking approach vertically stacks the chips, which enhances thermal management and reduces electrical leakage compared to traditional 2D designs. Apple is said to have expanded its cooperation with TSMC on the next-generation hybrid SoIC package, which also combines thermoplastic carbon fiber composite molding technology.<br/>
<br/>
The first device to be equipped with the M5 chip is expected to be a new iPad Pro, which will enter mass production in the second half of next year, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/04/m5-ipad-pro-mass-production-late-2025/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Assuming Apple maintains its typical upgrade cycle for its custom silicon, here are the devices we're expecting to benefit in chronological order:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>iPad Pro:</strong> M5 chips could debut in the devices in late 2025 or early-to-mid 2026.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>MacBook Pro:</strong> Models featuring M5 series chips are anticipated in late 2025.</li><br/>
<li><strong>MacBook Air:</strong> M5 variants will likely arrive in early 2026.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Apple Vision Pro:</strong> An updated version of the headset incorporating the M5 chip is expected between the fall of 2025 and spring of 2026.</li></ul>References to what are believed to be Apple's M5 chip have already been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/21/a19-and-m5-chips-discovered/">discovered</a> in official Apple code. According to one <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/04/apple-m5-chips-advanced-packaging-tsmc/">report</a>, thanks to its dual-use SoIC design, Apple also plans to deploy the M5 chip within its AI server infrastructure to bolster AI capabilities across both consumer devices and cloud services.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m5/">M5</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-silicon-m5-chip-enters-mass-production/">M5 Apple Silicon Chip Reportedly Enters Mass Production</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m5-apple-silicon-chip-reportedly-enters-mass-production.2448820/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Now Lets You Share Custom Feeds – Here&#039;s How</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/threads-now-lets-you-share-custom-feeds-heres-how/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-now-lets-you-share-custom-feeds-–-heres-how.2448818/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 03:40:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/threads-now-lets-you-share-custom-feeds-heres-how/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Threads is rolling out the ability for users to share custom feeds they've made, the social media platform announced on Tuesday. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
"Shared feeds are a new way for you to connect with people around similar interests and find profiles and conversations that are relevant to you," said the Meta-owned company in a <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2025/02/share-custom-feeds-on-threads/">newsroom post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The change means that users will be able to explore public feeds under a new Feeds tab on profiles, and pin feeds they like for quick access to their favorite people and topics.<br/>
<br/>
Before custom feeds can be shared, they must be made public. This can be done by tapping and holding a feed, selecting "Edit feeds," and then toggling on the switch next to "Public feed."<br/>
<br/>
Once that's done, you can share the custom feed in the following way: Tap and hold the feed you've created at the top of the Threads app, then tap "Edit feeds." Next, tap "View feed," and then either use the quote icon to post a preview of the feed, or use the "Share feed" button to send the feed as a link or direct message.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/01_Creating-Shared-Feed_Caoursel-2.jpg.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1672" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988224" /><br/>
Threads first rolled out custom feeds in November. Note that the ability to share custom feeds is still in the process of rolling out, so you may not see it immediately, depending on your location. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/threads-now-lets-you-share-custom-feeds-heres-how/">Threads Now Lets You Share Custom Feeds – Here&#039;s How</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-now-lets-you-share-custom-feeds-–-heres-how.2448818/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Users Can Now Send Images and Voice Messages to ChatGPT</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/whatsapp-send-images-voice-messages-chatgpt/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-users-can-now-send-images-and-voice-messages-to-chatgpt.2448816/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 03:05:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/whatsapp-send-images-voice-messages-chatgpt/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI has announced a couple of new ChatGPT features for WhatsApp users, adding support for voice messages and image-based interactions when communicated with the chat bot via the Meta-owned chat platform. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Whatsapp-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786421" /><br/>
Users can now send voice messages or upload images directly in their WhatsApp conversations with the AI assistant, said OpenAI in a <a href="https://x.com/OpenAI/status/1886966048970478016">post on Twitter (X)</a>, although ChatGPT will continue to respond exclusively to WhatsApp users through text.<br/>
<br/>
To access ChatGPT on WhatsApp, you'll need to add the number 1-800-CHAT-GPT (1-800-242-8478) to your contacts. The service then functions similarly to the web-based ChatGPT, but with the convenience of the WhatsApp interface.<br/>
<br/>
The expansion builds upon the initial WhatsApp integration launched in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/18/openai-chatgpt-phone-line/">December 2024</a>, which was limited to text-based interactions. OpenAI also plans to introduce account linking functionality that will allow users to connect their existing ChatGPT accounts — whether Free, Plus, or Pro — where they can keep tabs on their chat history and get more usage out of the service in Meta's app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"> 1-800-ChatGPT WhatsApp Updates<br><br>- You can now upload images when asking a question<br><br>- You can talk to ChatGPT using voice messages<br><br>- And coming soon, you can link your ChatGPT account (Free, Plus, Pro) for more usage</p>&mdash; OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1886966048970478016?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 5, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Any US phone number can contact ChatGPT and get 15 minutes of response time for free without an OpenAI account, but downloading the app and creating an account allows for additional call time.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/whatsapp-send-images-voice-messages-chatgpt/">WhatsApp Users Can Now Send Images and Voice Messages to ChatGPT</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-users-can-now-send-images-and-voice-messages-to-chatgpt.2448816/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Faces Potential App Store Antitrust Probe in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-potential-antitrust-probe-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-faces-potential-app-store-antitrust-probe-in-china.2448815/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 02:32:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-potential-antitrust-probe-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple could be facing a potential Chinese antitrust investigation into its App Store policies and developer fees, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-02-05/china-weighs-investigating-apple-over-app-store-policies-fees-including-30-cut">Bloomberg</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/App-Store-Blue-Banner-Chinese-Flag-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917631" /><br/>
China's State Administration for Market Regulation (SAMR) is said to have been critically examining Apple's practices and holding discussions with the company since last year, specifically about its 30% commission on in-app purchases and restrictions on external payment services, according to the outlet's sources. <br/>
<br/>
Chinese regulators are said to be particularly focused on whether Apple's fees for local developers are unreasonably high. They're also examining if the company's prohibition of third-party app stores and payment methods stifles competition and negatively impacts Chinese consumers. "If Apple resists making changes, the government may launch a formal investigation," <em>Bloomberg</em>'s sources said.<br/>
<br/>
The conversations are said to stem from long-running disputes between Apple and developers such as Tencent and ByteDance. A report in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/apple-pressures-bytedance-tencent-app-fees/">August</a> said Apple had been putting pressure on them to make significant changes to two of China's most popular apps in order to remove loopholes that circumvent Apple's typical 30% commission.<br/>
<br/>
The regulatory scrutiny comes at a time of escalating tensions between the United States and China. Just this week, SAMR announced a formal investigation into Google's practices moments after new US tariffs on Chinese goods took effect.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's position in China is particularly delicate. The country serves as the primary manufacturing base for iPhones and is Apple's largest market outside the United States. It's also having to compete with increasingly confident local rivals like Huawei, with Apple reporting an 11% decline in revenue from China over the holiday quarter.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is no stranger to regulatory scrutiny and has already had to implement a series of changes to avoid fines and other penalties elsewhere, including revamping its store practices in the European Union to comply with the Digital Markets Act. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-potential-antitrust-probe-china/">Apple Faces Potential App Store Antitrust Probe in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-faces-potential-app-store-antitrust-probe-in-china.2448815/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Plans to Launch Apple TV-Like Streaming Box</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/sonos-set-top-box/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-plans-to-launch-apple-tv-like-streaming-box.2448801/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 16:03:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/sonos-set-top-box/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos is developing a high-end streaming set-top box that's expected to launch this year, reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/sonos/606025/sonos-pinewood-video-player-features">The Verge</a></em>. While any set-top box will compete with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, Sonos plans to price its upcoming device at &#36;200 to &#36;400, which would make it notably more expensive than the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/sonos-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1092" height="614" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988202" /><br/>
According to <em>The Verge</em>, the hardware is a nondescript black box that's slightly thicker than a deck of cards, with an included remote control. It'll run a version of Android, but Sonos has developed a "beautiful" interface.<br/>
<br/>
The set-top box will offer content from Netflix, Max, Disney Plus, and other streaming services in a unified software experience that supports universal search. Sonos is said to be aiming to reduce the fragmentation of the streaming ecosystem, and the set-top box will be equipped with Sonos Voice Control. Apple has tried to do something similar, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is able to provide content suggestions from a range of services.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos' set-top box will double as an HDMI switch and it has HDMI ports with passthrough functionality. Users will be able to plug in gaming consoles, soundbars, and other devices. The device solves a latency problem that has long annoyed Sonos, and it will prevent TVs from experiencing audio sync delays with Sonos-branded soundbars.<br/>
<br/>
For Sonos users who have Sonos speakers but not a soundbar, the set-top box will allow for the configuration of a surround sound system with Sonos devices. It will also support Wi-Fi 7 and offer gigabit ethernet.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos struggled in 2024 after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/sonos-customer-service-software-quality/">a disastrous app launch</a> that ultimately led to Sonos CEO Patrick Spence <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/sonos-ceo-steps-down-after-app-redesign/">stepping down</a>, so the company needs a win in 2025 to restore its reputation. Sonos did not have much luck with its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/hands-on-sonos-ace-headphones/">Sonos Ace headphones</a> that came out around the time the app was refreshed, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/07/hands-on-with-the-sonos-arc-ultra/">Arc Ultra Soundbar</a> that launched late last year received better reviews.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/sonos-set-top-box/">Sonos Plans to Launch Apple TV-Like Streaming Box</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-plans-to-launch-apple-tv-like-streaming-box.2448801/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Launches Universal Cable That Can Charge Apple Watch and USB-C Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/nomad-universal-cable-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-universal-cable-that-can-charge-apple-watch-and-usb-c-devices.2448798/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:28:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/nomad-universal-cable-apple-watch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nomad today announced the launch of a unique cable that isn't quite like anything else on the market. The <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/universal-cable-apple-watch-carbide">Universal Cable for Apple Watch</a> includes a built-in Apple Watch fast charging puck along with two USB-C connectors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/nomad-apple-watch-cable.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988200" /><br/>
Priced at &#36;100, the 1.5 meter cable is able to charge an Apple Watch and another device like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> at the same time. It is a 100W USB-C PD cable, so it provides a small amount of power (8W) for the Apple Watch with the rest (92W) distributed to the other device that's plugged in. 100W is enough to charge even Apple's 16-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, as long as you have an appropriate power adapter.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch end of the cable can be plugged in at a power adapter or it can be used for device charging, so there are two layout options to choose from. Apple's most recent AirPods can charge from an Apple Watch charger, which adds more versatility. Note that transfer speeds are limited to USB 2 because the cable is designed for charging rather than data transfer.<br/>
<br/>
The cable has a double-braided Kevlar outer weave and it uses electroplated metal connectors for durability. There's also an integrated silicone cable tie to keep the cable neat even when traveling.<br/>
<br/>
The Universal Cable for Apple Watch can be <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/universal-cable-apple-watch-carbide">purchased from the Nomad website</a> for &#36;100.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/nomad-universal-cable-apple-watch/">Nomad Launches Universal Cable That Can Charge Apple Watch and USB-C Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-universal-cable-that-can-charge-apple-watch-and-usb-c-devices.2448798/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung is Working on a Tri-Fold Smartphone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/samsung-tri-fold-smartphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-is-working-on-a-tri-fold-smartphone.2448797/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:44:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/samsung-tri-fold-smartphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has been making foldable smartphones since 2019, but we have yet to see a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from Apple. Rumors suggest that Apple's first folding &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; could come out in 2026 or 2027, but by then, Samsung will be even further ahead in foldable device development.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/huawei-tri-fold-smartphone.jpg" alt="" width="2594" height="1458" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988193" /><em>Huawei's tri-fold Mate XT Ultimate</em></div><br/>
Right now, Samsung has the Galaxy Fold and the Galaxy Flip, which fold in different ways. The Galaxy Fold is larger and unfolds horizontally like a book, while the Flip has a vertical fold. According to rumors, Samsung is working on yet another foldable, this one with a tri-fold design.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's tri-fold device has been rumored for quite some time, and Samsung even teased it as a "multi-fold" device at its Unpacked event, but more information about the device came out this week. As noted by <em><a href="https://www.gsmarena.com/samsung_trifold_could_be_called_galaxy_g_fold-news-66351.php">GSMArena</a></em>, it's looking like Samsung could call it the Galaxy G Fold, which would make it a new product line distinct from the current Z Fold models.<br/>
<br/>
The tri-fold smartphone is expected to fold out into a 10-inch screen, which would make it significantly better than the current Z Fold6 flagship foldable smartphone from Samsung. The Z Fold6 is 7.6 inches when it's opened up, while the Z Flip6 is 6.7 inches unfolded.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung won't have the first tri-fold smartphone on the market, because Huawei has already released the <a href="https://consumer.huawei.com/cn/phones/mate-xt-ultimate-design/">Mate XT Ultimate</a>. You can't get Huawei's device in the United States, though, and it costs &#36;2,800, so Samsung will be first to a tri-fold smartphone in markets outside of China.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung typically announces new foldable smartphones around July, and it's looking like we could see the tri-fold smartphone unveiled this year ahead of a launch in early 2026.<br/>
<br/>
If Samsung's tri-fold smartphone launches in early 2026, it will beat any Apple foldable to market, since the earliest we expect to see an Apple foldable is 2026.<br/>
<br/>
As of 2024, Apple was supposedly working on a foldable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a design similar to the Galaxy Z Flip, which means a vertical fold. Such a device would likely be similar in size to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max, but with an option to fold it in half to make for a more compact size.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/samsung-tri-fold-smartphone/">Samsung is Working on a Tri-Fold Smartphone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-is-working-on-a-tri-fold-smartphone.2448797/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Check Out Doom Running on Apple&#039;s Lightning to HDMI Adapter</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/doom-apple-lightning-hdmi-adapter/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-doom-running-on-apples-lightning-to-hdmi-adapter.2448796/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:17:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/doom-apple-lightning-hdmi-adapter/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Installing Doom on a range of unusual hardware devices has become a fun challenge for programmers, and we've seen the game running on everything from the Apple Watch to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> Touch Bar. Over the weekend, another Doom demo was uploaded to YouTube, this time showing the game running on Apple's &#36;50 <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MW2P3AM/A/lightning-digital-av-adapter">Lightning to HDMI Adapter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="DOOM running on Apple Lightning to HDMI dongle" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4XCkeN0XuqA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-thumb-size="hqdefault"></iframe></div><br/>
The Lightning Digital AV Adapter is more than just a dongle, because it has an SoC inside and it runs a super simple version of iOS. Lightning does not have the bandwidth for transmitting HDMI, so Apple needed an adapter that would compress video from a connected Apple device, send it over the Lightning connection, and then decompress it into raw HDMI for viewing on a TV screen or display.<br/>
<br/>
Since the adapter has an SoC in it, it's able to run Doom. Actually getting access to the accessory took work, because Apple has it locked down, like any of its devices. While there is a MacBook and a display shown in the video, Doom is running on the SoC in the dongle.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/doom-apple-lightning-hdmi-adapter/">Check Out Doom Running on Apple&#039;s Lightning to HDMI Adapter</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-doom-running-on-apples-lightning-to-hdmi-adapter.2448796/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Heart Month Activity Challenge Launching on Valentine&#039;s Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-heart-month-2025-challenge/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-heart-month-activity-challenge-launching-on-valentines-day.2448778/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 11:33:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-heart-month-2025-challenge/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In honor of Heart Month, Apple Watch owners can earn an award by completing a workout to fill their Exercise ring on Friday, February 14, which is Valentine's Day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-heart-month-2025.jpg" alt="" width="1004" height="565" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988182" /><br/>
<blockquote>Show your heart some love! Close your Exercise ring this Valentine's Day, February 14, to earn this award.</blockquote><br/>
As with all of Apple's Activity Challenges, the Heart Month challenge will be accompanied by an award that can be viewed in the Fitness app as well as a series of animated stickers that can be used in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/heart_month_2025_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988184" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/heart_month_2025_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988185" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/heart_month_2025_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988186" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/heart_month_2025_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988183" /><br/>
Apple often also debuts themed Heart Month content in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a>, and Apple Books.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-heart-month-2025-challenge/">Apple Heart Month Activity Challenge Launching on Valentine&#039;s Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-heart-month-activity-challenge-launching-on-valentines-day.2448778/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Partiful Calls Apple a Copycat for New Invites App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/partiful-apple-invites-app-copycat/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/partiful-calls-apple-a-copycat-for-new-invites-app.2448774/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:51:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/partiful-apple-invites-app-copycat/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Invites</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The developers behind well-known event app and website <a href="https://partiful.com">Partiful</a> today suggested that Apple was in violation of its own <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> guidelines for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">release of the new Invites app</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/partiful-app.jpg" alt="" width="2160" height="1215" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988179" /><br/>
On social media, Partiful <a href="https://x.com/partiful/status/1886827459108331629">shared a screenshot</a> of rule 4.1, which covers copycat apps.<br/>
<blockquote>Come up with your own ideas. We know you have them, so make yours come to life. Don't simply copy the latest popular app on the App Store, or make some minor changes to another app's name or UI and pass it off as your own. In addition to risking an intellectual property infringement claim, it makes the App Store harder to navigate and just isn't fair to your fellow developers.</blockquote><br/>
Partiful is designed to allow users to send customized event invitations with just a few steps, and it has a feature set that is similar to Apple's new Invites app. Partiful still has options that set it apart from Invites, such as better cross-platform functionality. Unlike Invites, Partiful does not require event attendees to enter an email address to confirm their event attendance, and invitations can be created through an app or from the web.<br/>
<br/>
Apple lets invitations be sent to non-Apple users, but an email address is required. Creating an invite is tied to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+ subscription, so it is not free for anyone to use like Partiful.<br/>
<br/>
When Apple creates an app or a feature that has functionality found in a third-party app, it is referred to as sherlocking. The name dates back to a "Sherlock" search tool in OS X that Apple enhanced with features that were cribbed from a third-party app called Watson. Watson's developers accused Apple of copying the product without compensation, and from then on, sherlocking has been used to describe apps that are supplanted by Apple.<br/>
<br/>
There are similarities between Partiful and Invites, but event-focused apps and websites are a popular category and there are services that pre-date Partiful too, like Evite. Checking the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; shows no shortage of popular event planning apps, including Paperless, Invitation Maker, and Punchbowl, in addition to Evite and Partiful, so there is no clear indication that Apple set out to copy Partiful or any app in particular.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-invites/">Apple Invites</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/partiful-apple-invites-app-copycat/">Partiful Calls Apple a Copycat for New Invites App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/partiful-calls-apple-a-copycat-for-new-invites-app.2448774/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing Apple&#039;s New Invites App for Event Planning</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-app-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-apples-new-invites-app-for-event-planning.2448773/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:26:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-app-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today surprised us with a new Invites app, which is designed for planning events like birthday parties, vacations, and baby showers. We checked it out in our latest video to see how it works, what you can use it for, and to demonstrate all of the different features in the app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/o012gSAHW0M" title="New Apple Invites App First Look - Download It Now!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Invites is a standalone app that you can <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-invites/id6472498645">download from the App Store</a>, but it's also got an accompanying <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+ service. You need an &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ subscription to create an invite to an event, but there is no subscription needed to join an event. In fact, you don't even need an Apple device. People without an Apple device can be invited to an event and can join and see event details from a web browser, similar to how &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; works on any device through a browser.<br/>
<br/>
Creating an event is a simple process. You tap on the "+" button, and then there's an interface that walks you through each step. Apple offers a selection of backgrounds to choose from, some of which feature emoji characters and some that are event appropriate with balloons, confetti candy, popcorn, and more. You can also choose a photo from your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app or make an image with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> if you have an Apple Intelligence-capable device.<br/>
<br/>
After selecting a background, you can add an event title, a date and time, a location, and include a description that has information your guests need to know. There are options to set up a Shared Album that all attendees can contribute to during and after the event, plus there is an option to create a collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlist.<br/>
<br/>
When an event is ready to go, you can create a link that you can send out to a group of people through Messages or email. You can also send individual invites with a unique link for each person, though you need to give the app access to your Contacts for that. You can choose to allow anyone with the link to join, or you can turn on approvals so you'll need to greenlight anyone who requests to attend. Event creators can cancel an event at any time, change details, and remove attendees.<br/>
<br/>
If you receive a link to an invite, you'll be able to tap in and choose whether you're able to attend, not attend, or maybe attend. All invitees and the event creator can see who is going to an event, and Apple automatically adds weather information and directions to the event location.<br/>
<br/>
Weather information will be general for events that are several weeks or months out, but will get more specific as the event date approaches. The location listing can be tapped and it will open up in Maps with turn-by-turn directions.<br/>
<br/>
Invite creators can add notes that are sent out to everyone to provide updates on an upcoming event, and the selected playlist can be played from the Invite interface. &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; can be added to shared albums at any time, and will be available to all attendees.<br/>
<br/>
Events are shown in a card-style interface in the Invites app, and you can swipe between both events you've created and events you're attending. The app has sections for past events and for drafts that you've created but haven't sent out yet.<br/>
<br/>
Will you use the Invites app? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-app-hands-on/">Testing Apple&#039;s New Invites App for Event Planning</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-apples-new-invites-app-for-event-planning.2448773/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Raises Monthly AppleCare+ Subscription Price for All iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/applecare-iphone-price-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-raises-monthly-applecare-subscription-price-for-all-iphones.2448772/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:35:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/applecare-iphone-price-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>AppleCare</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week increased the prices for its monthly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ subscription prices for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, raising the cost by 50 cents for all models in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/applecare-apple-care-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1896" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828594" /><br/>
Standard &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models is now priced at &#36;10.49 per month, for example, up from the prior &#36;9.99 per month price. The 50 cent price increase applies to all available &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans for Apple's current &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup, and it includes both the standard plan and the Theft and Loss plan.<br/>
<br/>
The two-year &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ subscription prices have not changed, nor have the service fees and deductibles. The increased prices are only applicable when paying for &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ on a monthly basis.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not raised the prices of &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ subscription plans for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, or Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's price tweak for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ monthly subscriptions come as it prepares to shift &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ purchasing options to subscriptions. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/applecare-plus-policy-change-at-apple-stores/">is phasing out</a> one-time purchase &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plans in retail stores and for on-device purchase as of this week.<br/>
<br/>
In Apple Stores and in the Settings app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, customers who make a purchase will have the option to purchase &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ as a monthly or annual subscription that renews, which eliminates any lapse in coverage and provides Apple with ongoing revenue after a two-year period.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is keeping one-time &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ purchase options available in its online store for the time being, so customers who prefer buy a non-renewing &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ plan that expires at the end of two years can still opt for that.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/applecare-iphone-price-increase/">Apple Raises Monthly AppleCare+ Subscription Price for All iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-raises-monthly-applecare-subscription-price-for-all-iphones.2448772/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches New &#039;Invites&#039; App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-invites-app.2448768/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:00:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Invites</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/02/introducing-apple-invites-a-new-app-that-brings-people-together/">today announced</a> the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-invites/id6472498645">launch of a new app</a> called "Invites," which is designed to allow users to plan events like birthday parties, graduations, vacations, baby showers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/General-Apple-Invites-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988154" /><br/>
<blockquote>"With Apple Invites, an event comes to life from the moment the invitation is created, and users can share lasting memories even after they get together," said Brent Chiu-Watson, Apple's senior director of Worldwide Product Marketing for Apps and iCloud. "Apple Invites brings together capabilities our users already know and love across iPhone, iCloud, and Apple Music, making it easy to plan special events."<br/>
</blockquote>The app supports creating invitations that can be sent out to people. There are options to choose a background image from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, choose one of Apple's built-in images, or select an emoji background, with font customization available. Apple automatically adds in information from the Maps and Weather apps so that invitees have all of the data they need for an event, such as weather conditions and directions. <br/>
<br/>
Apple designed Invites with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> in mind. When creating an invite, there is an option to take advantage of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> to create original images using text-based descriptions. Writing Tools can also be employed to find the ideal phrasing for an invitation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-invites-screenshots.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988149" /><br/>
People who receive invites can RSVP, and there is a built-in method that allows the sender to track who has responded. When the event happens, there's an option to create a collaborative event soundtrack so everyone can contribute music, and a dedicated shared album lets event goers see photos and videos and contribute their own. <br/>
<br/>
Invites is <a href="https://www.apple.com/icloud/">an iCloud+ service</a>, which means that it is available to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+ subscribers. &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ is priced starting at &#36;0.99 per month, and it provides users with additional &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage over the free 5GB that comes with any device.<br/>
<br/>
While anyone is able to respond to an Invite that's sent out, creating invites is limited to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ subscribers. Apple Invites is available for all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models that run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> or later, and the app can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for free. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-invites/id6472498645">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-invites/">Apple Invites</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">Apple Launches New &#039;Invites&#039; App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-invites-app.2448768/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 Hit Lowest Price of the Year So Far at &#36;169 (&#36;80 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/airpods-pro-2-hit-lowest-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-hit-lowest-price-of-the-year-so-far-at-169-80-off.2448764/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:27:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/airpods-pro-2-hit-lowest-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week has Apple's AirPods Pro 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This is the lowest price that we've tracked so far in 2025, and Amazon is providing a mid February delivery estimate for most residences in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895403" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, we saw a better deal over the holiday season, but it's very unlikely that all-time low price will return any time soon. Amazon's price today is still a solid deal on the AirPods Pro 2, which feature USB-C charging and Active Noise Cancellation.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
AirPods discounts are abundant this week on Amazon, which also has the AirPods 4 for just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.99</strong></a> and the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;148.99</strong></a>. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/airpods-pro-2-hit-lowest-price/">AirPods Pro 2 Hit Lowest Price of the Year So Far at &#36;169 (&#36;80 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-hit-lowest-price-of-the-year-so-far-at-169-80-off.2448764/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Apple Invites&#039; Leaked on iCloud Website</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website.2448761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:11:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Invites</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update:</strong> The new Apple Invites app has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">officially been announced</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The main <a href="https://www.icloud.com/">iCloud.com page</a> has seemingly confirmed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/new-icloud-invite-service-report/">Apple's rumored invites tool</a>, which has yet to be officially announced by the company.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/iCloud-General-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-982796" /><br/>
The page says "Apple Invites" will be an iCloud+ feature:<blockquote>Upgrade to iCloud+ to get more storage, plan events with Apple Invites, and have peace of mind with privacy features like iCloud Private Relay, Hide My Email, and HomeKit Secure Video.</blockquote>iCloud+ is essentially Apple's name for paid iCloud storage plans, which start at &#36;0.99 per month in the United States. Apple includes some additional perks with iCloud+ plans at no additional cost, such as iCloud Private Relay and HomeKit Secure Video, and it seems that Apple Invites is the newest perk that is set to be offered.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Invites will be available on the web at iCloud.com/invites, and a new Apple Invites app for the iPhone and other devices is also likely.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Invites will help users to organize birthday parties and other events, according to the page description for iCloud.com/invites:<blockquote>Create online party invitations - for birthdays, graduations, baby showers & more. Track RSVPs, create shared albums, and send instantly by email or text.</blockquote>iCloud+ subscribers will get full access to Apple Invites, with no ads, additional costs, or limits on the amount of events they can host.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Invites will integrate with Apple Music, Apple Maps, Photos, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-Invites.jpg" alt="" width="1286" height="1004" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988130" /><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, Apple Invites could be announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/new-icloud-invite-service-report/">as early as this week</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-invites/">Apple Invites</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website/">&#039;Apple Invites&#039; Leaked on iCloud Website</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website.2448761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple This Month, Including All-New &#039;Invites&#039; App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/what-to-expect-from-apple-this-february/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apple-this-month-including-all-new-invites-app.2448759/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:56:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/what-to-expect-from-apple-this-february/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has yet to announce any new devices this year, but that should change in February. At a minimum, there will be Powerbeats Pro 2 next week, and there is a decent chance that the MacBook Air will be updated this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Calendar-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955995" /><br/>
On the software side, Apple is expected to announce an all-new "Invites" app soon, and the first iOS 18.4 beta should be released this month.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we recap what to expect from Apple in the month of February.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>'Invites' App</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/General-Calendar-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-832026" /><br/>
Last month, <em>9to5Mac</em> discovered iOS 18.3 code references to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/09/apple-working-on-new-invites-app/">potential new "Invites" app from Apple</a>, that would help users to organize meetings and other events. The report said the app would have iCloud integration, meaning that event invites would sync across Apple devices and be available on the web at iCloud.com.<br/>
<br/>
Over the weekend, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2025-02-02/apple-aapl-ai-and-ar-struggles-show-it-has-lost-some-of-its-product-edge"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said</a> the new iCloud-based service is codenamed "Confetti" within Apple. He said it will offer users a "new way to invite people to parties, functions, and meetings."<br/>
<br/>
Apple Invites could be announced as soon as this week, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website/">The name "Apple Invites" has leaked on iCloud.com</a>. The page says Apple Invites will be an iCloud+ feature, with an Apple Invites app likely.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Powerbeats Pro 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/apple-power-beats-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985456" /><br/>
Last year, Apple teased that Powerbeats Pro 2 would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/04/beats-teases-powerbeats-pro-2/">released in 2025</a>. A few days ago, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2025-02-02/apple-aapl-ai-and-ar-struggles-show-it-has-lost-some-of-its-product-edge"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said</a> Apple plans to announce the wireless earbuds on Tuesday, February 11, with U.S. pricing set at &#36;250.<br/>
<br/>
Powerbeats Pro are a sportier, fitness-focused alternative to AirPods Pro with built-in, adjustable ear hooks for a secure fit. According to Gurman, the Powerbeats Pro 2 will feature the same H2 chip as used in the AirPods Pro 2, which will enable improved active noise cancellation compared to the original Powerbeats Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's teaser video last year showed MLB star Shohei Ohtani wearing the Powerbeats Pro 2, revealing a more vertical, slimmer design compared to the original Powerbeats Pro, which launched in 2019 and are now discontinued.<br/>
<br/>
We previously discovered that Powerbeats Pro 2 will offer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/powerbeats-pro-2-heart-rate/">heart rate monitoring during workouts</a>. Based on our iOS 18 code findings, you will be able to connect the Powerbeats Pro 2 to gym equipment like a treadmill to measure heart rate, and the data will be visible in the Health app and other supported apps on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 code also revealed that Powerbeats Pro 2 will be available in four new color options, including a vibrant "Electric Orange."<br/>
<br/>
Based on other recent Beats headphones, other potential upgrades for the Powerbeats Pro 2 over the originals include improved sound quality, longer battery life, and a USB-C port instead of Lightning on the charging case.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New MacBook Air?</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898578" /><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, new MacBook Air models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/">will be announced "earlier" than some other devices</a> rumored to launch this spring, such as the iPhone SE 4 and iPad 11. He has repeatedly said the new MacBook Air models are already in production, so a release as early as February rather than March or April seems possible.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/15/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-rumors/">Likely upgrades</a> for the next 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models include the M4 chip, Thunderbolt 4 ports, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18.4 Beta</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Generic-iOS-18.4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984205" /><br/>
The first iOS 18.4 beta should be released at some point this month.<br/>
<br/>
The software update is expected to introduce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/siri-2025-updates/">several new Apple Intelligence features for Siri</a>, including on-screen awareness, deeper per-app controls, understanding of the user's personal context, and more. Apple Intelligence, which requires an iPhone 15 Pro or any iPhone 16, will also be made available in additional languages.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/24/ios-18-4-beta-coming-soon/">Other new features expected in iOS 18.4</a> include new emoji, the ability to set default map and translation apps in the EU, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's website suggests that iOS 18.4 will be released in April.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/what-to-expect-from-apple-this-february/">What to Expect From Apple This Month, Including All-New &#039;Invites&#039; App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apple-this-month-including-all-new-invites-app.2448759/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Opera Air Brings Meditation and Wellness to Web Browsing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/opera-air-brings-meditation-wellness-web-browsing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/opera-air-brings-meditation-and-wellness-to-web-browsing.2448742/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 02:55:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/opera-air-brings-meditation-wellness-web-browsing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Opera Browser</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Opera has announced <a href="https://www.opera.com/air">Opera Air</a>, a new web browser that integrates mindfulness and wellness features directly into the browsing experience. The browser aims to help users manage stress and maintain focus while navigating the internet.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/opera-air1.jpeg" alt="" width="7680" height="4320" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988087" /><br/>
The Norwegian browser maker has incorporated several science-backed wellness tools into Opera Air, including breathing exercises, meditation sessions, and binaural beats. Users can access these features through two main functions: "Take a Break" and "Boosts."<br/>
<br/>
The "Take a Break" feature offers guided exercises ranging from 3 to 15 minutes, including breathing exercises, meditation, and full body scans. Users can set reminders to take mindful breaks throughout their browsing sessions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/opera-air3.jpeg" alt="" width="7680" height="4320" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988088" /><br/>
Opera Air's "Boosts" feature takes advantage of binaural beats technology, which plays slightly different frequencies in each ear to influence brainwave activity. Users can choose from various preset options like "Creativity Boost," "Energized Focus," and "Deep Relaxation." The feature also allows customization of volume levels, nature sounds, and background music, with sessions lasting from 15 minutes to unlimited duration.<br/>
<br/>
Opera says the browser is designed to maintain its core functionality while introducing these wellness features in a non-disruptive way. Users can continue browsing or working while using features like the "Focused Calm" boost, which uses Alpha 8Hz beats combined with nature sounds to promote concentration.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dHHjOHOtQqY?si=AqPuHLkAD4V8W1CL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
To aid the sense of a calmer browsing environment, Opera Air also features a minimalist Scandinavian design with a frosted glass user interface. Opera Air is available to download today from the <a href="https://www.opera.com/air">company's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/opera-browser/">Opera Browser</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/opera-air-brings-meditation-wellness-web-browsing/">Opera Air Brings Meditation and Wellness to Web Browsing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/opera-air-brings-meditation-and-wellness-to-web-browsing.2448742/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
