<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:04:50 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iCloud &#039;Keep Downloaded&#039; Option Included in iOS 18 and macOS Sequoia</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-ios-18-macos-sequoia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-included-in-ios-18-and-macos-sequoia.2430145/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 04:23:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-ios-18-macos-sequoia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, Apple has added a new "Keep Downloaded" option when browsing items in iCloud, allowing users to designate which files and folders should remain permanently available locally on their device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-15-keep-downloaded.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956964" /><br/>
In previous versions of iOS and macOS, users had limited control over which files and folders were kept offline. iCloud's automatic management system would offload files from the device to free up space, potentially removing files that you might want to keep available at all times. <br/>
<br/>
Apple offered no straightforward way to prevent this – until now. In macOS Sequoia, when browsing iCloud Drive in Finder, right-clicking a file or folder reveals the new "Keep Downloaded" option. When enabled, the cloud symbol next to the item is opaque instead of transparent, indicating that it will remain on the device. <br/>
<br/>
In iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, the same option can be found in the Files app when a file or folder is long pressed to bring up the contextual menu. Users can now explicitly mark files to remain on their device, regardless of how much storage they take up.<br/>
<br/>
The ability to prevent iCloud items from being offloaded should be particularly welcomed by users who need to frequently access documents or files during travel or in areas with poor connectivity. macOS Sequoia, iOS 18, and iPadOS 18 are available in a beta capacity right now, and are limited to developers. The new option should be available to all users when the software launches to the public this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-ios-18-macos-sequoia/">iCloud &#039;Keep Downloaded&#039; Option Included in iOS 18 and macOS Sequoia</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-keep-downloaded-option-included-in-ios-18-and-macos-sequoia.2430145/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Alleged First Look at Apple Watch X / Series 10 With 2-Inch Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10-with-2-inch-display.2430143/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 02:44:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>91Mobiles</category>
		<category>Apple Watch X</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">planning a revamp</a> of the Apple Watch for the device's tenth anniversary, and <em><a href="https://www.91mobiles.com/hub/exclusive-apple-watch-series-10-cad-renders/">91mobiles</a></em> claims to have sourced CAD renders of what could be the "Apple Watch X" or Apple Watch Series 10 from industry insiders.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-watch-x-91mobiles.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956954" /><br/>
The site claims that the renders are of a "larger" model featuring a 2-inch display. The current Apple Watch Series 9 has a 1.7-inch display, while the Apple Watch Ultra has a display size of 1.93-inches, so this would be the biggest screen on an Apple Watch so far.<br/>
<br/>
That said, its dimensions are said to measure roughly 46 x 39.7 x 11.6mm, which would make it bigger overall than the Series 9 but smaller than the Ultra. Otherwise, the renders suggest a design similar to the Series 9, with a Digital Crown and Side button, and a square display.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said a significantly overhauled "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">Apple Watch X</a>" would launch in either 2024 or 2025, to mark the tenth anniversary of the device, so this could be the anniversary device, or it could be the Apple Watch Series 10. The original Apple Watch was announced in September 2014 and released in April 2015. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the "Apple Watch X" would be equipped with a thinner case. The <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter also said it would potentially have a magnetic band attachment system, although there's no evidence of that in the renders. <br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">claimed</a> that Apple Watch Series 10 will be thinner and come in larger screen sizes than previous models. Kuo said the screen size options on the next-generation Apple Watch will increase from 41mm to 45mm, and from 45mm to 49mm, while being encased in a thinner design. For reference, the Apple Watch Ultra has a 49mm case.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear at this point whether the CAD renders are accurate, but either way Apple typically launches new Apple Watch models around September alongside its latest iPhone lineup. Apple is said to be planning to incorporate blood pressure monitoring this year, with the watch able to detect hypertension, while sleep apnea detection is also said to be coming to the 2024 Apple Watch model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/91mobiles-com/">91Mobiles</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10/">Alleged First Look at Apple Watch X / Series 10 With 2-Inch Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10-with-2-inch-display.2430143/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods and Beats Firmware Updates Address Important Security Issue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/airpods-beats-firmware-security-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-and-beats-firmware-updates-address-important-security-issue.2430125/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:43:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/airpods-beats-firmware-security-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106340">release notes</a> for AirPods firmware typically offer few details on included changes, the company has published a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214111">separate support document</a> outlining a security issue that was fixed in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-all-airpods-new-firmware/">today's firmware updates</a> for AirPods, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/powerbeats-pro/">Powerbeats Pro</a>, and Beats Fit Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/AirPods-3-Pro-2-and-Max-New-Firmware.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1408" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891853" /><br/>
According to the document, today's firmware updates address a security issue that could have allowed an attacker within Bluetooth range to spoof the details of a device you've previously connected your headphones to, allowing the attacker to gain access to your headphones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple usually mentions in its support documents if a security issue is known to have been exploited in the wild, but the company has not indicated that this is the case with this issue. Still, it's a good idea to update the firmware on your headphones as soon as possible as others could be inspired to attempt to replicate an exploit of the issue now that its existence has been publicized.<br/>
<br/>
There is no straightforward mechanism for initiating a firmware update for AirPods and Beats headphones, with Apple simply stating that the updates are "automatically delivered while your headphones are paired with and in Bluetooth range of your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac."<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/airpods-beats-firmware-security-issue/">AirPods and Beats Firmware Updates Address Important Security Issue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-and-beats-firmware-updates-address-important-security-issue.2430125/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 RCS Support Rolling Out to Beta Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/ios-18-rcs-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rcs-support-rolling-out-to-beta-users.2430112/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:59:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/ios-18-rcs-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the second beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> that came out yesterday, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2/">added an RCS toggle</a>, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a> messaging was not working at that time. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support appears to now be rolling out, based on reports from &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; users.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-beta-2-rcs-toggle.jpg" alt="" width="2174" height="1223" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956804" /><br/>
Some testers who have &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; installed have confirmed that they are able to send &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; messages to Android users, with &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; features available. Texts that are RCS-based instead of SMS/MMS-based are denoted with an &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; label.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Y'all...! <a href="https://t.co/6NDjmH3WdH">pic.twitter.com/6NDjmH3WdH</a></p>— Snazzy Labs (@SnazzyLabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/SnazzyLabs/status/1805711143484506438?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, or Rich Communication Services, allows <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Android users to exchange higher quality photos and videos, audio messages, and larger file sizes. Features like read receipts and real-time typing indicators are supported too, with a full list of what's new available below.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Support for higher resolution photos and videos.</li><br/>
 	<li>Support for larger file sizes and file sharing.</li><br/>
 	<li>Audio messages.</li><br/>
 	<li>Cross-platform emoji reactions.</li><br/>
 	<li>Real-time typing indicators.</li><br/>
 	<li>Read receipts.</li><br/>
 	<li>Ability to send messages over cellular or Wi-Fi (SMS is cellular only). There is no cost to send an &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; message over Wi-Fi.</li><br/>
 	<li>Improved group chats.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; messages can be enabled in the Messages section of the Settings app, and are toggled on by default. At the current time, &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; messaging is only available to those in the United States who have a carrier that supports &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;. T-Mobile, AT&T, and Verizon users running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; should have the &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; toggle available, but those with MVNOs and smaller carriers will not be able to use the feature yet.<br/>
<br/>
Not all &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; users with T-Mobile, AT&T, and Verizon are seeing &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; enabled, so it appears that support is still rolling out.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is available in a beta capacity right now, and it is limited to developers. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; will be available to all &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; users when the software launches to the public this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/ios-18-rcs-support/">iOS 18 RCS Support Rolling Out to Beta Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rcs-support-rolling-out-to-beta-users.2430112/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI&#039;s ChatGPT App for Mac Now Available to All Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/chatgpt-mac-all-users/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac-now-available-to-all-users.2430106/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:15:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/chatgpt-mac-all-users/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The ChatGPT app for Mac is now available to all users, OpenAI <a href="https://x.com/OpenAI/status/1805679342439284831">announced today</a>. The app first came out in mid-May, but it saw a slow rollout that was limited to ChatGPT Plus subscribers until now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/2chatgpt-mac-app.jpg" alt="" width="2940" height="1912" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951953" /><br/>
OpenAI says that the ChatGPT Mac app is meant to make it easier for users to access ChatGPT and to ask questions about email, screenshots, websites, and content on the Mac. With the ChatGPT app installed, you can press Option + Space on the keyboard to bring up a chat interface for asking ChatGPT a question.<br/>
<br/>
There's a built-in Voice Mode for having voice conversations with ChatGPT, a search feature for looking through past conversations, and more. With the wider rollout, no subscription plan is necessary for using ChatGPT on the Mac. OpenAI has made the latest version of ChatGPT, GPT-4o, available for free, but for a limited number of requests.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The ChatGPT desktop app for macOS is now available for all users.<br><br>Get faster access to ChatGPT to chat about email, screenshots, and anything on your screen with the Option + Space shortcut: <a href="https://t.co/2rEx3PmMqg">https://t.co/2rEx3PmMqg</a> <a href="https://t.co/x9sT8AnjDm">pic.twitter.com/x9sT8AnjDm</a></p>&mdash; OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1805679342439284831?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-chatgpt-mobile-app-background-chat/">How to Speak With ChatGPT in the Background on iPhone</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple has established a partnership with OpenAI that will see ChatGPT integrated into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>. With user permission, Apple's built-in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> personal assistant can hand complicated requests over to ChatGPT, relaying the information to the user.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/chatgpt-mac-all-users/">OpenAI&#039;s ChatGPT App for Mac Now Available to All Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openais-chatgpt-app-for-mac-now-available-to-all-users.2430106/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods, AirPods Pro, AirPods Max and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-all-airpods-new-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-airpods-pro-airpods-max-and-more.2430102/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:35:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-all-airpods-new-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware update for several products, including the Lightning and USB-C versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, the first-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, the second and third-generation AirPods, the Beats Fit Pro, and the PowerBeats Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
The second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; models, the PowerBeats Pro, and the Beats Fit Pro now have firmware version 6F8, up from 6F7, while the other models have firmware version 6A326, up from 6A321.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not often provide details on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware beyond "bug fixes and other improvements," so it is unclear what's new in the update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't offer instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ or Beats in the case, connecting to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods or Beats‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌AirPods‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌AirPods to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the firmware release, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-all-airpods-new-firmware/">Apple Releases New Firmware for AirPods, AirPods Pro, AirPods Max and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-airpods-airpods-pro-airpods-max-and-more.2430102/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch SE and Apple Watch Ultra 2 Available for Low Prices on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-watch-se-ultra-2-amazon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-and-apple-watch-ultra-2-available-for-low-prices-on-amazon.2430093/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:37:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-watch-se-ultra-2-amazon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week has a collection of discounts on the Apple Watch SE and Apple Watch Ultra 2, providing near all-time low prices on both of these wearables.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-se-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952115" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is just &#36;10 higher compared to the all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's also available in all three aluminum colors.<br/>
<br/>
This model of the Apple Watch SE launched in September 2022 and remains Apple's most affordable Apple Watch. The Apple Watch SE lacks some of the upgraded features you'll find in some Series 9 or Ultra 2 models, like temperature sensing and ECG functionality, but it will otherwise provide you with all key Apple Watch features, and at the cheapest price possible.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ultra-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952114" /><br/>
<br/>
Finally, we're also tracking a solid deal on one model of the Apple Watch Ultra 2. You can get the model with the Indigo Alpine Loop (Small) for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;714.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;799.00. While this is the only model at &#36;714.00, Amazon also has a bigger collection of Ultra 2 models at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWZ5VVM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;719.00</strong></a>, a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Indigo Alpine Loop) for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWZ5VVM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Blue Ocean Band) for &#36;719.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-watch-se-ultra-2-amazon/">Apple Watch SE and Apple Watch Ultra 2 Available for Low Prices on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-and-apple-watch-ultra-2-available-for-low-prices-on-amazon.2430093/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tap to Pay on iPhone Now Available in Germany</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-germany/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-germany.2430091/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:45:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-germany/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Germany</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/de/newsroom/2024/06/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-germany/">today announced</a> that Tap to Pay on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is available in Germany, providing a way for independent sellers, small businesses, and larger merchants in the country to use an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a contactless payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/tap-to-pay-iphone-germany.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956919" /><br/>
Retailers can take advantage of the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to accept credit and debit card payments, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, and other tap-based payment methods. Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; works similarly to hardware-based payment systems like the Square Reader, but it does not require additional hardware to work.<br/>
<br/>
When a customer makes a purchase, a merchant that supports Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can accept a payment by having the customer bring a credit card, debit card, prepaid card, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple Watch, or other digital wallet close to the merchant's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The transaction is completed through NFC, with processing done using the Secure Element for security purposes.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is available to payment platforms and payment app developers in Germany. Adyen, Commerz Globalpay, myPOS, Nexi, SumUp, and Viva support Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; starting today, with mollie, PAYONE, Revolut, Sparkassen-Finanzgruppe, and Stripe set to implement support later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
Since Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; first launched in the United States in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/08/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-iphone-feature/">February 2022</a>, Apple has been working to expand it to additional countries. It is now available in 12 countries, including United States, United Kingdom, Canada, Australia, Japan, the Netherlands, Brazil, Italy, France, Taiwan, Ukraine, and Germany.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is compatible with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS and newer, so iPhones manufactured since September 2018 can use it. Tap to Pay also requires a contactless card or device, and it is compatible with cards from American Express, Global Discover Network, Diners, Mastercard, and Visa.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/germany/">Germany</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-germany/">Tap to Pay on iPhone Now Available in Germany</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-germany.2430091/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 60+ Upgrades to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-60-upgrades-to-expect.2430076/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:18:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro&#038;post_date=1719339538/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 13 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> is set to succeed 2023's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">over 25 new features</a> and improvements to Apple's high-end smartphones. With many users adopting three-year upgrade cycles, plenty of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> Pro owners will be looking to upgrade to the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; later this year, so this guide breaks down every major difference you should be aware of between the two generations based on rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-13-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956610" /></div><br/>
The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj;‌ Pro debuted in 2021, introducing a brighter display with ProMotion technology for refresh rates up to 120Hz, the A15 Bionic chip, a telephoto camera with 3x optical zoom, macro photography and photographic styles, Cinematic mode for recording videos with shallow depth of field, ProRes video recording, a 1TB storage option, and up to five hours of additional battery life. Three years later, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to offer over 60 upgrades. All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their 2021 predecessors are listed below, using information from reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">previously covered</a>. We will update this article as more rumors emerge in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
The design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to be a relatively significant evolution over the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro, iterating on the titanium frame and slightly rounded edges introduced on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models last year. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Surgical-grade stainless steel chassis with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Aerospace-grade titanium chassis with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Thermal design with copper heatsink and black foil battery casing</td><br/>
 <td>New thermal design with graphene heatsink and metal battery casing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More repairable design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Alpine Green, Silver, Gold, Graphite, and Sierra Blue color options</td><br/>
 <td>Black Titanium, White Titanium, Desert Titanium, and Titanium Gray color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="dimensions">Dimensions</h3><br/>
To accommodate larger displays, both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to grow in height and width. In addition to last year's increase in depth, the devices are due to be considerably larger, but with a notable reduction in weight thanks to the adoption of a titanium frame. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7.85mm depth</td><br/>
 <td>8.25mm depth (0.4mm thicker)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 146.7mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 160.8mm height</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 149.6mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 163.0mm height</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 71.5mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 78.1mm width</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 71.45mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 77.58mm width</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 204g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 238g weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 194g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 225g weight</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="displays">Displays</h2><br/>
Both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature larger displays than their predecessors, pushing the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max to be the biggest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> ever offered. There are also reportedly improvements to the underlying OLED technology in store, in addition to last year's slimmer bezels, making for a noticeable overall display upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6.1- or 6.7-inch display</td><br/>
 <td>6.3- or 6.9-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Notch" TrueDepth camera array</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Always-On Display</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Slimmer borders around the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 1,000 nits typical max brightness<br/>
Up to 1,200 nits peak HDR brightness</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 1,200 nits typical SDR brightness<br/>
Up to 1,600 nits peak HDR brightness</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="performance">Performance</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to bring notable improvements in processing power, including a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> Apple silicon chip and 33% more memory.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N5P" 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 Pro chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support Apple Intelligence</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated AV1 decoder</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="connectivity">Connectivity</h2><br/>
Connectivity is also due to get a significant upgrade on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, bolstering the device's 5G, Wi-Fi, Thread, and Ultra Wideband specifications.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X60 5G modem</td><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X75 5G modem</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 7 connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thread networking technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="cameras">Cameras</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are slated to receive a range of substantial camera enhancements, such as a larger main camera sensor, a 48-megapixel sensor on the ultra wide camera, and a dedicated hardware button for photography and videography on the side of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>"Capture Button" to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel main camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel main camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Photonic Engine for better low light performance</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1/1.65-inch main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro‌</strong>: 1/1.28-inch main camera sensor<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max</strong>: 1/1.14-inch main camera sensor (12% larger)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Sony IMX-703 main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: Sony IMX-803 main camera sensor<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: Sony IMX-903 main camera sensor with stacked design for better performance, a 14-bit Analog-to-Digital Converter (ADC) for high-quality image data conversion, and Digital Gain Control (DCG) for better dynamic range and noise control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7P main camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>8P main camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with sensor-shift optical image stabilization</td><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, optical image stabilization, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>77mm maximum focal length</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 120mm maximum focal length<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: "Super" telephoto camera with focal length above 300mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>5P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel ultra wide camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel ultra wide camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>6P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anti-reflective coating on camera lenses</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 3x optical zoom</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 5x optical zoom</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>13mm, 24mm, 28mm, 35mm, and 120mm focal length picker</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 3</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Shoot and instantly transfer 48-megapixel ProRAW images to Mac via USB 3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record video directly to an external drive</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 30 fps</td><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 60 fps with external recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Log video recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Academy Color Encoding System</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record spatial video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Action mode for improved video stabilization</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting bigger, denser batteries and faster charging capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Setting to prevent charging above 80%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Battery manufacture date, first use, and cycle count information in Settings</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 3,095 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 4,352 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 3,355 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 4,676 mAh battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 20W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models will also offer support for Apple Intelligence, Apple's new suite of personal AI features, later this year, as well as satellite connectivity, Crash Detection, and more storage.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Apple Intelligence</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Emergency SOS via Satellite</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance, designed to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Crash Detection</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning connector with USB 2 transfer speeds (up to 480Mb/s)</td><br/>
 <td>USB 3 transfer speeds (up to 10Gb/s, 20x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>DisplayPort support for up to 4K HDR video output</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 2TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is expected to launch in the fall. Apple usually hosts an event every September to unveil new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, with launch following just over a week later. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; was a fairly significant upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro, introducing a vast array of significant features including a titanium chassis, much slimmer bezels, the Action, and a USB-C port. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will build on these upgrades, offering larger displays, the Capture button, improved cameras, and Apple Intelligence support. With over 60 upgrades likely to be in store, many &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro users will find upgrading to an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; model worthwhile.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro/">iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 60+ Upgrades to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-60-upgrades-to-expect.2430076/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Lets You Customize AirPods Audio in System Settings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/macos-sequoia-headphone-accommodations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-lets-you-customize-airpods-audio-in-system-settings.2430065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:49:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/macos-sequoia-headphone-accommodations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[macOS Sequoia expands a long-existing accessibility feature on the iPhone and iPad to the Mac: Headphone Accommodations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Headphone-Accommodations.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956910" /><br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-2/">macOS Sequoia beta</a>, the Headphone Accommodations options are in the System Settings app under Accessibility → Audio. The settings allow you to customize the audio for all AirPods and select Beats headphones. For example, Apple says you can amplify soft sounds and adjust certain frequencies to help music, phone calls, and more sound more crisp.<br/>
<br/>
When a user configures Headphone Accommodations settings for second-generation AirPods Pro on macOS, the adjusted audio will persist when the headphones are connected to other audio sources, according to <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/macos-release-notes/macos-15-release-notes#Headphone-Accommodations">a note on Apple's developer website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
These settings were previously only available in the Settings app on the iPhone and iPad.<br/>
<br/>
macOS Sequoia is currently in beta for developers, with a public beta to follow in July. The update will likely be widely released in September or October.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/macos-sequoia-headphone-accommodations/">macOS Sequoia Lets You Customize AirPods Audio in System Settings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-lets-you-customize-airpods-audio-in-system-settings.2430065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Pill Bluetooth Speaker Makes a Comeback With Improved Sound, Water Resistance, and a Lower Price Tag</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-makes-a-comeback-with-improved-sound-water-resistance-and-a-lower-price-tag.2430052/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Launched in 2012 before Beats was acquired by Apple, the original Beats Pill shook up the portable Bluetooth speaker category with fun colors and well-regarded sound quality. The speaker got an upgrade in 2015 with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/10/07/apple-debuts-beats-pill-plus-speaker/">launch of the Pill+</a> under Apple's ownership, but over time it appeared to become an afterthought for Beats compared to headphones and earphones, and the Pill+ was eventually <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">discontinued in early 2022</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xtZmgIdQFDA" title="NEW Beats Pill: Beats Finally Brought it Back!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
After <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">several months of teasing</a>, Beats is officially announcing the <a href="https://www.beatsbydre.com/speakers/beats-pill">return of the Beats Pill</a> today with a host of upgrades and a lower price point of &#36;149.99. The new Pill features a completely redesigned speaker system consisting of a single tweeter and a single racetrack woofer, a removable lanyard, USB-C and Bluetooth connectivity, 24 hours of battery life, and IP67 water and sweat resistance.<br/>
<br/>
Available in Matte Black, Champagne Gold, and Statement Red color options, the new Beats Pill features a soft-touch silicone housing with a metal speaker grille and a Beats "b" logo, with several subtle physical buttons along the top for on-device controls. The new removable lanyard slips easily around the wrist to help secure it while being carried or even to let the speaker dangle from, although it can't be tightened up for additional security.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-pill-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956811" /><br/>
Compared to the previous Pill+, the reengineered single racetrack woofer in the Beats Pill uses stronger neodymium magnets to drive 28% more motor force, allowing the woofer to displace 90% more air volume, while radial ribbing around the edges minimizes low-end distortion. The new Pill also moves from dual tweeters to a redesigned single tweeter in its own housing for extra stability and to similarly reduce distortion. Both speakers are aligned to give the Pill a 20º inclined tilt, which provides better sound projection with less reflected sound.<br/>
<br/>
If you have two Beats Pill speakers, you can pair them up in either Amplify Mode, which gives you bigger overall sound for larger spaces, or Stereo Mode, which separates the sound output into left and right channels sent to the different speakers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-pill-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956812" /><br/>
The Beats Pill can serve as a speakerphone for your connected devices, with a noise-learning algorithm that suppresses ambient sound to target the user's voice, and full duplex support helps ensure your conversations are intelligible to both sides. Voice assistant support for connected devices is also include, so you can activate <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> or Google Assistant with the press of a button.<br/>
<br/>
USB-C comes to the Beats Pill for the first time, allowing for lossless audio over a wired connection, easy recharging, and the ability to charge other devices from the Pill's internal battery. The Pill itself has up to 24 hours of battery life, and a 10-minute Fast Fuel delivers up to two hours of playback. A black USB-C to USB-C cable is included in the box.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-pill-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956813" /><br/>
The new Pill has four buttons along the top edge, a Power button, a Center button, and Volume Up/Down buttons. Each of the buttons serves multiple purposes, so you can control a fair amount of features without needing to dig into your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. A press of the Power button turns the speaker on or off, while a brief tap lights up an adjacent LED for battery status, a double tap activates &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, and a triple tap reverses the charging direction when connected via USB-C. Pressing and holding the Power button while plugging the Pill in via USB-C activates wired audio input.<br/>
<br/>
The Center button is for your usual media controls, with a single press playing or pausing your audio, a double press skipping forward, and a triple press skipping backward. The Center button is also used in combination with the Volume Up/Down buttons to configure the paired speaker modes. Holding the Center buttons on two speakers activates Amplify Mode, and holding Center and Volume Up on one of them then activates Stereo Mode with that speaker becoming the left channel. The same combination returns to Amplify Mode or holding Center and Volume Down can be used to break the speaker group entirely.<br/>
<br/>
A proprietary chip platform from Beats offers seamless access across both Apple and Android platforms, with one-touch pairing, automatic setup across all devices connected to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> or Google account, and support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> and &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; Device tracking based on the speaker's last connected location.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-pill-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956814" /><br/>
The new Pill does have some heft, weighing in at 24 ounces (~680 grams), although that is 10% lighter than the Pill+. It measures a little over 8.5 inches (~22 cm) long by 2.8 inches (~7 cm) deep and high, just fractionally larger than the Pill+. It's certainly portable and you can easily toss it in a bag, but you're not going to want to carry it in your hand wherever you go.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.beatsbydre.com/speakers/beats-pill">revamped Beats Pill</a> is priced at &#36;149.99 and is available to order today in all three colors, with shipping beginning this Thursday, June 27.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">Beats Pill Bluetooth Speaker Makes a Comeback With Improved Sound, Water Resistance, and a Lower Price Tag</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-makes-a-comeback-with-improved-sound-water-resistance-and-a-lower-price-tag.2430052/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Day 2024 Will Run July 16-17</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/amazon-prime-day-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-2024-will-run-july-16-17.2430047/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 06:34:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/amazon-prime-day-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today <a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/retail/amazon-prime-day-2024-date">announced</a> that its annual <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimeday%2F">Prime Day sale event</a> will take place beginning Tuesday, July 16 and run through Wednesday, July 17. Amazon began Prime Day back in 2015, and since 2019 the event has been running for two days straight every summer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/amazon-prime-day-2024.jpg" alt="" width="2406" height="1352" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956893" /><br/>
Shoppers can expect massive discounts on an array of products, including Apple devices. Some deals will last the entire run of the sale, but there will also be lightning deals that drop every 30 minutes and last for select periods, or until they sell out.<br/>
<br/>
To get in on these Prime Day deals, you will need to be an Amazon Prime member. If you aren't, you can <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Fref%3Dst_wlp_opt_out%26ms3_c%3Dbe84addb4094c3d3fdf3ade361e920a0"><strong>join Prime</strong></a> to participate in this year's Prime Day. Once your initial free trial is over, Prime membership will run for &#36;14.99/month or &#36;139/year. For students, that's &#36;7.49/month or &#36;69/year, with a six month free trial for new students.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimeday%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EARLY DEALS</div>Amazon Prime Day 2024</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is already <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimeday%2F">highlighting early Prime Day deals</a> that you can shop now, weeks ahead of the event. For now, this mainly includes Amazon devices like Kindles, Echo Dot, Fire TVs, and other Amazon branded products.<br/>
<br/>
Once Prime Day kicks off, Amazon's website will be filled with lightning deals on everything from tech products to home appliances, clothing, toys, and much more. We'll be covering all of the best deals you can get throughout Prime Day, particularly on all of the Apple products that appear, so be sure to keep an eye on the MacRumors front page starting July 16.<br/>
<br/>
Prime Day discounts will be available to Amazon Prime members in Australia, Austria, Belgium, Brazil, Canada, Egypt, France, Germany, Italy, Japan, Luxembourg, Mexico, the Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Saudi Arabia, Singapore, Spain, Sweden, Turkey, the United Arab Emirates, the United States, and the United Kingdom.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon held two Prime Day events last year, one in July and a second in October. Given that we're only now hearing about the July event, we don't know yet if the retailer will again host a second Prime Day, which it called "Prime Big Deal Days," in the fall. If and when that is announced, you can also expect us to cover all of the deals that come out.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/amazon-prime-day-2024/">Amazon Prime Day 2024 Will Run July 16-17</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-2024-will-run-july-16-17.2430047/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Supplier Unveils &#039;Industry First&#039; Tandem OLED Laptop Panel</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/lg-display-making-tandem-oled-laptop-panels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-supplier-unveils-industry-first-tandem-oled-laptop-panel.2430041/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 05:31:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/lg-display-making-tandem-oled-laptop-panels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>LG Display</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OLED <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> panel maker LG Display has begun mass producing the industry's first 13-inch tandem OLED panel designed for laptops, the Korean company announced this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/lg-display-tandem-oled-laptop.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956859" /><br/>
LG Display supplies the majority of OLED panels for Apple's latest M4 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, which use a similar tandem structure. Tandem OLED panels combine two stacks of red, green, and blue (RGB) organic light emitting layers, which together offer better durability and performance compared to single-layer OLED panels such as the one used in Apple's iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
 LG has been developing the panels for the automotive industry since 2019, and says that efficiency gains mean they reduce power consumption by up to 40%, and enable up to three times the brightness. By designing the components and enhancing the structure of the 13-inch tandem OLED panel, LG Display says it has also been able to make it around 40% thinner and 28% lighter than existing OLED laptop screens, allowing for a sleek design and greater portability. <br/>
<br/>
From LG Display's <a href="https://news.lgdisplay.com/en/2024/06/lg-display-starts-mass-production-of-industrys-first-tandem-oled-for-laptops/">press release</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>The new panel combines convenience and performance with high definition. It boasts a WQXGA+ (2880×1800) high resolution and accurate color expression that meets 100% of the DCI-P3 standard color area established by the Digital Cinema Initiatives (DCI), allowing high-definition content to be presented with increased clarity.<br/>
<br/>
With OLED's characteristic self-emissive pixels and infinite contrast ratio, it has also been certified as Display HDR (High Dynamic Range) True Black 500 by the Video Electronics Standards Association (VESA). This confirms its ability to show both bright and dark images so well that it enhances their three-dimensionality and produces a display quality that is as close as possible to what the human eye naturally sees.</blockquote>There are currently no Macs with OLED displays. However, according to a November 2023 report by analyst Jeff Pu of Haitong International Technology Research, Apple is actively developing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/ipad-pro-macbook-pro-macbook-air-oled-launches/">OLED screen for the ‌MacBook Air</a>‌, although the release of an OLED MacBook Pro is expected to come first.<br/>
<br/>
An earlier report by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> claimed that a new MacBook Pro with an OLED display could be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/11/touchscreen-macs-report/">first touchscreen Mac in 2025</a>. Notably LG Display says that it has also embedded a touch sensor inside its latest tandem OLED panels to improve touch performance.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg-display/">LG Display</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/lg-display-making-tandem-oled-laptop-panels/">Apple Supplier Unveils &#039;Industry First&#039; Tandem OLED Laptop Panel</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-supplier-unveils-industry-first-tandem-oled-laptop-panel.2430041/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS 15 No Longer Needs Twice the Free Space for App Store Installs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/macos-15-app-store-no-more-double-space-installs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-15-no-longer-needs-twice-the-free-space-for-app-store-installs.2430025/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:24:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/macos-15-app-store-no-more-double-space-installs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>Mac App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with macOS Sequoia, app downloads and installations from the Mac App Store will no longer require double the amount of local storage space available. Instead, the free space requirement now matches the final install size of the app, plus a small buffer, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Mac-App-Store-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800078" /><br/>
The new space requirement in macOS 15 should significantly benefit users who download large games. Currently in macOS Sonoma, users have to ensure they have double the space available, which is often a challenge for games that can take up tens or even hundreds of gigabytes.<br/>
<br/>
But in macOS 15 beta 2, you only need to have enough space for the game's final size, plus the small buffer, as per the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/macos-release-notes/macos-15-release-notes">release notes</a>. By aligning the free space requirements more closely with actual app sizes, macOS 15 should give users a better idea ahead of time of whether they can install an app from the Mac App Store, which will make general storage management easier. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has told developers to update any messaging related to app size requirements to reflect the change, which should reduce confusion about how much free space is needed for new app installations. macOS Sequoia is currently in its second developer beta, with a public beta expected in July, followed by a general release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/macos-15-app-store-no-more-double-space-installs/">macOS 15 No Longer Needs Twice the Free Space for App Store Installs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-15-no-longer-needs-twice-the-free-space-for-app-store-installs.2430025/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pauses Work on Planned North Carolina Campus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-north-carolina-campus-paused/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pauses-work-on-planned-north-carolina-campus.2430005/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:58:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-north-carolina-campus-paused/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is delaying plans for a major new campus located in North Carolina, reports the <em><a href="https://www.bizjournals.com/triangle/news/2024/05/20/apple-rtp-jobs-north-carolina-construction-campus.html">Triangle Business Journal</a></em>. Back in 2021, Apple said it would invest more than &#36;1 billion in North Carolina, a project that included a new engineering and research center in the Research Triangle area of Raleigh and Durham.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-722008" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/12/apple_rtp_land.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><em>Assemblage of seven properties in Research Triangle Park owned by Apple</em></div><br/>
A limited amount of progress on the campus has been made since the announcement, and Apple has not provided updates on construction until now. Apple told <em>Triangle Business Journal</em> that it has paused work on the campus, and it is working with North Carolina Governor Roy Cooper and the North Carolina Department of Commerce to extend the project's timeline by four years.<br/>
<br/>
No reason was given for the delay, but Apple said that it is still committed to building in North Carolina.<br/>
<blockquote>Apple has been operating in North Carolina for over two decades. And we're deeply committed to growing our teams here. In the last three years, we've added more than 600 people to our team in Raleigh, and we're looking forward to developing our new campus in the coming years.</blockquote><br/>
Apple last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/30/apple-north-carolina-campus-first-phase/">filed development plans</a> for the first phase of construction, but the specific timeline for the project has never been clear. Apple's plans for Research Triangle Park include six buildings and a parking garage totaling 700,000 square feet of office space, 190,000 square feet of accessory space, and close to 3,000 parking spaces spanning 41 acres.<br/>
<br/>
Apple owns 281 acres of land in the area where it plans to build its campus, so there could ultimately be several phases of construction. As it prepares to build the NC research center, Apple is leasing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/07/29/apple-metlife-campus-nc/">more than 200,000 square feet</a> of office space in Cary, North Carolina.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-north-carolina-campus-paused/">Apple Pauses Work on Planned North Carolina Campus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pauses-work-on-planned-north-carolina-campus.2430005/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wasn&#039;t Interested in AI Partnership With Meta Due to Privacy Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-meta-ai-privacy-concerns/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wasnt-interested-in-ai-partnership-with-meta-due-to-privacy-concerns.2430002/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:27:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-meta-ai-privacy-concerns/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple turned down an AI partnership with Facebook parent company Meta due to privacy concerns, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-06-24/apple-spurned-idea-of-iphone-ai-partnership-with-meta-months-ago">Bloomberg</a></em>. Meta and Apple had a brief discussion about a possible partnership in March, but the talks did not progress and Apple does not plan to integrate Meta's large language model (LLM) into iOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956714" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/meta-ai.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="608" /><br/>
<br/>
Over the weekend, <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em> suggested that Apple and Meta <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-meta-talks-ai-model-ios-18/">were in active discussions</a> about integrating Llama, Facebook's LLM, into <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> as part of Apple Intelligence. The report suggested that the discussions were ongoing had not been finalized, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s follow-up indicates Apple never seriously considered a partnership.<br/>
<br/>
Preliminary talks happened at the same time that Apple began discussions with OpenAI and Google parent company Alphabet, but Apple decided not to move on to a more formal discussion because "it doesn't see that company's privacy practices as stringent enough."<br/>
<br/>
Apple did end up signing a deal with OpenAI, and ChatGPT will be integrated into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>. Users can opt-in to ChatGPT, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> able to hand some requests off to the more sophisticated AI model. Apple is also working on a deal with Google to integrate Gemini into its operating systems, and it is holding discussions with AI company Anthropic.<br/>
<br/>
At WWDC, Apple software engineering chief Craig Federighi said that Apple wants to provide users with a choice between different AI models, with the company planning to establish deals with multiple providers.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-meta-ai-privacy-concerns/">Apple Wasn&#039;t Interested in AI Partnership With Meta Due to Privacy Concerns</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wasnt-interested-in-ai-partnership-with-meta-due-to-privacy-concerns.2430002/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 197 With macOS Sequoia Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-197/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-197-with-macos-sequoia-support.2430001/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:11:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-197/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 197 includes fixes and updates for Canvas, CSS, Forms, JavaScript, Media, Rendering, Security, SVG, Web Inspector, WebDriver, and WebGL.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta, the newest version of macOS that Apple is beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-197/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 197 With macOS Sequoia Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-197-with-macos-sequoia-support.2430001/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Efforts to Automate iPhone Assembly Detailed in New Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-automating-iphone-assembly-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-efforts-to-automate-iphone-assembly-detailed-in-new-report.2429997/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-automating-iphone-assembly-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Foxconn</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-sets-bold-new-goals-for-automating-iphone-factories"><em>The Information</em> today reported</a> that shortly after COVID-19-related lockdowns and protests in China <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/06/apple-warns-of-lower-iphone-14-pro-shipments/">impacted iPhone assembler Foxconn</a> in late 2022, Apple's senior vice president of operations Sabih Khan instructed managers to reduce the number of workers on iPhone assembly lines by as much as 50% over the following few years.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-Assembly.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956778" /><br/>
To achieve this goal, Apple allegedly began approving high-cost automation projects for iPhone assembly that it previously shied away from. The report claims these efforts resulted in a "significant amount" of automation being involved for iPhone 15 production, but automation has still posed challenges for Apple due to manufacturing complexities.<br/>
<br/>
For example, the report claims that Apple had to cancel some automation processes for the iPhone 16 series due to a "high rate of defects":<blockquote>This year, Apple sought to build on some of its automation successes by using machines to install the iPhone's buttons, receiver, speaker and main logic board into its chassis, according to three people who worked in Apple's supply chain. But the machines stumbled in properly fastening those components, which have to be carefully screwed into position at odd angles, the people said.</blockquote>Apple's push for automation could allow it to move even more iPhone assembly to countries outside of China, such as India, Vietnam, and Thailand, as part of the company's efforts to diversify its supply chain in Southeast Asia.<br/>
<br/>
More details can be found in <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-sets-bold-new-goals-for-automating-iphone-factories"><em>The Information</em>'s report</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foxconn/">Foxconn</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-automating-iphone-assembly-report/">Apple&#039;s Efforts to Automate iPhone Assembly Detailed in New Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-efforts-to-automate-iphone-assembly-detailed-in-new-report.2429997/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything New in iOS 18 Beta 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2.2429989/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:52:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second betas of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> to developers, and the software adds support for new features that Apple is working on, plus it tweaks some of the interface changes that have been made in the updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-on-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955605" /><br/>
Apple will refine &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; over the course of the next few months, with multiple changes and refinements expected from now until September. We've highlighted everything new in the second &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone Mirroring</h2><br/>
When paired with a Mac running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta 2, &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta 2 supports the Mac-based <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring feature. With &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, you can control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; using your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring can be enabled by clicking on the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring icon on a Mac and following the instructions. It lets you open and use apps, manage notifications, and more, all while your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>RCS Toggle</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; beta 2 adds a toggle for the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a> messaging protocol that will replace SMS and MMS, but &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; is not yet functional. Right now, the &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; toggle only shows up for U.S. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users who have a carrier that supports &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, which includes T-Mobile, Verizon, and AT&amp;T.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-beta-2-rcs-toggle.jpg" alt="" width="2174" height="1223" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956804" /><br/>
&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; will improve text messaging conversations with Android users, allowing for higher-quality images and videos, read receipts, typing indicators, Tapback support, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Home Screen</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> icon on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> now has a dark mode, which changes the background color of the app. There's also a wallpaper tinting toggle that can be used in automatic mode, something that wasn't an option before. The toggle makes the wallpaper you've chosen darker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/app-store-dark-mode-icon.jpg" alt="" width="1460" height="821" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956805" /><br/>
For some icons, the second beta improves the contrast of the tint feature by adding more dark areas.<br/>
<br/>
Note that tinting and icon color changes seem to be quite buggy in beta 2, and sometimes tints won't deactivate until the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is restarted.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Widgets</h2><br/>
There's a new Connected Card Wallet widget app, but it does not appear to be functional as of yet. Connected Cards integrate with the Wallet app to display total card balance and transaction history. In the United States, this feature only works with Discover at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-wallet-app-connected-cards.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956806" /><br/>
<h2>Passwords App</h2><br/>
There's a "+" button in the main view of the Passwords app when you open it, so you can add a new item without having to tap the "All" icon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ios-18-passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956809" /><br/>
<h2>Control Center</h2><br/>
The power button in the Control Center has a more pronounced haptic feel when pressing it, and it only triggers with a press rather than just a tap. The change will prevent the power button from accidentally being activated when using Control Center.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>EU App Ecosystem Changes</h2><br/>
In the European Union, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/ipados-18-beta-2-includes-eu-changes/">iPadOS 18 beta adds support</a> for alternative app marketplaces and downloading apps from websites. These are the same changes that Apple made to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in iOS 17.4, with the updates now extended to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> as required by the European Commission.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
<h2>More New Changes</h2><br/>
Know of a new feature in beta 2 that we left out? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2/">Everything New in iOS 18 Beta 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2.2429989/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Beta 2 Adds Support for iPhone Mirroring</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/macos-sequoia-beta-2-iphone-mirroring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-beta-2-adds-support-for-iphone-mirroring.2429982/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:42:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/macos-sequoia-beta-2-iphone-mirroring/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the second developer beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, Apple has added support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, one of the main updates coming to the Mac. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring is a Continuity feature that lets you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
When you're signed in to the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> on a Mac and an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, you can use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring to interact with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; even when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is locked. You can open up and use apps, deal with notifications, send messages, and more.<br/>
<br/>
You can use your Mac keyboard, trackpad, or mouse with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which is useful for typing up long emails and other documents on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and it provides an easy way to keep up with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications without having to pull out your device and check it. When you click on a notification on your Mac when using &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, it is supposed to open up right into the app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Though it isn't enabled in this beta, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring will eventually allow files, photos, and videos to be dragged and dropped between your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac and vice versa. Apple plans to add that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring feature later in 2024, and it won't be available when &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; first launches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iphone-screen-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2501" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956795" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring requires an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> beta 2 and a Mac running &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; beta 2, and it is accessible using the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring icon in the Dock. It works on Macs that have an Apple silicon chip or a T2 Security Chip, and you'll need to have the devices near each other with Bluetooth and Wi-Fi and you'll need to be signed in to the same &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; with two-factor authentication turned on. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring can't be used when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sidecar/">Sidecar</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> are activated.<br/>
<br/>
Today's second beta also adds &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> support for remote control when using the SharePlay screen sharing feature. This option allows you to ask for permission to control someone's device remotely so that you can provide more direct technical assistance for problem solving.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; and &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; betas are only available to developers right now, but Apple plans to release a public beta in July that will allow anyone to try out the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring feature before it launches. The updates will see a public release this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/macos-sequoia-beta-2-iphone-mirroring/">macOS Sequoia Beta 2 Adds Support for iPhone Mirroring</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-beta-2-adds-support-for-iphone-mirroring.2429982/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
