<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:01:00 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple&#039;s Quarterly Earnings Report This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-q3-2024-earnings-preview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-quarterly-earnings-report-this-week.2432616/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:38:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-q3-2024-earnings-preview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will report its earnings results for the third quarter of its 2024 fiscal year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/aapl-q3-2024-earnings-report-date/">on Thursday, August 1</a> at 1:30 p.m. Pacific Time. Apple's CEO Tim Cook and CFO Luca Maestri will discuss the results on a conference call with analysts a half hour later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-iPad-Air-and-iPad-Pro-11-inch-and-13-inch-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949648" /><br/>
Keep reading for some key things to know about the quarter, including a recap of new products announced, revenue expectations, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Products During Quarter</h2><br/>
The quarter ran from March 31 through June 29, according to Apple's fiscal calendar. The following products launched during this period:<ul><li>11-inch iPad Pro with M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>13-inch iPad Pro with M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>11-inch iPad Air with M2 chip</li><br/>
<li>13-inch iPad Air with M2 chip</li><br/>
<li>Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li>Vision Pro pre-orders in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/vision-pro-launching-in-more-countries/">eight additional countries</a></li></ul><h2>Revenue Expectations</h2><br/>
Apple has not provided formal revenue guidance since before the COVID-19 pandemic, but the average Wall Street estimate for Apple's third quarter revenue is &#36;84.5 billion, according to data compiled by <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/AAPL/analysis/"><em>Yahoo Finance</em></a>. This would be around a 3% increase over the &#36;81.8 billion revenue the company reported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/03/apple-3q-2023-results/">in the year-ago quarter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This would be in line with the outlook that Apple's CFO provided on last quarter's earnings call:<blockquote>We expect our June quarter total company revenue to grow low-single-digits year-over-year in spite of a foreign exchange headwind of about 2.5 percentage points.</blockquote><h2>Conference Call</h2><br/>
Cook and Maestri will hold a conference call at 2:00 p.m. Pacific Time on Thursday to discuss the company's quarterly earnings results. The call should last around one hour, and it will include a Q&A segment with analysts.<br/>
<br/>
A live audio stream of the conference call will be available on <a href="https://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">Apple's Investor Relations page</a>, and a recording will be available later in the day for replay.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What's Next</h2><br/>
Apple's current quarter runs through September 28, and the company has yet to announce any new products during this period.<br/>
<br/>
AAPL is trading for around &#36;223 as of writing, down from a 52-week high of &#36;237.23.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-q3-2024-earnings-preview/">What to Expect From Apple&#039;s Quarterly Earnings Report This Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-quarterly-earnings-report-this-week.2432616/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iStat Menus 7.0 Brings Comprehensive Redesign and New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/istat-menus-7-0-brings-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/istat-menus-7-0-brings-comprehensive-redesign-and-new-features.2432615/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:15:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/istat-menus-7-0-brings-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iStat Menus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Version 7.0 of the popular system monitoring tool iStat Menus is <a href="https://bjango.com/mac/istatmenus/">now available</a>, bringing a comprehensive redesign and range of new features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/istat-menus-7.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960370" /><br/>
The redesign of iStat Menus 7.0 includes an updated interface with new menu bar modes, such as stacked labels and values, and new menu bar items, such as the Wi-Fi network name and GPU frames per second. For users of Apple silicon Macs, the update brings frequency monitoring and additional sensor support. Users can now choose from more theme options and menu background colors. Fan speeds can be controlled with greater precision, allowing for gradual ramp-up and complete control over the speed curve.<br/>
<br/>
The time menu has been enhanced with 7-day and 14-day rolling calendar modes, providing users with flexible scheduling options. The combined mode has undergone a major overhaul, allowing any item to be displayed in the menu bar with unique settings and more menu sections available in the dropdown menu.<br/>
<br/>
Weather monitoring has also seen improvements, offering a detailed view of current conditions, hourly forecasts, and weekly overviews. Users can access information such as temperature, wind speed and direction, chance of rain, humidity, UV index, and more, with data available for their current location or almost anywhere in the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/menus-1.jpg" alt="" width="2576" height="773" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960379" /><br/>
iStat Menus 7.0 offers more extensive notification capabilities, allowing users to set alerts for a wide range of events related to CPU, GPU, memory, disks, network, sensors, battery, power, and weather. Notifications can be customized to inform users about changes such as public IP updates, internet connection issues, CPU usage spikes, low disk space, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The app also provides detailed CPU information, including usage for individual cores, history graphs, load averages, uptime, and CPU frequency. GPU monitoring covers processor usage, memory, temperature, and frequency. Memory statistics include usage, history, memory pressure, compressed memory, swap, and a list of apps using the most memory.<br/>
<br/>
Disk usage and activity monitoring are also enhanced, showing used space, free space, and disk activity. S.M.A.R.T. status monitoring and detailed per-app disk usage are now available. Network monitoring features include history graphs, current bandwidth usage, a bandwidth breakdown for top apps, detailed connection info, IP addresses, and an internet connectivity indicator.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/menus-2.jpg" alt="" width="2576" height="790" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960380" /><br/>
Battery and power information is extensive, providing detailed current state information and configurable menu items that change based on whether the device is draining, charging, or fully charged. Battery levels for Bluetooth devices like AirPods, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad are also displayed. Real-time sensor listings include temperatures, fan speeds, voltages, current, and power, with customizable fan speed control based on temperature and battery state.<br/>
<br/>
The date and time features are highly customizable, with menu bar clocks, a calendar with upcoming events, and world clocks that include detailed sun and moon information. Each world clock can be given a custom name, making it easier to track time for colleagues or family members in different time zones. Combined mode is particularly useful for laptops, allowing multiple items to be combined into a single menu bar item to save space while still providing access to all relevant information.<br/>
<br/>
iStat Menus 7.0 is <a href="https://bjango.com/mac/istatmenus/">available for download</a> with a 14-day free trial, allowing users to explore its new features and enhancements before committing to a purchase. Additionally, it is available via Setapp, a subscription service that offers access to iStat Menus and over 250 other Mac apps for &#36;9.99 per month, with no additional fees or ads.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/istat-menus/">iStat Menus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/istat-menus-7-0-brings-new-features/">iStat Menus 7.0 Brings Comprehensive Redesign and New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/istat-menus-7-0-brings-comprehensive-redesign-and-new-features.2432615/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has Every M4 iPad Pro on Sale With Multiple Record Low Prices for Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-every-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale-with-multiple-record-low-prices-for-members.2432613/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:03:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a large collection of discounts on the <a href="https://howl.me/cmMGdhEepJe">2024 M4 iPad Pro</a> at Best Buy, which includes multiple all-time low prices on both 11-inch and 13-inch models. The majority of these deals will only be available to My Best Buy Plus/Total members, but there are a few instances of record low prices being matched at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
For the smaller 11-inch M4 iPad Pro, Best Buy has introduced a new best-ever price on the entry-level 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, available for <a href="https://howl.me/cmMFPxxvE8h"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> for members, down from &#36;999.00. Best Buy has every model of the 11-inch iPad Pro on sale right now, including both Wi-Fi and cellular versions, and you'll find steeper discounts for members.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFPxxvE8h">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;899.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFQmy1Gei">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,099.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,199.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,349.99 at Amazon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFRPRre0A">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,549.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFSDWvQXy">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,849.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFTEJUxTd">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,949.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;2,099.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-inch</h3><br/>
Similar to the 11-inch models, Best Buy has every Wi-Fi and cellular version of the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro on sale this week. Prices start at <a href="https://howl.me/cmMFUSaNsv1"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, and totals up to &#36;150 off these devices. Amazon is also matching the prices of quite a few 13-inch iPad Pro models without the need for a special membership.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFUSaNsv1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,199.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,299.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFWz9v0xi">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,389.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,499.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFYk8pTUn">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,899.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6S6LS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,839.00 at Amazon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMF0zTcj8I">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,149.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMF1Y7ND7f">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,249.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;2,399.00</li></ul>  Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/">Best Buy Has Every M4 iPad Pro on Sale With Multiple Record Low Prices for Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-every-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale-with-multiple-record-low-prices-for-members.2432613/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Pro&#039;s Tandem OLED Display Tech Could Extend to Future Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/vision-pro-tandem-oled-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-pros-tandem-oled-display-tech-could-extend-to-future-vision-pro.2432610/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:34:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/vision-pro-tandem-oled-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LG and Samsung have prototyped micro-OLED displays with tandem OLED technology, according to <a href="https://www.sisajournal-e.com/news/articleView.html?idxno=404430">Korean publication <em>Sisa Journal</em></a>, paving the way for a future model of Apple's Vision Pro mixed-reality headset to potentially adopt the technology.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-lenses.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898584" /><br/>
The report said it is unclear if or when LG and Samsung will begin mass production of tandem micro-OLED displays, but with a second-generation Vision Pro not expected to be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/no-apple-vision-pro-2-before-end-of-2026/">until late 2026 at the earliest</a>, there is still time for the two companies to commercialize the technology for potential inclusion in the next model.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple released new iPad Pro models with tandem OLED displays, which have two organic light-emitting layers stacked together for increased brightness, improved power efficiency, and longer longevity compared to single-layer OLED displays. These same benefits would extend to a future Vision Pro that adopts the technology.<br/>
<br/>
Here is how Apple described the iPad Pro's tandem OLED technology:<blockquote>The Ultra Retina XDR display features state-of-the-art tandem OLED technology that uses two OLED panels and combines the light from both to provide phenomenal full-screen brightness. The new iPad Pro supports an incredible 1000 nits of full-screen brightness for SDR and HDR content, and 1600 nits peak for HDR. No other device of its kind delivers this level of extreme dynamic range. Tandem OLED technology enables sub-millisecond control over the colour and luminance of each pixel, taking XDR precision further than ever. Specular highlights in photos and video appear even brighter, and there's more detail in shadows and low light than ever before on iPad — all while delivering even more responsiveness to content in motion.</blockquote>The current Vision Pro is equipped with two 4K micro-OLED displays supplied by Sony.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, the technology now exists for the next-generation Vision Pro to feature even brighter and more power efficient displays in a few years from now.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/vision-pro-tandem-oled-report/">iPad Pro&#039;s Tandem OLED Display Tech Could Extend to Future Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-pros-tandem-oled-display-tech-could-extend-to-future-vision-pro.2432610/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Beta Users Invited to &#039;Rate Your Experiences&#039; and Earn Points</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-intelligence-beta-users-rate-experiences/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-beta-users-invited-to-rate-your-experiences-and-earn-points.2432605/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:37:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-intelligence-beta-users-rate-experiences/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the latest macOS 15.1, iOS 18.1, and iPadOS 18.1 betas, Apple has introduced a new "Rate Your Experiences" feature in its Feedback Assistant app that lets users rate the generative content served by Apple Intelligence across apps, with the aim of using the feedback to refine and train Apple's generative models. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/rate-your-experiences-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960329" /><br/>
Apple describes the new feature like so:<br/>
<blockquote>Help improve Apple products and services! Content such as your emails from the Mail app and messages from the Messages app will be displayed to you, along with content generated from them for Apple Intelligence features. This data always remains on your device unless you choose to submit it to Apple, after rating your experience.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
In the new section, users are asked to "thumbs up" or "thumbs down" recent generated content to indicate their level of satisfaction with the results. If the "experience" shown was not good, users are invited to optionally offer more details for submission to Apple. This can be done by choosing from pre-defined feedback presented as a checkmark list, and by providing additional typed information for context.<br/>
<br/>
In the case of a summarized email in the Mail app, for example, users can choose from the following issues:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Hard to understand</li><br/>
  <li>Missed key detail</li><br/>
  <li>Incorrect attributions</li><br/>
  <li>Too long</li><br/>
  <li>Irrelevant additions</li><br/>
  <li>Stereotyping or bias</li><br/>
  <li>Overly suggestive or sexual</li><br/>
  <li>Vulgar or offensive</li><br/>
  <li>Other</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There are similar pre-set feedback options for other Apple Intelligence features such as Smart reply, Notifications summary, prioritized emails, Image Playground, Writing Tools, and more. The new section also includes a scoring system that lets users level up their score by providing feedback to Apple, although it's not explained what any points earned could be used for. <br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the first version of Apple Intelligence in the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 developer betas. While the betas include some useful Apple Intelligence features like Writing Tools, some of the Apple Intelligence additions <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">won't be coming until later</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-intelligence-beta-users-rate-experiences/">Apple Intelligence Beta Users Invited to &#039;Rate Your Experiences&#039; and Earn Points</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-beta-users-invited-to-rate-your-experiences-and-earn-points.2432605/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPhone 16 Pro Color Could Have Bronze Appearance</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-pro-color-could-have-bronze-appearance.2432596/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:00:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Fixed Focus Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Several iPhone 16 Pro rumors have suggested that Apple will eliminate the Blue Titanium option that it used for the iPhone 15 Pro devices and replace it with a rose or gold color. Now, the latest claim is that the new color is actually bronze or has a bronze-like appearance. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-16-pro-rose.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960320" /><br/>
According to the Weibo-based leaker "<a href="https://weibo.com/5821279480/Oq4eJxISx">Fixed focus digital</a>," a new iPhone 16 Pro Max color resembles a "bronze hue," while the surrounding frame has a titanium-like appearance. Earlier this month, another Chinese leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/iphone-16-pro-rose-color-coming/">suggested</a> that the color code for the new iPhone 16 Pro color is simply "Rose," not the previous "Rose Gold" color that Apple first offered back in 2015 for the iPhone 6S. <br/>
<br/>
It could well be that the two claims are not contradictory and are in fact referring to the same color, but as seen under different lighting conditions. It's worth mentioning that today's leaker only mentions the iPhone 16 Pro Max in relation to the new color, but it is reasonable to assume that it will come to both Pro models. Other colors that the iPhone 16 Pro and ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">expected</a> to be available in include black, white or silver, and gray or "Natural Titanium." <br/>
<br/>
Another rumor suggests that Apple plans to use an improved process for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/iphone-16-pro-new-polished-titanium-finish/">finishing and coloring titanium</a>, which will result in a glossier look than the brushed aluminum finish of the iPhone 15 Pro models. The glossy finish could look much more like the stainless steel that Apple used in prior years, but it will be more resistant to scratches.<br/>
<br/>
Apple typically releases its new iPhone series around mid-September, which means we are about six weeks out from the launch of the iPhone 16 series. Like the iPhone 15 series, this year's lineup is expected to stick with four models, but with the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max handsets getting slightly bigger display sizes. You can learn about plenty of other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">rumored design differences and new features</a> by following the link.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fixed-focus-digital/">Fixed Focus Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/">New iPhone 16 Pro Color Could Have Bronze Appearance</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-pro-color-could-have-bronze-appearance.2432596/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Revealed: iPhone 16 Colors and Redesigned Camera in Leaked Image</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revealed-iphone-16-colors-and-redesigned-camera-in-leaked-image.2432593/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:00:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Leaker Sonny Dickson today <a href="https://x.com/SonnyDickson/status/1818474212090429828">shared an image</a> displaying a selection of iPhone 16 dummy models that reveal Apple's planned new color options and the rumored redesigned camera bump coming to its iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-16-colors-dummies.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960310" /><br/>
The picture showcases five new colorways for the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus, and they match the descriptions previously predicted by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>: White, Black, Blue, Green, and Pink.<br/>
<br/>
The new colors suggest Apple is going for a less muted, less desaturated color palette for the standard iPhone 16 models this year, although there could be differences in materials used compared to the dummy models shown. As a reminder, the current iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus devices are available in Blue, Pink, Yellow, Green, and Black.<br/>
<br/>
For the 6.1- and 6.7-inch iPhone 16 models, Apple is also planning a new vertical camera lens arrangement that is a departure from the prior diagonal lens setup. The new orientation, evidenced in the dummy units, will presumably allow the standard iPhone 16 models to capture Spatial Video for the Vision Pro headset, something only the iPhone 15 Pro models are currently capable of doing. Prior iPhones have used a square-shaped camera bump to accommodate the diagonal lenses, but Apple is able to slim down the camera bump with the new lens arrangement.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus are anticipated to include an A18 chip, 8GB of RAM, a new "Capture" button on the right side for photo and video, the Action button previously exclusive to iPhone 15 Pro models, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">more</a>. All four devices in the iPhone 16 series are expected to launch around mid-September. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/">Revealed: iPhone 16 Colors and Redesigned Camera in Leaked Image</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revealed-iphone-16-colors-and-redesigned-camera-in-leaked-image.2432593/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Rolling Out More Natural Advanced Voice Mode for ChatGPT</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/openai-advanced-voice-mode-chatgpt/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-rolling-out-more-natural-advanced-voice-mode-for-chatgpt.2432573/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:57:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/openai-advanced-voice-mode-chatgpt/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI <a href="https://x.com/OpenAI/status/1818353580279316863">today said</a> that it has started to roll out Advanced Voice Mode to a small number of paid ChatGPT users, allowing them to test out more natural, real-time conversations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
Advanced Voice Mode allows ChatGPT to provide real-time responses that can be interrupted, plus it is able to sense and respond to humor, sarcasm, and more. The new model does not need to convert your speech to text and back again as the current ChatGPT voice does, leading to lower latency interactions.<br/>
<br/>
OpenAI demonstrated Advanced Voice Mode back in May, showing off an AI voice called Sky that <a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/05/31/g-s1-2263/voice-lab-analysis-striking-similarity-scarlett-johansson-chatgpt-sky-openai">sounded remarkably similar</a> to Scarlett Johansson. The voice was created and used without Johansson's permission, and she ended up <a href="https://x.com/BobbyAllyn/status/1792679435701014908?lang=en">releasing a statement</a> on the situation. She said that she turned down multiple offers from OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, who wanted Johansson to be the voice of ChatGPT. She said she was "shocked, angered, and in disbelief" that Altman created a voice that sounded "eerily similar" to her own voice. OpenAI claimed that the Sky voice was <a href="https://openai.com/index/how-the-voices-for-chatgpt-were-chosen/">not intended to resemble</a> the voice of Johansson, but it was removed after she hired legal counsel.<br/>
<br/>
OpenAI says that since it demoed Advanced Voice Mode, it has been working to improve the safety and quality of voice conversations. Advanced Voice Mode speaks in four preset voices and is built to block outputs that differ from those voices, preventing it from mimicking celebrity voices. OpenAI has also "implemented guardrails" to block requests for violent or copyrighted content, and the early tests will be used to improve the feature before a wider launch.<br/>
<br/>
Users who have been granted access to Advanced Voice Mode will receive an email with instructions, with OpenAI planning to add more people on a rolling basis. Everyone on Plus will have access to Advanced Voice Mode in the fall.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/openai-advanced-voice-mode-chatgpt/">OpenAI Rolling Out More Natural Advanced Voice Mode for ChatGPT</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-rolling-out-more-natural-advanced-voice-mode-for-chatgpt.2432573/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New &#039;Friend&#039; Necklace Offers AI Companionship</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/friend-necklace-ai-companionship/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-friend-necklace-offers-ai-companionship.2432570/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:47:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/friend-necklace-ai-companionship/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AI wearables like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/hands-on-rabbit-r1/">Rabbit R1</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/humane-ai-pin/">the AI Pin</a> have attempted to capitalize on the popularity of artificial intelligence and have largely flopped, but that isn't stopping the creator of a new <a href="https://www.friend.com">wearable device called Friend</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Friend Reveal Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O_Q1hoEhfk4" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Friend is an AI necklace that is meant to serve as a personal companion, and in a video that could be the start to an episode of Black Mirror, it's shown providing support, encouragement, and companionship to the wearer.<br/>
<br/>
The hardware component of Friend connects to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> via Bluetooth, continually listening to all interactions around the wearer. Pressing a button on the necklace allows the user to speak to Friend, with a message sent to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in response. Friend is also able to send messages without a conversational prompt, responding to what the wearer is doing.<br/>
<br/>
The Friend and its "memories" are stored on the necklace, with nothing uploaded to cloud servers. Friend creator Avi Schiffmann <a href="https://www.friend.com/blog.html">said in a blog post</a> that the device is an "expression of how lonely" he's felt. In an interview with <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/7/30/24207029/friend-ai-companion-gadget">The Verge</a></em>, Schiffmann said that Friend is designed to be supportive, validating, and able to encourage ideas. "It's a great brainstorming buddy," he said. "You can talk to it about relationships, things like that."<br/>
<br/>
Friend is <a href="https://www.friend.com/">available for pre-order</a> for &#36;99, and it is set to launch in January 2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/friend-necklace-ai-companionship/">New &#039;Friend&#039; Necklace Offers AI Companionship</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-friend-necklace-offers-ai-companionship.2432570/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Find My Is &#039;Super Creepy Surveillance Tech&#039; That Shouldn&#039;t Exist, Says Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/tim-sweeney-find-my-creepy-surveillance-tech/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-find-my-is-super-creepy-surveillance-tech-that-shouldnt-exist-says-epic-games-ceo-tim-sweeney.2432568/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:04:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/tim-sweeney-find-my-creepy-surveillance-tech/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Find My</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> CEO Tim Sweeney today commented on Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> service, referring to it as "super creepy surveillance tech" that "shouldn't exist."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/FindMy-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-779341" /><br/>
Sweeney went on to explain that several years ago, "a kid" stole a Mac laptop out of his car. Years later, Sweeney was checking &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, and as the Mac was still connected to his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> account, it showed him the location where the thief lived.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">This feature is super creepy surveillance tech and shouldn’t exist. Years ago, a kid stole a Mac laptop out of my car. Years later, I was checking out Find My and it showed a map with the house where the kid who stole my Mac lived. WTF Apple? How is that okay?!</p>&mdash; Tim Sweeney (@TimSweeneyEpic) <a href="https://twitter.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1818249443449225726?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Sweeney's take is curious, because providing the location of a lost or stolen device is exactly what the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; service is meant to do. Apple devices remain tied to a user's account if not removed, a feature that is meant to thwart theft.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-media-max-width="560"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A lot of people are saying this here. While technically true, it misses the point: you can&#39;t track the location of a device that&#39;s in someone&#39;s possession without tracking that person, and people have a right to privacy. This right applies to second hand device buyers and even to…</p>&mdash; Tim Sweeney (@TimSweeneyEpic) <a href="https://twitter.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1818280387455410311?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
After confusion from his Twitter followers over his comments, Sweeney said that the location of a device in someone's possession can't be tracked without tracking the person, and "people have a right to privacy." He claims that detection and recovery of a lost or stolen device should be "mediated by due process of law" and not exposed to the device owner "in vigilante fashion."<br/>
<br/>
When Sweeney saw how &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; worked, he said he turned off the feature on all of his devices.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> item trackers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/05/airtags-anti-stalking-measures-not-sufficient/">have been criticized</a> for their use by stalkers, the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; service has not been the target of similar complaints. &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/108794">Activation Lock</a> have been important theft deterrents, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/06/19/ios7-activation-lock-reduce-theft-cities/">cutting down on iPhone theft</a>. Apple recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/apple-to-allow-used-parts-for-repairs/">expanded Activation Lock</a> to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> components to prevent them from being disassembled for parts.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/tim-sweeney-find-my-creepy-surveillance-tech/">Apple&#039;s Find My Is &#039;Super Creepy Surveillance Tech&#039; That Shouldn&#039;t Exist, Says Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-find-my-is-super-creepy-surveillance-tech-that-shouldnt-exist-says-epic-games-ceo-tim-sweeney.2432568/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Emergency SOS via Satellite Launches in Japan</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/emergency-sos-via-satellite-japan/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/emergency-sos-via-satellite-launches-in-japan.2432563/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 12:45:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/emergency-sos-via-satellite-japan/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Japan</category>
		<category>Emergency SOS via Satellite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Emergency SOS via satellite expanded to Japan with the iOS 17.6 update that was released yesterday, <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/newsroom/2024/07/emergency-sos-via-satellite-available-today/">according to Apple</a>. Japanese customers with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> can use Emergency SOS via satellite to get in touch with emergency services even when a Wi-Fi or cellular connection is unavailable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/japan-emergency-sos-via-satellite.jpg" alt="" width="2900" height="1631" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960272" /><br/>
Apple first introduced Emergency SOS via satellite in 2022 alongside the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models, but it was initially limited to the United States and Canada. Apple has been working to bring it to additional countries since then.<br/>
<br/>
Japan has several different emergency contact numbers, and all of them work with Emergency SOS via satellite, including 119 for contacting fire and ambulance services, 110 for contacting the police, and 118 for contacting the coast guard. Satellite connectivity can also be used for updating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> location when out of range of cellular or Wi-Fi connectivity. The feature works for people living in Japan, as well as visitors to the country.<br/>
<br/>
Emergency SOS via satellite works through a partnership with Globalstar, with &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models able to connect to Globalstar satellites in countries where the feature has launched. The service is free for two years after activating an &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. Apple has not announced pricing for Emergency SOS via satellite after the two-year period expires.<br/>
<br/>
Emergency SOS via satellite is available in the United States, Canada, France, Germany, Ireland, the UK, Australia, Austria, Belgium, Italy, Luxembourg, New Zealand, Portugal, Switzerland, Spain, and the Netherlands.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/japan/">Japan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emergency-sos-via-satellite/">Emergency SOS via Satellite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/emergency-sos-via-satellite-japan/">Emergency SOS via Satellite Launches in Japan</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/emergency-sos-via-satellite-launches-in-japan.2432563/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>See Apple Intelligence in Action</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/apple-intelligence-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/see-apple-intelligence-in-action.2432554/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:48:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/apple-intelligence-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple released iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 betas <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">for developers yesterday</a>, introducing an early version of Apple Intelligence. Not all of the Apple Intelligence features are implemented yet, but we thought we'd go through what's available and see just what kind of changes AI will bring to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c0lDjLz033A" title="Apple Intelligence Beta Hands-On | Incredibly USEFUL Features!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
With Apple Intelligence, you can use Writing Tools to proofread text for spelling and grammar errors, or rewrite what you've written to change the tone. There are also options for summarizing any text, and Writing Tools are available across the operating system. You can use them anywhere you can write text.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> has a new design with a glow around the edges of the display when active, and there is a Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; option so you don't need to talk to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is able to maintain context between requests and follow along if you stumble over words, plus &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can answer all kinds of questions about your devices thanks to the integration of Apple's product knowledge and support database.<br/>
<br/>
Phone calls can be recorded, transcribed, and summarized, there are Smart Replies for Mail and Messages, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> has a Memory Maker feature, and there's a Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode that intelligently filters out notifications you don't need to see right away.<br/>
<br/>
If you want a more in-depth rundown of all of the features that are available, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">we have a dedicated guide</a> that highlights what's in the beta now. There are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">several Apple Intelligence features coming later</a>, including Image Playground, Genmoji, ChatGPT integration, and the smarter version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; that has onscreen awareness and can do more in and across apps. You won't find these features in the current iOS 18.1 beta, but Apple plans to roll them out across 2024 and 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence is limited to developers at the current time, with Apple working to refine the Apple Intelligence features and eliminate bugs. A beta version of Apple Intelligence will be available for all users later this fall, after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; launch. You will need an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>/Pro Max or later or an Apple silicon Mac or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to use Apple Intelligence due to the processor requirements. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/apple-intelligence-hands-on/">See Apple Intelligence in Action</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/see-apple-intelligence-in-action.2432554/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 2 Hit All-Time Low &#36;69.99 Price on Amazon, Plus Discounts on AirPods 3 and Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/airpods-2-hit-all-time-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-2-hit-all-time-low-69-99-price-on-amazon-plus-discounts-on-airpods-3-and-pro-2.2432533/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:23:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/airpods-2-hit-all-time-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today is discounting a collection of Apple's AirPods, including the AirPods 2, AirPods 3, and AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C. All of these deals represent the best prices we've tracked since Prime Day, and are overall solid second-best prices on most models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895408" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The AirPods 2 is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;69.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00, and the AirPods 3 is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;129.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00. Amazon also has the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. The AirPods 2 deal is a match for the all-time low price, while the other two are just about &#36;10 higher than their previous record low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;69.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/airpods-2-hit-all-time-low/">AirPods 2 Hit All-Time Low &#36;69.99 Price on Amazon, Plus Discounts on AirPods 3 and Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-2-hit-all-time-low-69-99-price-on-amazon-plus-discounts-on-airpods-3-and-pro-2.2432533/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Models &#039;Widely Expected&#039; to Support Wi-Fi 7</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/iphone-16-pro-wi-fi-7-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-widely-expected-to-support-wi-fi-7.2432527/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:05:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/iphone-16-pro-wi-fi-7-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are "widely expected" to support Wi-Fi 7, according to <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240729PD219/wi-fi-7-2025-ai-pc-iphone.html">Taiwanese supply chain publication <em>DigiTimes</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
Wi-Fi 7 support would enable the devices to send and receive data over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously, resulting in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. Wi-Fi 7 is expected to offer peak theoretical data transfer speeds of over 40 Gbps, a 4× increase over Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 7 support for iPhone 16 Pro models was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">previously rumored by supply chain analyst Jeff Pu</a>. The devices should be released in September.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro models gained support for Wi-Fi 6E, while all iPhone 11 through iPhone 14 models support standard Wi-Fi 6.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/iphone-16-pro-wi-fi-7-rumor/">iPhone 16 Pro Models &#039;Widely Expected&#039; to Support Wi-Fi 7</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-widely-expected-to-support-wi-fi-7.2432527/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Can Now Be Controlled With Brain-Computer Interface</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/vision-pro-can-now-be-controlled-with-brain/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-can-now-be-controlled-with-brain-computer-interface.2432526/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:54:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/vision-pro-can-now-be-controlled-with-brain/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset can now be controlled using only thoughts, thanks to integration with neurotechnology startup <a href="https://synchron.com">Synchron</a>'s brain-computer interface (BCI).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960264" /><br/>
The company today <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240730923591/en/Synchron-Announces-First-Use-of-Apple-Vision-Pro-with-a-Brain-Computer-Interface/">announced</a> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> has been successfully used by a patient through direct brain control facilitated by Synchron's brain-computer interface technology. Mark, a 64-year-old man suffering from amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), demonstrated the integration.<br/>
<br/>
With this technology, Mark controlled the cursor on the Vision Pro to play Solitaire, watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and send text messages without using his hands, which he can no longer move due to his condition. The Vision Pro's reliance on hand gestures would otherwise pose a barrier for users like Mark who have lost upper limb functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Mark has been practicing different skills and functions with his BCI twice a week since his implantation in August 2023. He noted that using the BCI to control the Vision Pro is similar to using it for his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and computer. Apple's suite of accessibility features across its platforms has been recognized for its excellence, which is why Synchron initially focused on integrating its BCI with Apple devices. <br/>
<br/>
Synchron's brain-computer interface allows individuals with severe physical limitations to control digital devices with their thoughts. The BCI is implanted in the blood vessel on the surface of the motor cortex via a minimally invasive endovascular procedure. The device detects motor intent from the brain and wirelessly transmits these signals to external devices, enabling hands-free control. Tom Oxley, CEO and Founder of Synchron, said:<blockquote>BCI is a platform to re-connect people with injury or disease back to the fast-moving consumer technology landscape. Vision Pro is a powerful system, but it relies on the use of hand gestures to exert control over the UI. We are sending control signals directly from the brain to replace the need for hand gestures. We are moving towards a new Bluetooth standard for Human Computer Interactions that do not require touch or speech. This is a critical unmet need for millions of people with paralysis.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Synchron is preparing for larger-scale clinical studies to expand the reach of its BCI technology. It has implanted its BCI in six patients in the United States and four in Australia. The company continues to seek approval from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration to commercialize its technology.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/vision-pro-can-now-be-controlled-with-brain/">Apple Vision Pro Can Now Be Controlled With Brain-Computer Interface</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-can-now-be-controlled-with-brain-computer-interface.2432526/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Used Google Tensor Chips to Develop Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/google-chips-used-to-develop-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-used-google-tensor-chips-to-develop-apple-intelligence.2432521/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 05:56:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/google-chips-used-to-develop-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Nvidia</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple used Tensor Processing Units (TPUs) developed by Google instead of Nvidia's widely-used graphics processing units (GPUs) to construct two critical components of Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
The decision is detailed in a <a href="https://machinelearning.apple.com/papers/apple_intelligence_foundation_language_models.pdf">new research paper</a> published by Apple that highlights its reliance on Google's cloud hardware (via <em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/29/apple-says-its-ai-models-were-trained-on-googles-custom-chips-.html">CNBC</a></em>). The paper reveals that Apple utilized 2,048 of Google's TPUv5p chips to build AI models and 8,192 TPUv4 processors for server AI models. The research paper does not mention Nvidia explicitly, but the absence of any reference to Nvidia's hardware in the description of Apple's AI infrastructure is telling and this omission suggests a deliberate choice to favor Google's technology. <br/>
<br/>
The decision is noteworthy given Nvidia's dominance in the AI processor market and since Apple very rarely discloses its hardware choices for development purposes. Nvidia's GPUs are highly sought after for AI applications due to their performance and efficiency. Unlike Nvidia, which sells its chips and systems as standalone products, Google provides access to its TPUs through cloud services. Customers using Google's TPUs have to develop their software within Google's ecosystem, which offers integrated tools and services to streamline the development and deployment of AI models. <br/>
<br/>
In the paper, Apple's engineers explain that the TPUs allowed them to train large, sophisticated AI models efficiently. They describe how Google's TPUs are organized into large clusters, enabling the processing power necessary for training Apple's AI models. Apple has announced plans to invest over &#36;5 billion in AI server enhancements over the next two years, which should bolster its AI capabilities and reduce its dependence on external hardware providers. <br/>
<br/>
In addition to detailing its use of Google's TPUs, the paper addresses ethical considerations in AI development. Apple emphasized its adherence to responsible data practices, claiming that no private user data was used in training its AI models. The company relied on a mix of publicly available, licensed, and open-sourced datasets for training purposes. Apple added that its training data set, which includes publicly available web data and licensed content, was curated to protect user privacy.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nvidia/">Nvidia</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/google-chips-used-to-develop-apple-intelligence/">Apple Used Google Tensor Chips to Develop Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-used-google-tensor-chips-to-develop-apple-intelligence.2432521/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some iPhone SE 4 OLED Panels to Be Supplied by LG Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/iphone-se-4-oled-panels-lg-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-se-4-oled-panels-to-be-supplied-by-lg-display.2432518/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:56:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/iphone-se-4-oled-panels-lg-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple supplier LG Display is expected to be the secondary vendor for the OLED panels that will feature on next year's fourth-generation iPhone SE models, reports <em><a href="https://www.thelec.net/news/articleView.html?idxno=4926">The Elec</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
The fourth-generation ‌iPhone SE‌ is rumored to feature an iPhone 14-like design with an OLED display, Face ID instead of Touch ID, a USB-C port, an Action button, and an all-screen look that does away with the Home Button. The device's display is expected to grow in size from 4.7 inches to 6.06 inches and use OLED for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
BOE will be the primary supplier of the OLED panels, with LG Display providing backup, according to today's report. In previous years, Apple has solely tasked China-based BOE to supply LCD-based iPhone SE panels. But BOE has struggled before with yield issues for OLED iPhone panels, so bringing LG Display into the picture as a secondary supplier could be Apple's way of having a security blanket in case of future problems.<br/>
<br/>
The panel prices for the iPhone SE 4 are said to be a lot lower than suppliers charge for the OLED displays used in the iPhone 15, since the panels for the SE will use legacy parts identical to those used in the iPhone 13 and iPhone 14, so the suppliers won't need to make new investments in R&D. Display manufacturers are believed to have been bidding to supply the panels since at least last August. Mass production of the device will reportedly begin in October of this year, with the iPhone SE 4 expected to arrive in spring 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/30/iphone-se-4-oled-panels-lg-display/">Some iPhone SE 4 OLED Panels to Be Supplied by LG Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-se-4-oled-panels-to-be-supplied-by-lg-display.2432518/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All of the Apple Intelligence Features Not Included in the iOS 18.1 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-of-the-apple-intelligence-features-not-included-in-the-ios-18-1-beta.2432499/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:05:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple introduced the first version of Apple Intelligence in the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 developer betas. While the betas include some useful Apple Intelligence features like Writing Tools, some of the Apple Intelligence additions won't be coming until later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
We've rounded up everything that's not yet been added to the betas, with Apple planning to introduce these features at a later date.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Image Playground</strong> - Both the standalone app and the functionality built into apps like Notes and Messages are missing from the current beta.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Genmoji</strong> - Genmoji is based on Image Playground, and it is unavailable.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Image Wand</strong> - Image Wand, the feature that inserts images into your Notes based on context, is also based on Image Playground so it won't be available until Image Playground is added to the beta.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Priority Notifications</strong> - Priority notifications show up at the top of the notification stack, so you can get to what's most important first. The feature also summarizes your incoming notifications so you can sort through them more quickly.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mail</strong> - Mail categories that sort your incoming messages are not yet available.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Photos</strong> - While the Memory Maker feature is active in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, the Clean Up tool that removes unwanted objects from images with a tap is not available.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Siri</strong> - Functionality that includes onscreen awareness, personal context, and the ability to take more actions in and across apps is not yet available.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>ChatGPT</strong> - ChatGPT integration with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> has not yet been implemented.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Additional Languages</strong> - Apple Intelligence is available in U.S. English only as of now, but support for additional languages will be coming in the future.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Additional Platforms</strong> - As Apple said in its <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/introducing-apple-intelligence-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">WWDC coverage</a> of Apple Intelligence, the Apple Intelligence feature set will eventually expand to additional platforms.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 are only available to developers right now, and Apple Intelligence is still in the early stages of testing. Apple Intelligence features will be available to everyone later this fall in an update to the initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; releases. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">All of the Apple Intelligence Features Not Included in the iOS 18.1 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-of-the-apple-intelligence-features-not-included-in-the-ios-18-1-beta.2432499/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma 14.6 Adds Dual External Display Support to M3 14-Inch MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/macos-sonoma-14-6-dual-display-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-6-adds-dual-external-display-support-to-m3-14-inch-macbook-pro.2432496/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 14:55:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/macos-sonoma-14-6-dual-display-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 update that Apple released today includes dual display support, an important feature specifically for the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro. With the new software, the 14-inch MacBook Pro with M3 chip is able to run two external displays in clamshell mode, aka when the lid is closed.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919851" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple introduced dual display support in clamshell mode for the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models when they were released in March 2024, but at the time, the option was not available for the M3 14-inch MacBook Pro released back in October 2023. Apple said at the time that it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-pro-multi-display-support/">planning to release</a> a software update that would add multi-display support to the M3 MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The change is mentioned in Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109035">macOS Sonoma update support document</a> and in <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/117373">a support document</a> on using dual monitors with the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro now supports one external display at 6K resolution when the lid is open, or two external displays at 5K resolution at up to 60Hz when the lid is closed.<br/>
<br/>
Higher-end MacBook Pro models with M3 Pro and M3 Max chips were already able to support multiple displays, so today's change only applies to the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro model.<br/>
<br/>
Aside from the display update, &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.6 addresses a number of security vulnerabilities as outlined in <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214119">Apple's security support document</a>. None of the vulnerabilities are known to have been actively exploited in the wild, but it is still a good idea to update as soon as possible.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/macos-sonoma-14-6-dual-display-support/">macOS Sonoma 14.6 Adds Dual External Display Support to M3 14-Inch MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-6-adds-dual-external-display-support-to-m3-14-inch-macbook-pro.2432496/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are All of the Apple Intelligence Features in the iOS 18.1 Developer Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-of-the-apple-intelligence-features-in-the-ios-18-1-developer-beta.2432493/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 14:11:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 for developers, introducing the first Apple Intelligence features. Apple Intelligence was previewed in June, and is Apple's version of artificial intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-Intelligence-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960229" /><br/>
Not all of the Apple Intelligence features are available as of yet, but we've rounded up a list of what's active in the beta. Note that iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 are limited to developers only at this time, with the software set to come out to all users in a beta capacity this fall.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence is in the early stages of refinement, and Apple is working out bugs and polishing the new features before launch. Apple Intelligence will improve over time, and the features that are missing in the developer beta will roll out later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Writing Tools</h2><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-writing-tools.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960221" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Proofread text for spelling and grammar errors, including word choice and sentence structure. You can accept all suggestions with a tap or go through them one by one with explanations. </li><br/>
 	<li>Rewrite for cleaning up what you've written and shifting the tone without impacting your content. Options include Friendly, Professional, and Concise.</li><br/>
 	<li>Options for selecting text and summarizing it. You can choose to create a paragraph, pull out key points, make a list, or create a table. Summaries are available in Mail, Messages, and more.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can select any text on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac and use Apple Intelligence to access Writing Tools for summaries and other features.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Siri</h2><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960222" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>New glow around the edges of the display when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is activated, applicable to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>. On Mac, the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; window can be placed anywhere. The glow animates responsively to the sound of your voice so you can tell when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is listening without interrupting other things you're doing.</li><br/>
 	<li>A double tap at the bottom of the display brings up the Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interface so you can type requests instead of speaking them. If this isn't working, you may need to restart. On Mac, you need to press the Command key twice to bring up Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;. Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; includes suggested requests so you can get your questions answered faster.</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can maintain context between requests so you can ask a question and then reference it in a second reply. If you ask about the temperature in Orlando, for example, and then follow up with "what's the humidity?" &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will know you mean in Orlando.</li><br/>
 	<li>If you stumble over your words when speaking to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, or shift what you're saying mid-sentence, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can follow along.</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has Apple's product knowledge and support base for answering questions about your device's features and settings, and can even find settings when you don't know the exact name.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Mail</h2><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-smart-replies.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960207" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>There is a summarize button for summarizing any of your incoming emails, plus you will see a brief summary of an email in your inbox list rather than the first few lines of the email.</li><br/>
 	<li>Mail surfaces time sensitive messages first when applicable, putting them at the top of your inbox so you see what's important right away.</li><br/>
 	<li>Smart Reply provides quick-tap responses to emails that you've been sent, with contextual options based on what's in the email.</li><br/>
<li>Multiple notifications from Mail will be summarized on your Lock Screen so you can see what's in an email without opening the app.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Messages</h2><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-messages-smart-reply.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960223" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Messages has Smart Reply options for incoming texts, which analyze the content of messages to offer suggestions of what you might want to say.</li><br/>
<li>Multiple Messages notifications are summarized on your Lock Screen.</li><br/>
<br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Photos</h2><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-memory-maker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960208" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>You can create a Memory Movie with just a description, such as "My cat in 2024," or "Orlando in the summer." The feature automatically picks relevant photos and chooses songs, but you can tweak through the Memory Mixes feature or choose a mood to guide the direction of the audio. You can also add in specific scenes and images you want to see throughout the memory when you're creating the prompt.</li><br/>
 	<li>Natural language search is available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, so you can just describe what you're looking for, such as "Eric rollerskating while wearing green."</li><br/>
 	<li>Search can also find specific moments in video clips.</li><br/>
<li>Search offers up smart complete suggestions for narrowing down what you might want to find</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Transcription</h2><br/>
In Notes and other apps, you can record audio and get a transcript along with a summary of your transcript, which is useful for recording lectures and other audio.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Focus Modes</h2><br/>
There is a dedicated Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode that only shows you important notifications that need attention while filtering out everything else.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-focus-mode-changes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960224" /><br/>
When customizing an existing Focus mode or creating a new one, there is a new toggle to turn on Intelligent Breakthrough and Silencing. This option allows important notifications to interrupt you, while muting notifications that are not important, which is the same thing that the Reduce Notifications Focus does. You can override the notification settings for specific apps and people, which is how it worked prior to iOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-focus-reduce-interruptions.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960225" /><br/>
<h2>Phone</h2><br/>
Phone call recording <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-call-recording-and-transcribing/">is available in iOS 18.1</a>. When starting a call, you can tap on the little record button in the upper left corner of the display. All participants are notified that the call is being recorded before the recording starts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-call-recording-1.jpg" alt="" width="5416" height="3047" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960199" /><br/>
Recorded phone calls are stored in the Notes app, where you can tap in to view a transcript and get a summary generated from that transcript.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Safari</h2><br/>
When reading an article in Reader Mode, there is an option to have Apple Intelligence summarize the article for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-safari-summarize.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960226" /><br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Report</h2><br/>
In the Privacy and Security section of the Settings app you can access an Apple Intelligence Report that lets you export your Apple Intelligence data as part of Apple's promise for transparency around Apple Intelligence. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> is required to access and export Apple Intelligence data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-report.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960227" /><br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Waitlist</h2><br/>
Developers that upgrade to iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, or &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 will need to go to the Settings app and join the Apple Intelligence waitlist. There is a waitlist mechanic to ensure that behind the scenes downloads go smoothly and that the system isn't overloaded.<br/>
<br/>
While on the waitlist, Apple devices download necessary files for on-device processing, and so far, the time from Apple Intelligence waitlist signups to activation has been quick. The waitlist is on a per-account basis, so you only need to sign up for it on one device to have access on multiple devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Compatibility</h2><br/>
The iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 betas are only available to registered developers with an eligible device. Devices that cannot run Apple Intelligence will not see the update.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max</li><br/>
 	<li>All Apple silicon iPads</li><br/>
 	<li>All Apple silicon Macs</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Availability</h2><br/>
Apple Intelligence is only available in U.S. English at this time, and it is not available to developers in the European Union or China. Device region and language need to be set to the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Launch Date</h2><br/>
Apple Intelligence will not be in the initial launch version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> that comes out in September alongside new iPhones. It will instead be introduced in a separate iOS 18.1 update that is likely to come out a few weeks after &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; debuts.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">Here Are All of the Apple Intelligence Features in the iOS 18.1 Developer Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-of-the-apple-intelligence-features-in-the-ios-18-1-developer-beta.2432493/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
