<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 03:03:25 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Max: Review and Unboxing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-review-unboxing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-max-review-and-unboxing.2437291/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:22:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-review-unboxing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Happy <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> launch day! &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models are now in the hands of customers around the world. We <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/hands-on-iphone-16/">took a look at the iPhone 16</a> already, and now we're back with an unboxing and quick review of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max, Apple's higher-end flagship devices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eSZDUIZ9MCo" title="iPhone 16 Pro Max Hands-On | Shot on iPhone 16 Pro" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Unboxing a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> got a little more boring this year, because for the first time, Apple's removed the stickers from the box. No more stickers and no more charger - there's just an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and a cable in there.<br/>
<br/>
Early leaks of the new "Desert" titanium shade made it look rather unappealing, but in person, the color is a soft, subtle gold with a darker shade on the casing and a lighter shade at the back. It's not ugly at all, and there's even a bit of pink in there so in some light, it's close to a rose gold. We've also got a white titanium &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, and it's fine. It's like the white titanium from last year, and there's not much more to say about it. The Pro colors are undeniably boring, especially compared to the lovely teal, pink, and ultramarine shades Apple used for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
Both the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max are larger in size and the bezels have been slimmed down. The thinner bezels are noticeable in person, even compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro models. If you've got an even earlier &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it's a big difference. The 16 Pro Max definitely feels a little larger in the hand, and the 16 Pro is closer to a Goldilocks size.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max have the same feature set this year with the exception of display size and battery life. You'll get the most battery out of the 16 Pro Max because a bigger casing allows for a bigger battery, but there are improvements to both models.<br/>
<br/>
There's a new Camera Control button on the right side of all the iPhones, and it's used for opening the Camera app to take photos and videos. A quick double press takes a photo, and a press and then a press and hold captures video, which is convenient. It's easier to use in landscape mode than portrait mode, and all those gestures for adjusting settings do take some time to get used to.<br/>
<br/>
We've got some demo images in our video, and also, we've shot this entire review using the 16 Pro and Pro Max so you can check out the video quality. These models support 4K 120fps recording, and you can adjust frame rate in post. Apple added an Audio Mix feature for customizing sound in video too, and we've used that here as well. You can block out sound around the person you're recording or direct all noise forward like in a movie, and Audio Mix is also customizable with a slider control.<br/>
<br/>
For your photos, there are new Photographic Styles that you can customize to get the perfect look for all of your images. You can use a new dial pad to go dramatic or subtle, and your personalized style can be applied in real time, in editing, to all photos, or just to one.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added a new 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera so you'll get better lighting in those wide shots or when taking macro photos, and the 5X zoom is now on both models. We're going to be doing a deep dive into the camera next week, so stay tuned for that.<br/>
<br/>
If you're coming from a newer &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, you're probably not going to notice much in terms of speed improvements with the new A18 Pro chip, because most of what you do on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; isn't stressing the processor. It'll make a difference for Apple Intelligence, but of course unless you install the iOS 18.1 beta, no Apple Intelligence features are available to use yet.<br/>
<br/>
Did you get a new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; or 16 Pro? Let us know what you think in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-review-unboxing/">iPhone 16 Pro Max: Review and Unboxing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-max-review-and-unboxing.2437291/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Full iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro Repair Manuals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-repair-manual/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-full-iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-repair-manuals.2437286/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 13:04:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-repair-manual/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following today's launch of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, Apple has shared repair manuals for the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120652">iPhone 16</a>, the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120662">iPhone 16 Plus</a>, the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120803">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, and the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120828">iPhone 16 Pro Max</a>. The repair manuals provide technical instructions on replacing genuine Apple parts in the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, and Apple says the information is intended for "individual technicians" that have the "knowledge, experience, and tools" that are necessary to repair electronic devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-iphone-battery-repair.png" alt="" width="880" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967524" /><br/>
Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120983">has support documents</a> on the tools that are required for various repairs, and while the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; tools aren't yet available on <a href="https://www.selfservicerepair.com/en-US/order">Apple's Self Service Repair website</a>, they'll likely be added soon.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to prior <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are easier to repair. Apple is using an electric battery removal process, and the steps for accessing a battery to replace it are outlined in a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120642">separate support document</a>. Per Apple's instructions, a 9-volt battery and 9-volt battery clips can be applied to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; battery to remove the adhesive that holds it in place.<br/>
<br/>
Note that the simpler electricity-based battery removal process is limited to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus. For the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and Pro Max, Apple is using standard adhesive tabs that need to be carefully pulled to release the battery.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's instructions for all of the battery repairs include expensive equipment like an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery press to put a replacement battery back in place. The cost of the tools required for device repair and the cost of genuine components make self repair almost as expensive as getting a repair from an Apple retail location or an Apple Authorized Service Provider, so these manuals are really aimed at independent repair shops rather than individual consumers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/18/iphone-16-repairability-changes/">made other changes</a> to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models this year to improve repairability, enabling on-device configuration for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> camera, allowing LiDAR Scanner repair, and offering support for swapping the TrueDepth camera modules between &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to offering repair instructions, Apple's manuals provide some insight into the internal structure of the new iPhones that we often don't see until there <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-teardown-video/">are device teardowns</a>. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, for example, has a metal casing for the battery, a change made for thermal reasons, and both Pro models have new casing structure that improves heat dissipation.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-repair-manual/">Apple Shares Full iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro Repair Manuals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-full-iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-repair-manuals.2437286/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working to Fix iPadOS 18 Issue With M4 iPad Pro Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-working-to-fix-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-to-fix-ipados-18-issue-with-m4-ipad-pro-models.2437285/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:51:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-working-to-fix-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In an internal memo shared with Apple Authorized Service Providers this week, Apple has acknowledged an issue with installing iPadOS 18 on iPad Pro models with the M4 chip. We <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/17/apple-pulls-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro/">first reported on this issue</a> earlier this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m4-iPad-Pro-Horizontal-Feature-Purple-and-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950741" /><br/>
The memo, obtained by <em>MacRumors</em>, states that a "small number" of these iPad Pro models are unable to power on after a customer attempted to install iPadOS 18 on the device. Apple is working to resolve the issue, and it has made iPadOS 18 unavailable on affected iPad Pro models in the meantime, according to the memo.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has advised technicians to attempt a force restart of a customer's iPad Pro model, if the device has experienced this issue.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear how long it will take for Apple to identify and implement a fix.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-working-to-fix-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro-issue/">Apple Working to Fix iPadOS 18 Issue With M4 iPad Pro Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-to-fix-ipados-18-issue-with-m4-ipad-pro-models.2437285/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 and &#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Rumored to Feature 120Hz ProMotion Displays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-and-17-air-120hz-promotion-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-and-iphone-17-air-rumored-to-feature-120hz-promotion-displays.2437281/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:22:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-and-17-air-120hz-promotion-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We don't mean to take away from the excitement of the iPhone 16 launch today, but there are more rumors to share about next year's iPhone 17 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iPhone-17-Slim-Feature-Single-Camera-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960528" /><br/>
Ross Young of Display Supply Chain Consultants today informed <em>MacRumors</em> that the standard iPhone 17 and a slimmer model that we are calling the "iPhone 17 Air" will both feature ProMotion, meaning that each device's display would be able to ramp up to a 120Hz refresh rate for smoother scrolling and video content when necessary.<br/>
<br/>
ProMotion would also allow the iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Air displays to ramp down to a more power-efficient refresh rate. iPhone 13 Pro models can ramp down to 10Hz, while iPhone 14 Pro through iPhone 16 Pro models can go as low as 1Hz, allowing for an always-on display that shows various Lock Screen elements even when the device is locked. It is unclear if the iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Air would ramp down to 10Hz or 1Hz.<br/>
<br/>
The standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus still have 60Hz displays.<br/>
<br/>
Young has a good track record with display-related information about future Apple products, including being the first source to reveal that the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">would feature larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 17 series in September 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-and-17-air-120hz-promotion-rumor/">iPhone 17 and &#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Rumored to Feature 120Hz ProMotion Displays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-and-iphone-17-air-rumored-to-feature-120hz-promotion-displays.2437281/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Halfbrick+ Lets You Play Popular iOS Games Like Fruit Ninja, Jetpack Joyride and Mega Jump for &#36;2.99/Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/halfbrick-plus-game-service/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halfbrick-lets-you-play-popular-ios-games-like-fruit-ninja-jetpack-joyride-and-mega-jump-for-2-99-month.2437278/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:11:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/halfbrick-plus-game-service/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.halfbrick.com">Halfbrick Studios</a> is a game company best known for super popular iOS titles like Fruit Ninja and Jetpack Joyride, which have historically been freemium titles. Starting last year, Halfbrick decided to go with a different monetization model, offering all of its games for a low monthly fee.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/halfbrick-plus.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="704" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967506" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.halfbrickplus.com">Halfbrick+</a>, a &#36;2.99 per month service (or &#36;30/year), offers a bunch of updated takes on classic iOS games, with more titles added regularly. You can play without ads, in-app purchases, or irritating freemium game mechanics that limit gameplay unless you shell out more money.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="The Golden Age of Mobile Gaming is Back! ï¸" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IjRSzwca09Y" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The service soft launched late last year, but it's ramping up as Halfbrick has worked to add multiple games in 2024. Titles include Fruit Ninja Classic, Dan the Man Classic, Jetpack Joyride Test Labs, Bears vs. Art, Lazy Dog, Monster Dash, and tons more, with a full list <a href="https://www.halfbrickplus.com/#games">available on the Halfbrick+ website</a>. New games are coming on a regular basis, as Halfbrick is developing its own titles exclusively for Halfbrick+, and working with other game developers to bring classic titles to the service.<br/>
<br/>
Just today, Halfbrick+ gained Mega Jump, an arcade platformer where the goal is to jump as high as possible while avoiding monsters and collecting coins. It's one of those classic <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> titles that you likely played years and years ago, but it's back and better than ever with no IAP through Halfbrick+.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Mega Jump Out Now Trailer Halfbrick+" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/X0mRY2RRfFk" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
In a couple of weeks, Nimble Quest will join Halfbrick+. If you're unfamiliar with Nimble Quest, it's a fun little game that uses the classic snake mechanic. Players control a conga line of heroes, destroying enemies, collecting new heroes, and gathering treasure.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Nimble Quest - App Store Preview - Halfbrick+" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nmx5_Is_eWs" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
There are some obvious similarities between Halfbrick+ and Apple's own <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> subscription service, but Halfbrick is focusing on a more curated experience with well-loved game mechanics and the addictive gameplay that Halfbrick is known for. The &#36;2.99 price point is purposely aggressive to keep it affordable for players, and there is a one-month free trial for anyone who wants <a href="https://www.halfbrickplus.com/">to give the service a go</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/halfbrick-plus-game-service/">Halfbrick+ Lets You Play Popular iOS Games Like Fruit Ninja, Jetpack Joyride and Mega Jump for &#36;2.99/Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halfbrick-lets-you-play-popular-ios-games-like-fruit-ninja-jetpack-joyride-and-mega-jump-for-2-99-month.2437278/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Pro No Longer Expected to Feature Under-Display Face ID [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-pro-under-screen-face-id-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-no-longer-expected-to-feature-under-display-face-id-updated.2437261/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 10:44:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-pro-under-screen-face-id-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Face ID</category>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update:</strong> Young has since said under-display Face ID is <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1837193959367659655">no longer expected for the iPhone 17 Pro</a>. His previous response was <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1837197288545857721">sent in error</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Original story follows.<br/>
<br/>
<hr/><br/>
<br/>
While the iPhone 16 series just began arriving to customers today, there are already rumors about the next-generation iPhone 17 series.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/Beyond-iPhone-13-Better-Blue-Face-ID-Single-Camera-Hole.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891051" /><br/>
In a post shared on social media platform X on Thursday, display industry analyst Ross Young <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1836912096250056937">said</a> he believes that next year's iPhone 17 Pro will feature under-display Face ID. This change would presumably extend to the iPhone 17 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
Under-display Face ID has been rumored for several years, but it has failed to materialize. However, Young has a good track record with display-related information about future Apple products, including being the first source to reveal that the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">would feature larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>, respectively. If he says the iPhone 17 Pro will have under-screen Face ID, there is a good chance it will.<br/>
<br/>
In April 2023, Young shared a roadmap that showed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/under-display-face-id-to-debut-on-iphone-17-pro/">both iPhone 17 Pro models would feature under-display Face ID</a>, but he said the devices would still have a hole in the screen for the front camera. He does not expect both under-display Face ID and an under-display front camera until the iPhone 19 Pro models in three years from now.<br/>
<br/>
With under-display Face ID, the iPhone 17 Pro models could have only a single hole at the top of the display, similar to recent Android smartphones from Samsung and Google. However, no specific design changes have been rumored yet.<br/>
<br/>
Another unanswered question: Will the Dynamic Island live on with under-display Face ID?<br/>
<br/>
With the iPhone 17 series still a year away, there is plenty of time remaining for additional rumors, which should give us a better idea of what to expect.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/face-id/">Face ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-pro-under-screen-face-id-rumor/">iPhone 17 Pro No Longer Expected to Feature Under-Display Face ID [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-no-longer-expected-to-feature-under-display-face-id-updated.2437261/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro: How to Use All the New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-pro-how-to-use-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-how-to-use-all-the-new-features.2437248/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 09:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-pro-how-to-use-new-features&#038;post_date=1726860120/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max launched today in markets around the world. If you're the new owner of one of Apple's latest models, then keep reading. Whether you're upgrading from an older iPhone or completely new to the devices, this article will help you get the most out your iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-pro-max.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964613" /><br/>
With the first round of pre-ordered devices now being delivered to customers and availability in stores, <em>MacRumors</em> has put together the following series of dedicated iPhone 16 how-to articles explaining all the new features that can be found on Apple's newest models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="all_iphone_16_models">All iPhone 16 Models</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-using-new-camera-control-button/">iPhone 16 Camera Control: Everything You Need to Know</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-adjust-camera-control-button-pressure/">How to Adjust Camera Control Button Pressure</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-camera-control-simple-shutter-button/">How to Disable Camera Control Clean Preview Mode</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-disable-camera-control-button-light-press/">How to Disable Camera Control Light Press Adjustments</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-camera-control-button-qr-code-scanner/">How to Use the Camera Control Button as a QR Code Scanner</a></li> <br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-use-camera-control-button-as-a-magnifier/">How to Use the Camera Control Button as a Magnifier</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-disable-camera-control-button/">How to Disable the Camera Control Button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-customize-action-button/">How to Customize the Action Button</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-adapt-colors-shadows-photographic-styles/">Adapt Your Shots in Real-Time With New Photographic Styles</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/hard-reset-force-restart-iphone-16/">How to Hard Reset or Force Restart All iPhone 16 Models</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_16_pro_and_iphone_16_pro_max">iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-pro-how-to-use-5x-optical-zoom/">How to Use 5x Optical Zoom</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-pro-choose-jpeg-xl-proraw-formats/">Using the New ProRAW Shooting Formats</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-pro-shoot-4k-video-120-fps-slow-mo/">How to Shoot 4K Video at 120 fps to Slow Down Reality</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ios_18">iOS 18</h2><br/>
All iPhone 16 models come with iOS 18 pre-installed. During the iOS 18 beta testing process from June to September, <em>MacRumors</em> wrote a series of in-depth feature guides highlighting every major new addition, plus how tos that walk you through using the new features. Be sure to refer to our ultimate walkthrough, and check out our AirPods Pro 2 new features roundup, to get yourself up to speed.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-ultimate-guide/">Ultimate iOS 18 Walkthrough: Guides and How Tos for New Features</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-airpods-pro/">Six New Features iOS 18 Brings to the AirPods Pro</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="forgot_to_pre-order">Forgot to Pre-order?</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="3020" height="1698" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967113" /><br/>
For customers who forgot to pre-order one of the new models or simply decided to wait, most configurations ordered online are now estimated for delivery in October, but the good news is that same-day or next-day pickup is now an option at select Apple Store locations around the world.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-pro-how-to-use-new-features/">iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro: How to Use All the New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-how-to-use-all-the-new-features.2437248/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: M2 iPad Air Hits New Low Prices, Plus Our Exclusive 20% Discount at Anker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-20-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-m2-ipad-air-hits-new-low-prices-plus-our-exclusive-20-discount-at-anker.2437244/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 09:07:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-20-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals includes our exclusive discount at Anker, offering 20% off nearly everything on the retailer's website. Other than the Anker deals, you can also find big discounts on M2 iPad Air, AirPods, and early Prime Day deals at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-new-purple-hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960078" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/anker-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967386" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take 20% off Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/anker-macrumors-20-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE 20% OFF</div>Anker Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week we partnered with Anker to offer our readers an exclusive 20 percent discount on Anker's best chargers, portable batteries, and more. You'll need to enter the code akmacrumors20ch at checkout to see the discount, and can find more information about what accessories work with the code <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/anker-macrumors-20-off/">in our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ipad-air-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967393" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;79 off M2 iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J59856%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apples-m2-ipad-air-new-low/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6FSV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>11-inch M2 iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;629.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J59856%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>13-inch M2 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;719.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
New record low prices hit Apple's M2 iPad Air this week, with the highlight being the 128GB Wi-Fi 13-inch iPad Air for &#36;719.99, down from &#36;799.99. All of the tablets in this sale require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/airpods-pro-2-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967392" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;59 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/18/amazon-has-apples-airpods-2/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple just released the new AirPods 4, but if you want to save money and purchase an older model there are still some great discounts available on Amazon. The AirPods 2 is on sale for &#36;89.00 and the AirPods Pro 2 is on sale for &#36;189.99, both of which represent solid second-best prices on each accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ipad-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967395" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;130 off 9th gen iPads</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cm6gD5OoS7a">Best Buy</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/15/best-buy-weekend-sale-ipad/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cm6gD5OoS7a"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cm1xsDF7BR1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy still has steep discounts on the 9th generation iPad as we head into the weekend, including the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet for just &#36;199.99, down from &#36;329.99. You can also find a &#36;130 discount on the 256GB Wi-Fi model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Amazon Prime Big Deal Days</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/fire-tv-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967396" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save with early Prime Day deals</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimebigdealdays%2F">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/17/amazon-october-prime-day-2024/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimebigdealdays%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EARLY DEALS</div>Amazon Prime Big Deal Days</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon announced that Prime Day is returning October 8-9, and you can already find a few very early discounts this week. These sales are mainly focused on Amazon branded products like Fire TVs and Fire tablets, but it'll keep expanding to include more items as October 8 grows closer.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-20-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: M2 iPad Air Hits New Low Prices, Plus Our Exclusive 20% Discount at Anker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-m2-ipad-air-hits-new-low-prices-plus-our-exclusive-20-discount-at-anker.2437244/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Teardown Video Reveals Metal-Enclosed Battery and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-teardown-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-teardown-video-reveals-metal-enclosed-battery-and-more.2437233/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 08:26:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-teardown-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube channel REWA Technology today shared an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hRKFrOTQCWM">iPhone 16 Pro teardown video</a>, offering a first look inside of the device following its release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iPhone-16-Pro-Battery-Teardown.jpg" alt="" width="2794" height="1557" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967415" /><br/>
Notably, the video reveals that the smaller iPhone 16 Pro is equipped with a metal-enclosed battery, confirming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">a rumor from last year</a>. The battery has a capacity of 3,582 mAh, which matches the figure that surfaced earlier this week in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-battery-capacities-revealed/">Brazilian regulatory filing</a>. For comparison, the iPhone 15 Pro has a 3,274 mAh battery.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, some iPhone 16 batteries use an adhesive that can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/18/iphone-16-and-16-plus-9v-battery-removal/">easily loosened with low-voltage electrical current</a>, such as from a 9V battery. <em>TechCrunch</em> said this change applies to the standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus, but not to the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max. The teardown video did not test the low-voltage removal process on the iPhone 16 Pro, but it does reveal that the device's battery still has adhesive pull tabs, which suggests that the new process might indeed be limited to the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hRKFrOTQCWM?si=K7ileqX_RV4H7PFo" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Meanwhile, a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Qt5YDKJV6g">separate teardown video</a> appears to show that the iPhone 16 Pro Max still has a battery enclosed in black foil instead of metal.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced that all four iPhone 16 models feature internal design changes for improved heat dissipation. In the teardown video, the iPhone 16 Pro's chassis appears to have a larger thermal sheet compared to the iPhone 15 Pro. Metal-enclosed batteries could also contribute to the heat dissipation improvements.<br/>
<br/>
The video also reveals that the iPhone 16 Pro has a slightly more compact logic board compared to the one in the iPhone 15 Pro, and a few other changes.<br/>
<br/>
Repair website iFixit will likely share its own iPhone 16 teardowns later.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-pro-teardown-video/">iPhone 16 Pro Teardown Video Reveals Metal-Enclosed Battery and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-teardown-video-reveals-metal-enclosed-battery-and-more.2437233/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Our Favorite iOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/the-macrumors-show-our-favorite-ios-18-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-our-favorite-ios-18-features.2437231/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 08:12:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/the-macrumors-show-our-favorite-ios-18-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> has now been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/apple-releases-ios-18/">officially released</a> after months of beta testing. On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/ios-18-our-favorite-features/id1602394741?i=1000670178529">The MacRumors Show</a>, we talk through our top features in Apple's latest major software update.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nxkWRa6VnzM?si=B1blrL89WTzQ7Ox6" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We go through some of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;'s significant system changes, including the redesigned Control Center and new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> customization tools, as well as some of the smaller quality-of-life enhancements such as the Passwords app, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a> support, improvements to the Notes app, and emojis as tapbacks in Messages. We also touch on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> mirroring in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, and some of the areas we'd like to see Apple work on for next year's updates. The next major version of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will be iOS 18.1, which will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/13/apple-intelligence-features-timing/">start to bring Apple Intelligence</a> to ordinary users around the world. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/13/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16-announced/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the Apple Watch Series 10, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a>, and everything else that was announced at Apple's "It's Glowtime" event.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/the-macrumors-show-our-favorite-ios-18-features/">The MacRumors Show: Our Favorite iOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-our-favorite-ios-18-features.2437231/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains How AirPods 4 Feature &#039;Great&#039; Active Noise Cancellation Without Ear Tips</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-explains-airpods-4-noise-cancellation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-airpods-4-feature-great-active-noise-cancellation-without-ear-tips.2437222/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 07:19:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-explains-airpods-4-noise-cancellation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a recent interview <a href="https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/weve-got-to-make-it-happen-how-apple-designed-airpods-4-for-effective-anc-130008844.html">with <em>Engadget</em></a>, Apple's vice president of hardware engineering Kate Bergeron and AirPods marketing director Eric Treski explained how the company was able to add "great" active noise cancellation (ANC) to the higher-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-unveils-airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a>, even though the earbuds have an "open-ear design" without silicone ear tips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/AirPods-Buyers-Guide-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966718" /><br/>
Apple said the H2 chip and "computational audio" were significant factors in adding ANC to the standard AirPods for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
"It's even computationally more intense in many ways than it is with the AirPods Pro," said Bergeron, in regards to ANC on the AirPods 4.<br/>
<br/>
"It's really, really hard to create this great ANC quality in a non-ear-tip product," said Treski. "The power of the H2 allows that, so we're actually doing a lot with the H2 chip to manage ANC quality and listen from the mics for environmental noise to make sure we're canceling as much as possible."<br/>
<br/>
Apple said the revised shape and acoustic architecture of the AirPods 4 also contributes to the earbuds having effective ANC.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.engadget.com/audio/headphones/weve-got-to-make-it-happen-how-apple-designed-airpods-4-for-effective-anc-130008844.html">full interview</a> offers additional details about how Apple designed the AirPods 4, which became available in stores today. There are two types of AirPods 4, with only the higher-end &#36;179 ones offering active noise cancellation.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 4</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/apple-explains-airpods-4-noise-cancellation/">Apple Explains How AirPods 4 Feature &#039;Great&#039; Active Noise Cancellation Without Ear Tips</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-airpods-4-feature-great-active-noise-cancellation-without-ear-tips.2437222/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Camera Control: Everything You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-using-new-camera-control-button/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-camera-control-everything-you-need-to-know.2437219/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 07:12:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-using-new-camera-control-button&#038;post_date=1726852363/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Camera Control</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest iPhone 16 models include a new Camera Control button (located on the lower right-hand side when holding the phone in portrait mode). The new button aims to make it easier to adjust photography settings when shooting with the iPhone in both portrait and landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-capture-button.jpg" alt="" width="960" height="540" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966095" /><br/>
A simple press of the Camera Control button brings up the Camera app when the iPhone is unlocked. Once the Camera app is open, another press takes a picture, while pressing and holding the button records video for as long as you hold it down.<br/>
<br/>
Within the Camera app, a light press on the button engages a haptic click that also allows for adjusting things like manual exposure and zoom, thanks to a handy sliding interface that operates similarly to a camera dial. This gesture also reveals a clean preview of the scene you're capturing by hiding all on-screen Camera app tools. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/camera-control-menu.jpg" alt="camera" width="3381" height="1902" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967316" /><br/>
You can also use the button as a touch interface on the menu the Camera Control button brings up: A light double press invokes a range of photographic adjustment tools in a subtle UI. You can swipe through this menu and select individual options with a further light press. You can also choose between multiple styles and adjust the tone. All of these tools are adjustable with a swipe, while a double light press returns you to the main Camera Control menu:<br/>
<div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><br/>
  <ul><br/>
    <li>Exposure</li><br/>
    <li>Depth</li><br/>
    <li>Zoom</li><br/>
  </ul><br/>
</div><br/>
<div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><br/>
  <ul><br/>
    <li>Cameras</li><br/>
    <li>Styles</li><br/>
    <li>Tone</li><br/>
  </ul><br/>
</div><br/>
<div style="clear: both;"></div><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-capture-button.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964713" /><br/>
The Camera Control button can also be used to trigger third-party camera apps, giving more flexibility to users who prefer other photography tools. It's also integrated with Visual Intelligence (an aspect of forthcoming Apple Intelligence), allowing users to pull up contextual information about objects or scenes in front of the camera. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Adjusting Camera Control Pressure</h2><br/>
If you're having trouble engaging the light-press functions, or you find that the button is a little too sensitive for you, you can adjust the level of pressure that it responds to. If you feel that it's overly sensitive, you can make it firmer; if it's not sensitive enough, you can make it respond to lighter presses. The following steps show you how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open <strong>Settings</strong> on your iPhone.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Accessibility</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Under "Physical & Motor," tap <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Switch from the <strong>Default</strong> setting to the <strong>Lighter</strong> or <strong>Firmer</strong> options.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/adjust-camera-control-pressure-sensitivity-iphone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967244" /><br/>
<br/>
If you stay on this menu screen, you can try out the different pressure levels of the Camera Control button without engaging the Camera app, so make sure you give all three options a try before settling on one.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Disable Clean Preview</h2><br/>
By default, using the Camera Control button in the Camera app engages Clean Preview mode. This option hides everything in the Camera UI when the Camera Control button is lightly pressed, so you don't need to worry about accidentally touching camera lens adjustments while shooting. Another advantage is that it removes all distractions from the screen, leaving only the image â€” perfect for composing a shot.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/clean-preview-example-camera-control.jpg" alt="camera" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967256" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Clean Preview enabled (left) vs. Clean Preview disabled</em></div><br/>
What if you do want to have access to all the various Camera app adjustments while also using Camera Control? Fortunately, there's an easy way to disable Clean Preview and make the other Camera tools visible. The following steps show you how it's done.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>On your iPhone, open <strong>Settings</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Camera</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Toggle off the switch next to <strong>Clean Preview</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/disable-clean-preview-camera-control-iphone-16.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967259" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. To reinstate Camera app features that are hidden by a light press on the Camera Control button, simply toggle back on the <strong>Clean Preview</strong> option in <strong>Settings âž Camera âž Camera Control</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Disable Light Press Adjustments</h2><br/>
If you find yourself accidentally engaging the Camera Control adjustments when taking a picture in high-motion environments (like inadvertently zooming in or changing exposure settings), you can remove light press functionality from the Camera Control button entirely. Here's how it's done:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open <strong>Settings</strong> on your iPhone.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Accessibility</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Under "Physical & Motor," tap <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Toggle off the switch next to <strong>Show Adjustments</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/disable-camera-control-light-press-adjustments-iphone-16.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967234" /><br/>
<br/>
This option removes the Camera Control interface and its corresponding light-press adjustments, so now you don't need to worry about accidentally engaging them while shooting. This essentially makes the Camera Control button a simple shutter button after you have opened the Camera app with the first press.<br/>
<br/>
To reinstate Camera Control adjustments that are activated by a light press, simply toggle back on the <strong>Show Adjustments</strong> option in <strong>Settings -> Accessibility -> Camera Control</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Change Camera Control Launch Camera Gesture</h2><br/>
If you find yourself accidentally opening the Camera app by unintentionally pressing the Camera Control button, you can either disable the button entirely (see below), or you can change the single-click gesture that invokes the Camera app to a double-click gesture. The following steps show you how to do the latter:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>On your iPhone, open <strong>Settings</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Camera</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Under "Launch Camera," tap <strong>Double Click</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/change-gesture-to-open-camera-app-iphone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967267" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. A single click of the Camera Control button will now do nothing, while a double click will get you into the Camera app or any other third-party camera app that you have assigned to the button.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Changing Camera Control Functionality</h2><br/>
While the new button aims to make it easier to adjust photography settings when shooting, if you want, you can make it work as a simple QR code scanner or a Magnifier. <br/>
<br/>
For people whose job involves frequently interact with QR codes, this Camera Control feature could be a game-changer. In warehouse environments, for example, employees could quickly scan inventory tags without navigating through multiple app screens, significantly speeding up stock checks and order processing. The neat thing is that the Camera Control button retains its zoom function in the app, and it also allows for one-handed operation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/magnifier-code-scanner.jpg" alt="magnifier scanner" width="3250" height="3030" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967327" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Magnifier tool (left) vs. Code scanner</em></div><br/>
As for Magnifier access, Camera Control could prove invaluable in various scenarios. For people with visual impairments, the feature allows for instant magnification of small text on menus, product labels, or medication instructions without them having to fumble through apps. <br/>
<br/>
Camera Control also retains its zoom adjustment function in the Magnifier tool, and adds a menu that includes Magnifier options for brightness, contrast, filters, torch, and more if you add them via the Magnifier's settings menu.<br/>
<br/>
Here's how to re-assign the Camera Control button for QR code scanning or magnifying:<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>On your iPhone, open <strong>Settings</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Camera</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Code Scanner</strong> or <strong>Magnifier</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/use-camera-control-code-scanner-magnifier.jpg" alt="settings" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967304" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. Now when you click Camera Control, depending on your preference the QR code scanner app or the Magnifier app will be instantly invoked. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Disable Camera Control</h2><br/>
If you find yourself accidentally opening the Camera app by unintentionally pressing the Camera Control button, or if you just don't find yourself using it for whatever reason, you can turn off the button's functionality completely. The following steps show you how it's done.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open <strong>Settings</strong> on your iPhone.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Accessibility</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Under "Physical & Motor," tap <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Toggle off the switch next to <strong>Camera Control</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/disable-camera-control-iphone-16.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967240" /><br/>
<br/>
Having done that, the Camera Control button will no longer engage the Camera app and its corresponding functionality, so you no longer have to worry about pressing it â€“ it won't do anything.<br/>
<br/>
To reinstate Camera Control features, simply toggle back on the "Camera Control" switch in <strong>Settings âž Accessibility âž Camera Control</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
If you don't quite get on with Camera Control, don't give up on it completely. It can take a while to get used to. It's also worth noting that the button will soon get additional features: In a software update coming later this year, Camera Control will introduce a two-stage shutter that lets you automatically lock focus and exposure with a light press â€” so you can re-frame your shot without losing focus on your subject.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/camera-control/">Camera Control</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-using-new-camera-control-button/">iPhone 16 Camera Control: Everything You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-camera-control-everything-you-need-to-know.2437219/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the New iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/hands-on-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-iphone-16.2437208/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 06:13:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/hands-on-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Happy <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> launch day! Apple's latest &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models are now in the hands of consumers, and we thought we'd do a quick first impressions overview for those of you who are waiting for a delivery or who are still on the fence about upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xf5U_eixb7w" title="iPhone 16 First Impressions" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
This year's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is the biggest upgrade for a standard model that we've seen in some time. Performance is not too far off from the Pro models, the Action Button is no longer Pro exclusive, and Apple brought the fun new Camera Control button to all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, not just the 16 Pro and Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
The Action Button is more useful than ever before with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> because you can assign Control Center actions and even third-party app functionality. It can turn on the flashlight, open the Translate app, toggle on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a>, open your favorite app, and so much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-hands-on-camera-control.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967295" /><br/>
Apple has talked up the new Camera Control button, which is meant to be used for taking photos in either landscape or portrait mode. It is a little confusing at first, because it's a button, but it also supports pressure sensitivity touch gestures like swipes. The placement is not super convenient in portrait mode and can be a little awkward to use, and it takes some time to adjust to how the button works.<br/>
<br/>
The button does do a lot, though, and you can press twice to snap a photo, press once and then press and hold to take a video, or use gestures to swap different tools to adjust photo parameters.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-hands-on-camera.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967296" /><br/>
If you're holding your camera in landscape orientation, the button placement makes more sense, but a lot of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> photography is done in portrait mode rather than landscape mode. Apple moved the camera lenses from a diagonal position to a vertical position, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models now support spatial photo and videos for the Vision Pro, but it's not clear how many people are actually using that functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added new Photographic Styles and a handy little adjustment pad for editing the intensity and look of those styles, so it's overall a much more useful feature than before. You can set up a favorite style and then apply it to all of your images for a custom look.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-hands-on-front.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967297" /><br/>
For video, there's an Audio Mix feature that changes the way that audio sounds in your video recordings. You can pull out the voice of the subject of a video while muting the background noise, or direct all sound forward like in a movie.<br/>
<br/>
There are new color options this year, and the teal &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that we tested was a bright, vibrant shade of blue. You can also get ultramarine (a dark purple blue), pink, white, and black.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-hands-on-back.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967298" /><br/>
As for the A18 chip, depending on which &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; you're upgrading from, you might not see any speed improvements because most &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps don't stress the CPU or GPU of modern processors, but the A18 does support Apple Intelligence. All &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models get the Apple Intelligence features coming in iOS 18.1 and later updates.<br/>
<br/>
For a smartphone starting at &#36;799, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is a surprisingly good value this year, and it's a worthwhile upgrade if you're coming from anything older than an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>. With the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and beyond, it's a less obvious upgrade, but there are still some great features to look forward to.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/hands-on-iphone-16/">Hands-On With the New iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-iphone-16.2437208/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Forgot to Pre-Order an iPhone 16? Apple Store Pickup Available Today at Most Locations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-apple-store-pickup-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/forgot-to-pre-order-an-iphone-16-apple-store-pickup-available-today-at-most-locations.2437193/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 04:44:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-apple-store-pickup-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max models are now being delivered to customers worldwide following the pre-order period that began on Friday, September 13. For those who didn't pre-order the Pro models or chose to wait, many configurations now have estimated delivery dates in October. However, there's good news for customers wanting their devices sooner: Select Apple Store locations globally are offering same-day or next-day pickup options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="3020" height="1698" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967113" /><br/>
As of writing, Apple's online stores in the United States and Canada haven't yet been updated to show pickup availability, but shortages aren't expected and there is unlikely to be much variation state by state. Meanwhile across the pond, all â€ŒiPhone 16 colors and configurations are available for Apple Store pickup today in countries including France, Germany, Italy, Spain, and the United Kingdom. Apple Stores in Australia, China, India, Japan, Malaysia, Mexico, South Korea, TÃ¼rkiye, and the UAE are also offering same-day pickup options.<br/>
<br/>
To order a product with â€ŒApple Storeâ€Œ pickup, add the product to your bag on Apple.com or in the â€ŒApple Storeâ€Œ app, proceed to checkout, select the "I'll pick it up" option, enter your ZIP or postal code, choose an available â€ŒApple Storeâ€Œ location, select a pickup date, and select a 15-minute check-in window. Payment is completed online, and a valid government-issued photo ID and the order number may be required upon pickup.<br/>
<br/>
â€ŒiPhone 16 models may also be available for walk-in customers at â€ŒApple Storeâ€Œ locations with sufficient inventory, but availability can't be guaranteed. Walk-in customers may be placed into a separate queue with lower priority upon arrival to the store.<br/>
<br/>
The standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus are a big update over previous standard models, coming with many features that were once limited to Pro models. New capabilities include a customizable Action button, a new Camera Control button for quick access to camera functions, a 48MP Fusion camera, macro photography, a new A18 chip capable of powering Apple Intelligence (forthcoming), and more.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 16 Pro models also have several new features, including larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays with thinner bezels, longer battery life, a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera, a faster A18 Pro chip, Wi-Fi 7 support, faster 5G, faster charging, and more. Click the tags at the bottom of this article for all the details.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-apple-store-pickup-today/">Forgot to Pre-Order an iPhone 16? Apple Store Pickup Available Today at Most Locations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/forgot-to-pre-order-an-iphone-16-apple-store-pickup-available-today-at-most-locations.2437193/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro Orders Start Arriving to Customers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-now-arriving-to-customers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-orders-start-arriving-to-customers.2437125/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:01:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-now-arriving-to-customers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's Friday, September 20 in Australia and New Zealand, so customers in those countries who pre-ordered an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, Apple Watch Series 10, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a> are starting to receive their device deliveries.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-pro-max.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964613" /><br/>
Apple fans who ordered a new product are sharing photos and first impressions of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, Apple Watch Series 10, and &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; on Instagram, Reddit, the <em>MacRumors</em> forums, and other social networks. If you've already received one of the new devices, let us know in the comments below and make sure to share pictures and your initial thoughts!<br/>
<br/>
With no retail stores in New Zealand, customers in Australia are the first to be able to pick up new devices or purchase an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>. Available in-store stock in Australia will provide insight into what we can expect in other Apple Stores around the world, but so far, there have been no rumors of shortages.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; orders did sell out during the pre-order period, and online shipping estimates now range into October. If you missed pre-orders, you can likely get one of the new devices at an &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; or a nearby location like Target, Walmart, or Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
Following New Zealand and Australia, sales and deliveries of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models and the new Apple Watches will begin in Asia, the Middle East, Europe, and finally, North America. Many Apple Stores worldwide will be opening up early at around 8:00 a.m. local time to allow customers to pick up reserved devices and make walk-in purchases.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to stay tuned to <em>MacRumors</em>, as we'll have a hands-on and unboxing tomorrow, followed by deep dives into the feature set of the new devices, camera comparisons, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-16-now-arriving-to-customers/">iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro Orders Start Arriving to Customers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-orders-start-arriving-to-customers.2437125/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS Sequoia Public Betas With Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apple-seeds-first-ios-18-1-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-ios-18-1-ipados-18-1-and-macos-sequoia-public-betas-with-apple-intelligence.2437076/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:46:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apple-seeds-first-ios-18-1-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first public betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its October launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
Public beta testers who have <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">signed up for Apple's beta testing program</a> can download the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 updates by opening up the Settings app, tapping into the Software Update section and selecting the Public Beta option.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 are the first updates that includes Apple Intelligence features. Not all AI capabilities have been added, but the beta features Writing Tools, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> changes, summaries, and smart replies. Note that to use Apple Intelligence features, you need an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, or M-series Mac or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Writing Tools are available whenever text can be selected and edited, and the feature can be used for spell checking, correcting grammar, rewriting your work with a new tone, and summarizing text.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has been overhauled with a new design that includes a subtle glow around the display, and Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; means you don't have to speak to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to get answers. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;â€Œ can follow along if you stumble over your words, and can maintain context between requests. Safari can summarize articles, and there's a new Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode that intelligently highlights only important notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Smart replies are available in Messages and Mail, plus the Mail app surfaces priority time sensitive messages and puts them at the top of your inbox. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> has a Memory Movie feature for creating slideshows based on text descriptions, and there is a Clean Up tool for unwanted objects in your photos.<br/>
<br/>
All iOS 18.1 users can now access phone call recording and transcribing, with recorded calls saved in the Notes app, but summarizing phone calls from those transcriptions is an Apple Intelligence feature. Today's update also brings spatial photo capabilities to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro and Pro Max. <br/>
<br/>
More on all of the features that are available in the betas right now can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">found in our Apple Intelligence guide</a>. Image Playground, Genmoji, and other new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">have not yet been implemented</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apple-seeds-first-ios-18-1-public-beta/">Apple Seeds First iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS Sequoia Public Betas With Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-ios-18-1-ipados-18-1-and-macos-sequoia-public-betas-with-apple-intelligence.2437076/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses Will Come to These Additional U.S. States</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apple-lists-3-more-states-committed-to-wallet-ids/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-iphone-drivers-licenses-will-come-to-these-additional-u-s-states.2437079/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apple-lists-3-more-states-committed-to-wallet-ids/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In select U.S. states, residents can <a href="https://learn.wallet.apple/id">add their driver's license or state ID to the Wallet app</a> on the iPhone and Apple Watch, providing a convenient and contactless way to display proof of identity or age at select airports and businesses, and in select apps. The list of states where the feature is available currently includes Arizona, Maryland, Colorado, Georgia, Ohio, Hawaii, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-california/">most recently California</a>, and Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/09/apple-brings-california-drivers-licenses-and-state-ids-to-apple-wallet/">announced</a> that Montana, New Mexico, and West Virginia are now committed to supporting the feature in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-wallet-drivers-license-feature-iPhone-15-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947140" /><br/>
Apple also announced that users will soon be able to present their Wallet app ID in person for select services, including CLEAR member enrollment at airports. The feature will also be supported in the CLEAR, MyChart, and Uber Eats apps soon.<br/>
<br/>
In 2022, Apple said Connecticut, Iowa, Kentucky, Mississippi, Oklahoma, and Utah were also committed to offering driver's licenses in the Wallet app, but none of those states have rolled out the feature yet, and it is unclear if any still plan to. The feature has yet to expand beyond the U.S., but it will work with Japan's My Number Card eventually.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Participating Airports</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-Wallet-ID-TSA.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-868295" /><br/>
Apple Wallet app IDs can be used at select TSA checkpoints within select U.S. airports:<ul><li>Baltimore/Washington International Thurgood Marshall Airport (BWI)</li><br/>
<li>Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA)</li><br/>
<li>Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX)</li><br/>
<li>Denver International Airport (DEN)</li><br/>
<li>Hartsfieldâ€“Jackson Atlanta International Airport (ATL)</li><br/>
<li>Cincinnati/Northern Kentucky Airport (CVG)</li><br/>
<li>John Glenn Columbus International Airport (CMH)</li><br/>
<li>San Francisco International Airport (SFO)</li><br/>
<li>San Jose Mineta International Airport (SJC)</li></ul>Apple says travelers should refer to TSA checkpoint signage to confirm availability of the feature, and the <a href="https://www.tsa.gov/travel/digital-id/map">TSA's website offers more details</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/apple-lists-3-more-states-committed-to-wallet-ids/">Apple Announces iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses Will Come to These Additional U.S. States</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-iphone-drivers-licenses-will-come-to-these-additional-u-s-states.2437079/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Expands to More Californians</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-california/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-expands-to-more-californians.2437074/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:30:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-california/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in California <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/09/apple-brings-california-drivers-licenses-and-state-ids-to-apple-wallet/">can now add</a> their digital driver's licenses and IDs in the Apple Wallet app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch, with California expanding an ongoing test of the digital license feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961769" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-california-drivers-license.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Several <em>MacRumors</em> readers have reported seeing the California license as an option in the Wallet app, under the label "California mDL Pilot." Prior to now, only a limited number of people were seeing the option.<br/>
<br/>
Wallet app integration is part of California's mobile driver's license effort, which kicked off a year ago. More than 500,000 people have already added a driver's license or ID to the California DMV Wallet app, where California tested the option before starting to roll it out to the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced California's Wallet license plans <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-drivers-license-california-soon/">back in August</a>, and said that it was working with California to bring IDs to Apple Wallet.<blockquote>"We're excited to be working with the state of California to bring IDs in Apple Wallet to Apple's home state soon, and provide residents with an easy, secure, and private way to present their California driver's license and state ID in person and in app using Apple Wallet," said Jennifer Bailey, Apple's vice president of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet. "Whether using IDs in Apple Wallet to breeze through travel, or to securely verify age or identity at businesses, California driver's licenses and state IDs in Apple Wallet make ID presentment seamless - all with the security built into iPhone and Apple Watch."</blockquote><br/>
IDs and licenses stored in the Wallet app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> can be used for TSA screenings at select airports (including SFO, LAX, and SJC) and for age verification at select stores. Right now, California's mobile wallet support is still in an early stage, and only 1.5 million participants are able to sign up.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/California?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#California</a> residents can now present their ID in Apple Wallet on iPhone and Apple Watch at select TSA checkpoints when departing from <a href="https://twitter.com/flyLAXairport?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@flyLAXairport</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/flySFO?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@flySFO</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/FlySJC?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FlySJC</a>.<br>Not a CA resident? Stay tuned for updates! Learn more at <a href="https://t.co/f4yOHhEKTp">https://t.co/f4yOHhEKTp</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TravelWithEase?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TravelWithEase</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/CA_DMV?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CA_DMV</a> <a href="https://t.co/k0ejZd7rhy">pic.twitter.com/k0ejZd7rhy</a></p>&mdash; TSA_Pacific (@TSA_Pacific) <a href="https://twitter.com/TSA_Pacific/status/1836816316952715287?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 19, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
California requires people to continue to carry a physical license or ID card because the digital license is not accepted by law enforcement, state government agencies, and most businesses.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced a new Wallet app that supported digital IDs back in 2022, but states have been slow to adopt the feature. So far, only Arizona, Colorado, Georgia, Maryland, Hawaii, and Ohio have implemented support. Apple said in 2022 that Connecticut, Iowa, Kentucky, Oklahoma, and Utah are working on support, and today added that Montana, New Mexico, and West Virginia also plan to adopt the functionality. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-california/">iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Expands to More Californians</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-expands-to-more-californians.2437074/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Display Shipments for M4 MacBook Air and Low-Cost iPad Expected to Start in October</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/display-shipments-macbook-air-ipad-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/display-shipments-for-m4-macbook-air-and-low-cost-ipad-expected-to-start-in-october.2437070/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:19:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/display-shipments-macbook-air-ipad-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Display panel shipments for refreshed versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> and the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> will begin in October, display analyst Ross Young said in a <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1836813783861178653">tweet for subscribers</a>. Apple is working on new M4 versions of the 13-inch and 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, as well as a new version of the 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m2-macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959392" /><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/15/m4-macs-and-new-ipads-at-next-apple-event/">expected to refresh</a> the MacBook Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> in October of this year, and it would make sense for a new low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to be introduced alongside those devices. Panel shipments that start in October suggest that the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; would not be ready for an October event.<br/>
<br/>
As for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said that new models with M4 chips <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/">will come out </a> in the first quarter of 2025, and on Twitter, he added that the October display shipment timing sounds correct for a Q1 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">This timing lines up for the MacBook Air, which is now scheduled for calendar Q1. January - March. <a href="https://t.co/PeiR2WLHDN">https://t.co/PeiR2WLHDN</a> <a href="https://t.co/05qJCCon29">https://t.co/05qJCCon29</a></p>&mdash; Mark Gurman (@markgurman) <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1836823803240010161?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 19, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
The October panel shipment timing is unusual for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, so we will need to see what Apple has planned in the coming months. Rumors right now suggest that we can count on an October event that features at least some new Macs and iPads. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/display-shipments-macbook-air-ipad-october/">Display Shipments for M4 MacBook Air and Low-Cost iPad Expected to Start in October</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/display-shipments-for-m4-macbook-air-and-low-cost-ipad-expected-to-start-in-october.2437070/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Suspends MacBook Air Supplier Due to &#039;Quality Issues&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/macbook-air-supplier-quality-issues-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-suspends-macbook-air-supplier-due-to-quality-issues.2437065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 09:36:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/macbook-air-supplier-quality-issues-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has suspended MacBook bearing supplier Kersen's production for inspection purposes due to "quality issues," and shifted orders to other suppliers through the end of the year, according to a report today from Taiwanese industry publication <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240919PD209.html"><em>DigiTimes</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/m1-macbook-air-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-771674" /><br/>
The report said the suspension came after Apple discovered a high defect rate with the Chinese supplier's bearings in August. The bearings are used in previous-generation MacBook Air models, rather than the latest models, according to the report.<br/>
<br/>
None of the MacBook Air models with defective bearings reached the market, the report added:<blockquote>Industry insiders indicate that the defects were present from the beginning, but Apple only detected them during destructive testing later in the process. A subsequent full batch inspection revealed a high defect rate. Fortunately, none of the faulty products have reached the market. However, bearing defects typically take one to two years of use before becoming noticeable to consumers.</blockquote>It is unclear exactly which component the report is referring to.<br/>
<br/>
The report cites industry sources who believe that Apple's alleged "aggressive pricing tactics" with component vendors increases the risk of quality issues.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/19/macbook-air-supplier-quality-issues-report/">Apple Reportedly Suspends MacBook Air Supplier Due to &#039;Quality Issues&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-suspends-macbook-air-supplier-due-to-quality-issues.2437065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
