<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 03:03:19 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Passwords App Bug Left Users Vulnerable to Phishing Attacks for Months Before Being Fixed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/19/apple-passwords-app-phishing-vulnerability/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-passwords-app-bug-left-users-vulnerable-to-phishing-attacks-for-months-before-being-fixed.2453467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 02:10:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/19/apple-passwords-app-phishing-vulnerability/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple fixed a bug in its Passwords app with December's iOS 18.2 update that had left users vulnerable to phishing attacks in the three months since the launch of iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Passwords-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959050" /><br/>
According to an Apple security update spotted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2025/03/18/apples-passwords-app-was-vulnerable-to-phishing-attacks-for-nearly-three-months-after-launch/">9to5Mac</a></em>, the Passwords app was sending unencrypted requests for the logos and icons associated with users' stored passwords.<br/>
<br/>
Without protections of encryption, an attacker on the same Wi-Fi network could redirect a user's browser to a clone phishing site where login details could be stolen. The vulnerability was first discovered by developer Mysk's security researchers and reported in September.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's iOS 18.2 security release notes described the bug like so:<br/>
<blockquote>Impact: A user in a privileged network position may be able to leak sensitive information<br/>
<br/>
Description: This issue was addressed by using HTTPS when sending information over the network.</blockquote><div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VUSB3FK1dKA?si=Z6oaAETbWB3SD4ro" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Apple lists the bug in security content updates for the Mac, iPad, and Vision Pro, indicating that this issue was fixed across multiple OSes.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/19/apple-passwords-app-phishing-vulnerability/">Apple Passwords App Bug Left Users Vulnerable to Phishing Attacks for Months Before Being Fixed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-passwords-app-bug-left-users-vulnerable-to-phishing-attacks-for-months-before-being-fixed.2453467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will Apple&#039;s Large-Screened Foldable be an iPad or a Mac?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-foldable-ipad-or-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-apples-large-screened-foldable-be-an-ipad-or-a-mac.2453448/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:09:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-foldable-ipad-or-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Along with a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple is working on a larger foldable device that's somewhere around 19 inches, but rumors have been split on whether it's an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> or a Mac. Some reports refer to the device as an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, while some call it a Mac, and the split seems to come down to the operating system on the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-Fold-Vertical-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988570" /><br/>
<h2>Is it a Mac?</h2><br/>
Some rumors have suggested that Apple is developing a foldable MacBook with an all-display design. The MacBook already has a foldable design, of course, but the difference here would be a single display without an included keyboard and trackpad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Foldable-Screen-MacBook-Concept-Astropad.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952144" /><br/>
A foldable Mac would be able to be folded in half and used like a traditional MacBook with a virtual keyboard, or it could be unfolded and used as a display when paired with an external keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> has referred to Apple's larger foldable device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/20-inch-foldable-macbook-crease-free-rumor/">as a MacBook</a>, and he thinks it's going to have an 18.8 to 20.2-inch display. Display analyst Ross Young has also written about Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">work on a notebook</a> with an 18.8-inch display.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em> said in December that Apple is working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/15/iphone-17-air-19-inch-macbook-report/">a 19-inch MacBook</a> with a foldable screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Is it an iPad?</h2><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has referred to Apple's large-screened foldable device as an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and he says it's going to have a display that's around 20 inches in size.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/FoldPad-Redux-24-Magenta-and-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934078" /><br/>
<em>The Elec</em> said in 2022 that Apple was developing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/apple-20-inch-display-future-macbook-pro/">a foldable device</a> around 20 inches in size that folds down to 15.3 inches, and research firm Omdia believes that Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-oled-roadmap/">20.3-inch foldable OLED iPad</a> that will be positioned as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While Kuo has also mainly referred to Apple's foldable as a MacBook, in 2023, he called it an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and said that it would come with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/30/foldable-ipad-kickstand-2024/">carbon fiber kickstand</a>. Of course, Kuo initially said that such a foldable would come in 2024, something that did not happen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Or both?</h2><br/>
When thinking of a foldable with an all-display design, it's easier to picture an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, which is already a single screen. It makes sense for Apple to create an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; that's able to fold down for portability and then unfold into a larger workspace, but what if it runs macOS?<br/>
<br/>
We don't have much of a reference for an all-display Mac since it's not a form factor we're familiar with, but a 20-inch device that's all display and folds in half would definitely be something of a hybrid &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Mac device.<br/>
<br/>
Analyst Jeff Pu <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/apple-foldable-macos-prediction/">recently said</a> that Apple's large-screened foldable will be a MacBook-iPad hybrid that's likely to run macOS, rather than iPadOS. Such a device would presumably have a touchscreen, and would require notable changes to the Mac operating system as it does not support touch input. Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/ios-19-big-design-changes/">also claimed</a> that some of the design updates that Apple is making in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> and macOS 16 to unify the operating systems will pave the way for foldable devices and touchscreen Macs, so a hybrid is a possibility.<br/>
<br/>
Whether the large-screened foldable is ultimately an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; or a Mac will come down to the operating system that Apple is planning to use. If the device runs macOS, it'll be in the Mac family, and if it runs iPadOS, it'll be in the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; family.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Launch Date</h2><br/>
Rumors about the release date for Apple's foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;/Mac have targeted as early as 2026 to as late as 2028, so it's not quite clear when we'll see the device. It's possible that Apple is planning a launch for as soon as next year, and if that's the case, rumors should really start picking up in the next couple of months.<br/>
<br/>
If we don't start hearing more soon, we can assume that Apple is aiming for a later launch date in 2027 or beyond.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-foldable-ipad-or-mac/">Will Apple&#039;s Large-Screened Foldable be an iPad or a Mac?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-apples-large-screened-foldable-be-an-ipad-or-a-mac.2453448/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 18.3.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-3-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-3-1.2453447/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 15:55:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-3-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 18.3.1, so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users who have upgraded to iOS 18.3.2 are no longer able to downgrade to the prior version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. Apple released iOS 18.3.2 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/11/apple-releases-ios-18-3-2/">on March 10</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.3.1-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988425" /><br/>
It is not unusual for Apple to stop signing older versions of iOS after releasing an update. Software that is not signed cannot be installed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; due to a server-side verification check, and it keeps &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users from installing outdated versions of iOS. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models compatible with &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; are only eligible to download and run iOS 18.3.2 at this time.<br/>
<br/>
By preventing customers from installing older versions of iOS or downgrading, Apple ensures that devices have the latest security improvements.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.3.2 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/11/ios-18-3-2-security-fixes/">introduced important security fixes</a>, addressing a vulnerability that may have been actively exploited.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-3-1/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 18.3.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-3-1.2453447/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nanoleaf Launches New Screen Mirror Lightstrip for Mac Displays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/nanoleaf-screen-mirror-lightstrip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-new-screen-mirror-lightstrip-for-mac-displays.2453442/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:48:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/nanoleaf-screen-mirror-lightstrip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nanoleaf today announced the launch of the PC Screen Mirror Lightstrip, a new desktop lighting option that is designed to make desktop gaming and entertainment more immersive with rainbow lighting effects.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/nanoleaf-light-strip.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995652" /><br/>
The Screen Mirror Lightstrip connects to a computer using USB-C, and it is able to provide real-time dynamic mirroring that matches whatever is on your screen. It can match the output of a game or a movie, or it can sync to music, with the lights changing to match the rhythm of a song. With a Nanoleaf Premium subscription, there is an Orchestrator mode that provides access to different moods for music experience customization.<br/>
<br/>
Nanoleaf designed the Screen Mirror Lightstrip for displays up to 32 inches in size, and it features a flexible zigzag design for simple and precise installation.<br/>
<br/>
The Lightstrip pairs to a display using the Nanoleaf Desktop app, which is available for both PCs and Macs. More than 16 million colors are supported for dynamic lighting animations and visual effects.<br/>
<br/>
The PC Screen Mirror Lightstrip from Nanoleaf is priced at &#36;50 and it can be <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/essentials/lightstrips/pc-screen-mirror-lightstrip/">pre-ordered from the Nanoleaf website</a>. It is set to ship at the end of March.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/nanoleaf-screen-mirror-lightstrip/">Nanoleaf Launches New Screen Mirror Lightstrip for Mac Displays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-new-screen-mirror-lightstrip-for-mac-displays.2453442/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next Year&#039;s iPhone 18 Pro Already Rumored to Have Five New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-18-pro-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-years-iphone-18-pro-already-rumored-to-have-five-new-features.2453438/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:00:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-18-pro-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 18 Pro models are still around a year and a half away from launching, there are already some early rumors about the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-ghost-hand.jpg" alt="" width="1785" height="1004" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966100" /><br/>
Below, we recap some key iPhone 18 Pro rumors so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Under-Screen Face ID</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/face-id.jpg" alt="" width="1023" height="573" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966000" /><br/>
In April 2023, display industry analyst Ross Young shared a roadmap showing that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/under-display-face-id-to-debut-on-iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro models would feature under-display Face ID</a>. In May 2024, however, Young said he heard this change had been <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1786098652420911128">delayed until 2026</a>. If so, that means that under-screen Face ID could debut on the iPhone 18 Pro and iPhone 18 Pro Max next year.<br/>
<br/>
Even with under-screen Face ID, it is expected that the Dynamic Island will live on, but it might become smaller. Alternatively, the iPhone 18 Pro models could have only a pinhole at the top of the display for the front camera, similar to Android smartphones like Google's Pixel 9 and Samsung's Galaxy S25. It's too early to know yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Variable Aperture</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-design-cameras.jpg" alt="" width="923" height="517" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966096" /><br/>
The main 48-megapixel Fusion camera on both iPhone 18 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-18-pro-rumored-camera-upgrade/">will offer variable aperture</a>, according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
With variable aperture, users would be able to control the amount of light that passes through the camera's lens and reaches the sensor. The main cameras on iPhone 14 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro models have a fixed aperture of ƒ/1.78, and the lens is always fully open and shooting with this widest aperture. With the iPhone 18 Pro models, users would be able to manually change the aperture, according to this rumor.<br/>
<br/>
A variable aperture on iPhone 18 Pro models should provide users with greater control over depth of field, which refers to how sharp a subject appears in the foreground compared to the background. However, given that iPhones have smaller image sensors due to size restraints, it is unclear exactly how meaningful this improvement would be.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Image Sensor</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/iphone-12-pro-max-sensor-shift.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-771522" /><br/>
Samsung is developing a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-18-samsung-camera-sensor-report/">three-layer stacked camera sensor</a> that Apple is expected to use for iPhone 18 Pro models, according to <em>DigiTimes</em>. This advanced image sensor would make the iPhone 18's camera more responsive, and offer other benefits like reduced noise in photos, increased dynamic range, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The exact technology is called "PD-TR-Logic," according to a <a href="https://x.com/Jukanlosreve/status/1874358213011005628">leaker known as "Jukanlosreve"</a>, and it refers to a camera sensor with three layers of circuitry affixed to it.<br/>
<br/>
Sony has long been the exclusive supplier of image sensors for iPhone cameras, so Samsung entering the fray would be notable.<br/>
<br/>
In July 2024, Kuo said he expected Samsung to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/2026-iphone-48mp-camera-sensor-samsung/">begin shipping 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera sensors to Apple</a> for iPhones as early as 2026, which is when the iPhone 18 Pro models are expected to be released.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>C2 Modem</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-c1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990815" /><br/>
Apple debuted its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-unveils-c1/">custom-designed C1 modem</a> in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> last month, as part of a multi-year plan to transition away from Qualcomm modems.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's second-generation C2 modem will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/iphone-18-pro-c2-modem-rumor/">debut in the iPhone 18 Pro models</a> next year, according to Jeff Pu, an analyst who covers companies within Apple's supply chain. Unsurprisingly, expect the C2 modem to be faster than the C1, and for it to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apples-second-5g-modem-said-to-support-mmwave/">gain mmWave support</a> in the United States. Further power efficiency improvements are likely too.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A20 Pro Chip With Apple Intelligence Upgrade</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-iPhone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964551" /><br/>
Apple's A20 Pro chip for the iPhone 18 Pro models will be manufactured with TSMC's third-generation 3nm process, despite an initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/iphone-18-enhanced-2nm-chip-12gb-ram/">2nm rumor</a>, according to Pu. That is the same process that is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/a19-and-a19-pro-n3p-rumor/">expected to be used for the A19 Pro chip</a> coming in the iPhone 17 Pro models, so the iPhone 18 Pro models could have relatively small overall performance improvements compared to the previous generation.<br/>
<br/>
Pu does expect the A20 Pro chip to have one upgrade that he said will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/a20-chip-still-3nm-rumor/">benefit Apple Intelligence capabilities</a>. Specifically, he said the chip will use TSMC's so-called <a href="https://3dfabric.tsmc.com/english/dedicatedFoundry/technology/cowos.htm">Chip on Wafer on Substrate (CoWoS)</a> packaging technology, which would allow for tighter integration of the chip's processor, unified memory, and Neural Engine.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-18/">iPhone 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-18-pro-rumors/">Next Year&#039;s iPhone 18 Pro Already Rumored to Have Five New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-years-iphone-18-pro-already-rumored-to-have-five-new-features.2453438/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Experiencing Outage [Update: Fixed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-music-intermittent-issues/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-experiencing-outage-update-fixed.2453437/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:54:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-music-intermittent-issues/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> is facing an ongoing outage, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's System Status page</a>. The downtime started at 2:26 p.m. Eastern Time, and has not yet been resolved. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962031" /><br/>
Apple says that some users may be experiencing intermittent issues with the service, though it does not appear to be malfunctioning for all users. <br/>
<br/>
We'll update this article when the issue has been resolved. <br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> As of 4:20 p.m. Eastern Time, Apple says the issue has been fixed. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-music-intermittent-issues/">Apple Music Experiencing Outage [Update: Fixed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-experiencing-outage-update-fixed.2453437/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Now Available in Puerto Rico</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-pay-puerto-rico/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-now-available-in-puerto-rico.2453436/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:42:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-pay-puerto-rico/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> today expanded to Puerto Rico, which means <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac users living in the territory are now able to use &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; for purchases in retail stores and online, even without a mainland credit or debit card. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/apple-pay-puerto-rico.jpg" alt="" width="1641" height="923" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995614" /><br/>
Though Puerto Rico is a U.S. territory, &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; was not previously available for Puerto Rico banks, though Puerto Ricans have had access to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> and have been able to use &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; with U.S. credit and debit cards. <br/>
<br/>
As of right now, Banco Popular in Puerto Rico supports &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;, so Banco Popular cardholders in the territory can add eligible cards to the Wallet app to use as a contactless payment method. Banco Popular cards are able to be used at any location that accepts &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first launched &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; in 2014, and has expanded it to dozens of countries and territories around the world. <br/>
<br/>
In addition to expanding &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; to Puerto Rico today, Apple also launched the Tap to Provision feature in Hong Kong, Macao, and Mongolia. Tap to Provision lets users add eligible credit and debit cards to the Wallet app by tapping the card on the back of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-pay-puerto-rico/">Apple Pay Now Available in Puerto Rico</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-now-available-in-puerto-rico.2453436/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New MagSafe Charger Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/magsafe-charger-firmware-update-march-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-magsafe-charger-firmware.2453432/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:33:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/magsafe-charger-firmware-update-march-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a firmware update for the 25W <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> Charger that is compatible with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 and later and the latest AirPods. The updated firmware is version 2A146, up from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/25w-magsafe-charger-firmware-update/">the 2A143 firmware</a> that came out earlier this year. In the Settings app, the new firmware is version 136, up from 133.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965150" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/new-magsafe-charger.jpg" alt="" width="1764" height="992" /><br/>
Apple launched the 2024 &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charger alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, and it is able to charge them at up to 25W. For the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, charging is capped at 15W.<br/>
<br/>
Because firmware updates are released quietly over the air, Apple does not provide release notes. We don't know what new features or bug fixes might be included in the software.<br/>
<br/>
There is no clear method for updating a ‌&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;‌ charger's firmware, but it needs to be plugged in and connected to an Apple device for a firmware update to initiate. You can check your ‌&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;‌ Charger's firmware by following the instructions in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/check-firmware-apple-magsafe-charger/">MagSafe Charger how to</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/magsafe-charger-firmware-update-march-2025/">Apple Releases New MagSafe Charger Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-magsafe-charger-firmware.2453432/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Long-Rumored Foldable iPhone is Starting to Sound Serious</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/foldable-iphone-rumors-sounding-serious/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-long-rumored-foldable-iphone-is-starting-to-sound-serious.2453431/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:31:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/foldable-iphone-rumors-sounding-serious/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While it might feel like a foldable iPhone has been two years away for years now, rumors about the device are finally starting to sound serious.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Homescreen.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995585" /><br/>
There are now several sources who agree that Apple's first foldable iPhone will feature a 7.8-inch inner display when unfolded, along with a 5.5-inch outer display. Those sources <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/06/kuo-apple-foldable-iphone-book-style-2000/">include analysts Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/apple-foldable-macos-prediction/">Jeff Pu</a>, along with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/alleged-display-sizes-apple-foldable-iphone/">Weibo account Digital Chat Station</a>. The fact that these display sizes are now agreed upon and have been leaked indicates that Apple may have finalized at least some of the device's specifications.<br/>
<br/>
The foldable iPhone will open up like a book, according to Kuo, rather than have a clamshell design like Samsung's Galaxy Z Flip.<br/>
<br/>
Pu said the foldable iPhone recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/apple-foldables-mass-production-2026/">entered the New Product Introduction (NPI) stage at manufacturer Foxconn</a>, suggesting that Apple is moving forward with plans to release the device. Pu and Kuo both believe that the foldable iPhone will enter mass production in the fourth quarter of 2026, which means the device could launch as soon as next year in limited quantities, but a release at some point in 2027 seems more likely.<br/>
<br/>
As funny as it might sound, the foldable iPhone seems to be two years away for real this time.<br/>
<br/>
Barclays analyst Tim Long recently estimated that Apple's first foldable iPhone <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/foldable-iphone-price-estimate/">could start at around &#36;2,299 in the U.S.</a>, meaning it would cost nearly twice as much as the iPhone 16 Pro Max, which starts at &#36;1,199 there.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the 7.8-inch inner display and 5.5-inch outer display, Kuo said the foldable iPhone will feature two rear cameras, one front camera, a Touch ID power button instead of Face ID, and a high-density battery. He expects the device to be as thin as 4.5mm when unfolded, and between 9mm and 9.5mm when folded. He also said the device will have a titanium exterior, but the hinge will use a mix of titanium and stainless steel.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/foldable-iphone-rumors-sounding-serious/">Apple&#039;s Long-Rumored Foldable iPhone is Starting to Sound Serious</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-long-rumored-foldable-iphone-is-starting-to-sound-serious.2453431/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Spring Sale Adds New Deals on Connected Health Galaxy Devices, Plus Monitor and TV Savings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/samsung-spring-sale-connected-health/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-spring-sale-adds-new-deals-on-connected-health-galaxy-devices-plus-monitor-and-tv-savings.2453429/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:27:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/samsung-spring-sale-connected-health/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung expanded its springtime deals this week with fresh discounts and offers across its website, including <a href="https://howl.link/eiieqstmoeyp2">new sales on connected health products</a> like the Galaxy Watch and Galaxy Ring. You'll also find savings on popular Samsung monitors and storage below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/samsung-health-deals.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995581" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For the <a href="https://howl.link/eiieqstmoeyp2">Galaxy products</a>, Samsung is hosting deals on the <a href="https://howl.link/wr1ozpldygkh0">new Galaxy S25 Ultra</a>, the Galaxy S Fold6 and Z Flip 6, the Galaxy Ring, Galaxy Watch Ultra, Galaxy Watch 7, and Galaxy Buds 3 Pro. Many of these sales have extra savings when you have an older device to trade in, but if you don't, Samsung is still providing cash discounts on some products.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/eiieqstmoeyp2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Samsung Galaxy Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find all of these Galaxy discounts listed below, alongside some ongoing sales on Samsung monitors, TVs, storage, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/eiieqstmoeyp2">Galaxy Products</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/wr1ozpldygkh0">Galaxy S25 Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9rn5heo5brtwc">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,300</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9rn5heo5brtwc">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> - Save up to &#36;700</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/xqamoxz18az2f">Galaxy Ring</a> - Get up to &#36;250 trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/14vx5j52aye6j">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;325</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/zyhlv7pgnni0m">Galaxy Watch 7</a> - Save up to &#36;200</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/gnqxpqhxaeowp">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;150</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/faul5vo4dharo">TVs</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/qkwmypkc5obhd">The Frame</a> - Save up to &#36;1,300</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/basyw1q0kj7hr">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ykww20f4u23u4">65-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/btdmfxv0poeju">65-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,499.99, down from &#36;2,699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVRaSFAOn">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,179.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/9xnvn5zl1fo05">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;2,149.99, down from &#36;3,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/p7y8pcx52jg1k">Monitors and Storage</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVMG7DfcK">990 EVO 5.0 NVMe SSD 2TB</a> - &#36;124.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVLMVgenn">2TB Portable SSD</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;284.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/x8w555bikl3xj">32-inch Odyssey Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKayx1Nx">34-inch Odyssey OLED G8 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKXc8UKH">32-inch Odyssey Quantum Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;699.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/sbn4b7dlrp8pq">Refrigerators</a></h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/rj0skwxvkajxt">Large Capacity Side-by-Side Fridge</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,666.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/wvh01oaq72v2w">4-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ozmz1x8zug5xn">Mega Capacity 3-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;2,399.00, down from &#36;3,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/2ywoezhcm8c5r">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;2,799.00, down from &#36;4,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ot6h8iqi1q361">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;3,199.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/samsung-spring-sale-connected-health/">Samsung Spring Sale Adds New Deals on Connected Health Galaxy Devices, Plus Monitor and TV Savings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-spring-sale-adds-new-deals-on-connected-health-galaxy-devices-plus-monitor-and-tv-savings.2453429/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Restricting New Pebble Smartwatches From &#039;Being Awesome&#039; With iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/pebble-smartwatch-apple-restrictions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-restricting-new-pebble-smartwatches-from-being-awesome-with-iphone.2453428/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:19:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/pebble-smartwatch-apple-restrictions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Pebble</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Two new PebbleOS smartwatches <a href="https://ericmigi.com/blog/introducing-two-new-pebbleos-watches">were announced today</a> by original Pebble watch creator Eric Migicovsky, revitalizing a Kickstarter-launched brand that had three years of mega popularity before it folded in 2016.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/pebble-smartwatches.jpg" alt="" width="2037" height="1146" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995576" /><br/>
Called the Core 2 Duo and the Core Time 2, the two smartwatches run a PebbleOS, which is based on the source code for the software that ran on the original Pebble smartwatch. After Pebble shut down, assets were acquired by Fitbit, which was then acquired by Google. Google agreed to open source PebbleOS earlier this year, paving the way for the return of Pebble watches.<br/>
<br/>
Like the original Pebble watches, the Core 2 Duo and Core Time 2 are platform agnostic and designed to work with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Android, but Migicovsky <a href="https://ericmigi.com/blog/apple-restricts-pebble-from-being-awesome-with-iphones">is already warning customers</a> that Apple's restrictions are going to prevent the new devices from working like the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Migicovsky says that it was difficult to design for iPhones when he was working on the original Pebble watch, and in the last eight years, "things have actually gotten worse." He said that his company will "build a good app for iOS," but that it is impossible for a third-party smartwatch to replicate the functions of the Apple Watch. He shared an extensive list of the limitations:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>There's no option for sending text messages or iMessages.</li><br/>
 	<li>There's no option for replying to notifications or taking actions like marking something as done.</li><br/>
 	<li>There is little inter-app communication, which makes it difficult for Pebble to work with other iOS apps.</li><br/>
 	<li>If the iOS app is closed, the watch can't access the app or the internet.</li><br/>
 	<li>The watch cannot detect if you're using your phone, so it will buzz and display a notification regardless.</li><br/>
 	<li>There's no easy option to allow developers to create watch faces and apps for Pebble that would be available through the Pebble iOS app.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Migicovsky lamented that Pebble is required to go through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, which is a "gigantic pain" because with every update, a "random app reviewer" could "make up some BS excuse" and deny updates. He says that Apple makes it "nearly impossible for 3rd party wearable developers" to create an experience that mirrors the Apple Watch experience.<br/>
<blockquote>Apple claims their restrictions on competitors are only about security, privacy, crafting a better experience etc etc. At least that's what they tell you as they tuck you into bed. I personally don't agree - they're clearly using their market power to lock consumers into their walled ecosystem.</blockquote><br/>
According to Migicovsky, the new Pebble watches will have less developed functionality on iOS than Android, which "is Apple's fault." He said that he does not want to see complaints about the lack of functionality, so he is sharing the info now so customers can make an informed decision about whether to buy the product. "If you're worried about this," he wrote, "the easiest solution is to buy an Android phone."<br/>
<br/>
Migicovsky calls on "Pebble-curious" &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to complain loudly to Apple or switch to Android, while also asking elected representatives in the U.S. to support legislation that would require Apple to make changes to its rules. In Europe, Migicovsky plans to petition Apple to request interoperability for Apple Watch APIs.<br/>
<br/>
Migicovsky last clashed with Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/beeper-mini-brings-imessage-to-android/">over the Beeper Mini app</a>, and he has been outspoken about Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules since then, meeting with the FTC <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/22/doj-and-ftc-looking-into-beeper-controversy/">and the U.S. Department of Justice</a>. Beeper Mini reverse engineered iMessage protocols and encryption, using Apple's own iMessage servers to let Android users send "blue bubble" texts to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users without the need for an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/beeper-mini-continued-outages/">blocked the functionality</a>, and Beeper was ultimately forced to give up on the idea.<br/>
<br/>
The Core 2 Duo watch is priced starting at &#36;149, and the Core Time 2 is priced starting at &#36;225, with pre-orders <a href="https://store.repebble.com">available on the Repebble website</a>. Both devices feature an always-on e-paper screen, physical buttons, step and sleep tracking, and a 30 day battery life, with the more expensive model also offering a heart rate monitor. The Core 2 Duo will ship starting in July, while the Core Time 2 will ship starting in December.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/pebble/">Pebble</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/pebble-smartwatch-apple-restrictions/">Apple Restricting New Pebble Smartwatches From &#039;Being Awesome&#039; With iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-restricting-new-pebble-smartwatches-from-being-awesome-with-iphone.2453428/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Provides Update on Expanding AirPods Hearing Aid Feature to Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/airpods-hearing-aid-feature-canada-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-provides-update-on-expanding-airpods-hearing-aid-feature-to-canada.2453424/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:41:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/airpods-hearing-aid-feature-canada-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the AirPods hearing aid and hearing test features received Health Canada approval at the federal level in December, the features are not yet available in Canada. According to reports <a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/toronto/consumer-alert/article/i-think-its-sinful-to-hold-it-back-consumers-frustrated-apple-hearing-aid-feature-not-available-in-canada/">from <em>CTV News</em></a> and the <a href="https://www.thestar.com/life/health-wellness/apple-s-airpods-hearing-aid-feature-is-available-in-106-countries-but-not-canada-here/article_76c5641a-0346-11f0-a88b-9fa7e7f24a0b.html"><em>Toronto Star</em></a> this month, the features have yet to launch in Canada because regulations vary at the provincial level.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/airpods-pro-2-hearing-aids.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964676" /><br/>
In the most populous Canadian province of Ontario, for example, hearing aids require a prescription from a physician or an audiologist.<br/>
<br/>
The good news is that Apple recently told the <em>Toronto Star</em> that it is working with Canadian provinces to get approval to release the AirPods hearing aid and hearing test features over the counter. Apple told the newspaper that it hopes to make the features available as soon as possible, but it did not provide a timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
With the clinical-grade hearing aid feature, AirPods Pro 2 can amplify the sound around you. The feature is intended for adults with perceived mild to moderate hearing loss, according to Apple. There is no additional cost to use the feature.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the five-minute hearing test allows adults to identify if they have hearing loss by measuring their ability to hear different frequencies of sound. Afterwards, the results will show a hearing loss classification and recommended next steps.<br/>
<br/>
The two features first launched in the U.S. and <a href="https://www.apple.com/airpods-pro/feature-availability/">select other countries</a> in late October, and they continue to roll out to more countries.<br/>
<br/>
There is a third AirPods hearing health feature — hearing protection — that is available in Canada.<br/>
<br/>
All three features require AirPods Pro 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/airpods-hearing-aid-feature-canada-update/">Apple Provides Update on Expanding AirPods Hearing Aid Feature to Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-provides-update-on-expanding-airpods-hearing-aid-feature-to-canada.2453424/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Unlike the iPhone 16e, the iPhone 17 Air is Expected to Feature MagSafe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-air-magsafe-expected/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unlike-the-iphone-16e-the-iphone-17-air-is-expected-to-feature-magsafe.2453421/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 09:05:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-air-magsafe-expected/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-air-with-17-features/">iPhone 17 Air</a> will support MagSafe, <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PiWMGlfrL">according to Digital Chat Station</a>, an account with millions of followers on Chinese social media platform Weibo. The account has a decent track record with Apple product rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/magsafe-dark-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970550" /><br/>
In a post yesterday, the account said all of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/iphone-17-air-magsafe-action-button/">iPhone 17 dummy models</a> shared by Sonny Dickson over the weekend are accurate. They said the dummy models align with their own information that they received, including all four iPhone 17 models supporting MagSafe for magnetic wireless charging and magnetic accessories.<br/>
<br/>
"The entire series has MagSafe," the post says, in computer-translated English.<br/>
<br/>
It was not entirely clear if the iPhone 17 Air would support MagSafe given the feature is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/28/apple-provides-reason-iphone-16e-no-magsafe/">missing on the lower-end iPhone 16e</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-air-magsafe-expected/">Unlike the iPhone 16e, the iPhone 17 Air is Expected to Feature MagSafe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unlike-the-iphone-16e-the-iphone-17-air-is-expected-to-feature-magsafe.2453421/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Stop Videos From Looping in the Photos App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/stop-videos-looping-ios-photos-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/stop-videos-from-looping-in-the-photos-app.2453420/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:53:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/stop-videos-looping-ios-photos-app&#038;post_date=1742323982/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Photos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Have you noticed your iPhone videos keep playing on repeat in the Photos app? Since Apple's iOS 18.2 update, the stock Photos app automatically replays videos until you manually pause them – a feature that might be fine at first but can quickly become annoying, especially with longer clips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/icloud-photos.jpg" alt="" width="836" height="470" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897381" /><br/>
The auto-loop feature can be fun for short clips or when showing someone a quick video, but it forces you to take action to stop each video rather than letting it end naturally. It can be disruptive when you're browsing through multiple short clips in your library, and proves particularly annoying when viewing longer content where you likely don't want to see the same three-minute video play twice in a row.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, Apple provides a simple toggle to disable the behavior:<br/>
<ol><br/>
    <li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app on your iPhone or iPad.</li><br/>
    <li>Scroll down and tap through to <strong>Apps ➝ Photos</strong>.</li><br/>
    <li>Scroll until you find the <strong>Loop Videos</strong> option.</li><br/>
    <li>Toggle the switch to the <strong>OFF</strong> position.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/stop-auto-looping-videos-photos-app.jpg" alt="" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995536" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all you need to do. Videos in your Photos app will now play once and then stop automatically. No more endless replays.<br/>
<br/>
If you prefer videos not to play automatically at all when you open them, there's a related setting you can adjust. In the same Settings menu, toggle off the <strong>Auto-Play Motion</strong> option, and videos will stay still until you manually press the play button.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/stop-videos-looping-ios-photos-app/">Stop Videos From Looping in the Photos App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/stop-videos-from-looping-in-the-photos-app.2453420/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Keyboards Buyer&#039;s Guide: 10+ Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-keyboards/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-keyboards-buyers-guide-10-differences-compared.2453419/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:40:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-keyboards&#038;post_date=1742323208/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		<category>Magic Keyboard</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple now sells three different keyboards for each member of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup, with the exception of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, which is too small for a physically connected keyboard. It is compatible with Bluetooth keyboards only.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/ipad-air-magic-keyboard-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-992623" /><br/>
While choosing between &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; keyboards is now a clear-cut issue since there is only one available for each type of &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, it is now even more important to consider their slightly different features and designs when choosing an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. All of the differences between the three models, as well as the recently discontinued Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, are listed below:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Magic Keyboard Folio<br/>
(2022–2025)</th><br/>
 <th>Magic Keyboard for &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;<br/>
(2020–2025)</th><br/>
 <th>Magic Keyboard for &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;<br/>
(2025)</th><br/>
 <th>Magic Keyboard for &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;<br/>
(2024–2025)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Detachable keyboard</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Separate magnetic kickstand</td><br/>
 <td>Integrated "floating" cantilever design</td><br/>
 <td>Integrated "floating" cantilever design</td><br/>
 <td>Integrated "floating" cantilever design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port for passthrough charging</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port for passthrough charging</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port for passthrough charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Plastic hinge</td><br/>
 <td>Redesigned aluminum hinge</td><br/>
 <td>Redesigned aluminum hinge</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.84 pounds (381 grams)</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-Inch</strong>: 1.3 pounds (590 grams)<br/>
<strong>13-Inch</strong>: 1.56 pounds (710 grams)</td><br/>
 <td><em>TBC</em></td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-Inch</strong>: 1.28 pounds (580 grams)<br/>
 <strong>13-Inch</strong>: 1.46 pounds (662 grams)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Silicone top case</td><br/>
 <td>Silicone top case</td><br/>
 <td>Silicone top case</td><br/>
 <td>Aluminum top case</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>14-key function row</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>14-key function row</td><br/>
 <td>14-key function row</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Backlighting</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Backlighting</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Trackpad</td><br/>
 <td>Trackpad</td><br/>
 <td>Larger trackpad</td><br/>
 <td>Larger trackpad</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Physical click</td><br/>
 <td>Physical click</td><br/>
 <td>Physical click</td><br/>
 <td>Haptic feedback</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in White only</td><br/>
 <td>Available in White or Black</td><br/>
 <td>Available in White only</td><br/>
 <td>Available in White or Black</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Compatible with &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; with A14 or A16</td><br/>
 <td>Compatible with &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with A14, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>, or M3 and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with A12X, A12Z, &zwnj;M1&zwnj;, and &zwnj;M2&zwnj;</td><br/>
 <td>Compatible with &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with A14, &zwnj;M1&zwnj;, &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, or M3</td><br/>
 <td>Compatible with &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with M4</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&#36;249</td><br/>
 <td><em>Discontinued</em></td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-Inch</strong>: &#36;269<br/>
<strong>13-Inch</strong>: &#36;319</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-Inch</strong>: &#36;299<br/>
<strong>13-Inch</strong>: &#36;349</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
All of the keyboards feature scissor mechanism with 1mm travel for quiet, responsive typing and connect via a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-connector/">Smart Connector</a> on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, meaning there is no need for charging or Bluetooth.<br/>
<br/>
The Magic Keyboard Folio is unique in offering a magnetic kickstand, separate from the keyboard itself, to prop the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; up independently. While this is extremely useful for users who want to use their &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; on a table, it is not a very good experience for use on a lap. The Magic Keyboards for &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; do not have a separate magnetic kickstand, instead prioritizing an all-in-one design that works well on a user's lap and is far more akin to a MacBook.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s Magic keyboards are very similar, but the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s version has an aluminum top case, giving it a more premium feel and appearance. Likewise, its haptic feedback emulates a physical click more uniformly and is equal to a MacBook, allowing users to choose how forcefully they want to click the trackpad. Backlighting may be essential for those who plan to often use their &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in dark environments. However, both models feature a 14-key function row and a large trackpad.<br/>
<br/>
If you already have the original Magic Keyboard for &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, the new versions are a notable upgrade, especially for the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. If you're an &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; user, it's important to note that you will lose backlighting if you upgrade to the latest version of the accessory.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-keyboard/">Magic Keyboard</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-keyboards/">iPad Keyboards Buyer&#039;s Guide: 10+ Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-keyboards-buyers-guide-10-differences-compared.2453419/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s What&#039;s Rumored for the Regular iPhone 17 This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/base-iphone-17-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-whats-rumored-for-the-regular-iphone-17-this-year.2453416/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 08:00:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/base-iphone-17-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Rumors indicate that the lowest-end iPhone 17 model will have the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/video-shows-iphone-17-mockups-internal-documents/">same overall design</a> as the lowest-end iPhone 16, so what is actually changing this year?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-teal.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964610" /><br/>
Below, we recap three key features that are coming on the regular iPhone 17, according to sources such as Ross Young, Ming-Chi Kuo, and Jeff Pu. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>ProMotion Display</h2><br/>
The regular iPhone 17 and the ultra-thin "iPhone 17 Air" are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/30/iphone-17-120hz-promotion-display/">expected to feature ProMotion</a>, for a variable refresh rate up to 120Hz.<br/>
<br/>
ProMotion has been limited to the Pro models since it debuted on the iPhone 13 Pro and the iPhone 13 Pro Max back in 2021.<br/>
<br/>
ProMotion support would result in smoother-looking scrolling and videos, and the technology contributes to longer battery life. It could also pave the way for an always-on display, so long as the refresh rate can ramp down to as low as 1Hz. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Upgraded Front Camera</h2><br/>
All four iPhone 17 models are expected to have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-more/">24-megapixel front camera</a>, up from 12 megapixels on all iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
With a higher 24-megapixel resolution, photos can maintain their quality even when cropped to a greater degree, providing more flexibility in post-processing.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said the upgraded camera will "significantly improve" image quality.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple-Designed Wi-Fi 7 Chip</h2><br/>
Apple's first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/iphone-17-series-apple-wifi-7-chip/">custom-designed Wi-Fi chip</a> is expected to debut in all iPhone 17 models.<br/>
<br/>
The chip is expected to support Wi-Fi 7, which allows for data transmission over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously, with a supported router. Benefits include faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
The entire iPhone 16 lineup already supports Wi-Fi 7, so the spec is not much of a surprise, but the fact that the chip will be designed by Apple is notable.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A19 Chip</h2><br/>
The A19 chip in the regular iPhone 17 is expected to be made <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/a19-and-a19-pro-n3p-rumor/">with TSMC's newer third-generation 3nm process</a>, which is known as "N3P."<br/>
<br/>
Expect year-over-year performance and power efficiency gains as usual.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/base-iphone-17-rumors/">Here&#039;s What&#039;s Rumored for the Regular iPhone 17 This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-whats-rumored-for-the-regular-iphone-17-this-year.2453416/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Steeper Discounts Hit New M3 iPad Air on Amazon, Now Starting at &#36;549</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/m3-ipad-air-steep-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steeper-discounts-hit-new-m3-ipad-air-on-amazon-now-starting-at-549.2453410/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:40:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/m3-ipad-air-steep-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon has introduced even steeper discounts on the new M3 iPad Air, offering as much as &#36;70 off these tablets, which just debuted last week. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;549.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch M3 iPad Air, down from &#36;599.00. Some of these deals are beating last week's launch discounts by as much as &#36;10.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m3-ipad-air-new-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993614" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Most of the deals in this article require you to clip an on-page coupon on Amazon in order to see the final sale price. You can find <a href="https://howl.link/97ew5v18bsa62">matching prices at Best Buy</a>, but you'll need to be a My Best Buy Plus/Total member, whereas on Amazon the deals are available to everyone.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;549.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;53 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;747.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One of the most notable new discounts is on the 1TB Wi-Fi 13-inch M3 iPad Air, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ7347KC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,229.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. This one is only available in Space Gray, and it's the deepest pre-order discount we've tracked so far on the M3 iPad Air. Amazon also has the new 13-inch iPad Air Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ7FJWBF%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;319.00, which is the accessory's first discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11-inch M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;549.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76RM7P%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;649.00, down from &#36;699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ7466KC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;847.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74CF3K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>13-inch M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;747.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75R957%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;849.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75PK41%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ7347KC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,229.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/m3-ipad-air-steep-discounts/">Steeper Discounts Hit New M3 iPad Air on Amazon, Now Starting at &#36;549</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steeper-discounts-hit-new-m3-ipad-air-on-amazon-now-starting-at-549.2453410/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Pro Said to Feature 12GB of RAM, 48-Megapixel Telephoto Camera, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-48mp-telephoto/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-said-to-feature-12gb-of-ram-48-megapixel-telephoto-camera-and-more.2453407/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:26:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-48mp-telephoto/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a research note with investment firm GF Securities on Monday, analyst Jeff Pu said both the iPhone 17 Pro and the iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature a 48-megapixel Telephoto rear camera, up from a 12-megapixel Telephoto camera on iPhone 16 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-17-Pro-Render-Front-Page-Tech.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990064" /><br/>
This means all three Fusion, Ultra Wide, and Telephoto cameras on the iPhone 17 Pro models would be 48 megapixels.<br/>
<br/>
The devices are expected to have a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/13/iphone-17-pro-camera-design-leak/">rectangular camera bump</a>.<br/>
<br/>
He also expects the iPhone 17 Pro models to be equipped with 12GB of RAM, up from 8GB in iPhone 16 Pro models. This increase in memory would contribute to improved performance for Apple Intelligence and multitasking.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max will have familiar 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch screen sizes, respectively, he said.<br/>
<br/>
The devices will have an A19 Pro chip made with TSMC's newer third-generation 3nm process, N3P, according to the analyst.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-48mp-telephoto/">iPhone 17 Pro Said to Feature 12GB of RAM, 48-Megapixel Telephoto Camera, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-said-to-feature-12gb-of-ram-48-megapixel-telephoto-camera-and-more.2453407/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Prioritizing Foldable Display Efficiency to Boost Battery Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-prioritizing-foldable-display-efficiency/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-prioritizing-foldable-display-efficiency-to-boost-battery-life.2453404/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:58:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-prioritizing-foldable-display-efficiency/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has worked to increase the power efficiency of its first foldable display, a new rumor claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Iridescent-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-995555" /><br/>
According to the latest post from the Weibo user known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a>," Apple's first foldable display prioritizes power efficiency. To achieve this, the company has successfully reduced the display driver integrated circuit (IC) from 28nm to 16nm—a significant advancement. This may help prolong battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/apple-foldables-mass-production-2026/">According to analyst Jeff Pu</a>, Apple's first foldable recently entered the New Product Introduction (NPI) phase at Foxconn,  with mass production slated to begin in the second half of 2026. Reports suggest Apple could launch the device either late next year or in early 2027.<br/>
<br/>
The Weibo user has a number of accurate previous claims, including that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 7 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/28/iphone-7-already-rumored-to-be-waterproof/">would be water-resistant</a>, the standard &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 models would continue using the A15 Bionic chip (with the more advanced A16 chip being exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro models), and Apple would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-developing-its-own-ai-server-processor/">build servers</a> to support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a> hardware. These predictions were later corroborated by multiple credible sources and subsequently proven to be correct. <br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-prioritizing-foldable-display-efficiency/">Apple Prioritizing Foldable Display Efficiency to Boost Battery Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-prioritizing-foldable-display-efficiency-to-boost-battery-life.2453404/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Fifth Avenue is Closing Overnight Later This Week, Here&#039;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-fifth-avenue-reduced-hours/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fifth-avenue-is-closing-overnight-later-this-week-heres-why.2453401/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 06:49:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-fifth-avenue-reduced-hours/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iconic <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/fifthavenue/">Fifth Avenue store</a> in New York City is normally open 24/7, but it will be closed overnight on some days this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-Fifth-Avenue-Hero.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1612" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-995482" /><br/>
According to Apple's website, the store will be closed between the hours of 10 p.m. and 8 a.m. local time starting Wednesday evening until Saturday morning. <br/>
<br/>
The store already closed briefly on Monday.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is closing the store to complete maintenance on the store's glass cube entrance, according to a source familiar with the matter.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's official explanation is "cube preservation."<br/>
<br/>
Opened in 2006, Apple Fifth Avenue features a street-level glass cube entrance, leading to an underground store. Apple's CEO Tim Cook and other company executives often attend the store for major new product launches.<br/>
<br/>
The store's cube has been outfitted with everything from a giant Apple Vision Pro headset outline to colorful Siri glow in recent years.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/18/apple-fifth-avenue-reduced-hours/">Apple Fifth Avenue is Closing Overnight Later This Week, Here&#039;s Why</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fifth-avenue-is-closing-overnight-later-this-week-heres-why.2453401/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
