<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 08:03:22 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates Internal &#039;Unreleased Products&#039; Document Amid Rumors of New iPads and Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-updates-unreleased-products-document/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-internal-unreleased-products-document-amid-rumors-of-new-ipads-and-macs.2420551/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 07:52:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-updates-unreleased-products-document/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated an internal support document about "unannounced or unreleased products," according to a proven source familiar with the matter. The update comes amid rumors that Apple is planning to release new iPads and Macs soon, although there is no guarantee that these things are directly related, and coincidences happen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
The document informs Apple support advisors how to respond to a customer's potential questions about unannounced products and services, or announced but still unreleased products. The document was "restructured and optimized" today, according to Apple's changelog, but we do not know what specific changes were made.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to announce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">updated iPad Pro, iPad Air, and MacBook Air models by late March</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
The next iPad Pro models are widely expected to be the first iPads equipped with brighter and more vivid OLED displays. Other rumored or likely features for the iPad Pro include the M3 chip, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">MagSafe wireless charging</a>, a redesigned Magic Keyboard with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">larger trackpad and an aluminum top casing</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/">landscape-oriented front camera</a>.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">larger 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> is expected alongside an updated 10.9-inch model. Other rumored or likely features for the iPad Air include the M2 chip, a redesigned rear camera bump, Wi-Fi 6E support, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air are expected to be updated with the M3 chip simultaneously, with key benefits over the M2 chip including faster performance and hardware-accelerated ray tracing for improved graphics rendering in games.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes are expected for the MacBook Air this year, but the laptops will likely gain support for Wi-Fi 6E like other Macs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already updated the 14-inch MacBook Pro, 16-inch MacBook Pro, and 24-inch iMac with the M3 chip in October 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Apple often releases a new iPhone color option in March or April too.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-updates-unreleased-products-document/">Apple Updates Internal &#039;Unreleased Products&#039; Document Amid Rumors of New iPads and Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-internal-unreleased-products-document-amid-rumors-of-new-ipads-and-macs.2420551/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPadOS 18 Rumored to Drop Support for These iPad Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-18-rumored-to-drop-support-for-these-ipad-models.2420545/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:55:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPadOS 18 will drop support for iPad models equipped with the A10X Fusion chip, according to a post on X today from a private account with a proven track record of sharing build numbers for upcoming iOS and iPadOS updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPad-Air-5.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938463" /><br/>
This means that iPadOS 18 would not be compatible with the first-generation 10.5-inch iPad Pro or the second-generation 12.9-inch iPad Pro models released in 2017. It almost certainly means that iPadOS 18 would drop support for iPad models powered by the regular A10 Fusion chip, including the sixth-generation and seventh-generation iPads.<br/>
<br/>
The post was spotted by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>, and it has since been deleted. However, this was likely because the account prefers to keep a low profile, and many of its previously-deleted posts contained accurate information.<br/>
<br/>
If this rumor is accurate, iPadOS 18 would be compatible with the following iPad models:<ul><li>iPad Pro: 2018 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad Air: 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad mini: 2019 and later</li><br/>
<li>iPad: 2020 and later</li></ul>Apple is expected to announce iPadOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the update should be released to all users with a compatible iPad in September. So far, key new features rumored for the update include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI functionality for Siri and more</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support in the Messages app</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The same source also expects iOS 18 to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/">iPadOS 18 Rumored to Drop Support for These iPad Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-18-rumored-to-drop-support-for-these-ipad-models.2420545/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumored to Be Compatible With These iPhone Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-be-compatible-with-these-iphone-models.2420543/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:31:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will be compatible with the iPhone XR, and thereby also the iPhone XS and iPhone XS Max models with the same A12 Bionic chip, according to a post on X today from a private account with a proven track record of sharing build numbers for upcoming iOS updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-18-Mock-iPhone-16-Feature-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936483" /><br/>
The post was spotted by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>, and it has since been deleted. However, this was likely because the account prefers to keep a low profile, and many of its previously-deleted posts contained accurate information.<br/>
<br/>
If this rumor is accurate, iOS 18 would be compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17:<ul><li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XR</li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (2nd generation)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (3rd generation)</li></ul>Apple is expected to announce iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the update should be released to all users with a compatible iPhone in September. So far, the update is rumored to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI functionality for Siri and more</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support in the Messages app</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/">design changes</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The same source expects iPadOS 18 to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ipados-18-compatible-ipads-rumor/">drop support for iPad models with the A10X Fusion chip</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">iOS 18 Rumored to Be Compatible With These iPhone Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-be-compatible-with-these-iphone-models.2420543/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Major Shareholders Planning to Force Apple to Reveal Use of AI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/shareholders-to-force-apple-to-reveal-ai-use/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-shareholders-planning-to-force-apple-to-reveal-use-of-ai.2420535/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:18:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/shareholders-to-force-apple-to-reveal-ai-use/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some of Apple's biggest investors are set to pressure the company tomorrow to reveal its use of artificial intelligence tools (via the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/387c446c-55e0-4f54-a4b4-80bf9d5bc2f3"><em>Financial Times</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Apple's annual shareholder meeting takes place tomorrow, allowing those with a major stake in the company to put forward proposals. One resolution proposed by the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) asks Apple to disclose its use of AI and any ethical guidelines that the company has adopted regarding the technology.<br/>
<br/>
The resolution is set to be supported by Norges Bank Investment Management and Legal & General, Apple's eighth and 10th-largest shareholders. Norges Bank, which operates the world's biggest sovereign wealth fund, wrote in its voting disclosures that Apple's board should account for "social consequences of its operations and products." Likewise, Legal & General said that Apple "discloses very little about its approach to managing AI-related risks."<br/>
<br/>
Legal & General met with Apple to discuss AI, but it declined to increase transparency around its development and use of the technology. "Apple should be transparent in their uses of AI and their risk management processes," the company said.<br/>
<br/>
The major investor advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services is encouraging Apple investors to support the AI resolution, arguing that Apple's guidelines "do not specifically identify the potential risks resulting from the use of AI" and, as a result, "there are concerns regarding shareholders' ability to properly evaluate the risks associated with the use of AI."<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, Apple is urging investors to reject the resolution, claiming that "the scope of the requested report is overly broad and could encompass disclosure of strategic plans and initiatives harmful to our competitive position." Shareholder petitions in the United States are usually non-binding, but those that review support from more than 30% of investors usually put sufficient pressure on the company to act. Apple is widely expected to announce a range of new AI features for its devices at WWDC later this year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/shareholders-to-force-apple-to-reveal-ai-use/">Major Shareholders Planning to Force Apple to Reveal Use of AI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/major-shareholders-planning-to-force-apple-to-reveal-use-of-ai.2420535/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus to Feature ProMotion Always-On Displays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/iphone-17-always-on-promotion-displays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-and-iphone-17-plus-to-feature-promotion-always-on-displays.2420522/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:13:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/iphone-17-always-on-promotion-displays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next year's iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus will adopt OLED displays with low-power backplane technology, bringing ProMotion to Apple's standard iPhone models for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/iPhone-15-Pro-Multi-Purpose-button-Mute-Switch-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890433" /><br/>
The current iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus use low-temperature polycrystalline silicon (LTPS) panels, while Apple's iPhone 15 Pro models use more advanced low-temperature polycrystalline oxide (LTPO) panels. LTPO panels support ProMotion, allowing the display to ramp up to a 120Hz refresh rate for smoother scrolling and video content when required. <br/>
<br/>
ProMotion also allows the display to ramp down to a more power-efficient refresh rate as low as 1Hz, which is why the iPhone 15 Pro screens feature an always-on capability that shows the Lock Screen's clock, widgets, notifications, and wallpaper even when the device is locked.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to retain the use of the less advanced LTPS panels in this year's iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus to maintain differentiation between its standard and Pro models, meaning Apple's 2025 iPhone series will be the first to feature ProMotion and always-on displays across the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=26198">The Elec</a></em>, Chinese supplier BOE is hoping to supply Apple with LTPO panels for the iPhone 17 series, but questions still remain about whether it can reach the required production capacity while maintaining Apple's quality control standards. <br/>
<br/>
If BOE cannot meet the requirements, Apple will likely turn to other suppliers like Samsung and LG Display for the LTPO panels, and rely on BOE for LTPS-based OLED panels for its legacy iPhone models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/#whats_next_for_the_iphone_se">rumored iPhone SE 4</a>.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/iphone-16-pro-to-feature-taller-aspect-ratio/">display analyst Ross Young</a>, this year's iPhone 16 Pro models will feature a taller aspect ratio of 19.6:9, a change that will trickle down to the standard iPhone 17 models the following year. The devices are expected to increase from 6.12- and 6.69-inches to 6.27- and 6.86-inches, respectively. This represents a display size increase of 2.5% on both devices.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/22/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/">Six Reasons to Wait for Next Year's iPhone 17</a></li></ul><br/>
All in all, this means that the standard ‌iPhone‌ 17 models look set to receive a substantial panel upgrade, with larger sizes as well as LTPO for ProMotion and always-on displays.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/iphone-17-always-on-promotion-displays/">iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus to Feature ProMotion Always-On Displays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-and-iphone-17-plus-to-feature-promotion-always-on-displays.2420522/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Air Lineup: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-ipad-air-lineup-what-to-expect.2420486/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 15:38:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1709001532/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2024 iPad Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In 2023, Apple didn't make any updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup, and it's been even longer since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> was refreshed. Apple last unveiled a new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; in March 2022, so we're at the two-year mark and it's overdue for an update. Luckily, rumors suggest that we're going to get new iPads as soon as March, and there are exciting changes in store for the Air lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
In this guide, we've rounded up all of the rumors about the new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="size_and_design">Size and Design</h2><br/>
Apple is planning for another 10.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; that's similar in design to the current version, but for the first time, we're expecting <em>two</em> &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models rather than one. As with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> lineup, Apple will release the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; in two sizes.<br/>
<br/>
The standard 10.9-inch model will be the smaller size, and at the larger end, Apple is working on a 12.9-inch version. At 12.9 inches, the larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be the same size as the current 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There aren't rumors of design changes, so we can expect both models to have the same edge-to-edge display with slim bezels and an aluminum chassis with flat, rounded edges that wrap around the screen. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has always been a bit thicker than the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with thicker bezels, and that's going to continue.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that the upcoming &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models that will also be refreshed in March will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/">have thinner frames</a> due to the swap over to OLED display technology. With OLED, the new larger-screened &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will be over 1mm thinner, while the 11-inch model will be almost 1mm thinner.<br/>
<br/>
The changes to &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; thickness should be quite noticeable and the design will distinguish the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; from the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, even though Apple will have two iPads that are roughly the same size.<br/>
<br/>
We've also seen leaked renders of the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which suggest that the new models could have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/">redesigned rear camera</a> with a protruding pill-shaped camera bump similar to the design that we're expecting for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> camera.<br/>
<br/>
Based on rumors, we won't see design changes, but Apple will likely introduce new color options. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; comes in a range of pastel colors right now, and Apple could introduce a selection of new shades.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="m3_chip">M3 Chip</h2><br/>
Since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip came out, Apple has used M-series chips in the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models. This time around, we're expecting Apple to bring either the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip or the M3 chip to the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip is the prior-generation M-series chip that first came out in 2022, and it's almost two years old. The argument for the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; is that it would give Apple a way to further distinguish the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; from the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, plus it would keep costs down. The 3-nanometer M3 chips are more expensive to produce than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple opts for the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, it will bring speed and power efficiency improvements, but it would be a much smaller bump than the M3 chip. It is not entirely clear which chip Apple will use.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip came out last year, and it's the first chip built using next-generation 3-nanometer architecture. It has an 8-core CPU and 10-core GPU, and it supports hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for games with better graphics.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's M3 Macs are able to play console-level games like Death Stranding and Resident Evil, so we can expect the same technology for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; if it ends up with the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 offers 2.5x better GPU speeds than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; in the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with half the power. As for the CPU, the M3 is up to 30 percent faster than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; performance cores and up to 50 percent faster than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; efficiency cores.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="bluetooth_and_wi-fi">Bluetooth and Wi-Fi</h2><br/>
Since the current &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is two years old, it's lacking some of the general technology improvements that Apple has brought to other devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been updating its products with Bluetooth 5.3, so we can expect that to come to the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;. Bluetooth 5.3 brings more reliable connectivity with Bluetooth accessories as well as better power efficiency for longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 6E is also expected, and it will let &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models connect to faster 6GHz Wi-Fi networks.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad_air_vs._ipad_pro">iPad Air vs. iPad Pro</h2><br/>
Display technology will be one of the main distinguishing factors between the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. While the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will have an OLED display, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models will continue to use more affordable LCD display technology.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> on the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and instead the current model has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> power button, which Apple may maintain in order to keep the premium &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; feature exclusive to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
We're not expecting major differences in performance as both models rumored to use the M3 chip, but the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; may have more memory for the OLED display. Rear camera technology will also be a differentiator because the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; has a dual camera setup with Wide and Ultra Wide lenses, while the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has just a single-lens Wide camera.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="pricing">Pricing</h2><br/>
The current 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;599, and the new model is likely to have the same starting price.<br/>
<br/>
As for the 12.9-inch version, it would make the most sense to price it at &#36;200 over the 11-inch model, so it could start at &#36;799. Prior to when the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; was updated with mini-LED, there was a &#36;200 price difference between the two sizes. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is to offer customers more options at a wider range of price points. For around the price of the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, customers will instead be able to opt for a larger 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/21/new-ipads-and-macbook-airs-spring-2024-rumor/">said multiple times</a> that new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models will come in the March/April timeframe, and the latest news suggests a release toward the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">end of March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple sometimes holds a spring event right around March, so we could be hearing news about a possible event in the next week or two.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/">Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Air Lineup: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-ipad-air-lineup-what-to-expect.2420486/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix No Longer Allowing Subscribers to Pay Through Apple&#039;s App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/netflix-stops-allowing-app-store-payment/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-no-longer-allowing-subscribers-to-pay-through-apples-app-store.2420481/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 14:27:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/netflix-stops-allowing-app-store-payment/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix subscribers who still pay their monthly fees through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> in-app purchase system will soon need to add a new payment method to keep their accounts active, Netflix is telling customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884792" /><br/>
Though Netflix stopped allowing customers to subscribe to its streaming service on iOS devices <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/12/28/netflix-no-more-itunes-billing-options/">way back in 2018</a>, it has allowed customers that were already subscribed that way to continue using in-app purchase to pay. Payment through Apple's platform is set to stop, however, because Netflix does not want to continue to pay Apple a 15 percent cut of those subscription fees.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/02/26/netflix-billing-app-store-support-ending/">9to5Mac</a></em>, the U.S. Netflix support site now says that customers in "some" countries will need to add a new payment method. It isn't clear which countries the new Netflix policy is applicable to, but given that it was added to the U.S. site, it likely applies to customers in the United States.<br/>
<blockquote>Some Apple-billed members in select countries may be prompted to add a new payment method to continue their subscription.</blockquote><br/>
There is no word on how many Netflix subscribers are still paying through in-app purchase since it's been nearly six years since Netflix removed the option. Since 2018, Netflix has required customers who have Apple devices to sign up for a new Netflix subscription on the Netflix website. There is no option to subscribe through the Netflix app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and these devices open to a sign-in screen.<br/>
<br/>
When Netflix first removed the option to pay through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, it said customers who paid for subscriptions with in-app purchases could continue to use that billing method until their accounts were canceled, but Netflix seems to have run out of patience.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/netflix-stops-allowing-app-store-payment/">Netflix No Longer Allowing Subscribers to Pay Through Apple&#039;s App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-no-longer-allowing-subscribers-to-pay-through-apples-app-store.2420481/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Offers Massive &#36;600 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, Available for &#36;999.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/samsung-viewfinity-massive-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-offers-massive-600-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-available-for-999-99.2420449/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:47:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/samsung-viewfinity-massive-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung kicked off a <a href="https://howl.me/clq2oxlzaSU">new sale on computer monitors</a> this week, including a match of the all-time low price on the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor. You can get this display for <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"><strong>&#36;999.99</strong></a> on Samsung's website, down from &#36;1,599.99. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-Slimfit-Camera-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%3Fth%3D1">Amazon is matching this sale</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/viewfinity-feb-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934207" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is a massive &#36;600 discount on the Smart Monitor, which features a matte 5K display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4. The monitor is a good (and cheaper) alternative to Apple's Studio Display. The last time we tracked this deal was about one month ago, so if you've been waiting for a solid markdown on the Samsung display, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;600 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;999.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the ViewFinity display sale, Samsung has a few other monitor discounts right now, which we've listed below. You can also find other Samsung products on sale this week, including offers and savings on <a href="https://howl.me/clIpsUUt4NJ">Galaxy smartphones, watches, and tablets</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clIpn1jjNHg">27-inch Smart Monitor M8</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;649.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvB7Tvgrn">34-inch ViewFinity Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clIpmLoB8FX">49-inch Odyssey G9 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvCVqsFVX">55-inch Odyssey Ark Mini-LED Curved Gaming Screen</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/samsung-viewfinity-massive-discount/">Samsung Offers Massive &#36;600 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, Available for &#36;999.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-offers-massive-600-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-available-for-999-99.2420449/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Could Revive iPhone Sales in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/ios-18-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-ai-features-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china.2420448/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:35:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/ios-18-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>'s rumored AI features could revive faltering <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China, according to <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240223PD204.html"><em>DigiTimes</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
In a paywalled report, <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></em> explains that despite the Chinese market pivoting toward high-end devices, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales have reportedly struggled since the start of 2024 in the region against rival brands offering generative AI features and foldable displays.<br/>
<br/>
In December 2023, Apple reportedly saw a 13% decline in revenue in China, following months as the top smartphone brand in the country by shipments, and there have been further reports of even more severe declines of up to 40% in recent weeks. Chinese consumers apparently see Apple's diminutive selection of AI features as contradictory to its image as a pioneering brand. <br/>
<br/>
<em>&zwnj;DigiTimes&zwnj;</em> reiterated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">previous rumors</a> suggesting that &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will contain a number of new AI features, but cautioned that Apple needs to make significant progress in the AI space to meet consumer expectations and revive the company's popularity in China amid fierce competition from brands like Huawei, which are heavily investing in AI research and development. <br/>
<br/>
On an earnings call earlier this year, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said the company was working on generative AI and would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">share details "later this year."</a> Apple is expected to preview &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the update should be released in September. Some new AI features could be exclusive to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models later in the year, with the lineup rumored to get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">"significantly" upgraded Neural Engine</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/ios-18-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china/">iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Could Revive iPhone Sales in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-ai-features-could-revive-iphone-sales-in-china.2420448/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Game Developers Describe &#039;Smell of Death&#039; Around Apple Arcade</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/developers-describe-apple-arcade-smell-of-death/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-developers-describe-smell-of-death-around-apple-arcade.2420447/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:24:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/developers-describe-apple-arcade-smell-of-death/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some game developers are dissatisfied with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> amid concerns about the subscription service's future, a new report claims. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/12/applearcade.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="606" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-723048" /><br/>
Sources speaking to <a href="https://mobilegamer.biz/inside-apple-arcade-axed-games-declining-payouts-disillusioned-studios-and-an-uncertain-future/"><em>mobilegamer.biz</em></a> described a "smell of death" around  Apple's games subscription service and noted the difference between the company's investment in TV and music, and its interest in games. "At the very top of the company there needs to be a passion and respect for games, and there just isn't," one developer said. "It all depends on how much buy-in there is from those guys at the top, and I don't think they really value Arcade or invest in it the same way you see them invest in music or TV."<br/>
<br/>
The service initially touted generous upfront payments to developers. Most games released on &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; in the service's first few years were apparently profitable, providing a lifeline for studios. "Despite its imperfections, we're very very happy Arcade exists. It has made premium games viable on mobile," one games studio executive said, explaining that their company would not exist without Apple's support.<br/>
<br/>
The report claims that &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;'s payouts to developers have been falling for several years, noticeably starting in October 2020. Both upfront payments and the per-play "bonus pool" have shrunk, and Apple is said to be evasive about how these sums are calculated. "They have this opaque metric that they call a qualifying session, and bonus pool payments are made based on that," one source said. "But no-one knows what a qualifying session actually is – it has something to do with if the game was launched, how long the player played for and how often they return. But it's a black box, really."<br/>
<br/>
"<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> Greats" are not eligible for upfront payments, receiving bonus pool contributions only. As a result, games with shorter narratives and premium indie titles earn less than games with longer-term retention. This apparently explains the slow loss of certain types of games on the service. Moreover, there has apparently been a strong shift toward prominent family-friendly IP in Apple's commissioning decisions, with one or two new "&zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Greats" per month. Very few original games are greenlit for the service unless they meet these requirements.<br/>
<br/>
While some developers spoke about their relationship positively, others described the company as "vindictive" or "spiteful" in its dealings. Some developers claim that the &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; team has not made its strategy shift and overall direction clear, and often simply stops replying to emails. "I got the sense they didn't really know where they were going with it all – almost like they weren't sure if they'd have jobs at the end of it," one studio representative said.<br/>
<br/>
Developers similarly spoke about their difficulties getting marketing support or obtaining features on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, even when their games are struggling to get traction on &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;. "We have to basically beg for featuring from Apple. Getting that banner featuring at the top is like squeezing blood from a stone," one developer added.<br/>
<br/>
Apple "rebooted" the subscription service in April 2021, cancelling a large number of projects. Some developers believe that Netflix's competitive move into gaming subscriptions has prompted Apple to consider another &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; reboot, but the long-term future of the service is unclear.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/developers-describe-apple-arcade-smell-of-death/">Game Developers Describe &#039;Smell of Death&#039; Around Apple Arcade</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-developers-describe-smell-of-death-around-apple-arcade.2420447/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Decision to Disable Web Apps Attracts Scrutiny in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/disabled-web-apps-attract-eu-scrutiny/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-decision-to-disable-web-apps-attracts-scrutiny-in-eu.2420446/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:07:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/disabled-web-apps-attract-eu-scrutiny/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The European Commission is considering investigating Apple's move to disable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> web apps in the EU, the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d2f7328c-5851-4f16-8f8d-93f0098b6adc"><em>Financial Times</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
Following the release of the second beta version of iOS 17.4, it emerged that Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/ios-17-4-nerfs-web-apps-in-the-eu/">restricted the functionality of iOS web apps in the EU</a>. Web apps can no longer launch from the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; in their own top-level window that takes up the entire screen, relegating them to a simple shortcut with an option to open within Safari instead. Critics argue that the move undermines the role of web apps as viable alternatives to native apps in iOS.<br/>
<br/>
EU competition regulators sent questions to developers last week to determine the impact of the change in what is apparently seen as a precursor to an in-depth probe. The European Commission confirmed its scrutiny to the <em>Financial Times</em>: <blockquote>We are indeed looking at the compliance packages of all gatekeepers, including Apple. In that context, we're in particular looking into the issue of progressive web apps, and can confirm sending the requests for information to Apple and to app developers, who can provide useful information for our assessment.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Apple claims that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/15/ios-17-4-web-apps-removed-apple/">it had to make the change to how web apps work</a> in iOS to comply with the EU's Digital Markets Act (DMA), arguing that third-party browsers used with web apps in Europe could expose users to unlawful security and privacy risks. It believes that the adjustments will only affect a small number of users.<br/>
<br/>
A potential probe into web apps could come after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">March 6 deadline</a> for Apple to comply with the DMA, but formal proceedings could be prevented if Apple makes further concessions.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/disabled-web-apps-attract-eu-scrutiny/">Apple&#039;s Decision to Disable Web Apps Attracts Scrutiny in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-decision-to-disable-web-apps-attracts-scrutiny-in-eu.2420446/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Not-So-FineWoven iPhone Case &#039;Browning Like a Rotten Banana&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/finewoven-iphone-cases-brown-like-rotten-banana/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/not-so-finewoven-iphone-case-browning-like-a-rotten-banana.2420436/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/finewoven-iphone-cases-brown-like-rotten-banana/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's &#36;59 FineWoven cases for iPhone 15 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">took heavy flak</a> when they were released last September for being subpar compared to the leather Apple cases they replaced. Now, <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> columnist Joanna Stern has distilled customers' ire by <a href="https://x.com/JoannaStern/status/1761072266639458745">sharing</a> her own experience with the case after five months of use.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/finewoven-case-stern.jpeg" alt="" width="3000" height="1999" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938281" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image credit: Joanna Stern</em></div><br/>
From <a href="https://techthings.cmail20.com/t/d-e-eosyk-irijhkzjj-r/">Stern's newsletter</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>There it is, everyone. My iPhone 15 Pro Max's FineWoven case after five months of use. The edges are peeling, the fabric is scratched up like an old CD and it's browning like a rotten banana. I've been waiting for the CDC to show up at my house to declare it a biomedical concern.<br/>
Some of you will say: "JOANNA! How gross are you?" Others—those who bought this case for &#36;59 when it came out in September—will likely say: "Yep. Same issues here."<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
Early on, tech news sites like <a href="https://techthings.createsend1.com/t/d-l-eosyk-irijhkzjj-t/">The Verge</a> complained about scratches in the fabric. At online retailers, the people who gave the case one or two stars all point out the same issues—peeling edges, scratches, proclivity to get dirty. <a href="https://techthings.createsend1.com/t/d-l-eosyk-irijhkzjj-i/">On Best Buy</a>, many say they'll never buy an Apple case again and that it’s the worst product Apple's ever made. <a href="https://techthings.createsend1.com/t/d-l-eosyk-irijhkzjj-d/">Same on Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
An Apple spokesman said that the company's cases are engineered at the highest standard to protect iPhones and that the FineWoven case's durable microtwill will protect an iPhone for years.</blockquote>An <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT204172">Apple support document</a> offers advice about cleaning its FineWoven cases, but the section's small print admits that "The material may look different and show wear over time as the fibers get compressed with normal use" and that "some scratches may diminish over time."<br/>
<br/>
Responding to Stern's five-month review, <em>Daring Fireball</em>'s John Gruber created <a href="https://twitter.com/gruber/status/1761517510111695133">identical polls</a> across multiple social media platforms asking FineWoven case owners for their opinion, and respondents appear to have overwhelmingly voted in agreement that "It's a piece of junk."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">If you own an Apple FineWoven iPhone case and have used it regularly for the last few months:<a href="https://t.co/4XQ7cu7nlB">https://t.co/4XQ7cu7nlB</a></p>&mdash; John Gruber (@gruber) <a href="https://twitter.com/gruber/status/1761517510111695133">February 24, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Despite the continued bad publicity almost six months on from the cases' debut, Apple still appears unwilling to admit that its leather alternative material is a letdown. But in the court of public opinion, all the evidence suggests this is an open and shut case: FineWoven is just bad. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/finewoven-iphone-cases-brown-like-rotten-banana/">Not-So-FineWoven iPhone Case &#039;Browning Like a Rotten Banana&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/not-so-finewoven-iphone-case-browning-like-a-rotten-banana.2420436/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Both iPhone 16 Pro Models Again Rumored to Feature 5x Optical Zoom</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/both-iphone-16-pro-models-5x-optical-zoom-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/both-iphone-16-pro-models-again-rumored-to-feature-5x-optical-zoom.2420433/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:40:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/both-iphone-16-pro-models-5x-optical-zoom-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>TrendForce</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to expand the iPhone 15 Pro Max's tetraprism camera with up to 5x optical zoom to both the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max this year, according to Taiwanese research firm TrendForce. This is a rumor we have heard from other sources before, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/tetraprism-lens-iphone-16-pro/">our own reporting</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPhone-16-Cameras-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919420" /><br/>
TrendForce briefly mentioned this information today <a href="https://www.trendforce.com/presscenter/news/20240226-12042.html">in a press release</a> focused on the overall smartphone camera lens market:<blockquote>Following the successful launch of the iPhone 15 Pro Max with its exclusive Tetraprism telephoto zoom lens, the industry is expected to see an increase in the adoption of periscopic lens modules. Apple plans to bring this advanced hardware upgrade to the iPhone 16 Pro, making it accessible to more users in the Pro series.</blockquote>In the iPhone 15 Pro Max, the tetraprism camera system has a "folded" design that allows it to fit inside the smartphone, enabling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/">up to 5x optical zoom and up to 25x digital zoom</a>. By comparison, the smaller iPhone 15 Pro remains limited to up to 3x optical zoom, in line with the iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
It has been rumored that the iPhone 16 Pro will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">larger 6.3-inch display</a>, compared to the 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro. This change would increase the overall size of the device, which could provide additional internal space for a tetraprism camera.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil the iPhone 16 series in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trendforce/">TrendForce</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/both-iphone-16-pro-models-5x-optical-zoom-rumor/">Both iPhone 16 Pro Models Again Rumored to Feature 5x Optical Zoom</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/both-iphone-16-pro-models-again-rumored-to-feature-5x-optical-zoom.2420433/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Begged Apple to Adopt Bing as Safari&#039;s Default Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/microsoft-begged-apple-to-adopt-bing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-begged-apple-to-adopt-bing-as-safaris-default-search-engine.2420432/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:29:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/microsoft-begged-apple-to-adopt-bing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		<category>Bing</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft repeatedly attempted to persuade Apple to switch to Bing as the default search engine for Safari or even buy it outright, it has emerged.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/microsoft-bing-chatgpt.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-884498" /><br/>
The information was disclosed in <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.223205/gov.uscourts.dcd.223205.835.0.pdf">documents</a> as part of Google's ongoing antitrust case against the U.S. Justice Department (via <em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/02/24/google-says-microsoft-offered-to-sell-bing-to-apple-in-2018.html">CNBC</a></em>). According to the filings, Microsoft approached Apple in 2009, 2013, 2015, 2016, 2018, and 2020, proposing that Bing should replace Google as the default search engine in Safari.<br/>
<br/>
Apple consistently declined these offers, citing concerns over Bing's search quality relative to Google's. The documents reveal that in 2018 Microsoft not only suggested making Bing the default search engine but also offered to sell Bing to Apple or establish a joint venture around the search engine. These proposals were similarly turned down by Apple.<br/>
<br/>
The court filings provide insight into Apple's decision-making process, highlighting the company's evaluation of Bing's capabilities against Google's. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a>, Apple's Senior Vice President of Services, is quoted in the filings expressing skepticism about Bing's search quality and Microsoft's investment in search technology. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/25/google-apple-search-default-8-12-billion/">Google pays billions of dollars</a> to remain the default search engine on Apple devices. Google argues that Microsoft's repeated pitches to Apple demonstrate the competitive nature of the search engine market, countering allegations that Google holds a monopoly in web search advertising. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bing/">Bing</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/microsoft-begged-apple-to-adopt-bing/">Microsoft Begged Apple to Adopt Bing as Safari&#039;s Default Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-begged-apple-to-adopt-bing-as-safaris-default-search-engine.2420432/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Would You Let Siri Help to Write Your Messages?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/siri-generative-ai-google-gemini-messages/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/would-you-let-siri-help-to-write-your-messages.2420429/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 04:31:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/siri-generative-ai-google-gemini-messages/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">generative AI push</a>, Apple is expected to feature tight integration between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and the Messages app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. We won't have a fuller idea about how that will work until Apple previews its next major software update at WWDC in June, but in the meantime, Google has just <a href="https://blog.google/products/android/new-android-features-february-2024/">announced</a> its own equivalent feature for Android.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/gemini-google-messages.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938245" /><br/>
In an update for the beta version of Google Messages arriving this week, users will be able to interact with Google's Gemini chatbot (previously called "Bard") right inside the app, where it can help to draft messages, brainstorm ideas, plan events, or simply allow for a "fun conversation." Google says the feature is only available to English-language Messages users for now.<br/>
<br/>
Android Auto is also getting an AI assistant that can automatically summarize long texts or busy group chats while users are driving. It will also suggest relevant replies and actions that users can tap once to send a message, share their ETA, or start a call. We have not heard rumors mention AI in relation to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, so whether or not Apple has similar features in the works is unknown.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and iPadOS 18 will include a "slew of new AI features," according to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">recent report</a> by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. The report claims Apple is training both &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and Spotlight search on large language models, with the goal of improving each feature's ability to answer complex questions accurately. The revamped version of Spotlight could also offer deeper integration with "specific" functions and features in apps.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman says that one of the tentpole AI features Apple is developing is an improved interaction between &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; and the Messages app, which would let &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; auto-complete sentences more effectively and answer complex questions. Apple has also explored AI-powered features that would allow users to automatically generate playlists in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and presentation slides in the Keynote app. Some new AI features announced later on in the year could well be exclusive to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, which are rumored to get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">"significantly" upgraded Neural Engine</a>.<br/>
<br/>
According to the latest data from TF International Securities, Apple's weekly smartphone sales in the Chinese market have declined by 30-40% in recent weeks, which is said to be partly due to rival Chinese smartphones <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240223PD204/apple-ai-ios-china-smartphone-iphone-sales.html">already offering generative AI features</a> of their own.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/siri-generative-ai-google-gemini-messages/">Would You Let Siri Help to Write Your Messages?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/would-you-let-siri-help-to-write-your-messages.2420429/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s How Much It Costs Apple to Make a Vision Pro Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/price-apple-pays-to-make-vision-pro-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-much-it-costs-apple-to-make-a-vision-pro-headset.2420426/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:38:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/price-apple-pays-to-make-vision-pro-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting at &#36;3,500, Apple's Vision Pro price puts it at the top-end of the AR/VR headset market, but a significant portion of the cost is down to the device's premium "bill of materials," which is thought to come in at just over &#36;1,500.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Making-Vision-Pro.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931759" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://omdia.tech.informa.com/blogs/2023/jul/oledos-and-oled-displays-will-account-for-35-of-apples-vision-pro-vr-device-component-costs">Omdia's research</a>, the components used in Vision Pro are estimated to cost Apple a total of &#36;1,542. The most expensive component is said to be the two 1.25-inch micro-OLED displays inside the headset, one for each eye. The displays provide a total of 23 million pixels, which Apple says is "more pixels than a 4K TV." Omdia estimates that Apple pays &#36;228 for each display, or &#36;456 per headset. <br/>
<br/>
The second most expensive components are the M2 and R1 chips. The M2 is the main processor, which is the same chip that was first introduced in the 2022 MacBook Air. The M2 is responsible for processing content, running the visionOS operating system, executing computer vision algorithms, and providing graphical content. The R1 chip is responsible for all of the information coming from the cameras, sensors, and microphones. Together they cost Apple a total of &#36;240.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/02/24/apples-vision-pro-why-its-so-expensive.html">CNBC</a></em>, it is hard to extrapolate Apple's profit margin from these estimated figures, since they do not take into account research and development costs, packaging, shipping, sales, marketing, and any capital expenditures that can add up-front costs to large parts orders. Nevertheless, they do give an idea of how expensive the parts alone are in a given device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to produce fewer than 400,000 Vision Pro headsets in 2024 due to the complexity of manufacturing, according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. However, Apple is said to be already working on a new version of the Apple Vision Pro that will be priced more affordably. The chips in the device are likely to be on par with the iPhone rather than Mac-level chips, and Apple may also use lower resolution internal displays and cheaper materials. It could also drop the outward-facing EyeSight feature that lets other people see a simulated rendering of the wearer's eyes.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman believes that Apple is working on a next-generation version of the Vision Pro that could see a launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">sometime in late 2025</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/price-apple-pays-to-make-vision-pro-headset/">Here&#039;s How Much It Costs Apple to Make a Vision Pro Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-much-it-costs-apple-to-make-a-vision-pro-headset.2420426/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AT&amp;T Giving &#36;5 Credit to Customers Following Major Network Outage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/att-crediting-customers-for-network-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/at-t-giving-5-credit-to-customers-following-major-network-outage.2420387/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 11:02:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/att-crediting-customers-for-network-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AT&T has <a href="https://www.att.com/makeitright/">announced</a> that it will be providing impacted customers with a &#36;5 bill credit per account as compensation for the network's major outage across the U.S. on Thursday. The credits will automatically be applied within two bill cycles, it said.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ATT-Banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937556" /><br/>
AT&T said the bill credit offer does not apply to AT&T Business, prepaid, or Cricket customers. A spokesperson for the carrier <a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/at-t-will-give-5-account-credits-after-thursdays-network-outage/">told <em>CNET</em></a> that those customers will "have options available to them if they were potentially impacted by the outage."<br/>
<br/>
The carrier's full statement apologizing for the outage:<blockquote>We apologize for Thursday's network outage. We recognize the frustration this outage has caused and know we let many of our customers down. We understand this may have impacted their ability to connect with family, friends, and others. Small business owners may have been impacted, potentially disrupting an essential way they connect with customers.<br/>
<br/>
To help make it right, we're reaching out to potentially impacted customers and we're automatically applying a credit to their accounts. We want to reassure our customers of our commitment to reliably connect them – anytime and anywhere. We're crediting them for the average cost of a full day of service.<br/>
<br/>
We're also taking steps to prevent this from happening again in the future. Our priority is to continuously improve and be sure our customers stay connected.</blockquote>AT&T also <a href="https://about.att.com/ecms/dam/snrdocs/network-employee-letter.pdf">shared the letter</a> that its CEO John Stankey sent to the company's employees. In it, he said the company "let down" many of its customers and has "already implemented changes to prevent what happened on Thursday."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>'Incorrect Process'</h2><br/>
Based on its initial review, AT&T <a href="https://about.att.com/pages/network-update">said</a> it believed that the outage was caused by the "application and execution of an incorrect process used as we were expanding our network," not a cyber attack. The U.S. government on Thursday said the FBI and the Department of Homeland Security were looking into the outage.<br/>
<br/>
The outage began in the early hours of Thursday morning, with tens of thousands of customers complaining that they were unable to make cellular phone calls, send or receive text messages, or use cellular data. AT&T said about three-quarters of its customers were able to access its network by around 6 a.m. Eastern Time on Thursday, and it said that it had fully restored its network by around 1 p.m. Eastern Time that day.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/att-crediting-customers-for-network-outage/">AT&amp;T Giving &#36;5 Credit to Customers Following Major Network Outage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/at-t-giving-5-credit-to-customers-following-major-network-outage.2420387/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumored to Have Design Changes, macOS Revamp Coming Later</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-have-design-changes-macos-revamp-coming-later.2420382/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 08:55:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will likely include some design changes, but a macOS revamp might be a year or two away, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-25/apple-ponders-making-new-wearables-ai-glasses-airpods-with-cameras-smart-ring-lt1kb7cd"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909207" /><br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-25/apple-ponders-making-new-wearables-ai-glasses-airpods-with-cameras-smart-ring-lt1kb7cd"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, Gurman said Apple is working to update the design of iOS as "early as this year." A sketchy rumor claimed that iOS 18 would feature some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/ios-18-visionos-design-elements-rumor/">visionOS-inspired design elements</a>, and while Gurman agreed that iOS could take some design cues from visionOS, he does not expect a "total overhaul that mirrors visionOS."<br/>
<br/>
While he hedged with "as early as this year" wording today in regards to iOS design changes, Gurman was more firm about iOS 18 being redesigned in a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-11-12/apple-aapl-plans-ambitious-ios-18-and-macos-15-updates-seeks-to-squash-bugs-lovjlsf6">November edition</a> of his newsletter, when he said Apple's senior management had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/">described iOS 18 as "ambitious and compelling,"</a> with "major new features and designs."<br/>
<br/>
As for macOS, Gurman said Apple has started early work on design changes for that operating system that could debut in 2025 or 2026. The platform last received a major redesign with macOS Big Sur in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/">iOS 18 Rumored to Have Design Changes, macOS Revamp Coming Later</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-have-design-changes-macos-revamp-coming-later.2420382/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Has &#039;Explored&#039; a Smart Ring, Glasses, and AirPods With Cameras</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/apple-has-explored-smart-ring-and-glasses/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-has-explored-a-smart-ring-glasses-and-airpods-with-cameras.2420380/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 08:07:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/apple-has-explored-smart-ring-and-glasses/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has considered developing several new wearable devices over the years, including a smart ring for health and fitness, smart glasses, and upgraded AirPods with built-in cameras and more sensors, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-25/apple-ponders-making-new-wearables-ai-glasses-airpods-with-cameras-smart-ring-lt1kb7cd"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/samsung-galaxy-ring.jpg" alt="" width="940" height="529" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937059" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Samsung's upcoming Galaxy Ring</em></div><br/>
Below, we recap what Gurman shared about these devices in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-25/apple-ponders-making-new-wearables-ai-glasses-airpods-with-cameras-smart-ring-lt1kb7cd"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smart Ring</h2><br/>
A few years ago, Apple's industrial design team presented the idea of a "smart ring" focused on health and fitness features to executives on the company's health team, according to Gurman. However, he said Apple is not actively developing the finger-worn device at this time, so it is unclear if it will ever be released.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the ring could be a lower-cost alternative to the Apple Watch that could sync health and fitness data with a paired iPhone. It would compete with products like the <a href="https://ouraring.com/">Oura Ring</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development/">Samsung's upcoming Galaxy Ring</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smart Glasses</h2><br/>
It has long been rumored that Apple eventually hopes to release advanced AR glasses based on its Vision Pro headset. In the meantime, Gurman said the company has considered developing a "less ambitious" pair of smart glasses that would compete with the likes of Meta's Ray-Ban Smart Glasses and Amazon's Echo Frames.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has discussed creating glasses that would serve as an "AirPods replacement," with built-in speakers, cameras, health sensors, and AI capabilities, according to Gurman. The glasses are in a "technology investigation" stage within Apple's hardware engineering division, he said, so it sounds like a release is still far off. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods With Cameras</h2><br/>
Apple engineers last year started exploring how to fit low-resolution camera sensors into AirPods, according to Gurman. If ever released, he believes these AirPods could offer AI features that "assist people in their daily routines."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/apple-has-explored-smart-ring-and-glasses/">Apple Has &#039;Explored&#039; a Smart Ring, Glasses, and AirPods With Cameras</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-has-explored-a-smart-ring-glasses-and-airpods-with-cameras.2420380/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has Lowest Prices of the Year So Far on iPad Air, MacBook Air, and MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/best-buy-lowest-prices-ipad-macbook/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-lowest-prices-of-the-year-so-far-on-ipad-air-macbook-air-and-macbook-pro.2420376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:10:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/best-buy-lowest-prices-ipad-macbook/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is back this weekend with a <a href="https://howl.me/clG8QCkba7O">sale on Apple MacBooks and iPads</a>, including some of the best prices we've ever seen on MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, iPad Air, and more. Some of these deals require a <a href="https://howl.me/clsfFR2NQAO">My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total membership</a>, which start at &#36;49.99/year. In addition to exclusive access to select discounts, you'll get free 2-day shipping, an extended 60-day return window, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/best-buy-blue-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937846" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-best-buy-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938106" /><br/>
The cheapest iPad in this sale is the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clEadOydYiR"><strong>&#36;249.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. For a more recent model, Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi 10th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, which is an all-time low price at &#36;100 off. You'll find every model of the 10th generation iPad on sale at a record low price during this sale. This includes all Wi-Fi and cellular tablets, in all colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEadOydYiR"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi 9th gen iPad for &#36;249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi 10th gen iPad for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKbvh8PEh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi 10th gen iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKduB2Qbr"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular 10th gen iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKdXDXcha"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular 10th gen iPad for &#36;649.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-air-blue-.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937845" /><br/>
You can get every model of the 5th generation iPad Air on sale at an all-time low price right now at Best Buy, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;599.00. These are &#36;150 off across the board, and also include best-ever prices on both cellular models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-mini-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937844" /><br/>
Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for <a href="https://howl.me/clEafckZntZ"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> this weekend, down from &#36;499.00, and the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clHYsjeNRxs"><strong>&#36;549.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;649.00. Both of these are solid second-best prices on the iPad mini 6.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEafckZntZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clHYsjeNRxs"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937843" /><br/>
The cheapest MacBook Air deal you'll find this weekend at Best Buy is on the 256GB 13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;749.99, down from &#36;999.00. If you want a more recently updated model, the 256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air is priced at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. You can also get the 512GB M2 model on sale at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Across the board these are the best prices we've ever seen on the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALl0A1vd6"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937842" /><br/>
Unlike the MacBook Air deals, Best Buy's MacBook Pro sales all require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership in order to see the all-time low prices. If you don't have one, you can still get solid second-best prices on these computers at Best Buy this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
These deals are focused on the 14-inch models of the MacBook Pro. Some highlights include the 512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/clALsjD0UdF"><strong>&#36;1,399.00</strong></a> and the 512GB M3 Pro model at <a href="https://howl.me/clALtdDDDQt"><strong>&#36;1,749.00</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: My Best Buy Plus/Total membership required to see final deal price.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALsjD0UdF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 14-inch MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clG8SPDAJYd"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 14-inch MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;1,599.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALtdDDDQt"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;1,749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clALuHQfnL8"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;2,149.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clG8UfisKWG"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>M3 Max 14-inch MacBook Pro (1TB) for &#36;2,949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/best-buy-lowest-prices-ipad-macbook/">Best Buy Has Lowest Prices of the Year So Far on iPad Air, MacBook Air, and MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-lowest-prices-of-the-year-so-far-on-ipad-air-macbook-air-and-macbook-pro.2420376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
