<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 05:03:55 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma 14.4 Bug &#039;Destroys Saved Versions in iCloud Drive&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/sonoma-bug-destroys-saved-versions-icloud-drive/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-4-bug-destroys-saved-versions-in-icloud-drive.2422273/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:12:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/sonoma-bug-destroys-saved-versions-icloud-drive/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		<category>iCloud Drive</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/"> macOS Sonoma 14.4 software update</a> appears to be guilty of another bug, this time affecting saved versions in iCloud Drive.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iCloud-Bug-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834609" /><br/>
Versions are normally created automatically when users save files using apps that work with the version system in macOS. (To check if your Mac is using the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-gb/guide/mac-help/mh40710/mac">past versions system</a>, look for a "Revert To" option in the app's File menu.)<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://eclecticlight.co/2024/03/18/serious-bug-in-sonoma-14-4-will-destroy-saved-versions-in-icloud-drive/"><em>The Electric Light Company</em>'s Howard Oakley</a>, users running macOS 14.4 that have "Optimize Mac Storage" enabled should be aware that they are at risk of losing all previously saved versions of a file if they opt to remove it from iCloud Drive local storage. <br/>
<blockquote>In previous versions of macOS, when a file is evicted from local storage in iCloud Drive [using the Remove Download option in the right-click contextual menu], all its saved versions have been preserved. Download that file again from iCloud Drive, and versions saved on that Mac (but not other Macs or devices) have remained fully accessible. Do that in 14.4, and all previous versions are now removed, and lost forever.</blockquote>Oakley said his own tests confirmed that this behavior does not happen in macOS Sonoma 14.3 or macOS Ventura, so it is exclusive to macOS 14.4. For users who have already updated, he suggests either not saving files to iCloud Drive at all, or turning off Optimize Mac Storage. <br/>
<br/>
To perform the latter in System Settings, click your Apple ID, select iCloud, and then toggle off the switch next to "Optimize Mac Storage." You may need to perform this action twice – reports suggest it can turn back on by itself. For a more exhaustive account of the problem, see Oakley's <a href="https://eclecticlight.co/2024/03/19/sonomas-lost-versions-bug-what-it-is-and-how-to-safeguard-versions/">subsequent post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There are several bugs reported in macOS 14.4, and we have recorded some of the most prominent issues in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/do-not-update-macos-sonoma-14-4/">dedicated article</a> that we have updated since this story was published. Have you been affected by the latest bug? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-drive/">iCloud Drive</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/sonoma-bug-destroys-saved-versions-icloud-drive/">macOS Sonoma 14.4 Bug &#039;Destroys Saved Versions in iCloud Drive&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-4-bug-destroys-saved-versions-in-icloud-drive.2422273/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 to Feature New Scratch Resistant Anti-Reflective Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-to-feature-new-scratch-resistant-anti-reflective-display.2422268/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 02:51:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Corning</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next year's iPhone 17 will feature an anti-reflective display that is more scratch-resistant than Apple's Ceramic Shield found on iPhone 15 models, according to a new rumor out of Asia.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-15-galaxy-s24-ultra-corning-glass.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941959" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Anti-reflection properties of Galaxy S24 Ultra (bottom) vs. iPhone 15 (Image: <a href="https://x.com/UniverseIce/status/1749261102310199416?s=20">IceUniverse</a>)</em></div><br/>
Chinese Weibo leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/n/刹那数码">Instant Digital</a> claimed on Tuesday that the outer glass on the iPhone 17 is set to have a "super-hard anti-reflective layer" that is "more scratch-resistant than you think." The coating equipment has just been handed over to China's supply chain, according to the leaker, but not in time for it to feature in this year's upcoming iPhone 16 series.<br/>
<br/>
"Ceramic Shield" is a marketing name for a glass-ceramic material developed by Corning in collaboration with Apple. Apple says the Ceramic Shield on the iPhone 15 is "tougher than any smartphone glass." Introduced on iPhone 12 models in 2020, Apple advertised the ceramic-infused glass as increasing drop performance by 4x compared to the iPhone 11.<br/>
<br/>
More recently, Samsung debuted its newest Galaxy S24 Ultra, which features a Gorilla Glass Armor display panel, also developed by Corning. <a href="https://www.corning.com/gorillaglass/worldwide/en/corning-gorilla-armor.html">According to Corning</a>, the Armor panel cuts reflections by 75 percent compared to a typical glass surface, and is resistant to micro scratches that build up over time on competing glass panels. Corning also claims the panels offer over 4x more scratch resistance than competitive aluminosilicate cover glasses.<br/>
<br/>
It's not clear whether Apple is planning to adopt Gorilla Glass Armor for the iPhone 17, but the description matches the Chinese leaker's claims. Corning could also be supplying Apple with an equivalent technology that will be branded under another name. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/22/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/">Six Reasons to Wait for Next Year's iPhone 17</a></li></ul><br/>
Corning has been a longtime Apple supplier, with Gorilla Glass used in devices across Apple's product lineup. In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/10/apple-awards-corning-45m-manufacturing-fund/">2021</a>, Apple said it had invested a combined &#36;495 million to support Corning's ongoing research and development into "state-of-the-art glass processes," which led to the creation of Ceramic Shield.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/corning/">Corning</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/">iPhone 17 to Feature New Scratch Resistant Anti-Reflective Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-to-feature-new-scratch-resistant-anti-reflective-display.2422268/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>When Will Apple Announce WWDC 2024 Dates?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-2024-wwdc-dates/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-will-apple-announce-wwdc-2024-dates.2422235/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:13:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-2024-wwdc-dates/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 35th annual Worldwide Developers Conference isn't set to take place until June, but we are creeping closer to the general time when Apple tends to announce the dates for its developer event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/WWDC24-Header.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941927" /><br/>
Apple could make its first WWDC event date announcement in less than two weeks at the end of March or the beginning of April. Here are Apple's past WWDC announcement dates:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>2023 - Wednesday, March 29</li><br/>
 	<li>2022 - Tuesday, April 5</li><br/>
 	<li>2021 - Tuesday, March 30</li><br/>
 	<li>2020 - Friday, March 13</li><br/>
 	<li>2019 - Thursday, March 14</li><br/>
 	<li>2018 - Tuesday, March 13</li><br/>
 	<li>2017 - Thursday, February 16</li><br/>
 	<li>2016 - Monday, April 18</li><br/>
 	<li>2015 - Tuesday, April 14</li><br/>
 	<li>2014 - Thursday, April 3</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Given these dates, we could see a WWDC announcement from Apple anytime from Tuesday, March 26 to Friday, March 29, though Apple might also hold the announcement until the next week, unveiling dates on Tuesday, April 2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>WWDC Date Possibilities</h2><br/>
For the last several years, Apple held WWDC during the first week of June, and that's also the most likely target date this year.<br/>
<br/>
June 3 to June 7 would make the most sense based on past WWDC events, though June 10 to June 14 is also possible. Past WWDC dates:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>2023 - June 5 to June 9</li><br/>
 	<li>2022 - June 6 to June 10</li><br/>
 	<li>2021 - June 7 to June 11</li><br/>
 	<li>2020 - June 22 to June 26</li><br/>
 	<li>2019 - June 3 to June 7</li><br/>
 	<li>2018 - June 4 to June 8</li><br/>
 	<li>2017 - June 5 to June 9</li><br/>
 	<li>2016 - June 12 to June 17</li><br/>
 	<li>2015 - June 8 to June 12</li><br/>
 	<li>2014 - June 2 to June 6</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>WWDC Software Announcements</h2><br/>
Apple will unveil <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, macOS 15, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> Software 18, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2 at WWDC this year, and the updates will be provided to developers directly after the keynote event.<br/>
<br/>
Betas will be limited to developers for the first month or so, but if Apple follows tradition, the software will be made available through public betas in July 2024.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is the only update that we've heard much about, and Apple is said to be focusing heavily on artificial intelligence this year. There will be new AI additions across the OS, and <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> believes it could be one of the biggest updates we've seen to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in years. All of the rumors about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/"><strong>what's coming in iOS 18</strong></a> can be found in our roundup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Possible Hardware Announcements at WWDC</h2><br/>
There are no rumors yet that Apple will introduce new hardware, but we are waiting on refreshes for several Macs. Apple has yet to update the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> with M3 chips, so there is a possibility that some of these new Macs will see a debut at WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Read More</h2><br/>
We have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/"><strong>a dedicated WWDC 2024 roundup</strong></a> that will be updated on a regular basis as we learn more about what to expect from this year's developer event.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-2024-wwdc-dates/">When Will Apple Announce WWDC 2024 Dates?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-will-apple-announce-wwdc-2024-dates.2422235/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working on Solution for EU Core Technology Fee Possibly Bankrupting Apps That Go Unexpectedly Viral</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-eu-core-technology-fee-viral-solution/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-on-solution-for-eu-core-technology-fee-possibly-bankrupting-apps-that-go-unexpectedly-viral.2422232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:07:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-eu-core-technology-fee-viral-solution/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Since Apple announced plans for the 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee that apps distributed using the new EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> business terms must pay, there <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-eu-fees-could-bankrupt-app-developers/">have been ongoing concerns</a> about what that fee might mean for a developer that suddenly has a free app go viral.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
Apple's VP of regulatory law Kyle Andeers today met with developers during a workshop on Apple's Digital Markets Act compliance. iOS developer Riley Testut, best known for Game Boy Advance emulator GBA4iOS, asked what Apple would do if a young developer unwittingly racked up millions in fees.<br/>
<br/>
Testut explained that when he was younger, that exact situation happened to him. Back in 2014 as an 18-year-old high school student, he released GBA4iOS outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; using an enterprise certificate. The app was unexpectedly downloaded more than 10 million times, and under Apple's new rules with Core Technology Fee, Testut said that would have cost &#36;5 million euros, bankrupting his family. He asked whether Apple would actually collect that fee in a similar situation, charging the high price even though it could financially ruin a family.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe src="https://mastodon.social/@stroughtonsmith/112118127201793072/embed" class="mastodon-embed" style="max-width: 100%; border: 0" width="400" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><script src="https://mastodon.social/embed.js" async="async"></script></div><br/>
In response, Andeers said that Apple is working on figuring out a solution, but has not done so yet. He said Apple does not want to stifle innovation and wants to figure out how to keep young app makers and their parents from feeling scared to release an app. Andeers told Testut to "stay tuned" for an answer.<blockquote>What we are trying to do is tear apart a model that has been integrated for 15 years. And so for 15 years, the way we've monetized everything was through the commission. It covered everything from technology to distribution to payment processing, and the beauty of that model is that it allowed developers to take risks. Apple only got paid if the developer got paid, and that was an incredible engine for innovation over the last 15 years. We've seen it go from 500 apps to more than 1.5 million.<br/>
<br/>
To your point, we've seen kids everywhere from 8-year-olds, 9-year-olds, 10-year-olds, to teenagers come up with some amazing applications and it's been one of the great success stories of the App Store. In terms of the Core Technology Fee and our business model, we had to change. The mandates of the DMA forced us to tear apart what we had built and price each component individually. And so we now have a fee associated with technology, tools, and services, we now have a fee associated with distribution and the services we provide through the App Store, and then we have a separate fee for payment processing if a developer wants to use it.<br/>
<br/>
To your point - what is the impact on the dreamer, the kid who is just getting started. It could be a kid, it could be an adult, it could be a grandparent. We want to continue to encourage those sorts of developers. We build a store based on individual entrepreneurs, not so much catering to large corporate interests. And so we really wanted to figure out how do we solve for that.<br/>
<br/>
We haven't figured out that solution here. I fully appreciate that. We looked at the data. We didn't see many examples of where you had that viral app or an app just took off that incurred huge costs. That said, I don't care what the data said. We don't care what the data said. We want people to continue to feel... and not be scared... some parents... hey, I've got four kids who play around with this stuff. I don't have five million euros to pay. This is something we need to figure out, and it is something we're working on. So I would say on that one, stay tuned.</blockquote><br/>
It is not clear when Apple might come up with a solution or what that solution might be, but it sounds like the company might soon have some kind of option for these rare fringe cases when an app goes unexpectedly viral.<br/>
<br/>
The 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee (CTF) that Apple is charging applies to all apps created under Apple's new business terms, both those distributed in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and those distributed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the European Union. The CTF must be paid for every "first" app install over one million installs.<br/>
<br/>
A free app that is distributed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and downloaded over a million times will owe 0.50 euros for every subsequent "first" install, aka the first time a customer downloads an app on a device each year. The fee is incurred whether or not an app charges, creating a situation where an app developer could owe Apple money without ever making a dime.<br/>
<br/>
As it stands, the CTF is a major unknown for any kind of freemium or free app built under the new business terms that might go viral, effectively making it very risky to develop a free or freemium app outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. A free or freemium app that gets two million annual "first installs" would need to pay an estimated &#36;45,290 in fees per month, or more than half a million dollars per year, even with no money earned. That's not a sustainable model for free apps, and freemium apps would need to earn at least 0.50 euros per user to break even.<br/>
<br/>
App developers are able to continue to use Apple's current &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; business terms instead of adopting the new terms, paying just 15 to 30 percent commission to Apple with no change. That prevents distribution outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and it prevents developers from using third-party alternative payment solutions in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Adopting any of the new features that Apple has implemented because of the Digital Markets Act requires opting in to the updated business terms.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been tweaking the app ecosystem rules that it introduced in the European Union based on developer feedback. Developers can now opt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/">back in to the current App Store rules</a> after trying out the new rules, though this is only available one time. Apple also recently did away with an app marketplace restriction that required alternative marketplaces to offer apps from any third-party developer that wanted to participate.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party app stores are now able to offer apps only from their own catalog, and developers will soon be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-announces-app-downloads-from-websites/">distribute apps directly from their websites</a> as long as they meet Apple's requirements. Note that all of these changes are limited to the European Union, and the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; is operating as before in the United States and other countries.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-eu-core-technology-fee-viral-solution/">Apple Working on Solution for EU Core Technology Fee Possibly Bankrupting Apps That Go Unexpectedly Viral</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-on-solution-for-eu-core-technology-fee-possibly-bankrupting-apps-that-go-unexpectedly-viral.2422232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPads Likely to Begin Shipping in April</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april.2422217/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 09:52:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new iPad Pro models with OLED displays will likely begin shipping to customers in April, according to <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/blog/the-latest-insights-on-the-apple-oled-ipad-ramp">information shared today by Ross Young</a>, CEO of display industry research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman also said the new iPad Pro models might not ship until "deeper" into April <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-17/apple-aapl-revamped-carplay-becomes-last-hope-after-apple-car-is-canceled-ltvif8zt">in his <em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> on Sunday:<blockquote>I've repeatedly said that new software for the iPad Pro — a variant of iPadOS 17.4 designed for the updated models —  won't be complete until the end of March or even sometime in April. Once the OS is finished, Apple needs to send it off to the factories to be installed on the new hardware. That process could last a couple weeks, probably taking us deeper into next month.</blockquote>Young expects Apple to announce the new iPad Pro models in "late March or early April," so the devices could still be unveiled later this month. Gurman has also said that an announcement is possible <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/new-ipads-end-of-march-or-april-gurman/">as early as the "end of March."</a><br/>
<br/>
Young reiterated that Apple plans to launch a larger 12.9-inch iPad Air as well, and it will likely be announced alongside the new iPad Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
The following iPad-related announcements are expected in March or April:<ul><li>Two new iPad Pro models with the M3 chip, OLED displays, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/">thinner enclosure</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape-oriented front camera</a>, a redesigned rear camera bump and other design tweaks, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">possibly MagSafe wireless charging</a></li><br/>
<li>Two new iPad Air models with the M2 chip and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape-oriented front camera</a>, including a first-ever 12.9-inch model</li><br/>
<li>A new Magic Keyboard for the iPad Pro with a larger trackpad, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">a partially-aluminum enclosure</a>, and other design tweaks</li><br/>
<li>A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/">new Apple Pencil</a></li></ul>Gurman previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/03/no-apple-event-for-new-ipads-macs-gurman/">ruled out an Apple Event for the new iPads</a>. Instead, the devices will likely be announced in a press release on the Apple Newsroom website, like the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models with the M3 chip <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">were earlier this month</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Young said Samsung will be the exclusive supplier of OLED displays for the 12.9-inch iPad Pro, while Samsung and LG will apparently split orders for the 11.1-inch model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/">New iPads Likely to Begin Shipping in April</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april.2422217/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma 14.4: Reasons Not to Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/do-not-update-macos-sonoma-14-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-4-reasons-not-to-update.2422216/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 09:36:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/do-not-update-macos-sonoma-14-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Since Apple unveiled <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/">macOS Sonoma 14.4 on March 7</a>, the transition to the latest software update has not been entirely smooth for everyone, and a number of issues have been reported by users that significantly impact their daily workflow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Reasons-to-Not-Upgrade-to-macOS-Sonoma-14.4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941874" /><br/>
This article lists the most prominent challenges users have faced since updating to macOS Sonoma 14.4, and offers potential solutions where available.<br/>
<br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">USB Hub and Monitor Ports</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Lost Connectivity</span><br><br/>
Some users have experienced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-usb-hub-issues-reported/">connectivity issues with USB hubs and monitors with USB ports</a> since updating to macOS 14.4, with several reports of mice, keyboards, and other peripherals no longer being detected. While Apple works on a fix, a handful of users have had some success by changing the setting "Allow accessories to connect" to "Ask for new accessories" under the Security section of System Settings ➝ Privacy & Security.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Java Processes </span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Unexpected Terminations</span><br><br/>
Oracle last week warned that the macOS 14.4 update can cause Java processes to "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/oracle-warns-about-macos-14-4-java-issues/">terminate unexpectedly</a>" on Macs. The issue affects all Java versions from Java 8 to the early access builds of JDK 22, and there is no workaround available. Affected users might be unable to return to a stable configuration unless they have a complete backup of their systems prior to the OS update.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Printer Operation</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Removed or Corrupted Drivers</span><br><br/>
The update may <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255522015?sortBy=best">remove or corrupt printer drivers</a>. Specifically, the core CUPS software for printing operations over a network seems to be removed. HP printers in particular appear to be affected, but the exact commonalities between the reports, such as the use of <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/MacOS/comments/1b9n1mj/new_mac_os_144_update_broke_printing_no_drivers/">Microsoft Defender or JAMF mobile device management software</a>, are not entirely clear. Some users have found a workaround by granting Full Disk Access to certain processes in System Settings ➝ Privacy & Security. Despite these attempts, a comprehensive solution has not yet been found.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">PACE/iLok Protections</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Audio Unit Plugins Crash</span><br><br/>
There have been reports of compatibility issues with PACE products, including the <a href="https://help.ilok.com/faq_licenses.html#sonoma_14_4_plugins">iLok License Manager</a>, connected to Apple silicon Macs running macOS 14.4. The problem specifically impacts plugins from various manufacturers that are safeguarded by PACE/iLok, including those <a href="https://help.uaudio.com/hc/en-us/articles/24492336117652-PACE-iLok-Issue-with-macOS-Sonoma-14-4-Update">made by Universal Audio</a>, when used with host DAWs such as Logic Pro. Temporarily setting a DAW and the iLok License Manager application to <a href="https://help.ilok.com/faq_licenses.html#sonoma_14_4_plugins">run in Rosetta mode</a> appears to circumvent the issue. <br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">iCloud Drive</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Destroys Saved Versions</span><br><br/>
Users running macOS 14.4 that have "Optimize Mac Storage" enabled should be aware that they are at risk of losing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/sonoma-bug-destroys-saved-versions-icloud-drive/">all previously saved versions of a file</a> if they opt to remove it from iCloud Drive local storage. Versions are normally created automatically when users save files using apps that work with the version system in macOS. If you have already updated, either do not save files to iCloud Drive at all, or turning off Optimize Mac Storage. To perform the latter in System Settings, click your Apple ID, select iCloud, and then toggle off the switch next to "Optimize Mac Storage."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Consider Not Updating</h2><br/>
If you anticipate that any of these problems could significantly impact your daily operations or productivity, it may be prudent to delay updating to the latest version of macOS Sonoma until Apple addresses these concerns with a subsequent fix. Have you identified any other issues since updating? Let us know in the comments and we might include them here if they turn out to be commonplace.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/do-not-update-macos-sonoma-14-4/">macOS Sonoma 14.4: Reasons Not to Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-4-reasons-not-to-update.2422216/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Humorous Apple Ad Highlights iPhone 15 Storage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-iphone-15-storage-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/humorous-apple-ad-highlights-iphone-15-storage.2422215/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 09:21:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-iphone-15-storage-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest ad for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models focuses on the device's storage, highlighting the 128GB of available storage space for the entry-level device.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="iPhone 15 Storage Don't Let Me Go Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bks2zGnssMY" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The ad features a man looking through his photos, and each photo on the device sings "Don't Let Go" by Terrace Martin, Mr. Talkbox, and PJ Morton. He ultimately decides not to delete his images. The spot ends with the tagline "Lots of storage for lots of photos."<br/>
<br/>
While the standard &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models start with 128GB of storage, Apple offers 256GB and 512GB upgrade options, with an additional 1TB option for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max models start with double the storage at 256GB, with 512GB and 1TB available when upgrading.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-iphone-15-storage-ad/">Humorous Apple Ad Highlights iPhone 15 Storage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/humorous-apple-ad-highlights-iphone-15-storage.2422215/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Publishes Details About New &#039;MM1&#039; AI Model</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-mm1-ai-model-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-publishes-details-about-new-mm1-ai-model.2422211/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:46:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-mm1-ai-model-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple researchers have developed a new method for training large language models (LLMs) that seamlessly integrates both text and visual information. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
The company's findings, detailed in a research paper titled "<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2403.09611">MM1: Methods, Analysis & Insights from Multimodal LLM Pre-training</a>," showcase a new approach to creating more intelligent and flexible AI systems. By utilizing a diverse dataset comprising image-caption pairs, interleaved image-text documents, and text-only data, Apple's claims that the MM1 model sets a new standard in AI's ability to perform tasks such as image captioning, visual question answering, and natural language inference with a high level of accuracy.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's research focuses on the combination of different types of training data and model architectures, which enables the AI to understand and generate language based on a mix of visual and linguistic cues. This capability is vital for tasks that require a nuanced comprehension of the world, such as interpreting complex images or answering questions that involve visual elements.<br/>
<br/>
The paper also highlights the MM1 model's exceptional in-context learning abilities, particularly in the largest 30 billion parameter configuration of the model. This version apparently exhibits remarkable capabilities for multi-step reasoning over multiple images using few-shot "chain-of-thought" prompting, a technique that allows the AI to perform complex, open-ended problem solving based on minimal examples. <br/>
<br/>
This research emerges as part of Apple's broader initiative to enhance its AI capabilities amid growing competition. Earlier today, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">reported</a> that Apple is in discussions with Google to license Google's Gemini generative large-language models to power new features coming to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-mm1-ai-model-details/">Apple Publishes Details About New &#039;MM1&#039; AI Model</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-publishes-details-about-new-mm1-ai-model.2422211/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker and Jackery Introduce Discounts on Portable Power Stations, Bluetooth Speakers, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/anker-and-jackery-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-and-jackery-introduce-discounts-on-portable-power-stations-bluetooth-speakers-and-more.2422207/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:34:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/anker-and-jackery-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXW5JQ21%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T_1710770307988">Anker</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Jackery</a> are kicking off the week with discounts on portable power stations, as well as a wide array of wall chargers and other USB-C accessories. All of the products in this sale can be found on Amazon, and some will require you to clip an on-page coupon then head to the checkout screen before you see the final sale price<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/jackery-anker-deals.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941846" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Highlights of Jackery's deals include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a>, available for just &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00. This is a miniature-sized portable power station that can fit in the palm of your hand and weighs just 2.13 lbs, while featuring a 31,000 mAh capacity and 128W output. For these Jackery products, you can enter the code JAPLUS05 on Amazon and get an extra 5 percent discount when you purchase over &#36;1,000 through March 25.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Switching to the Anker deals, some of the best markdowns can be found on the company's Soundcore brand of Bluetooth speakers. You can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> for &#36;63.99, down from &#36;79.99, and the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXW5JQ21%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T_1710770307988">Soundcore Motion X600 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> for &#36;149.98, down from &#36;199.99. Anker also has a huge collection of batteries, cables, hubs, and more on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;16 OFF</div>Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker for &#36;63.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXW5JQ21%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T_1710770307988"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Soundcore Motion X600 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker for &#36;149.98</div></a></div><h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2D47DQD1FRWW3%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2D47DQD1FRWW3_1710770158851">Solar Generator 300 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;479.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IF0PS8UT4GJ7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IF0PS8UT4GJ7_1710770002372">Expansion Battery Pack for 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;698.99, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S52LG1288F1D%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S52LG1288F1D_1710770092703">Explorer 2000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU_1710770037246">Expansion Battery Pack for 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;63.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXW5JQ21%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T_1710770307988">Soundcore Motion X600 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;149.98, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV66XQ66">Nano Portable Charger with Built-In Lightning Connector</a> - &#36;18.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725913103">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;37.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;157.24 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725956687">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1770-Powerhouse%2Fdp%2FB099Z2RDS5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F1200 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;749.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,098.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,399.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Foldable-MacBook%2Fdp%2FB09C5RG6KV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;33.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;55.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;42.99, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;75.00, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/anker-and-jackery-discounts/">Anker and Jackery Introduce Discounts on Portable Power Stations, Bluetooth Speakers, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-and-jackery-introduce-discounts-on-portable-power-stations-bluetooth-speakers-and-more.2422207/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next iPad Air Again Rumored to Feature Landscape Front Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/ipad-air-landscape-front-camera-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-ipad-air-again-rumored-to-feature-landscape-front-camera.2422205/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:15:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/ipad-air-landscape-front-camera-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>ShrimpApplePro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The next-generation iPad Air will be equipped with a landscape front camera, according to the <a href="https://twitter.com/VNchocoTaco/status/1769727515453800930">leaker known as "ShrimpApplePro."</a><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Air-5-Colors-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1494" height="840" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941843" /><br/>
If this information is accurate, the front camera on the next iPad Air would be located in the bezel to the right of the screen when the device is held upright. As a result, the front camera would be positioned at the top of the iPad when the device is in landscape orientation, making it centered with the user's eyes during video calls. This change would be especially beneficial to those who use the iPad Air with a Magic Keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
On the current iPad Air, the front camera is in the top bezel above the screen, resulting in it being off-center in landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
The leaker does not expect the next iPad Air to have any other significant design changes. They also cast doubt on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">larger 12.9-inch iPad Air</a>, but that model has been widely rumored by multiple sources, so it would be surprising if it did not launch.<br/>
<br/>
A landscape front camera had already been rumored for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">both the next iPad Pro and iPad Air</a>, so it is becoming an increasingly likely design change. Apple already repositioned the front camera on the entry-level iPad 10 a few years ago, so it would make sense for the change to be expanded to the entire iPad lineup eventually.<br/>
<br/>
"During ‌Face ID‌ setup, iPad needs to be in landscape with the camera at the top of the screen," read <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/">hidden code in iPadOS 17.4</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil new iPads in late March or in April.<br/>
<br/>
"ShrimpApplePro" has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shrimpapplepro/">mixed track record</a> with Apple rumors over the past few years. The leaker accurately revealed details about devices like the iPhone 15 Pro and Apple Watch Series 9, but they were incorrect about the Apple Watch Ultra 2 being available in a Space Black finish and the iPad mini being updated in 2023. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shrimpapplepro/">ShrimpApplePro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/ipad-air-landscape-front-camera-rumor/">Next iPad Air Again Rumored to Feature Landscape Front Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-ipad-air-again-rumored-to-feature-landscape-front-camera.2422205/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4.1 Update for iPhone is Imminent</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/ios-17-4-1-is-imminent/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-1-update-for-iphone-is-imminent.2422201/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:27:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/ios-17-4-1-is-imminent/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 17.4.1 and iPadOS 17.4.1 should be released within the next few days, with a build number of 21E235, according to a source with a proven track record.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/General-iOS-17-Feature-Orange-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898582" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> previously reported that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/apple-preparing-ios-17-4-1/">internally testing iOS 17.4.1</a>. As a minor update for the iPhone, it will likely address software bugs and/or security vulnerabilities. It is unclear if the update will include any other changes.<br/>
<br/>
As to be expected, Apple has also been internally testing iOS 17.5, and the first beta of that update is likely to be released this week.<br/>
<br/>
We consider it likely that there will also be a macOS 14.4.1 update for the Mac at some point, as there have been complaints about several bugs on macOS 14.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-usb-hub-issues-reported/">related to USB hubs</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/oracle-warns-about-macos-14-4-java-issues/">Java</a>, Bluetooth, printers, audio plugins, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/ios-17-4-1-is-imminent/">iOS 17.4.1 Update for iPhone is Imminent</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-1-update-for-iphone-is-imminent.2422201/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Announce New iPads on March 26, Rumors Claim</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-march-26-launch-date-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-announce-new-ipads-on-march-26-rumors-claim.2422198/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:02:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-march-26-launch-date-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is widely expected to release new iPad Air and OLED iPad Pro models in the next few weeks. According to new rumors coming out of Asia, the company will announce its new iPads on Tuesday, March 26.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/When-To-Expect-New-iPads-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925410" /><br/>
Chinese leaker Instant Digital on Weibo this morning <a href="https://s.weibo.com/weibo?q=%23新款iPad或3月26日发布%23">claimed</a> that the date will see some sort of announcement from Apple related to new iPads, but stopped short of calling it an official launch date. Instead, Apple could announce pre-order availability, with shipping dates to follow.<br/>
<br/>
Separately, Chinese website <em><a href="https://www.ithome.com/0/756/324.htm">IT Home</a></em> claimed that March 26 will see Apple release new iPads. However, the outlet appears to have interpreted this as a launch date based on when several Amazon listings for third-party protective cases for the new iPads go live, rather than specific information from a trusted source.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/new-ipads-end-of-march-or-april-gurman/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, Apple plans to release new iPad Pro and iPad Air models around the end of March or in April. That said, the well-connected reporter now seems to be leaning more towards the possibility of an April release.<br/>
<br/>
Writing in the latest subscriber edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-17/apple-aapl-revamped-carplay-becomes-last-hope-after-apple-car-is-canceled-ltvif8zt">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman said he wanted to clear up confusion about when he believed Apple would release new iPads (specifically new iPad Pro models). <br/>
<br/>
Gurman reiterated that a new variant of iPadOS 17.4 designed for the updated models won't be complete until the end of March or even sometime in April. "Once the OS is finished, Apple needs to send it off to the factories to be installed on the new hardware. That process could last a couple weeks, probably taking us deeper into next month," he wrote.<br/>
<br/>
Two new iPad Pro models are expected to feature a new M3 chip, OLED displays, a thinner enclosure, a landscape-oriented front camera, a redesigned camera bump, and possibly MagSafe wireless charging.<br/>
<br/>
The two new iPad Air models are expected to feature Apple's M2 chip and a landscape-oriented front camera, including a first-ever 12.9-inch model.<br/>
<br/>
Other announcements expected in the March-April window include a new Magic Keyboard for the iPad Pro with a larger trackpad, and a new Apple Pencil.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/03/no-apple-event-for-new-ipads-macs-gurman/">ruled out an Apple Event for the new iPads</a>. Instead, he believes they will be announced in a press release on the Apple Newsroom website, like the new 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models were earlier this month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-march-26-launch-date-rumor/">Apple to Announce New iPads on March 26, Rumors Claim</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-announce-new-ipads-on-march-26-rumors-claim.2422198/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple in Talks With Google to Bring Gemini AI Features to iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-in-talks-with-google-to-bring-gemini-ai-features-to-iphone.2422190/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:15:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is in discussions with Google to integrate its Gemini AI engine into the iPhone as part of iOS 18, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-18/apple-in-talks-to-license-google-gemini-for-iphone-ios-18-generative-ai-tools"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/google-gemini.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941761" /><br/>
In a report citing people familiar with the situation, Gurman claims the two companies are in "active negotiations" to let Apple license Google's generative large-language models in order to power some new features coming in iOS 18. <br/>
<br/>
"The two parties haven't decided the terms or branding of an AI agreement or finalized how it would be implemented," according to the report's sources.<br/>
<br/>
With the release of iOS 18 later this year, Apple is rumored to be bringing major new AI capabilities to its iPhone operating system. According to Gurman, however, Apple is focusing on features that operate on-device and do not require an internet connection. <br/>
<br/>
To power additional cloud-based generative AI features, such as the ability to create images and write essays based on single prompts, Apple is seeking a partner that has the necessary large-scale hardware infrastructure and compute capabilities already in place.<br/>
<br/>
According to previous reporting by Gurman, Apple has been internally testing an "Apple GPT" rival that could compete with OpenAI's ChatGPT. The company has also been designing an "Ajax" framework for large language models, and is said to be spending <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/apple-conversational-ai-spending/">millions of dollars a day</a> on conversational AI research as training language models requires a lot of hardware.<br/>
<br/>
However, the technology is still not as advanced as tools from Google and other rivals, making a partnership look like the better option, according to the latest report.<br/>
<br/>
If the negotiations come to nothing, Apple could seek another generative AI provider such as OpenAI or turn to multiple partners. But if the talks bring about a deal, it could make up for any losses that result from the regulatory pressure facing the two companies' existing search partnership. <br/>
<br/>
Google has paid Apple billions of dollars for several years to keep its search engine the default option in Safari browser on Apple devices. However, the existing deal is facing regulatory scrutiny from the U.S. Department of Justice and the European Commission over concerns that it helps Google maintain a search monopoly. <br/>
<br/>
Both <em>The Information</em> and analyst Jeff Pu claim that Apple will have some kind of generative AI feature available on the ‌iPhone‌ and iPad <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-generative-ai-late-2024-jeff-pu/">around late 2024</a>, which is when iOS 18 will be coming out. However, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/02/no-sign-of-apple-generative-ai-coming-2024/">said in August</a> that there is "no sign" of generative AI technology coming in 2024, and he claimed that Apple's work on generative AI is "significantly behind its competitors."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">Apple in Talks With Google to Bring Gemini AI Features to iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-in-talks-with-google-to-bring-gemini-ai-features-to-iphone.2422190/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air Hits All-Time Low Prices at Best Buy, Get Up to &#36;300 Off</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/apples-m2-macbook-air-low-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-macbook-air-hits-all-time-low-prices-at-best-buy-get-up-to-300-off.2422160/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 10:04:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/apples-m2-macbook-air-low-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy's <a href="https://howl.me/clP3pE3bdqq">weekend sale</a> includes great deals on the 13-inch and 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, both of which have hit all-time low prices. Anyone can get these deals and you don't need a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership to see the discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937843" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, you can get the 256GB model for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3a0AyvQe"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model has hit <a href="https://howl.me/clP3bKRUICQ"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Both of these are record low prices on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3a0AyvQe"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3bKRUICQ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch M2 MacBook Air is available for &#36;100 off across the board this weekend at Best Buy. The 256GB model is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> and the 512GB model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"><strong>&#36;1,099.00</strong></a>. You can get both models in all four colors: Starlight, Space Gray, Silver, and Midnight.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m2-macbook-air-under-1000/">discontinued</a> the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air earlier this month, following the introduction of the M3 MacBook Air. At the same time, the company knocked the price of the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air down by &#36;100, selling them alongside the M3 models.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/apples-m2-macbook-air-low-prices/">Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air Hits All-Time Low Prices at Best Buy, Get Up to &#36;300 Off</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-macbook-air-hits-all-time-low-prices-at-best-buy-get-up-to-300-off.2422160/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Two New AirPods 4 Models Expected to Launch in September or October</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/airpods-4-production-and-launch-timing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/two-new-airpods-4-models-expected-to-launch-in-september-or-october.2422158/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 07:56:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/airpods-4-production-and-launch-timing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple suppliers will begin production of two new fourth-generation AirPods models in May, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-17/apple-aapl-revamped-carplay-becomes-last-hope-after-apple-car-is-canceled-ltvif8zt"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Based on this production timeframe, he expects the headphones to be released in September or October.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/airpods-3-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893120" /><br/>
Gurman expects both fourth-generation AirPods models to feature a new design with better fit, improved sound quality, and an updated charging case with a USB-C port. The higher-end ones will also feature active noise cancellation and a speaker in the charging case that can play a sound for Find My location tracking, he said.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to discontinue the second-generation and third-generation AirPods after launching the two fourth-generation models, he previously said.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman does not expect new AirPods Pro to launch until next year at the earliest, but he said the current models will get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/airpods-pro-to-gain-hearing-aid-mode-ios-18/">new hearing aid mode with iOS 18</a>. He added that Apple is also working on a hearing test feature for AirPods.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/airpods-4-production-and-launch-timing/">Two New AirPods 4 Models Expected to Launch in September or October</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/two-new-airpods-4-models-expected-to-launch-in-september-or-october.2422158/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Apple ID&#039; Expected to Change to &#039;Apple Account&#039; Starting With iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/apple-id-rebrand-to-apple-account-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-id-expected-to-change-to-apple-account-starting-with-ios-18.2422155/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 07:13:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/apple-id-rebrand-to-apple-account-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple ID</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>MacRumors</em> was first to report that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-id-to-apple-account-rebrand/">planning to rebrand "Apple ID" to "Apple Account"</a> across its software platforms and websites like iCloud.com as early as this year, and now <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-17/apple-aapl-revamped-carplay-becomes-last-hope-after-apple-car-is-canceled-ltvif8zt"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> has corroborated this change.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17-Passkey-With-Apple-ACCOUNT-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941734" /><em>A mockup of the new Apple Account branding</em></div><br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-17/apple-aapl-revamped-carplay-becomes-last-hope-after-apple-car-is-canceled-ltvif8zt"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, Gurman said the new "Apple Account" branding will start to be used later this year both online and in Apple's next major software releases, such as iOS 18 for the iPhone and watchOS 11 for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already refers to funds added to an Apple ID as an "<a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT208687">Apple Account balance</a>," and Gurman said there is an "Apple Account" team within the company. With the full rebranding later this year, the term Apple ID is expected to be completely phased out, over two decades after the company started using it. Apple's reasoning behind the decision is not known, but "Apple Account" would be more straightforward branding.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will preview iOS 18 and its other major software updates at its developers conference WWDC in June, and the rebranding to "Apple Account" will likely be announced then. The updates should be widely released in September.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/17/apple-id-rebrand-to-apple-account-ios-18/">&#039;Apple ID&#039; Expected to Change to &#039;Apple Account&#039; Starting With iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-id-expected-to-change-to-apple-account-starting-with-ios-18.2422155/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Larger Store at Canada&#039;s Square One Mall Opens Next Saturday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/new-apple-square-one-store-opens-march-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-larger-store-at-canadas-square-one-mall-opens-next-saturday.2422114/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:37:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/new-apple-square-one-store-opens-march-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's relocated store at the Square One shopping mall in Mississauga, Ontario will hold its grand opening on Saturday, March 23 at 10 a.m. local time, according to updated wording on the store's construction facade, shared with us  <a href="https://twitter.com/ApolloZhaoD/status/1769095750946865601">by Apollo Zhao</a>. Mississauga is located just west of Toronto, the most populous city in Canada.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Square-One-New.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941679" /><em>The new Apple Square One (via <a href="https://twitter.com/ApolloZhaoD/status/1769095750946865601">Apollo Zhao</a>)</em></div><br/>
Thursday, March 21 <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/retail/squareone/">will be the final day of business</a> at Apple's existing Square One store, which originally opened in August 2009.<br/>
<br/>
The new store is located on the second floor of Square One, above the central food court, and it has a very wide, partially-curved facade. It has a significantly larger footprint than the existing store, which will allow it to better accommodate the heavy customer traffic at Canada's second-largest indoor shopping mall.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Get ready. Great things are in store. <br>Apple Square One<br>Opens Saturday March, 23 at 10:00 am <a href="https://t.co/MXFZn6OO90">pic.twitter.com/MXFZn6OO90</a></p>&mdash;  (@ApolloZhaoD) <a href="https://twitter.com/ApolloZhaoD/status/1769095750946865601?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 16, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/new-apple-square-one-store-opens-march-23/">Apple&#039;s Larger Store at Canada&#039;s Square One Mall Opens Next Saturday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-larger-store-at-canadas-square-one-mall-opens-next-saturday.2422114/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Oracle Warns macOS 14.4 Can Cause Java to Terminate Unexpectedly</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/oracle-warns-about-macos-14-4-java-issues/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oracle-warns-macos-14-4-can-cause-java-to-terminate-unexpectedly.2422104/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 11:04:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/oracle-warns-about-macos-14-4-java-issues/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		<category>Java</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Oracle this week warned that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/">macOS 14.4 update</a> released earlier this month for Macs can cause Java processes to "terminate unexpectedly."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-feature-purple-green.jpg" alt="" width="2585" height="1454" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898568" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://blogs.oracle.com/java/post/java-on-macos-14-4">blog post</a> on Friday, Oracle's Senior Director of Product Management Aurelio Garcia-Ribeyro recommended that Apple silicon Mac users who rely on Java avoid updating to macOS 14.4 until the issue is resolved by Apple:<blockquote>An issue introduced by macOS 14.4, which causes Java process[es] to terminate unexpectedly, is affecting all Java versions from Java 8 to the early access builds of JDK 22. There is no workaround available, and since there is no easy way to revert a macOS update, affected users might be unable to return to a stable configuration unless they have a complete backup of their systems prior to the OS update.</blockquote>The blog post and <a href="https://bugs.java.com/bugdatabase/view_bug?bug_id=8327860">bug report</a> include more technical details about the issue.<br/>
<br/>
Oracle says it has notified Apple about the issue. Apple did not immediately respond to our request for comment about the matter.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> macOS 14.4 also has <a href="https://support.izotope.com/hc/en-us/articles/17519558551581-Issues-with-macOS-14-4-Sonoma">compatibility</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/sonnoxplugins/status/1766062245551694135">issues</a> with audio plugins protected by PACE/iLok. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/java/">Java</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/oracle-warns-about-macos-14-4-java-issues/">Oracle Warns macOS 14.4 Can Cause Java to Terminate Unexpectedly</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oracle-warns-macos-14-4-can-cause-java-to-terminate-unexpectedly.2422104/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Samsung&#039;s ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor With Steep &#36;700 Discount, Plus More Display Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-with-steep-700-discount-plus-more-display-deals.2422090/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 07:18:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung this weekend has the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor at a steep discount, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. In addition to this &#36;700 discount, you'll find deals on <a href="https://howl.me/clLNSBlHkaL">4K and 5K Samsung monitors</a> in Samsung's new sale, including the Smart Monitor M8, as well as storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/samsung-viewfinity-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939071" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor is at a very solid second-best price this weekend, just &#36;50 higher compared to the previous record low price. This monitor has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also being discounted during this sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clP2G8L9fVC"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> in Warm White, down from &#36;699.99. This is a 4K smart monitor with a design that looks similar to the new iMac line, and it's at another great second-best price during Samsung's monitor sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/samsung-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905732" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP2G8L9fVC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, when you <a href="https://howl.me/clM4GKBZeXm">sign up to learn more</a> about Samsung's upcoming TV and audio product lineup, you can get &#36;100 off your purchase. The new slate of Samsung TVs and audio equipment is set to be unveiled on March 21, and this &#36;100 discount offer will be available through that date.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2hIAozaO">27-inch Odyssey HDR10 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;269.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gYG78Q9">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;549.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gbHK6cQ">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNROoH7so">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs/Audio</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN0R87SoM">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNX3ZnLNR">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNYXDQ23m">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNWfhuoAS">85-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;2,399.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-discount/">Get Samsung&#039;s ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor With Steep &#36;700 Discount, Plus More Display Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-with-steep-700-discount-plus-more-display-deals.2422090/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 14 vs. iPhone 16: 30+ Upgrades to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16-30-upgrades-to-expect.2422087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16&#038;post_date=1710608400/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 14</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After over a year of reports, there are now more than a dozen specific rumors about the features and improvements set to be offered by the two non-Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models later in 2024. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPhone-14-vs-16-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-941488" /></div><br/>
While the upgrades that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; offers over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> will likely be at the center of Apple's marketing strategy later this year, many users are on two-year upgrade cycles, so the features introduced on both the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will stack up. All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their two direct forerunners are listed below, using information from a range of reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">previously covered</a>. We will update this article as more rumors emerge in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
This guide focuses on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, but to learn about how we are expecting the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro to improve on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">see our other comparison article</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design">Design</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to largely carry over the design of their predecessors. As a result, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will be a relatively significant evolution over the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌, featuring slightly rounded edges, a frosted glass back, and a vertical rear camera arrangement to facilitate spatial video capture. Other important design changes are expected to include the removal of the mute switch in favor of the Action button introduced on last year's Pro models and the introduction of an all-new "Capture" button.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Aluminum chassis with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Aluminum chassis with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Glossy glass back</td><br/>
 <td>Color-infused frosted glass back</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Notch" TrueDepth camera array</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Diagonally arranged rear camera array</td><br/>
 <td>Vertically arranged rear camera array to support spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action Button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>"Capture Button" to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="displays">Displays</h3><br/>
For &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; users, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will offer many of the display upgrades that came to the previous generation, as well as a more efficient OLED panel thanks to micro-lens technology.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>800 nits max brightness (typical)</td><br/>
 <td>1,000 nits max brightness (typical)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1,200 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 <td>1,600 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>2,000 nits peak brightness (outdoor)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="cameras">Cameras</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; introduced a major camera upgrade for Apple's standard smartphone lineup, bringing over the 48-megapixel camera of the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro. With a number of other improvements such as spatial video capture, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; should be a significant camera upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.5 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.6 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x and 1x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, and 2x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_memory_and_connectivity">Chip, Memory, and Connectivity</h3><br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models rumored to receive the same A18 chip as the Pro models, the new models could offer a major performance improvement over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, which features the A15 Bionic chip first introduced in 2021. The 2GB of additional memory and the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip are also due to be notable upgrades. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N5P" enhanced 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory (+33%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting denser batteries and faster charging capabilities. It is worth noting that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus is rumored to feature a smaller battery than its predecessors, but it is not clear how this will affect actual battery life. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 14</strong>: 3,279 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 14 Plus</strong>: 4,325 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 3,561 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 4,006 mAh battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 27W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging (48% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; (33% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Setting to prevent charging above 80%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Battery manufacture date, first use, and cycle count information in Settings</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h3><br/>
While many of Apple's devices are rumored to receive a series of new AI-based features via software updates later this year, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to take these further with exclusive capabilities facilitated by a more powerful Neural Engine in the A18 chip and an upgraded microphone.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Upcoming support for new AI features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></td><br/>
 <td>Upcoming support for new AI features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, plus a suite of device-exclusive AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance, designed to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; was a fairly significant upgrade over the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ in 2023, introducing a more modern design with the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;, a USB-C port, and q 48-megapixel camera. The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; will build on these upgrades, offering the Capture and Action buttons, AI features, and spatial video capture. With over 30 upgrades rumored to be in store, many ‌current &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ users will find upgrading to an ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model worthwhile, if not essential.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to launch in the fall. Apple usually hosts an event every September to unveil new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, with launch following just over a week later. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16/">iPhone 14 vs. iPhone 16: 30+ Upgrades to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-vs-iphone-16-30-upgrades-to-expect.2422087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
