<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 13:03:19 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games Lays Off Over 800 Employees as Apple Legal Battle Drags On</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/epic-games-layoffs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-lays-off-over-800-employees-as-apple-legal-battle-drags-on.2405337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:54:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/epic-games-layoffs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, the company behind popular video game Fortnite, is laying off 830 employees or approximately 16 percent of its workforce. The layoffs come amid Epic's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/">ongoing legal battle with Apple</a>, which started way back in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite_apple_featured.jpg" alt="" width="2140" height="1204" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-754674" /><br/>
Just this week, &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/">asked the Supreme Court to hear the case</a>, a request that follows two major losses and likely hundreds of thousands or more in legal fees. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; has been trying to paint Apple as a monopolist, and it wants to be able to sell digital skins and other goods to Apple customers without having to pay a cut to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
As a result of the legal dispute, Fortnite has been unavailable from Apple's App Stores for several years now, and those who want to play the game on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> must seek alternate means to do so, such as web-based platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Epic CEO Tim Sweeney in a memo sent out to employees and <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/site/en-US/news/layoffs-at-epic">shared on the company's website</a> said that it has been "spending way more money" than it earns to grow Fortnite, and other efforts to cut costs have "ended up far short of financial sustainability."<br/>
<br/>
Sweeney says that layoffs are the only way to stabilize the company's finances. Employees will be provided with severance that includes six months of base pay and six months of paid healthcare.<br/>
<br/>
As for the fight against Apple, Sweeney claims that &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is taking steps to cut down on legal expenses, but will continue on with its legal battles so the "metaverse can thrive and bring opportunity to Epic and all other developers."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/epic-games-layoffs/">Epic Games Lays Off Over 800 Employees as Apple Legal Battle Drags On</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-lays-off-over-800-employees-as-apple-legal-battle-drags-on.2405337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iCloud Website Updated With iOS 17 and macOS Sonoma Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-icloud-website-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-icloud-website-updated-with-ios-17-and-macos-sonoma-features.2405328/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:07:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-icloud-website-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, Apple has updated its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> website with design changes and some of the new features that came in the software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iCloud-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803318" /><br/>
Apple says that the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; homepage is now customizable, with options to select specific folders for Notes, a specific mailbox in the Mail app, favorite <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, and more. Tiles are now interactive, so you can do things like mark a Reminder as complete or archive an email, plus there are browser notifications that can be set up for &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also redesigned Calendar, Contacts, Reminders, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-drive/">iCloud Drive</a>. The full release notes for the new version of the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; website are below.<blockquote><h3>General</h3><br/>
<strong>Customize What You See in Tiles</strong><br/>
Choose a specific folder for Notes, a mailbox for Mail, display just your favorite Photos, and more. You can also configure your homepage to show multiple layouts of the same tile so you can see more content from your favorite apps. Access layout options in the menu in the lower-left corner of a tile.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Quick Actions From Tiles</strong><br/>
Mark reminders as complete, flag an email, see a preview of a file in Drive, and more. Perform actions from tiles by hovering on content and selecting to reveal quick actions. If you're on a touch device, swipe to the left.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Browser Notifications</strong><br/>
Get notified of new email or event invitations and updates with browser notifications on a PC for Mail and Calendar. You can configure browser notifications in iCloud Settings on the web.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Updated Design</strong><br/>
New design and layouts across Calendar, Contacts, Reminders, Drive, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iCloud Mail</h3><br/>
<strong>Attach from iCloud</strong><br/>
Attach photos and files to email messages directly from iCloud.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Undo Send</strong><br/>
Easily unsend an email message that you just sent before it reaches the recipient's inbox.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iCloud Calendar</h3><br/>
<strong>Calendar Identity Control</strong><br/>
Control the email address others see in event invitations and even use your Custom Email Domain to unite your Calendar and Mail identities. Manage it all from iCloud Calendar settings.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iCloud Drive</h3><br/>
<strong>List View</strong><br/>
Switch between viewing your files as icons or in as a list with the toggle in the upper left corner.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Preview Your Files</strong><br/>
Press the Space bar after selecting a file or photo to get a quick preview before opening or downloading it. You can also access quick view through the options menu.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Access File Options</strong><br/>
Easily access actions like renaming a file or downloading a copy through the options menu.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iCloud Photos</h3><br/>
<strong>Memories</strong><br/>
See your Memories and play them in a full-screen view by clicking on the memory.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Slideshow</strong><br/>
To view your selection in a slideshow, select Play Slideshow from the menu in the upper right corner.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Notes</h3><br/>
<strong>Linked Notes</strong><br/>
Create links to other notes by typing &gt;&gt; or Command + K as a shortcut to add links while writing in your note.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Shared Folders</strong><br/>
Collaborate with others on an entire folder of notes.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Enhanced Search</strong><br/>
Use suggested search to refine your search against categories like shared notes, checklists, tags and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Reminders</h3><br/>
<strong>Customize Your Reminders</strong><br/>
Add dates, locations, flags, and more using the edit details button.</blockquote>Apple's &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; website is available at <a href="https://www.icloud.com">iCloud.com</a> on any web browser, and it is particularly useful to those who are on a PC and may not otherwise have access to their &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; content on the machine.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Tim!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-icloud-website-update/">Apple&#039;s iCloud Website Updated With iOS 17 and macOS Sonoma Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-icloud-website-updated-with-ios-17-and-macos-sonoma-features.2405328/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1.2405318/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:24:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first public beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.1 update, allowing non-developers to test out the software ahead of its release. The public beta comes a day after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/apple-first-beta-macos-sonoma-14-1/">the first developer beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1 includes updates for the Music app, introducing an option to favorite songs, albums, artists, and more. No other major new additions have been found in the beta as of yet, but we could see more features added as the beta progresses.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-public-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1.2405318/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Betas of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 to Public Beta Testers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-to-public-beta-testers.2405314/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:15:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 updates to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to try out the software ahead of its release. The public iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 betas come a day after Apple released the betas for developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912331" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
In the iOS 17.1 beta, Apple added an option to favorite songs, albums, playlists, artists, and more, from within <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and through the Now Playing widget.<br/>
<br/>
AirDrop transfers can now be finished over the internet after being initiated, and when you activate the flashlight, there's an indicator in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> even if you don't have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or Pro Max. For more on what's new in the update, we have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.1 beta 1 tidbits article</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also released a new beta of tvOS 17.1 with the same &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; changes, plus there is a public beta of watchOS 10.1 available for public beta testers. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/watchos-10-1-beta-namedrop-apple-watch/">watchOS 10.1 enables NameDrop</a> on Apple Watch for sharing contact information with other Apple Watch and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users over AirDrop. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-public-beta-1/">Apple Releases First Betas of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 to Public Beta Testers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-betas-of-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-to-public-beta-testers.2405314/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Appeals Epic Games Ruling Over &#039;Anti-Steering&#039; Provisions to U.S. Supreme Court</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-appeals-epic-games-ruling-over-anti-steering-provisions-to-u-s-supreme-court.2405291/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:52:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a day after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/">Epic Games appealed one portion</a> of its legal dispute with Apple to the U.S. Supreme Court, Apple has now done the same for the portion that was ruled in Epic's favor, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-28/apple-asks-supreme-court-to-reverse-app-store-ruling-won-by-epic">reports <em>Bloomberg</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
The dispute between Apple and Epic <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">dates back to 2020</a> with Epic seeking to overturn Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules requiring content purchases within iOS apps to go through Apple, which takes a 15% to 30% cut of the revenue.<br/>
<br/>
In multiple rounds of the dispute, Apple has won on every count with the exception of one regarding Apple's "anti-steering" rule that bars developers of many iOS apps from directing users to methods of purchase available outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, circumventing Apple's revenue cut.<br/>
<br/>
Apple had said it was considering appealing the ruling over its anti-steering provision to the Supreme Court, and back in July a judge ruled that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/app-store-rule-change-epic-games-delayed/">did not have to make changes to its policies</a> pending the potential appeal, which has now been filed.<br/>
<br/>
The Supreme Court will decide in the coming months whether it will hear either or both of Epic's and Apple's appeals, but if it does not take up either petition, the previous rulings will stand. Apple would be able to continue to disallow third-party payment processing within apps but would have to allow developers to inform users about other purchasing options outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/">Apple Appeals Epic Games Ruling Over &#039;Anti-Steering&#039; Provisions to U.S. Supreme Court</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-appeals-epic-games-ruling-over-anti-steering-provisions-to-u-s-supreme-court.2405291/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Adds Custom Playlist Art Options to Apple Music</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/custom-apple-music-playlist-art-options/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-adds-custom-playlist-art-options-to-apple-music.2405286/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:24:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/custom-apple-music-playlist-art-options/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple added a new feature to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> app in the first beta of iOS 17.1 that offers a selection of color-matched playlist artwork options for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17-Playlist-Artwork-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-914404" /><br/>
As of beta one, Apple provides eight different artwork styles featuring geometric shapes and gradients, with the title of the playlist in the top left corner. The colors used in the artwork are picked from the album artwork of whatever song is first in the playlist. The default artwork continues to be the tiled album artwork of the first four songs in a playlist and the ability to choose a custom image from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> or Files remains.<br/>
<br/>
Previously, users had to keep the basic tiled image or upload a custom image. Since not all users have custom graphics or photos they want to use for playlists and the default artwork is relatively simple, playlists can be difficult to identify and look fairly generic. Now, users can quickly and easily set a unique appearance for each playlist that fits in with &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;'s UI.<br/>
<br/>
Other &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; changes and improvements in iOS 17.1 include favoriting songs from the Lock Screen and suggested songs in playlists. The ability for multiple users to collaborate on and add to the same playlist and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; SharePlay for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> are also expected to be added in a future update. iOS 17.1 introduces a host of new features, including NameDrop to Apple Watch, UK <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">bank balances in the Wallet app</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">more</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/custom-apple-music-playlist-art-options/">iOS 17.1 Adds Custom Playlist Art Options to Apple Music</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-adds-custom-playlist-art-options-to-apple-music.2405286/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Take Up to &#36;300 Off the 14-Inch MacBook Pro With All-Time Low Prices Starting at &#36;1,749</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/deals-14-inch-macbook-pro-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-take-up-to-300-off-the-14-inch-macbook-pro-with-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-1-749.2405284/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:20:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/deals-14-inch-macbook-pro-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[B&H Photo today has all-time low prices on a few models of the 14-inch MacBook Pro, with as much as &#36;300 off these notebooks. All three MacBook Pro devices on sale include free two-day shipping, and B&H Photo notes that these sale prices will end later tonight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-MacBook-Pro-M2-Feature-Blue-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-881249" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 10-Core M2 Pro/512GB 14-inch MacBook Pro, this model is available for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746355-REG/apple_mphh3ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/kw/APMBM2P512S/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;1,749.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,999.00. Both the Silver and Space Gray are on sale at this price, which is a match of the all-time low price on this model of the 14-inch MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746355-REG/apple_mphh3ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/kw/APMBM2P512S/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (10-Core M2 Pro/512GB) for &#36;1,749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
B&H Photo also has the 12-Core M2 Pro/1TB 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746356-REG/apple_mphf3ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/kw/APMBM2P1TBG/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;2,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;2,499.00. This one is only available in Space Gray, and it's another match of a record low price on the 14-inch MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746356-REG/apple_mphf3ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/kw/APMBM2P1TBG/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M2 Pro/1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, you can get the 12-Core M2 Max/1TB 14-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746358-REG/apple_mphg3ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/kw/APMBM2M1TBG/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;2,799.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;3,099.00. This model is again only available in Space Gray, and at &#36;300 off it's an all-time low price. As of writing, all of these discounts can only be found on B&H Photo.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746358-REG/apple_mphg3ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/kw/APMBM2M1TBG/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (12-Core M2 Max/1TB) for &#36;2,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/deals-14-inch-macbook-pro-3/">Deals: Take Up to &#36;300 Off the 14-Inch MacBook Pro With All-Time Low Prices Starting at &#36;1,749</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-take-up-to-300-off-the-14-inch-macbook-pro-with-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-1-749.2405284/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Concerns Highlighted in Two More Reports</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-overheating-concerns-highlighted-in-two-more-reports.2405278/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 06:25:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max overheating concerns continue to make headlines this week, with the topic <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/personal-tech/apple-new-iphone-15-overheat-dbd5171a">highlighted by <em>The Wall Street Journal</em></a> and <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-27/apple-iphone-15-pro-users-complain-that-device-can-get-too-hot"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
Both of the reports document anecdotal complaints from customers, and outline potential causes, but it's unclear how many devices are actually affected. <em>Bloomberg</em> said the overheating could be caused or compounded by the iPhone's setup process, suggesting that the higher temperatures might sometimes be a temporary condition. <br/>
<br/>
<em>The Wall Street Journal</em> quoted a customer who felt his iPhone 15 Pro Max remained hotter than his iPhone 13 Pro Max a few days after setting up the device:<blockquote>Thomas Galvin, a 23-year-old from Cleveland, says his iPhone 15 Pro Max has been "super hot" and that he is considering returning it. Apple customer support told him the heat was a result of setting up the new phone, but even a few days later, it is still "way worse than the iPhone 13 Pro Max," he said.</blockquote><em>The Wall Street Journal</em>'s Joanna Stern said her iPhone 15 Pro Max did heat up while charging and performing processor-intensive tasks, such as gaming, but she said her iPhone 14 Pro Max reached similar temperatures in the same test. During typical everyday usage, Stern said the temperature of both devices was in a normal range. Many customers on social media have also said their iPhone 15 Pro is not experiencing any overheating, and the lack of hard data makes it unclear if there is a widespread problem.<br/>
<br/>
On Wednesday, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said the titanium frame on iPhone 15 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/">negatively impacts thermal efficiency</a>. Kuo believes that Apple will likely address the issue through software updates, but he said improvements may be limited unless Apple lowers the performance of the A17 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not commented on the concerns, and it's unclear if the company will actually make any software optimizations in future iOS updates.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/">iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Concerns Highlighted in Two More Reports</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-overheating-concerns-highlighted-in-two-more-reports.2405278/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Apple Payments Services&#039; Company Likely Behind New Apple Wallet Features in UK, Potentially More to Follow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-payments-services-behind-uk-wallet-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-payments-services-company-likely-behind-new-apple-wallet-features-in-uk-potentially-more-to-follow.2405276/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 06:15:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-payments-services-behind-uk-wallet-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An Apple-acquired company now renamed "Apple Payments Services" is likely behind the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">UK-exclusive Apple Wallet features</a> in iOS 17.1, potentially hinting that Apple has plans to launch additional financial services in the country.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/credit-kudos-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-840785" /><br/>
Last year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/23/apple-acquires-uk-banking-startup/">Apple acquired Credit Kudos</a>, a UK open banking startup that sought to help lenders make better decisions. <em>MacRumors</em> has now learned  that Apple filed to change the name of Credit Kudos to Apple Payments Services Limited in July. "Credit Kudos" is now simply a trading name of Apple Payments Services.<br/>
<br/>
Credit Kudos offered insights and scores based on loan applications drawn from transaction and loan outcome banking data, sourced by the UK's open banking framework. The ability to see account balances directly in Apple Wallet is a new UK-exclusive feature in iOS 17.1, powered by the country's regulated open banking API. Since Credit Kudos' expertise focused on UK open banking, it seems highly likely that last year's acquisition is behind the new feature. <br/>
<br/>
It is not clear what Apple has planned for Credit Kudos' technology in the future, but it is almost certain that it extends beyond balance visibility in Apple Wallet, especially considering Apple paid £131 million (&#36;170 million) for the company in March 2022. The relatively recent decision to rename the company to Apple Payments Services similarly suggests that the company's work is ongoing. <em>MacRumors</em> understands that 31 employees left Credit Kudos following Apple's acquisition, but a team of over a dozen employees, as well as co-founder and CEO Freddy Kelly, remain at the company. <br/>
<br/>
Credit Kudos's API offered lenders a way to get faster, automated decision-making about loans with reduced risk and higher rates of acceptance. It is therefore plausible that the company's technology could aid Apple with the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> in the UK. The UK is among Apple's most important markets, with the country possessing the largest number of Apple Stores outside the United States and China, and new features and services are often first to reach the UK after launching in the U.S.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's main credit product, &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;, is available exclusively in the United States. It is possible that Apple could modify Credit Kudos's technology to work with the U.S.'s growing open banking sector to strengthen &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;'s credit checker, but Apple could also use it to credit check &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; applications in the UK directly since Credit Kudos is a licensed credit reference agency.<br/>
<br/>
Credit markets and financial regulation vary massively in countries around the world, so it would not be straightforward for Apple to launch &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; internationally. Apple would likely need to seek specific solutions to make lending decisions in each country, so it seems plausible that Credit Kudos could be the chosen credit checking platform for the UK.<br/>
<br/>
Following the success of &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; in the U.S., it could make sense for Apple to expand into overseas markets. While visiting Germany in 2019, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/09/30/tim-cook-visits-germany/">confirmed his interest</a> in launching &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; internationally.<br/>
<br/>
Apple often acquires smaller businesses to bolster its technologies and expertise without obviously or immediately rolling it into a product or service. On the other hand, many acquisitions do go on to be key parts of Apple's ecosystem. In recent years, Apple has acquired businesses such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/12/11/apple-acquires-shazam/">Shazam</a>, a music recognition service, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/25/apple-acquires-self-driving-car-startup-drive-ai/">Drive.ai</a>, an autonomous vehicles company. Acquired apps such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/03/31/apple-acquires-weather-app-dark-sky/">Dark Sky</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/03/22/apple-acquires-popular-automation-app-workflow/">Workflow</a> were folded into or became new Apple apps. Specialized classical music streaming service <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/30/apple-acquires-primephonic-classical-music-service/">Primephonic</a> is one of the latest companies to be integrated into existing Apple products, becoming the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> Classical app.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-payments-services-behind-uk-wallet-features/">&#039;Apple Payments Services&#039; Company Likely Behind New Apple Wallet Features in UK, Potentially More to Follow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-payments-services-company-likely-behind-new-apple-wallet-features-in-uk-potentially-more-to-follow.2405276/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Video Review: 72 Hours Using the iPhone 15 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/72-hours-using-the-iphone-15-pro-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-review-72-hours-using-the-iphone-15-pro-max.2405272/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 06:00:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/72-hours-using-the-iphone-15-pro-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera picked up a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max on launch day, and he spent the last four days using it non-stop to give <em>MacRumors</em> readers an idea of how the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> experience is going and his first thoughts on the features Apple added this year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SGZ_9Q2Pnfg?si=DvZ5K7RCkULejY05" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
There have been complaints about the new &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/">getting too hot</a>, but other than a heat issue when using an uncertified USB-C cable to connect to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, Dan hasn't run into trouble and he hasn't seen overheating problems. The same is true for the rest of us at <em>MacRumors</em> - our iPhones appear to be functioning as intended and running cool following the initial setup and syncing period.<br/>
<br/>
With the switch to titanium, Apple lowered the weight of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, plus added contoured edges that are much more comfortable to hold. Dan says that this is one of the most notable changes for him, and it makes picking up an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> downright uncomfortable.<br/>
<br/>
Battery life has been solid, but the Action Button is a work in progress and it can take some time to figure out what's most useful. We'll have a dedicated Action Button video coming sometime in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
As for the camera, it's unsurprisingly pretty great. 24-megapixel photos make a difference, and the 5x Telephoto lens is an improvement over the prior 3x version. We're also planning an in-depth camera comparison, so stay tuned for that.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch Dan's full video, and if you have one of the new &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, let us know what you think in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/72-hours-using-the-iphone-15-pro-max/">Video Review: 72 Hours Using the iPhone 15 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-review-72-hours-using-the-iphone-15-pro-max.2405272/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to View Your UK Bank Account Balance and Deposits in Apple Wallet</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-view-your-uk-bank-account-balance-and-deposits-in-apple-wallet.2405247/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 03:09:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet&#038;post_date=1695906595/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 17.1, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">currently in beta</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in the UK can now view the account balance of their bank cards and credit cards right within Apple's Wallet app. Keep reading to learn how it works.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/uk-bank-account-apple-wallet-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914320" /><br/>
Apple's Wallet app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has been able to display <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> transactions made using your bank and credit cards for a while now, but if you are a Wallet app user in the United Kingdom, a new integration in iOS 17.1 means you can view your current account balance from your bank, along with a history of your deposits and payments. If you have a credit card, you can also view your remaining credit.<br/>
<br/>
To get the additional account information, your bank needs to support the Open Banking API that Apple has implemented. Supporting banks currently include Barclays, Monzo, Startling, HSBC, Lloyds, and RBS, with more banks likely to come on board when iOS 17.1 is released to the public.<br/>
<br/>
The following steps show you how integration is securely authorized through the Wallet app. It's a simple enough process, and Apple will automatically redirect you to your bank app to authenticate the connection. Note that until iOS 17.1 is officially released, <strong>the iOS 17.1 developer beta must be installed on your iPhone</strong> for this to work.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Wallet app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
<li>Tap a card from a supporting bank.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Get Started</strong> under "See Balances and Full Transaction History for This Account."</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Continue</strong> to connect your account to Wallet.</li><br/>
<li>Check the account details that you are about to give Wallet permission to access, then tap <strong>Continue</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>In your bank app, enter your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s passcode or use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> to grant Wallet permission to access the specified account details.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet.jpg" alt="" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914317" /><br/>
<br/>
After following these steps, you'll be directed back to the Wallet app, where you will now see the available balance of your account underneath the bank card, along with your transaction history. If it's a credit card, you'll also see the remaining balance available, while a tap on the balance will also reveal your credit limit.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Wallet also keeps annual transaction histories for linked accounts. You can access them for each account in <strong>Settings -> Wallet & Apple Pay</strong>: Tap the connected account under "Connections," tap the card under "Accounts," then tap <strong>Account Activity</strong>, where you can view transactions by year.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple users in the UK still unable to make use of Apple Cash or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, it's nice to see Apple exclusively supporting a British banking standard in its Wallet app. Note that Open Banking is UK-specific: No US equivalent is currently available.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">How to View Your UK Bank Account Balance and Deposits in Apple Wallet</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-view-your-uk-bank-account-balance-and-deposits-in-apple-wallet.2405247/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the New AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;199.99 Thanks to Amazon&#039;s &#36;49 Discount [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/new-airpods-pro-2-usb-c/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-new-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-199-99-thanks-to-amazons-49-discount-updated.2405016/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 03:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/new-airpods-pro-2-usb-c/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last week, Apple launched the all-new AirPods Pro 2 with the USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case. At the same time, we began tracking the first ever discount on the earbuds, and over the past day or two that &#36;49 markdown is back at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-USB-C-Port-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911675" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the new model of the AirPods Pro 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. Given that the accessory isn't even a week old yet, this is the best deal we've seen so far, and Amazon provides an estimated delivery date of late September/early October.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are a few minor changes to the AirPods Pro 2 besides the addition of USB-C, including additional dust resistance and support for lossless audio with the Vision Pro headset. Apple doesn't sell the USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case separately, so if you want USB-C support you'll have to purchase a full new set of earbuds.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This deal has now expired. If the AirPods Pro 2 return to &#36;199.99, we'll be sure to update this article again.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update 2:</strong> The &#36;199.99 sale price briefly reappeared this afternoon, but has once again expired. If you don't see the deal on Amazon, be sure to check back later, as it could return later in the day. <br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update 3:</strong> As of the morning of September 28, the price continues to fluctuate at Amazon, so keep checking and grab a pair whenever it's dropped to &#36;199.99 if you're interested.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/new-airpods-pro-2-usb-c/">Get the New AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;199.99 Thanks to Amazon&#039;s &#36;49 Discount [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-new-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-199-99-thanks-to-amazons-49-discount-updated.2405016/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Jony Ive and OpenAI in Advanced Talks to Build &#039;the iPhone of Artificial Intelligence&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/jony-ive-iphone-artificial-intelligence-openai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/jony-ive-and-openai-in-advanced-talks-to-build-the-iphone-of-artificial-intelligence.2405241/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 02:00:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/jony-ive-iphone-artificial-intelligence-openai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Financial Times</category>
		<category>Jony Ive</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Former Apple designer Jony Ive and OpenAI's Sam Altman are in advanced talks with SoftBank's Masayoshi Son to launch a &#36;1 billion venture to build "the iPhone of artificial intelligence," according to the <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4c64ffc1-f57b-4e22-a4a5-f9f90a7419b7">Financial Times</a></em>. The news follows a report on Wednesday that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/jony-ive-openai-design-ai-hardware/">claimed</a> Ive and Altman are in discussions about creating an AI gadget.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/jony-ive.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914301" /><br/>
According to <em>FT</em>, Altman wants Ive's design agency LoveFrom to help develop the ChatGPT creator's first consumer device. From the paywalled report:<br/>
<blockquote>Altman and Ive have held brainstorming sessions at the designer's San Francisco studio about what a new consumer product centered on OpenAI's technology would look like, the people said.<br/>
<br/>
They hope to create a more natural and intuitive user experience for interacting with AI, in the way that the iPhone's innovations in touchscreen computing unleashed the mass-market potential of the mobile internet.<br/>
<br/>
The process of identifying a design or device remains at an early stage with many different ideas on the table, they said.</blockquote>Son, Softbank's founder and CEO, has been involved in some of the discussions, which have centered around creating a company drawing from Softbank, Altman's OpenAI, and Ive's LoveFrom design agency. <br/>
<br/>
Son is said to be pitching a central role for British chip designer Arm, in which the Japanese conglomerate holds a 90% stake. Son is also offering &#36;1 billion investment in the venture, according to the report.<br/>
<br/>
Ive is said to have been concerned about the compulsive nature of smartphone users' behavior, and the designer sees the project as an opportunity to create a way of interacting with computers that is less reliant on screens.<br/>
<br/>
Discussions are said to be "serious," but no deal has been agreed, and it could be several months before any official announcement, cautioned people with knowledge of the matter. Any resulting device would likely remain years away from launching.<br/>
<br/>
Ive left Apple to begin LoveFrom in 2019, recruiting at least four of his former Apple colleagues to work with him at the firm, including Wan Si, Chris Wilson, Patch Kessler, and Jeff Tiller.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ft-com/">Financial Times</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jony-ive/">Jony Ive</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/jony-ive-iphone-artificial-intelligence-openai/">Jony Ive and OpenAI in Advanced Talks to Build &#039;the iPhone of Artificial Intelligence&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/jony-ive-and-openai-in-advanced-talks-to-build-the-iphone-of-artificial-intelligence.2405241/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta Debuts &#36;500 Quest 3 as Apple Prepares to Launch &#36;3,500 Vision Pro Headset Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/meta-quest-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-debuts-500-quest-3-as-apple-prepares-to-launch-3-500-vision-pro-headset-next-year.2405179/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 16:06:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/meta-quest-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Facebook</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Facebook parent company Meta <a href="https://www.meta.com/quest/quest-3">today announced</a> the upcoming launch of the &#36;500 Meta Quest 3, its newest mixed reality headset that goes up against the much more expensive Vision Pro that Apple plans to launch next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/meta-quest-3.jpg" alt="" width="1385" height="779" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914163" /><br/>
Meta claims that the Quest 3 was redesigned from the inside out, and it features "4K+ Infinite Display resolution" thanks to two displays with a 2064x2208 resolution per eye and an "experimental" 120Hz refresh rate. Comparatively, Apple's headset uses 4K micro-OLED displays and provide a total of 23 million pixels.<br/>
<br/>
The Quest 3 is equipped with 3D spatial audio and a 40 percent louder volume range than the Quest 2. Meta is using Qualcomm's Snapdragon XR2 Gen 2 chip for the headset, and it offers double the GPU processing power of the Meta Quest 2. Meta says with the new chip, the Quest 3 supports "fast-action gaming, seamless full-color, and high-resolution passthrough."<br/>
<br/>
Two RGB cameras with 10x better resolution than the Quest 2 provide a view of the surrounding area, and virtual objects are able to be manipulated in your physical space. This is the augmented reality part of the headset, and it mirrors what's possible with the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/meta-quest-3-controllers.jpg" alt="" width="1758" height="989" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914164" /><br/>
The Meta Quest 3 weighs in at 515 grams, which is over a pound, and it is slightly heavier than the Quest 2. There is, however, a slimmer optic profile thanks to new pancake lenses, so Meta says the headset is more comfortable to wear. There is a soft adjustable strap that holds it on the head, and the facial interface can be adjusted to improve comfort and field of view. There is 110 degree horizontal field of view and a 96 degree vertical field of view for extended peripheral vision, plus sharpness in the center field of view has been increased by 25 percent. Unlike Apple's headset, there is no eye tracking or iris scanning.<br/>
<br/>
For input, the Meta Quest 3 uses two Touch Plus Controllers that serve as a "natural extension" of the hands and offer tactile haptic feedback. Meta is using computer vision and machine learning sensors to follow hand gestures, and there are a series of cameras that enable controller-free navigation, which is similar to what's possible with the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
The Meta Quest 3 lasts for up to 2.2 hours per charge on average, and it does not include an external battery pack. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> also lasts for two hours when connected to its external battery, but it can run all day when hooked up to a power source.<br/>
<br/>
Other features include 8GB RAM, Wi-Fi 6E, an LED that lets people nearby know when cameras are in use, and support for connecting to a PC with the Meta Quest Link Cable and Air Link.<br/>
<br/>
The Meta Quest 3 is priced at &#36;499.99 for 128GB of storage or &#36;649.99 for 512GB of storage and can be pre-ordered from the <a href="https://www.meta.com/quest/quest-3">Meta website</a>, <a href="https://howl.me/ckGhrU7nxKN">Best Buy</a>, and other retailers starting today. Orders are set to start arriving in October.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facebook/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/meta-quest-3/">Meta Debuts &#36;500 Quest 3 as Apple Prepares to Launch &#36;3,500 Vision Pro Headset Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-debuts-500-quest-3-as-apple-prepares-to-launch-3-500-vision-pro-headset-next-year.2405179/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Yale Launches Apple Home Key-Enabled Assure Lock 2 Plus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/yale-home-key-lock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/yale-launches-apple-home-key-enabled-assure-lock-2-plus.2405167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/yale-home-key-lock/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		<category>Yale</category>
		<category>Home Keys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yale today announced the launch of the <a href="https://shopyalehome.com/pages/yale-assure-lock-2-plus">Yale Assure Lock 2 Plus</a>, its latest smart lock that has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> integration and Apple Home Key support. With Home Key integration in the Wallet app, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or an Apple Watch can be used to unlock the door with just a tap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/yale-home-key-lock.jpg" alt="" width="1510" height="848" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914168" /><br/>
The Assure Lock 2 Plus is a keyless entry lock, which means it does not have a backup key option. Aside from Home Key, it can be accessed with &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; commands or entry codes. The entry codes can be used to provide guests with access, and there is an optional Wi-Fi module for remote access to the lock.<br/>
<br/>
Yale today also debuted the <a href="https://shopyalehome.com/pages/yale-assure-lock-2-touch">Assure Lock 2 Touch</a>, a &#36;199 smart lock that has a fingerprint sensor and &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; integration, but no support for Home Key. Yale does not offer a lock that provides both Home Key support and a fingerprint sensor, so those interested in a Yale lock will need to choose.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://shopyalehome.com/pages/yale-assure-lock-2-plus">Yale Assure Lock 2 Plus with Home Key</a> is priced at &#36;210 for Bluetooth connectivity, or &#36;290 for Wi-Fi support. The Wi-Fi models require a 2.4GHz network.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://shopyalehome.com/pages/yale-assure-lock-2-touch">Yale Assure Lock 2 Touch</a> is priced at &#36;199 for the Bluetooth version, with both keyed and key-free models available. A version with Wi-Fi connectivity is priced at &#36;280.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/yale/">Yale</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-keys/">Home Keys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/yale-home-key-lock/">Yale Launches Apple Home Key-Enabled Assure Lock 2 Plus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/yale-launches-apple-home-key-enabled-assure-lock-2-plus.2405167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling Refurbished 2023 Mac Studio Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/refurbished-2023-mac-studio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-2023-mac-studio-models.2405162/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:56:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/refurbished-2023-mac-studio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac Studio</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Max and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> models to its <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/refurbished/mac/mac-studio">online store for refurbished products</a> in the U.S., allowing the desktop machines to be purchased at a discounted price for the first time since their June 2023 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/mac-studio-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-859358" /><br/>
The entry-level &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; with 32GB RAM and 512GB SSD is available for &#36;1,699, which is a &#36;300 discount off of the standard &#36;1,999 price. The base model &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra machine with 64GB RAM and a 1TB SSD is priced at &#36;3,399, a &#36;600 discount off of the regular &#36;3,999 price.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is offering multiple &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; models for purchase at the current time, and all of them offer similar ~15 percent discounts off of the standard prices. Discounts range from &#36;300 to &#36;1300 depending on configuration and starting price.<br/>
<br/>
The 2023 &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; models were introduced in June 2023 alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> models. They offer &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; performance and the same &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra chip in a more compact package.<br/>
<br/>
All of Apple's refurbished Macs are close to identical to new products. They are subject to a refurbishment process that includes full functionality testing, with any defective modules replaced, as well as a thorough cleaning and inspection. Refurbished products are eligible for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ and have the same 14-day return period as new Apple devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac-Studio">Mac Studio (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-studio.237">Mac Studio</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/refurbished-2023-mac-studio/">Apple Now Selling Refurbished 2023 Mac Studio Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-2023-mac-studio-models.2405162/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games Asks Supreme Court to Hear Apple Case</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-asks-supreme-court-to-hear-apple-case.2405160/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:44:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> today filed a petition for a writ of certiorari with the Supreme Court, which basically means the company is asking the Supreme Court to make a ruling in its ongoing legal battle with Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
The Supreme Court is the last stop for &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; after it lost an appeal earlier this year. The Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals in April 2023 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/24/epic-games-loses-appeal-app-store-battle/">sided with the lower court</a> and ruled that Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules do not violate antitrust law by not allowing for third-party marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
Since 2020, Epic has been pushing for a ruling that would allow it to skirt the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and offer apps directly to consumers through sideloading or an alternate store, but its legal arguments <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/10/epic-games-vs-apple-decision/">have not been successful</a>. Epic ultimately wants to sell digital skins and other goods to its Fortnite customers without having to give Apple a 30 percent cut of its proceeds.<blockquote>Epic also offers digital goods--such as outfits--that users can purchase for use within Fortnite. Epic has invested vast sums in developing not just Fortnite but those digital add-ons, to which Apple contributes nothing. But Apple required Epic to use its IAP and pay the 30% commission on every in-app purchase that any iPhone user made directly from Epic, no matter how many years after downloading Fortnite from the App Store.</blockquote>Epic's 488 page filing lists several reasons why the Supreme Court should hear the case, focusing on errors made by the lower courts and the significance of the case, as any major &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; change would impact hundreds of thousands of developers.<br/>
<br/>
The Supreme Court could opt not to hear Epic's case, and it only accepts a fraction of the cases that it is asked to review each year.<br/>
<br/>
When the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals made its decision, it upheld the ruling of the lower court, including the mandate that Apple allow developers to direct customers to purchase options outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Apple does not want to make these &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes, and so it too may ask the Supreme Court to make a ruling on that portion of the case.<br/>
<br/>
Apple back in in July <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/app-store-rule-change-epic-games-delayed/">was given 90 days</a> after the appeals court ruling to decide whether it would petition the Supreme Court. Apple has not yet contacted the Supreme Court, nor has it hit that 90 day limit. When the 90-day limit expires, Apple will either need to ask the Supreme Court to hear the case or implement the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes that it has been ordered to make.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/epic-games-supreme-court/">Epic Games Asks Supreme Court to Hear Apple Case</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-asks-supreme-court-to-hear-apple-case.2405160/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything New in iOS 17.1 Beta 1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-17-1-beta-1.2405150/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:57:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a week after releasing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, Apple has seeded the first beta of iOS 17.1 to developers. iOS 17.1 adds some features that Apple promised were coming to &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; in the future, plus it refines and improves some existing features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912333" /><br/>
This guide covers everything new in the first iOS 17.1 beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music Favorites</h2><br/>
You can favorite songs, albums, playlists, and artists in the iOS 17.1 Music app. Favorited music is added to the Library and improves recommendations. Favoriting replaces the prior "Love" system and favoriting can be done from the Lock Screen's Now Playing widget.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-music-favorite.jpg" alt="" width="1290" height="822" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914260" /><br/>
A star next to a track in an album means that it's a favorite, while a dot is next to the most played track. With the favorites system, the Music app is suggesting songs to add to playlists.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-music-song-suggestions.jpg" alt="" width="1290" height="1229" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914261" /><br/>
Eventually, Apple plans to provide a Favorite Songs playlist and offer collaborative playlists, but these features do not appear to be implemented as of yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirDrop</h2><br/>
AirDrop transfers can now be completed over a cellular connection or Wi-Fi if you walk out of the range of the person you're sharing with. That means you will not have to stay close to someone if you are transferring a large number of files.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/ios-17-1-airdrop.jpg" alt="" width="1290" height="1796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914263" /><br/>
There is a new "Out of Range" toggle in the AirDrop section of the Settings menu that you can toggle to allow or disallow transfers over cellular.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>NameDrop on Apple Watch</h2><br/>
With watchOS 10.1 and iOS 17.1, an Apple Watch and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> can now be used to exchange contact information through the NameDrop feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/namedrop-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="2501" height="1396" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-906032" /><br/>
<h2>Ringtones and Text Tones</h2><br/>
The more than <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-ringtones-text-tones/">20 new ringtones and text tones</a> that were added in the launch version of &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have disappeared in the first beta of iOS 17.1, but Apple will likely re-add them in a later update.<br/>
<br/>
Custom tones for Mail and Messages have been re-added.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>UK Bank Balances in the Wallet App</h2><br/>
UK users can <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-to-developers.2405112/post-32568420">add their UK bank accounts</a> to the Wallet app in iOS 17.1, allowing them to see their account balances, payments, purchases, and deposits.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Books App</h2><br/>
The "Reading Now" section in the Apple Books app has been renamed to "Read Now."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Journal App</h2><br/>
There is no sign of the promised Journal app in iOS 17.1, but there are mentions of Journaling Suggestions in the code, which indicates that it could be coming before too long.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Dynamic Island Flashlight Indicator </h2><br/>
When the flashlight is activated on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro, &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, or &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, there is now a flashlight icon in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> that lets you know that It is on. The flashlight icon for the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj; was previously limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
 <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/dynamic-island-flashlight.jpg" alt="" width="1179" height="561" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914275" /><br/>
<h2>Controller Support</h2><br/>
iOS 17.1 <a href="https://x.com/aaronp613/status/1707161935358157268?s=20">includes support</a> for the Nintendo Switch N64 Controller.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Extend Wallpaper</h2><br/>
When you are setting up a new wallpaper, Apple has added an "Extend" option that can be used if the image does not fit the display.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More iOS 17.1 Beta 1 Features</h2><br/>
Know of a feature that we left out in this list? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">Everything New in iOS 17.1 Beta 1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-17-1-beta-1.2405150/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Details: Action Button, USB-C Port, Face ID, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-details-action-button-usb-c-port-face-id-and-more.2405145/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:34:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Significant changes are expected to arrive with Apple's fourth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, in terms of both design and hardware, <em>MacRumors</em> has learned.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/iphone-se-4-modified-flag-edges.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886982" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, known internally under the codename Ghost, is expected to receive a new design derived almost entirely from the base model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>. According to our sources, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will use a modified version of the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; chassis and will even maintain &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; test parameters for internal testing. <br/>
<br/>
As far as the chassis is concerned, two major changes are expected – an Action button and a USB-C port. The Action button, recently debuted on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, is a multi-purpose button which replaces the mute switch on newer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. It can be configured to perform a variety of actions, depending on the user's preference.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is also set to receive a USB-C port in order to comply with upcoming European Union regulations. Our sources have seen extensive references to the E85 connector, which is what Apple calls USB-C internally. Apart from these two major differences, no significant changes are planned for the chassis compared to the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, and it will likely not feature the curved edges of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup.<br/>
<br/>
As for the back of the device, the next &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will feature a single camera with the flash aligned in an arrangement similar to the third-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;. The exact design of the camera bump, however, remains unclear at the time of writing. Apple has developed at least five different designs for the camera bump, with minor differences among them. They fall into two major categories:<br/>
<ul><li>Camera and flash encompassed in a single, oblong-shaped camera bump</li><br/>
<li>Only the camera ring raised from the main backplate surface</li></ul><br/>
Preliminary information suggests that the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 may feature a 48-megapixel rear camera, providing for a significant upgrade from the current model.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will also likely receive a new OLED panel, derived from the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. The device will not feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> home button, but will instead have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> as the means of biometric identification. Multiple references to "Pearl," Apple's internal codename for &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; and associated hardware, have been spotted in relation to the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also working on an in-house 5G modem, codenamed “Sinope”, and is using the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 to test the new hardware. Current information suggests that the new modem is being tested on the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 and a derivative of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, known as "D84S." Originally, the new 5G modem was meant to make its debut with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, being available across the entire range. According to information from our sources, this may no longer be the case. Additionally, Qualcomm recently issued a press release stating that the company would be providing smartphone modems for Apple until 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Previous claims have suggested that Apple was developing the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 exclusively for modem testing, and that it was not intended for mass production or release to the general public. This theory seems unlikely, as it does not explain the amount of effort put into the overall design of the device including multiple camera bump iterations, as well as part changes.<br/>
<br/>
If the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 had been intended exclusively for modem testing, this likely would not necessitate a camera redesign or the inclusion of an Action button. From a pragmatic point of view, it would make more sense to reuse existing parts with only a minimum amount of modification, as was done with the D84S.<br/>
<br/>
It's worth noting that the information presented here is preliminary, pre-preproduction information. The fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is still early in the development process, and changes are always possible. As a result, the information may not fully align with the specifications of final mass-production units, assuming the project makes it to this stage.<br/>
<br/>
For additional details on what to expect, check out our dedicated guide for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">iPhone SE 4</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-se-4-details/">iPhone SE 4 Details: Action Button, USB-C Port, Face ID, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-details-action-button-usb-c-port-face-id-and-more.2405145/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Battery Health Features Remain Limited to iPhone 15 Models on First iOS 17.1 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-battery-health-features-iphone-15-only/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-battery-health-features-remain-limited-to-iphone-15-models-on-first-ios-17-1-beta.2405140/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:03:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-battery-health-features-iphone-15-only/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[All four iPhone 15 models have two new battery health features in the Settings app, including the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/check-battery-cycle-count-iphone-15/">view the battery's cycle count</a> and an option to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/iphone-15-80-percent-battery-limit-option/">more strictly limit charging beyond 80%</a>. On <a href="https://twitter.com/BetaProfiles/status/1704476683414409443">social media</a>, some users hoped these features would expand to older iPhone models in a future software update, but we are able to confirm that they remain limited to the iPhone 15 lineup as of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-1/">first iOS 17.1 beta</a> released today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17-Battery-Cycle-Count-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914246" /><br/>
It's early in the iOS 17.1 beta testing cycle, so there is still a chance the features are added to older iPhone models in a later beta. However, it's also possible there are hardware-related reasons behind the battery health features being limited to the iPhone 15 lineup. We've reached out to Apple for comment on the matter.<br/>
<br/>
On iPhone 15 models, the 80% charging limit option can be found in the Settings app under Battery → Battery Health & Charging → Charging Optimization. It is separate from the pre-existing Optimized Battery Charging feature on iPhones, which intelligently delays charging past 80% until a more appropriate time by learning the device's daily charging routine. When the 80% limit is enabled, the iPhone will never charge beyond that percentage, except on rare occasions to "maintain accurate battery state-of-charge estimates."<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT210512">support document</a>, Apple says reducing the time that an iPhone battery is fully charged can reduce the wear on the battery and improve its lifespan.<br/>
<br/>
On iPhone 15 models, the battery's cycle count, manufacturing date, and first use date can be viewed in the Settings app under General → About. This information can provide additional insight into the health of the battery. The battery's maximum capacity remains listed under Battery → Battery Health & Charging.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 is expected to be released in late October.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-battery-health-features-iphone-15-only/">New Battery Health Features Remain Limited to iPhone 15 Models on First iOS 17.1 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-battery-health-features-remain-limited-to-iphone-15-models-on-first-ios-17-1-beta.2405140/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
