<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 17:09:33 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From the &#039;Scary Fast&#039; October 30 Apple Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-october-2023-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-the-scary-fast-october-30-apple-event.2408923/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:52:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-october-2023-event&#038;post_date=1698443569/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Event</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple earlier this week surprised us with an unexpected October event, and curiously, it is set to take place on Monday, October 30 at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time. Apple has never hosted a nighttime event before, so Monday should be quite interesting.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vvQEWR12rtU" title="what to expect at scary fast event" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The "Scary Fast" event will be focused on the Mac, which has been confirmed by Apple's artwork for the event. On Apple's website, there is an Apple logo that morphs into the Mac Finder icon, so it's Macs that we're going to see.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors have been mixed about what we can expect at the event, but it's sounding like we'll get the entire M3 chip lineup. We've outlined what we've heard is coming, but we might also get some unexpected announcements.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="14-inch_and_16-inch_macbook_pro">14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
The 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models were updated with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips in January 2023, so it is early for an update, but it is not unheard of for Apple to refresh a Mac twice in a single year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/macbook-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893124" /><br/>
Apple is expected to update the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with its next-generation M3 Pro and M3 Max chips, which will come less than a year after Apple debuted the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
The base M3 Pro chip will have a 12-core CPU and 18-core GPU, with upgrades available for a 14-core CPU and 20-core GPU. The base M3 Max chip will have a 16-core GPU and a 32-core GPU, with an option to upgrade to a 40-core GPU.<br/>
<br/>
Upgrading from &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro/&zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max to M3 Pro and M3 Max should bring notable performance improvements, especially when it comes to the GPU and the ability for the MacBook Pro to run high-end games.<br/>
<br/>
There was a recent rumor from <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></em> suggesting that the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models will get more power-efficient miniLED displays, so there is a chance that we'll also see tweaks to display performance.<br/>
<br/>
If we get the M3 upgrade and a new miniLED display, the MacBook Pro models could have significant improvements to their battery life. Aside from the new chips and the possible new display, we are not expecting any other design changes for the MacBook Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="imac">iMac</h2><br/>
Apple hasn't refreshed the 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> since 2021, and it's still using the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip. The &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is expected to get an update at Apple's event, and the new version will use the M3 chip, the same chip that will be in the 13-inch MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iMac-M3-Blue-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917291" /><br/>
Jumping from &zwnj;M1&zwnj; to M3 will improve both CPU and GPU performance, but most notably the GPU performance. The M3 chip supports more RAM, so we could see more maximum memory available with an update, as well as a higher-capacity SSD.<br/>
<br/>
There won't be notable design changes to the display of the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> believes that Apple will tweak the stand. Some of the internal components in the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; will be relocated and redesigned, with a new manufacturing process used to attach the stand.<br/>
<br/>
An upgrade to Wi-Fi 6E is likely, as is Bluetooth 5.3. These are technologies that have been introduced in other Macs over the last year. The M3 &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is reportedly being tested in orange, blue, pink, and silver finishes, so we should see some of the same color options that were available with the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="usb-c_accessories">USB-C Accessories</h2><br/>
Apple is expected to eliminate the Lightning port in several of its Mac accessories, including the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard. Instead of Lightning, these devices will adopt a USB-C port as part of Apple's transition to USB-C across its entire product lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/magic-mouse-2-lightning.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-835832" /><br/>
<h2 id="other_possibilities">Other Possibilities</h2><br/>
Aside from the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; and refreshed 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models, there are no other rumors that suggest other devices are getting updated. <br/>
<br/>
Initial information indicated that the 13-inch MacBook Pro could see a refresh with an M3 chip, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/m3-13-inch-macbook-pro-unlikely-to-be-at-event/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> has since confirmed the 13-inch MacBook Pro will be refreshed at a later date.<br/>
<br/>
Other Macs, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> won't be updated until 2024, and the same goes for the iPads and AirPods. We are not expecting new iPads or new versions of the AirPods until next year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="how_to_watch">How to Watch</h2><br/>
Apple's "Scary Fast" event begins at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time on Monday, October 30. Apple is streaming the event on its <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">Events website</a> that can be viewed on any web browser, plus there will be a <a href="https://youtu.be/ctkW3V0Mh-k">livestream on YouTube</a>.<br/>
<br/>
For those with access to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; set-top box or a smart TV, Apple will also offer an event livestream option for your TV.<br/>
<br/>
For those unable to watch, <em>MacRumors</em> will be providing full event coverage on MacRumors.com and the <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive">MacRumorsLive Twitter account</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-event/">Apple Event</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-october-2023-event/">What to Expect From the &#039;Scary Fast&#039; October 30 Apple Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-the-scary-fast-october-30-apple-event.2408923/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Public Beta of iOS 17.2 With Journal App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-2-with-journal-app.2408915/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:40:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 updates to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to try out the software ahead of its release. The public iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 betas come a day after Apple released the betas for developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918853" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 adds the Journal app designed to let <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users record their daily activities and thoughts. Apple offers prompts that can be used as inspiration, and journal entires can be outfitted with images, voice recordings, location tags, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Collaborative playlists are now available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> so you can create playlists that multiple people contribute to, and there's also now a Favorites playlist that has all the music you've favorited. Stickers can be used as tapback reactions in the Messages app, the Action Button on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models can now be set to a new Translate function, and Apple has implemented support for iMessage Contact Key Verification.<br/>
<br/>
There are new Weather and Clock widgets, tweaks to the TV app, updates to Message syncing across devices, new Memoji options, and more, with the full list of features we've found so far available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.2 beta features article</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also released new public betas of tvOS 17.2 and watchOS 10.2. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Public Beta of iOS 17.2 With Journal App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-2-with-journal-app.2408915/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macos-sonoma-14-2-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2.2408914/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:40:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macos-sonoma-14-2-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first public beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2 update, allowing non-developers to test out the software ahead of its release. The public beta comes a day after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-1/">the first developer beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 adds Messages sticker reactions, which make it quicker to add a sticker or an emoji to an iMessage. It also includes support for collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists, allowing multiple people to add songs to a single playlist. <br/>
<br/>
There's a new Favorites &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; playlist as well, better support for Messages in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> syncing, and iMessage Contact Key Verification for people who face extraordinary digital threats. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macos-sonoma-14-2-public-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2.2408914/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Early Black Friday Sale Has 15-Inch MacBook Air at Record Low &#36;999 Price (&#36;300 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/best-buy-early-black-friday-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-early-black-friday-sale-has-15-inch-macbook-air-at-record-low-999-price-300-off.2408908/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:20:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/best-buy-early-black-friday-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is joining the <a href="https://howl.me/ckSzIUk6sei">early Black Friday sale</a> club this weekend, offering My Best Buy Plus and Total members a chance to save on Apple products, video games, TVs, headphones, and much more. We're tracking another similar <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/sonos-early-black-friday-sale/">early Black Friday sale at Sonos</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/macbook-air-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919064" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You'll need to be a My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total member in order to see these deals. These memberships <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxsZbYnLm">start at &#36;49.99 per year</a>, and provide a few bonuses over the free version of My Best Buy. This includes free two-day shipping, exclusive access to sales like this weekend's early Black Friday event, extended 60-day return window on most products, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckSzIhnEM7l"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckSxndcNcwD"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In terms of Apple products, Best Buy's early Black Friday sale has a new all-time low price on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air. You can get the 256GB model for &#36;999.00 and the 512GB model for &#36;1,199.00, thanks to an extra &#36;50 discount with your My Best Buy Plus or Total membership. These total &#36;300 in savings and are the steepest prices we've ever seen on these notebooks.<br/>
<br/>
If you don't have a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership, you can still get &#36;250 off these 15-inch MacBook Air models at both Best Buy and Amazon (prices reflected below). We're also tracking all-time low prices on two other MacBook Air models below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>13.3-inch M1 MacBook Air (256GB) - &#36;749.99 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxo25HorZ">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li>13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) - &#36;899.00 at <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxn9qnXnb">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) - &#36;1,049.00 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxldeCBca">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) - &#36;1,249.00 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxndcNcwD">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;1,499.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Beyond Apple products, you can also find a few solid deals on Samsung monitors and TVs during this event. The <a href="https://howl.me/ckSBf4iR34F">Odyssey 49-inch Gaming Monitor</a> is available at &#36;1,299.99 (&#36;900 off) and the <a href="https://howl.me/ckSBfJ7YaPw">85-inch Neo QLED 8K Smart TV</a> is available at &#36;2,499.99 for My Best Buy Plus or Total members (&#36;2,000 off). <a href="https://howl.me/ckSBgNEm62U">Browse the full sale</a> for even more deals.<br/>
<br/>
We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/best-buy-early-black-friday-sale/">Best Buy Early Black Friday Sale Has 15-Inch MacBook Air at Record Low &#36;999 Price (&#36;300 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-early-black-friday-sale-has-15-inch-macbook-air-at-record-low-999-price-300-off.2408908/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Mac Event Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/the-macrumors-show-scary-fast-event-expectations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-scary-fast-mac-event-expectations.2408906/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:00:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/the-macrumors-show-scary-fast-event-expectations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/lets-talk-apples-scary-fast-october-mac-event/id1602394741?i=1000632854100">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss our expectations about Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">"Scary Fast" event</a>, which is widely <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/">rumored</a> to see the announcement of new Mac models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Qu3eAzqRywQ?si=EEp0ff4sM_vaiur9" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We talk through the unusual nature of the event, with Apple announcing it less than one week in advance, opting for an unorthodox 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time start, and even offering an explicit nod to the arrival of new Macs with a Finder easter egg. The event is expected to see the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/">debut of the M3 chip</a> and some of its more powerful variants. Two Mac models are currently in the running to be announced, with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> and high-end MacBook Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/">rumored to be on the table</a>. We also discuss our feelings about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> as we approach three years since their introduction and more.<br/>
<br/>
The podcast is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so head over and subscribe to keep up with new episodes and short clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion with Luke Miani about the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> with USB-C, the direction of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup, and Vision Pro. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is now on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@macrumorsshow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/the-macrumors-show-scary-fast-event-expectations/">The MacRumors Show: &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Mac Event Expectations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-scary-fast-mac-event-expectations.2408906/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro Max From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-15-pro-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-max-from-grid-studio.2408901/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 09:22:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-15-pro-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 256GB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max from Apple. For those unfamiliar with <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">GRID Studio</a>, the company takes old, discarded Apple devices and turns them into clever artwork.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/GRID-1.jpg" alt="" width="1348" height="759" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919076" /><br/>
Each of GRID Studio's pieces features a deconstructed Apple device with the components laid out underneath a glass frame. There are labels for each part, along with interesting and relevant historical facts and details.<br/>
<br/>
One of GRID Studio's most popular offerings is the GRID 1, <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">priced at &#36;400</a>. The GRID 1 features the original Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from 2007, highlighting the components that made up what has become the most popular smartphone in the world. The iconic original &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; casing is positioned next to the power button, headphone socket, speaker, logic board, ear piece, and other components, and this is before the days where Apple started making its own chips.<br/>
<br/>
The GRID 4, <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/framed-iphone-4">available for just &#36;99</a>, is another great piece of Apple history. It highlights the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4, which is the first major redesign that Apple came out with. The GRID 4 includes the popular square-style frame that dictated several generations of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/GRID-iPhone4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919077" /><br/>
GRID Studio's <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-5">&#36;139 GRID 5</a> shows off the internal components from the 2012 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5 is notable because it was the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that was developed under Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, and the last &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that Apple CEO Steve Jobs was directly involved with. Compared to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4s, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5 brought a taller 4-inch display and it was also the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to feature a Lightning port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/GRID-iPhone-5.jpg" alt="" width="1816" height="1022" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919078" /><br/>
For Apple Watch fans, GRID Studio has the <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/apple-watch-series-0">&#36;199 GRID Watch 1st Gen</a>, which features the components from the first Apple Watch that Apple released in April 2015. Apple Watches today still use the same design that Apple introduced with the original model, though the display has grown and the bezels have been slimmed down. The original Apple Watch included the S1 chip, Apple's first system-on-a-chip, and the first Apple Watch heart rate sensor.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/GRID-APPLE-WATCH.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919079" /><br/>
In addition to art pieces featuring torn-apart devices, GRID Studio also sells a range of fun t-shirts that are aimed at Apple fans. The <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-command-t-shirt">&#36;39 GRID Command t-shirt</a>, for example, features the command key design recreated with a series of rainbow Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Command-Tshirt.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919081" /><br/>
Now is a good time to check out the <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio website</a> because the company is hosting its autumn sale. From October 27 to October 29, the GRID 4 is available for &#36;99, while all Apple A-series mobile processor artwork is priced at &#36;79. All other items are available at a 15 percent discount with the promo code A15.<br/>
<br/>
GRID Studio will be providing one lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader with a 256GB &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/Y31Ww/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (October 27) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on November 3. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after November 3 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-15-pro-max/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro Max From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-max-from-grid-studio.2408901/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Early Black Friday Sale Has 20% Off Home Theater Audio Bundles This Weekend Only</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/sonos-early-black-friday-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-early-black-friday-sale-has-20-off-home-theater-audio-bundles-this-weekend-only.2408894/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 08:31:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/sonos-early-black-friday-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Although we're still a few days away from November, early Black Friday sales have begun at a few retailers. One of the most notable sales is at <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos</a>, which is offering 20 percent off select home theater bundles for two days only.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/sonos-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919046" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Sonos. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale only covers multi-device bundles, and it will run through Sunday, October 29. These bundles include soundbars, subwoofers, and speakers, and they offer as much as &#36;385 off these home audio products. You can find all of the bundles on sale in the list below, and no coupon codes are required to see these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">20% OFF</div>Sonos Bundle Discounts</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-ray-sub-mini">Ray soundbar + Sub Mini</a> - &#36;566, down from &#36;708</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-beam-sub-mini">Beam soundbar + Sub Mini</a> - &#36;742, down from &#36;928</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/immersive-set-beam-sub-mini-era-100-pair">Beam soundbar + Era 100 Speaker (2) + Sub Mini</a> - &#36;1,240, down from &#36;1,426</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-arc-sub">Arc soundbar + Sub</a> - &#36;1,358, down from &#36;1,698</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/premium-immersive-set-arc-sub-era-100-pair">Arc soundbar + Era 100 speakers (2) + Sub</a> - &#36;1,856, down from &#36;2,196</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/ultimate-immersive-set-arc-sub-era-300-pair">Arc soundbar + Era 300 speakers (2) + Sub</a> - &#36;2,211, down from &#36;2,596</li></ul> We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/sonos-early-black-friday-sale/">Sonos Early Black Friday Sale Has 20% Off Home Theater Audio Bundles This Weekend Only</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-early-black-friday-sale-has-20-off-home-theater-audio-bundles-this-weekend-only.2408894/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Teams Up With EA SPORTS FC for New Ad Campaign and Exclusive Game Benefits</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/beats-ea-sports-fc-collab/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-teams-up-with-ea-sports-fc-for-new-ad-campaign-and-exclusive-game-benefits.2408890/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/beats-ea-sports-fc-collab/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Beats brand is announcing a new collaboration today with EA SPORTS FC and star footballer Erling Haaland, which involves a new ad and multiple in-game Beats integrations for <a href="https://www.ea.com/games/ea-sports-fc/fc-24">EA SPORTS FC 24</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ClORGJ4Ed7Q?si=KTf21t6uLJEXkX-n" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The new ad featuring Haaland was built using EA's Frostbite game engine to remix scenes of Haaland from the recent Beats ad <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EuUXiJW2HjY">"The King & The Viking"</a> featuring Haaland and NBA legend LeBron James.<br/>
<br/>
Under the new partnership, users who play EA SPORTS FC 24 by November 1 will receive Founder status in the game with access to exclusive in-game rewards such as a permanent Erling Haaland item in Ultimate Team mode and custom digital Beats Studio Pro in a Haaland-inspired Viking theme.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/beats-ea-sports-fc-ambassador.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919008" /><br/>
And coming in December, FC 24 Player Career mode will add the ability for users to purchase additional virtual Beats headphones from their in-game salaries to earn Personality Points that enhance their on-field performance. As players advance through the mode, they'll be able to become Beats Ambassadors for additional salary and other benefits, while Manager Career mode will allow users to outfit their teams with Beats-inspired kits.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/beats-ea-sports-fc-collab/">Beats Teams Up With EA SPORTS FC for New Ad Campaign and Exclusive Game Benefits</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-teams-up-with-ea-sports-fc-for-new-ad-campaign-and-exclusive-game-benefits.2408890/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Halloween Deals: The Best Apple Product and Accessory Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/halloween-deals-best-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halloween-deals-the-best-apple-product-and-accessory-sales.2408884/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:26:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/halloween-deals-best-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Halloween is just a few days away, and in anticipation of the holiday we're tracking multiple sales and promotions on Apple-related accessories from retailers like Sonos, Belkin, Hyper, Best Buy, and many more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/MR-Halloween-Deals-2022-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-871798" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best Apple Deals</h2><br/>
In addition to accessories, we're tracking a few discounts on Apple products like the iPad, iPad Air, AirPods, and Apple Watch Ultra. All of the devices in the list below can be found on Amazon (with the exception of the HomePod at B&H Photo), and none require coupon codes in order to see their discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">9th Gen iPad</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746862-REG/apple_mqj83ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODW/BI/2696/KBID/3612">HomePod (2nd Gen)</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3KXJPB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">iPad Air</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLD4SWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">12.9-inch iPad Pro (128GB Wi-Fi)</a> - &#36;989.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLC5CPN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">12.9-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi)</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT6Q8V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch Ultra</a> - &#36;659.00, down from &#36;799.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air Deals</h2><br/>
Amazon and Best Buy are hosting quite a few all-time low prices on nearly every MacBook Air this weekend. Specifically, you'll find record low prices on the 15-inch MacBook Air, 13.6-inch MacBook Air, and 13.3-inch MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/macbook-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919017" /><br/>
Shoppers should note that Best Buy does have a better deal for the 15-inch MacBook Air, but only if you have a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership. If you do, these notebooks have hit a new all-time low price of &#36;999.00, which is &#36;300 in savings for the 256GB model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckSxldeCBca"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air for &#36;999.00 at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you don't have a My Best Buy membership, you can <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxsZbYnLm">sign up to take advantage of this deal and many more</a>. The base "Plus" plan starts at &#36;49.99 per year and provides access to thousands of deals and early events, like the current Black Friday Early Access sale.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>13.3-inch M1 MacBook Air (256GB) - &#36;749.99 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxo25HorZ">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li>13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) - &#36;899.00 at <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxn9qnXnb">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) - &#36;1,049.00 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75NSLJY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxldeCBca">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) - &#36;1,249.00 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76D4RWJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckSxndcNcwD">Best Buy</a>, down from &#36;1,499.00</li></ul><h2>iPhone 15 Deals</h2><br/>
Apple's newest iPhones continue to see steep markdowns at various cellular carriers, including AT&T and Verizon. At <a href="http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13610485">AT&T</a>, new and existing customers can get up to &#36;1,000 off iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max, and up to &#36;700 off iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Plus with an eligible trade in.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iphone-15-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919016" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13610485"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<a href="http://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13666715">Verizon</a> is also offering up to &#36;1,000 off the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max this season, after you trade in an older device and add a new line. If you buy a new smartphone and add a new line on an Unlimited plan, you'll also be eligible for a free Apple TV 4K and six months of Apple One from Verizon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="http://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13666715"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
As always, anyone looking into carrier deals should read the fine print on each offer as there are stipulations for each deal.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sonos</h2><br/>
This weekend only, <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos</a> is offering 20 percent off select home theater bundles. This includes products like the Sonos Arc soundbar, Ray soundbar, Sub (gen 3) subwoofer, and more. All the items in this sale will expire on Sunday, October 29.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/sonos-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918536" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">20% OFF</div>Sonos Bundle Discounts</div></a></div><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-ray-sub-mini">Ray soundbar + Sub Mini</a> - &#36;565.99, down from &#36;708.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-beam-sub-mini">Beam soundbar + Sub Mini</a> - &#36;742.00, down from &#36;928.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/immersive-set-beam-sub-mini-era-100-pair">Beam Soundbar + Era 100 Speaker (2) + Sub Mini</a> - &#36;1,240.99, down from &#36;1,426.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-arc-sub">Arc soundbar + Sub</a> - &#36;1,358.40, down from &#36;1,698</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/premium-immersive-set-arc-sub-era-100-pair">Arc soundbar + Era 100 speakers (2) + Sub</a> - &#36;1,855.98, down from &#36;2,196.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/ultimate-immersive-set-arc-sub-era-300-pair">Arc soundbar + Era 300 speakers (2) + Sub</a> - &#36;2,211.08, down from &#36;2,596.00</li></ul><h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<a href="https://howl.me/ckR7NszxdAd">Anker's</a> Halloween sale has up to &#36;800 off its popular portable PowerHouse batteries. Additionally, we're tracking a <a href="https://howl.me/ckNTaeRyl5Y">few ongoing Anker discounts</a> on the retailer's website as well as on Amazon, all listed below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/anker-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919015" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckR7NszxdAd"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;800 OFF</div>Anker Halloween Sale</div></a></div><strong>PowerHouse Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckR7LvAenzD">PowerHouse 757</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckR7KJntz73">SOLIX C1000</a> - &#36;899.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckR7MpFovaI">SOLIX F1200</a> - &#36;1,059.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckR7J01K5no">PowerHouse 767</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Wall Chargers</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469063005">67W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNThhu2KvF">150W 4-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;87.99, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTkDolYuU">Prime 240W 4-Port Desktop Charger</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Portable Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTeKlQeKI">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.50, down from &#36;29.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK77HJ">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTo2cHQpF">PowerCore 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;36.52, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTnSeYEIs">PowerCore 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTlSZyqr4">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTmKHIliZ">PowerCore 26,000 mAh</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckNTckazLPK">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;110.49, down from &#36;129.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469007512">Amazon</a>]</li></ul><h2>Hyper</h2><br/>
Hyper is offering up to 31 percent off select products this Halloween, including battery packs, USB-C accessories, MagSafe-compatible chargers, and more. This event will run through Halloween on Tuesday, October 31 and all sales have been applied automatically.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/hyper-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919014" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43456&murl=https://www.hypershop.com/collections/halloween-sale?page=1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 31% OFF</div>Hyper Halloween Sale</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43456&murl=https://www.hypershop.com/products/hypershield-stand-go-sleeve-for-15-16-macbook-pro-air?variant=39758528282686">HyperShield Stand & Go Sleeve for 15"/16" MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;31.04, down from &#36;44.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43456&murl=https://www.hypershop.com/products/hyperjuice-magnetic-wireless-battery-pack">HyperJuice Magnetic Battery Pack</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43456&murl=https://www.hypershop.com/products/hyperjuice-140w-pd-3-1-usb-c-charger-us-only">HyperJuice 140W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;89.69, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43456&murl=https://www.hypershop.com/products/hyperjuice-4-in-1-wireless-charger-with-magsafe">HyperJuice 4-in-1 Wireless Charger with MagSafe</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><h2>Belkin</h2><br/>
<a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/c/153062/214281/3736">Belkin</a> has introduced a pre-Black Friday sitewide sale in late October. You can get up to 30 percent off sitewide by using the code PBF23 at checkout. This sale covers 15 percent off MagSafe chargers, 20 percent off portable batteries, 20 percent off wall chargers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/belkin-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919013" /><ul><li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/xkbgZv">BoostCharge Power Bank 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;31.99, down from &#36;39.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/0JgVZL">BoostCharge Pro Dual USB-C Wall Charger</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/xknreA">BoostCharge Pro Power Bank 10,000 mAh with Apple Watch Charger</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/4PKvEo">BoostCharge Pro 2-in-1 Wireless Charger</a> - &#36;84.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/DK1vOy">BoostCharge Pro 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Pad</a> - &#36;127.49, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
Samsung's current weeklong sale is coinciding with Halloween this time around, and it has a wide variety of discounts, including sales on <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPbMCoHS6">monitors</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPcQwr1xo">TVs</a>. The highlights of the sale include the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display at &#36;300 off and the Smart Monitor M8 at &#36;200 off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/samsung-halloween.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919012" /><br/>
Starting with the newer 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display, this monitor is available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"><strong>&#36;1,299.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. This is a match of the all-time low price on the device, which we last tracked around Prime Day, and you'll find the same price <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-ViewFinity-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87">on Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxOKKNxdNh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>ViewFinity S9 Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The ViewFinity S9 is a 27-inch display with a Thunderbolt 4 port, three USB-C ports, and a Mini DisplayPort, and it includes 90 watts of power for machines connected through the Thunderbolt 4 port. A removable 4K SlimFit webcam supports tilt adjustments, as well as Auto Framing of subjects in the shot, similar to Apple's Center Stage feature. Built-in speakers with an Adaptive Sound+ option to automatically adjust noise levels are also included.<br/>
<br/>
The new model of the 32-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also on sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;699.99. This is a second-best price on the M80C model, and Samsung has every color at this price. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-Streaming-Slim-fit-Experience-Speakers%2Fdp%2FB0C3WMX69W">On Amazon</a>, it's only available in Warm White.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckLj1VlnZZS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>Smart Monitor M80C for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've gathered a few more monitors and TVs on sale below, but be sure to head to Samsung to see the full extent of the sale. This event is set to run the rest of the month, and end on November 1. The prices on Amazon are not directly part of the Samsung website event, so they could expire sooner.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPfgT45F4">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Monitor</a> - &#36;279.99 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPgKIod0i">34-inch OLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPrWHb9fr">49-inch Odyssey OLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,399.99 (&#36;400 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPiqMBwhC">55-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;999.99 (&#36;500 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPjtEBtoT">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,799.99 (&#36;500 off)</li></ul> <h2>More Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="http://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?B=695070&U=63177&M=54540&urllink=">Pad & Quill</a> - Get 50 percent off sitewide with Pad & Quill's going out of business sale</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://adorama.rfvk.net/7Wgry">Adorama</a> - Get up to 70 percent off audio equipment, home electronics, and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?icep_ff3=1&pub=5575340917&toolid=10001&campid=5338201023&customid=&ipn=psmain&icep_vectorid=229466&kwid=902099&mtid=824&kw=lg">eBay</a> - Get 20 percent off home decor</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1200223&u=63177&m=80610&urllink=www%2Eesrgear%2Ecom%2Fcategories%2Fiphone%2D15%2Dpro%2Dmax%2Dcases%2F&afftrack=">ESR</a> - Get 20 percent off iPhone 15 Pro Max cases with code AFFNEW20</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13665142?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.jbl.com%2Fhalloween-sale%2F">JBL</a> - Get up to 50 percent off Bluetooth speakers and headphones</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://moment.8ocm68.net/c/153062/775342/11129">Moment</a> - Early holiday deals including savings on iPhone accessories and photography equipment</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=J2shFQg6J/U&offerid=688498.3&type=3&subid=0">Newegg</a> - Save on computer equipment</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/halloween-deals-best-apple/">Halloween Deals: The Best Apple Product and Accessory Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halloween-deals-the-best-apple-product-and-accessory-sales.2408884/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Magic Mouse With USB-C Port Expected at Apple Event Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/usb-c-magic-mouse-expected-at-apple-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-magic-mouse-with-usb-c-port-expected-at-apple-event-next-week.2408877/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 06:28:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/usb-c-magic-mouse-expected-at-apple-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Magic Mouse</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will likely announce new versions of its Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad for the Mac at its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">"Scary Fast" event on Monday, October 30</a>, according to a report today from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-27/apple-october-30-scary-fast-event-new-imacs-macbook-pros-products-to-expect"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. The updated accessories are expected to be equipped with USB-C ports instead of Lightning ports for charging. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/magic-mouse-2-lightning.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-835832" /><br/>
The accessories will likely be unveiled alongside an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/next-gen-imac-details-rumored-ahead-of-event/">updated 24-inch iMac with an M3 chip</a>, which Gurman also expects to be announced at the event.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear if the accessories will have any design changes beyond the switch to USB-C. They look largely the same as they did when they received their last major update in October 2015, although there have been some minor revisions over the years, including a switch to braided cables, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/20/new-m1-imac-accessories/">new color options</a> that are only available with the 24-inch iMac. Apple also released a Magic Keyboard with a Touch ID button in 2021.<br/>
<br/>
While the Magic Mouse lasts around a month or longer between charges, the position of the Lightning port on the bottom of the mouse has been a meme in the Apple community for many years, as it prevents the mouse from being used while charging. It's unclear if the USB-C port on the new version will be placed in a more convenient location.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models are equipped with USB-C ports instead of Lightning. The latest Siri Remote for the Apple TV also has a USB-C port, and Apple discontinued the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger with Lightning ports.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's event on October 30 begins at the unusual time of 5 p.m. Pacific/8 p.m. Eastern, so make sure to mark your calendar correctly.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-mouse/">Magic Mouse</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/usb-c-magic-mouse-expected-at-apple-event/">New Magic Mouse With USB-C Port Expected at Apple Event Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-magic-mouse-with-usb-c-port-expected-at-apple-event-next-week.2408877/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Maps Gains Immersive View for Routes and Other AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/google-maps-immersive-view-for-routes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-maps-gains-immersive-view-for-routes-and-other-ai-features.2408860/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:58:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/google-maps-immersive-view-for-routes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google Maps</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google Maps is getting a new Immersive View for routes that uses artificial intelligence, Street View, and aerial images to preview every step of a journey ahead of time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/google-maps-immersive-view-routes.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918934" /><br/>
When users get directions for driving, walking, or cycling, Google Maps now offers a "multidimensional experience" that can be used to preview bike lanes, sidewalks, intersections, and parking along the route, <a href="https://blog.google/products/maps/google-maps-october-2023-update/">according to Google</a>. <br/>
<br/>
A time slider can be used to see air quality information and how the route looks as the weather changes throughout the day, while AI and historical driving trends simulate how many cars might be on the road at a given time. <br/>
<br/>
Immersive View for routes is rolling out in Amsterdam, Barcelona, Dublin, Florence, Las Vegas, London, Los Angeles, Miami, New York, Paris, San Francisco, San Jose, Seattle, Tokyo and Venice on Android and iOS.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to Immersive View for routes, Search with Live View is being replaced with Lens in Maps, which uses AI and augmented reality to help users orient themselves in a new neighborhood. <br/>
<br/>
Tapping the Lens icon in the search bar and lifting your phone now gives you AR-delivered information about nearby ATMs, transit stations, restaurants, coffee shops, and stores. Google says Lens in Maps is rolling out to more than 50 new cities including A​​ustin, Las Vegas, Rome, São Paulo and Taipei.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, the navigation map is getting updated colors, more realistic buildings, and improved highway lane details. These updates start rolling out in the coming months in 12 countries, including the U.S., Canada, France and Germany. <br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the U.S. is also set to get information about high-occupancy vehicle (HOV) lanes along a route, and in Europe, AI-powered speed limit information is expanding to 20 countries. Both features start rolling out on Android, iOS, and for cars with Google Built-in in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Google says EV drivers on Android and iOS will now see even more helpful charging station information, including whether a charger is compatible with their vehicle and whether the available chargers are fast, medium, or slow. This also includes the ability to see when a charger was last used so you know it's not a broken charger. These updates start rolling out globally on iOS and Android this week wherever EV charging station information is available. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-maps/">Google Maps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/google-maps-immersive-view-for-routes/">Google Maps Gains Immersive View for Routes and Other AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-maps-gains-immersive-view-for-routes-and-other-ai-features.2408860/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Bloomberg: 13-Inch MacBook Pro With M3 Chip Unlikely to Be Announced at &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/m3-13-inch-macbook-pro-unlikely-to-be-at-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bloomberg-13-inch-macbook-pro-with-m3-chip-unlikely-to-be-announced-at-scary-fast-event.2408858/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:37:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/m3-13-inch-macbook-pro-unlikely-to-be-at-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new version of the 13-inch MacBook Pro featuring the M3 chip is unlikely to appear at Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">"Scary Fast" Mac event</a> next week, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-27/apple-october-30-scary-fast-event-new-imacs-macbook-pros-products-to-expect"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.</a><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/Touch-Bar-13-Inch-MacBook-Pro.jpg" alt="" width="1364" height="769" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-853221" /><br/>
In the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-22/what-is-apple-doing-in-ai-revamping-siri-search-apple-music-and-other-apps-lo1ffr7p">"Power On" newsletter</a> shared over the weekend, Gurman said that supplies of the 13-inch MacBook Pro were running low and indicated that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/">could be replaced next week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
He now says that the new machine likely won't appear at Apple's upcoming event. The new entry-level MacBook Pro, codenamed "J504," apparently remains in the works and features a "base version of the M3 chip." Gurman has reported the existence of the device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/14/updated-13-inch-macbook-pro-gurman/">since April</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This means that the main models in the running for announcement at the event are the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> and the 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro, all with M3-series chips. Gurman added that he is not expecting to see any other refreshed devices at the event, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-new-ipads-scheduled-for-march-2024-launch/">including iPads</a> or AirPods.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro-13/">MacBook Pro 13"</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_13">13" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/m3-13-inch-macbook-pro-unlikely-to-be-at-event/">Bloomberg: 13-Inch MacBook Pro With M3 Chip Unlikely to Be Announced at &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bloomberg-13-inch-macbook-pro-with-m3-chip-unlikely-to-be-announced-at-scary-fast-event.2408858/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Potential Apple Watch Ban Issued by U.S. Trade Tribunal in Masimo Patent Battle</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/potential-apple-watch-ban-issued-by-u-s-trade-tribunal-in-masimo-patent-battle.2408852/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 03:32:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) on Thursday ordered a ban on Apple Watch imports into the country after finding that Apple violated pulse oximetry company Masimo's patents with the devices (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-trade-tribunal-issues-potential-apple-watch-import-ban-masimo-patent-fight-2023-10-26/">Reuters</a></em>). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/apple-watch-6s-202009.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786980" /><br/>
The ban is now subject to presidential review, so it does not take effect immediately, and Apple can take the ban to the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit after the 60-day review period ends. Presidents have rarely vetoed bans in the past.<br/>
<blockquote>"Masimo has wrongly attempted to use the ITC to keep a potentially lifesaving product from millions of U.S. consumers while making way for their own watch that copies Apple," an Apple spokesperson said. "While today's decision has no immediate impact on sales of Apple Watch, we believe it should be reversed, and will continue our efforts to appeal."</blockquote>Masimo Chief Executive Officer Joe Kiani said the decision "sends a powerful message that even the world's largest company is not above the law."<br/>
<br/>
Since 2021, Masimo has been embroiled in an ongoing battle with Apple over several health capabilities found in some Apple Watch models, and Masimo has been pushing to have the models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/06/30/masimo-apple-watch-series-6-itc-import-ban/">banned</a> in the United States. The ITC decision did not specify which models of Apple Watches would be affected by the ban, but Masimo's original complaint said the Apple Watch Series 6, released in 2020, infringed its patents.<br/>
<br/>
Masimo accuses Apple of having <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/01/09/apple-masimo-apple-watch-lawsuit/">illegally poached Masimo employees</a> and stole trade secrets when developing the Apple Watch. The company is seeking over &#36;1.8 billion in damages and co-ownership of five Apple pulse oximetry patents that Masimo says use its technology.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. Patent and Trademark Office ended up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/11/apple-watch-masimo-patent-infringement/">invalidating all but two of the patents</a>, but the ITC in January said that Apple had infringed on a Masimo patent relating to light-based technology for reading blood-oxygen levels.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also facing an Apple Watch import ban in a separate patent court battle with medical technology company AliveCor. The ITC issued a ban in February, and the Biden administration <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/22/biden-admin-upholds-apple-watch-patent-ruling/">declined to overrule the decision</a>, but the ban has been placed on hold while proceedings over the validity of AliveCor's patents are completed. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">Potential Apple Watch Ban Issued by U.S. Trade Tribunal in Masimo Patent Battle</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/potential-apple-watch-ban-issued-by-u-s-trade-tribunal-in-masimo-patent-battle.2408852/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything New in iOS 17.2 Beta 1: Journal App, Translate Action, iMessage Sticker Reactions and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-17-2-beta-1-journal-app-translate-action-imessage-sticker-reactions-and-more.2408805/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:28:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first beta of an upcoming iOS 17.2 update, and it adds a whole slew of features. You can now access the Journal app that Apple has been working on, and share playlists with friends so they can add songs. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918854" /><br/>
iOS 17.2 is limited to developers right now, but it should soon be coming to public beta testers. We're expecting to see iOS 17.2 released to the public around November or December. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Journal App</h2><br/>
iOS 17.2 includes the Journal app that Apple announced as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>. With the Journal app, users can record their daily activities and thoughts, with Apple providing optional prompts that can be used as inspiration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Journal-App-iOS-17-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1469" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918878" /><br/>
A Journal entry can be added by tapping on the "+" button in the Journal app, and from there, users can choose a suggestion as the basis for their writing or just opt for "New Entry" to write anything at all.<br/>
<br/>
Entries are automatically tagged with a date for organizational purposes, but there are options for bookmarking, too. Journal entries can include images, voice recordings, and location tags.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Messages App Sticker Tapback Reactions</h2><br/>
You can now long press on any chat bubble in the Messages app to add a sticker response that serves as an alternative to a tapback reaction. Tapping on "Add Sticker" lets you choose either a sticker or an emoji to apply to the corner of an iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tapback-reply-sticker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918892" /><br/>
There was already an option to drag a sticker or an emoji onto any message bubble, but this is a much quicker method of quickly responding to an incoming message with a quick graphic that is more expressive than a tapback reaction.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</h2><br/>
There is now an option to create a playlist in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> that multiple people can add to. In a playlist you have made, tap on the three dot icon in top right of the app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-collaborative-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="5484" height="3085" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918890" /><br/>
From there, select the Collaborate option and choose "Start Collaboration." You'll be able to create a link to the playlist, and anyone who has access to that link can add to it. You can also invite people to join via QR code, and if you want, you can approve each person that asks to join.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Favorites Apple Music Playlist</h2><br/>
Songs that you have favorited in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app are now aggregated into a Favorites playlist.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-favorite-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918891" /><br/>
<h2>Apple Music Listening History Focus Filter</h2><br/>
There is a Focus Filter for the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Listening History feature, so if you want to let someone else use your device to listen to music, you can activate this to turn off the Listening History so their song choices won't affect your recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-focus-filters.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918906" /><br/>
<h2>Action Button Translate</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max users can now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-translate-action-button/">choose a new Translate option</a> for the Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-translate.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918874" /><br/>
When the Action Button is set as Translate, pressing to hold causes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to pop up a Translate window that listens for spoken text. It is able to translate from one set language to another, using the languages that you have previously set up in the Translate app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMessage Contact Key Verification</h2><br/>
First previewed in December 2022, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-imessage-contact-key-verification/">iMessage Contact Key Verification</a> is a feature designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-iMessage-Contact-Key-Verification_screen-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876653" /><br/>
Users can ensure that there is no "man in the middle" snooping on iMessage conversations, and there is a Contact Verification Code so that iMessage users can verify that they're speaking to the correct individual during in-person meetings or on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Messages in iCloud Syncing</h2><br/>
The "Messages" section in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> in the Settings app has been renamed to "Messages in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;." It shows the total amount of storage that messages are taking up, the number of messages synced to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;, and the time of the last sync. There's also a "Sync Now" option to force an update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-messages-in-icloud.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918896" /><br/>
Apple previously said that additional settings would be synced through Messages in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, like Text Message Forwarding, Send &amp; Receive accounts, and SMS filters across devices, so this may see those additional settings syncing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple TV App</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/">removed the separate tabs</a> for Movies and TV shows in the Store section of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said that Apple also plans to remove the option to purchase TV shows and movies from the iTunes app as part of a TV app redesign, but that has not yet happened.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tv-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918905" /><br/>
<h2>Emergency Alerts Local Awareness</h2><br/>
Under Notifications &gt; Emergency Alerts in the Settings app, there is a new "Local Awareness" option that can be turned on. Apple says that Local Awareness uses your approximate location to improve the timeliness, accuracy, and reliability of emergency alerts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-emergency-local-awareness.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918902" /><br/>
<h2>Weather Widgets</h2><br/>
There are new Details, Daily Forecast, and Sunrise/Sunset widgets. Detail shows information like precipitation chance, UV index, wind speed, and air quality, while Daily Forecast offers the weather for the next few days in a small widget size. Sunrise/Sunset shows the sunrise and sunset times for each day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/weather-app-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918889" /><br/>
<h2>Digital Clock Widget</h2><br/>
There is a new Digital Clock widget that can be added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-clock-widget.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918894" /><br/>
<h2>Contact Posters</h2><br/>
You can now select a rainbow-colored text for your name when setting up a Contact Poster in the Contacts app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-contact-poster-rainbow.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918893" /><br/>
<h2>Books Page Turning Animation</h2><br/>
There's a new "Fast Fade" option for the page turning animation in the Books app. Apple has also removed the icon that you could turn on to scroll through content quickly.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-page-turn-animation.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918897" /><br/>
<h2>AirPlay</h2><br/>
There's a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> Receiver" setting that will allow the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset to stream or share content to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-airplay-handoff.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918898" /><br/>
It also looks like the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; feature for hotels that Apple announced earlier this year is live or will be live soon. It is designed to let you &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; content from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to an AirPlay-equipped smart TV.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Memoji</h2><br/>
Apple added a "Body" section for Memoji where users can customize waist, bust, shoulders, and arms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-memoji-body.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918895" /><br/>
<h2>News App</h2><br/>
The News app now supports Live Activities for following news-related events such as elections.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-apple-news-live-activities.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918899" /><br/>
<h2>More iOS 17.2 Beta 1 Features</h2><br/>
Know of a feature that we left out in this list? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">Everything New in iOS 17.2 Beta 1: Journal App, Translate Action, iMessage Sticker Reactions and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-17-2-beta-1-journal-app-translate-action-imessage-sticker-reactions-and-more.2408805/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the New Journal App in the iOS 17.2 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-journal-app-in-the-ios-17-2-beta.2408798/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 13:45:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first iOS 17.2 beta, and it has the long-awaited Journal app that Apple initially announced as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>. We've installed iOS 17.2 and thought we'd go hands-on with the Journal app to give <em>MacRumors</em> readers a first look at how it works.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/09sClt3NmuU" title="Apple&#39;s NEW Journal App - Full Walkthrough in iOS 17.2" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Journal app has a simple, straightforward UI. When you open it up, you're presented with a "+" button, and tapping on it lets you start a new entry. When you first open the app, you can decide what information the Journal app can pull from your phone for writing prompts. Options include workout activity, media like podcasts and music, photos, and significant locations.<br/>
<br/>
There is a setting to prefer suggestions with others when you're around your contacts or large groups, and an option to be discoverable by others to help prioritize the suggestions of other people. Journal options can be toggled on and off in the Settings app under Privacy &amp; Security &gt; Journaling Suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
You can opt to write whatever you like, or choose from one of Apple's prompts that are based on your device usage. Prompts include invitations to reflect on your day, recall a new idea, think of what made you smile, think about what you could do to improve your life, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Journal entries can be customized with images, location information, and voice recordings. Entries are organized by date, and can also be bookmarked so you can save your favorite entries. To keep your Journal secure, you can set it up so you need a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> scan to unlock it. <br/>
<br/>
Will you use the Journal app? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app-hands-on/">Hands-On With the New Journal App in the iOS 17.2 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-journal-app-in-the-ios-17-2-beta.2408798/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV App Features Revamped Navigation in tvOS 17.2 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-app-features-revamped-navigation-in-tvos-17-2-beta.2408783/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:40:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the tvOS 17.2 beta has updated its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, making it easier to navigate and find content to watch. There is a dedicated sidebar that houses content from different apps and streaming services, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-tv-app-redesign.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918880" /><br/>
The sidebar has dedicated sections for Search, Watch Now, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, MLS Season Pass, Sports, the Store, and the Library.<br/>
<br/>
In a separate "Channels and Apps" area, users can access content from specific streaming services that integrate with the TV app. Options include ABC, CBS, Comedy Central, Hulu, ESPN, Discovery, Peacock, Prime Video, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping into a channel like Hulu shows content and watch suggestions just for that service.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-tv-app-hulu.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918881" /><br/>
Up Next in Watch Now has not changed, but Apple has added a new "My TV" section below the top charts that houses TV suggestions from multiple networks as a replacement for "My Channels." There isn't any dedicated Channels section in Watch Now, but a Channels and Apps feature has been added to the Store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-tv-app-my-tv.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918882" /><br/>
Apple has also made tweaks to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. In the Store section, there are no longer separate tabs for Movies and TV Shows, with everything integrated together.<br/>
<br/>
The changes to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app come after a report from <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> that said Apple would introduce a new design in December. Gurman's report said that Apple would remove standalone iTunes &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; apps that are available for renting and purchasing TV shows and movies, but that has not yet happened.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/">Apple TV App Features Revamped Navigation in tvOS 17.2 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-app-features-revamped-navigation-in-tvos-17-2-beta.2408783/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Beta Adds Translate Option for Action Button</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-translate-action-button/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-adds-translate-option-for-action-button.2408779/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:20:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-translate-action-button/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max users can select a new "Translate" option for the Action Button with the new iOS 17.2 beta. Apple promised that a Translate option was coming for the Action Button, but said that it would not be available right when the new iPhones launched in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-translate.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918874" /><br/>
When the Action Button is set as Translate, pressing to hold causes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to pop up a Translate window that listens for spoken text. It is able to translate from one set language to another, using the languages that you have previously set up in the Translate app.<br/>
<br/>
The languages you translate between can be changed by selecting different languages in the Translate app. The Translate app supports Chinese, English, Dutch, French, German, Indonesian, Italian, Spanish, Korean, Japanese, Polish, Portuguese, Russian, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, and Vietnamese. <br/>
<br/>
To choose the Translate option for the Action Button, open up the Settings app, scroll down to Action Button, and then swipe through until you get to the Translate function. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-translate-action-button/">iOS 17.2 Beta Adds Translate Option for Action Button</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-adds-translate-option-for-action-button.2408779/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iMessage Contact Key Verification Added in iOS 17.2 and macOS Sonoma 14.2 Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-imessage-contact-key-verification/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imessage-contact-key-verification-added-in-ios-17-2-and-macos-sonoma-14-2-betas.2408775/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:56:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-imessage-contact-key-verification/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to the new Journal app, the iOS 17.2 and macOS 14.2 updates add support for iMessage Contact Key Verification, a feature that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/new-imessage-apple-id-security-features/">first previewed</a> in December of last year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-iMessage-Contact-Key-Verification_screen-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876653" /><br/>
Designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials, iMessage Contact Key Verification allows people to verify the identify of the person they're corresponding with. It is available today in the iOS 17.2, iPadOS 17.2, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2, and watchOS 10.2 betas. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac users who have iMessage Contact Key Verification enabled will be notified if a malicious entity somehow succeeds in breaching cloud data servers and is able to eavesdrop on a conversation.<br/>
<br/>
The feature also includes a Contact Verification Code that can be used in person or on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>.<br/>
<blockquote>With iMessage Contact Key Verification, users can choose to further verify that they are messaging only with the people they intend. Contact Key Verification uses Key Transparency to enable automatic verification that the iMessage key distribution service returns device keys that have been logged to a verifiable and auditable map. When a user enables Contact Key Verification, they will be notified about any validation errors directly in the Messages conversation transcript and Apple ID Settings.<br/>
<br/>
For even higher security, iMessage contact key verification users can compare a Contact Verification Code in person, on FaceTime, or through another secure call. They can also choose to create or edit a contact and save a public key to turn on CKV with that person.</blockquote><br/>
To use iMessage Contact Key Verification, all devices signed into an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> account must have the iOS 17.2 beta, macOS 17.2 beta, and/or watchOS 10.2 beta.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-imessage-contact-key-verification/">iMessage Contact Key Verification Added in iOS 17.2 and macOS Sonoma 14.2 Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imessage-contact-key-verification-added-in-ios-17-2-and-macos-sonoma-14-2-betas.2408775/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Beta Introduces Journal App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-introduces-journal-app.2408767/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:39:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iOS 17.2 beta that Apple seeded to developers today includes the first iteration of the Journal app that Apple announced way back in June when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> was initially previewed. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Journal-App-iOS-17.jpeg" alt="" width="2612" height="1828" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898865" /><br/>
Apple's Journal app will let <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users record their daily thoughts and activities. It incorporates data like photos, music listened to, workouts, and more, plus it suggests topics to write about. <br/>
<br/>
Entries can have integrated photos, music, and audio recordings, and important moments can be highlighted. <br/>
<br/>
The Journal app is passcode and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> protected for privacy purposes, and all of the suggestions are done on-device. Entries are end-to-end encrypted. <br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-journal-app/">iOS 17.2 Beta Introduces Journal App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-introduces-journal-app.2408767/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-1-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2-to-developers.2408764/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:26:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-1-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming one day after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-ios-17-1/">launch of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Cool.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918852" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
There's no word yet on what's included in the iOS 17.2 beta yet, but we are waiting on the Journal app that Apple has said is coming in a later version of &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;. We are also still waiting on the option to use stickers as a tapback reaction in Messages, an arrow for catching up on missed Messages conversations, and a favorite songs playlist in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>.<br/>
<br/>
We'll update our article when we learn what's new in the iOS 17.2 beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-1-to-developers/">Apple Seeds First Betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2-to-developers.2408764/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
