<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 03:03:48 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Might Make Transferring an eSIM From an iPhone to an Android Phone Easier</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/ios-19-esim-android-transfer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-might-make-transferring-an-esim-from-an-iphone-to-an-android-phone-easier.2457788/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:47:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/ios-19-esim-android-transfer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> update could make it easier for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users to transfer an eSIM to an Android smartphone, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.androidauthority.com/ios-19-esim-transfer-to-android-3561644/">Android Authority</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Phone-App-Icon-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954687" /><br/>
The site found strings in the Android 16 beta version of Google's SIM Manager that reference a new "Transfer to Android" feature. The setting would include an option for wirelessly transferring an eSIM from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to an Android phone.<br/>
<br/>
While it is simple to transfer an eSIM from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, that is not true when trying to transfer an eSIM from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to an Android device as of right now. Moving from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to an Android phone typically requires contacting a carrier, but that might not be the case in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Transfer to Android could be added to the "Transfer or Reset &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;" interface that's located under the General section of the Settings app. Apple may expand the eSIM Quick Transfer feature for swapping an eSIM between iPhones to Android devices, plus it looks like there may be a QR code backup in case a wireless connection fails.<br/>
<br/>
Code in the Google SIM Manager suggests that &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; will be required to initiate a transfer, hence why it may be an &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj; feature.<br/>
<blockquote>On your other device, go to <b>Settings</b> app > <b>General</b> > <b>Transfer or Reset iPhone</b> > <b>Transfer to Android</b> > <br/>
<br/>
<b>"Still can't connect wirelessly?"</b>" Make sure your other device is running iOS 19 or later versions."</blockquote><br/>
We could perhaps hear more about the eSIM transferring feature at WWDC, though it may also be something that's quietly introduced. Google could also be working on a reciprocal feature that would make it easier for an Android user to transfer to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/ios-19-esim-android-transfer/">iOS 19 Might Make Transferring an eSIM From an iPhone to an Android Phone Easier</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-might-make-transferring-an-esim-from-an-iphone-to-an-android-phone-easier.2457788/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Texas Governor Signs Off on App Store Law Against Tim Cook&#039;s Wishes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/texas-signs-app-store-age-verification-law/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/texas-governor-signs-off-on-app-store-law-against-tim-cooks-wishes.2457784/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:21:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/texas-signs-app-store-age-verification-law/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Child Safety Features</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Texas Governor Greg Abbott today signed into law the App Store Accountability Act, which will require Apple and Google to verify the age of App Store and Play Store users, respectively. The law will require users who are under the age of 18 to receive parental consent to download apps or make in-app purchases, according <a href="https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/texas-poised-enforce-age-verification-apple-google-app-stores-2025-05-27/">to <em>Reuters</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
Apple CEO Tim Cook had <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/tim-cook-called-texas-governor-to-stop-online-child-safety-legislation-22858ad4">reportedly</a> asked Abbott to veto the legislation on a phone call, but evidently his attempt was unsuccessful.<br/>
<br/>
The bill had already passed both the Senate and House of Representatives in Texas, and now that it has been signed by Abbott, it will take effect on January 1, 2026. Texas is the second U.S. state to pass a child safety law of this kind, following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/26/utah-app-store-age-verification-law/">Utah in March</a>. Utah's law took effect earlier this month, but it will not be fully enforced until next year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/27/apple-child-age-verification-overhaul/">several new child safety measures</a> in February, after these bills were proposed. While setting up an iPhone or iPad running iOS 18.4 or iPadOS 18.4 or later, the person who will be using the device must select their age range, with the available options including 12 or younger, 13 to 18, and 19 or older. If the account is for a child under the age of 13, there is a Connect to Family option. A parent needs to provide consent for a child to use the ‌App Store‌ and other features, with Face ID or Touch ID authentication required.<br/>
<br/>
It remains to be seen if Apple's expanded age-verification measures will be enough to fully satisfy the laws in Texas and Utah, and others that may follow.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Google both opposed these age verification laws, citing privacy concerns related to having to collect age information for all users.<br/>
<br/>
"If enacted, app marketplaces will be required to collect and keep sensitive personal identifying information for every Texan who wants to download an app, even if it's an app that simply provides weather updates or sports scores," said Apple.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-child-safety-features/">Apple Child Safety Features</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/texas-signs-app-store-age-verification-law/">Texas Governor Signs Off on App Store Law Against Tim Cook&#039;s Wishes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/texas-governor-signs-off-on-app-store-law-against-tim-cooks-wishes.2457784/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Launch Dedicated Gaming App in iOS 19</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-ios-19-gaming-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-dedicated-gaming-app-in-ios-19.2457782/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:56:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-ios-19-gaming-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on a standalone multi-platform app for games, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-27/apple-to-debut-dedicated-gaming-app-within-days-of-switch-2-s-arrival">Bloomberg</a></em>. The app will let Apple users launch games, plus it will have sections for in-game achievements, leaderboards, editorial content, and communication.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Arcade-hero.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984891" /><br/>
Apple plans to preinstall the app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> later this year, which corresponds with the launch timing of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>, macOS 16, and tvOS 19. The gaming app will debut at the Worldwide Developers Conference that's set to take place on June 9.<br/>
<br/>
The upcoming app is set to replace Game Center, which Apple has long used for inviting friends to play mobile games and tracking achievements. While Apple plans to use the new gaming app to promote <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, it will include all of the third-party games that are currently located in the Games section of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It sounds like Apple is aiming to split out the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s gaming, making it easier for customers to find and download games on their devices. On the Mac, the app will also "tap into" games that are downloaded outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While the gaming app will be previewed at WWDC, it will roll out to iPhones, iPads, Macs, and Apple TVs in September when the operating systems launch to the public.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-ios-19-gaming-app/">Apple to Launch Dedicated Gaming App in iOS 19</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-dedicated-gaming-app-in-ios-19.2457782/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Acquires Gaming Studio RAC7</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-acquires-gaming-studio-rac7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acquires-gaming-studio-rac7.2457780/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:22:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-acquires-gaming-studio-rac7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has purchased game studio RAC7, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.digitaltrends.com/gaming/apple-acquires-rac7-sneaky-sasquatch/">Digital Trends</a></em>. RAC7 is a small, two-person company that developed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> game Sneaky Sasquatch, and the acquisition was confirmed by an Apple spokesperson.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/sneaky-sasquatch.jpg" alt="" width="1028" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003079" /><br/>
From <em>Digital Trends</em>:<br/>
<blockquote>We love Sneaky Sasquatch and are excited that the 2-person RAC7 team has joined Apple to continue their work on it with us. We will continue to deliver a great experience for Apple Arcade players with hundreds of games from many of the best game developers in the world.</blockquote><br/>
RAC7 will become an internal game studio within Apple, and Apple purchased the company to help Sneaky Sasquatch continue to grow on &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;. Sneaky Sasquatch was one of the first games to launch on &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; when the service went live, and it has continued to be popular with subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already works with developers and game companies to create titles for &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;, but this is the company's first game studio acquisition. <em>Digital Trends</em> notes that Apple does not appear to be implementing a new gaming strategy, describing the RAC7 acquisition as a unique situation.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-arcade/">subscription gaming service</a>, priced at &#36;6.99 per month. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; has hundreds of games, with no additional subscription fees or in-app purchases.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-acquires-gaming-studio-rac7/">Apple Acquires Gaming Studio RAC7</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acquires-gaming-studio-rac7.2457780/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Earn a Running Day Apple Watch Activity Award on June 4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-watch-running-day-activity/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-earn-a-running-day-apple-watch-activity-award-on-june-4.2457777/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:30:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-watch-running-day-activity/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next Apple Watch activity challenge is set to take place on June 4 to celebrate Global Running Day. Apple started hosting an activity challenge for running day last year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/apple-watch-world-running-day.jpg" alt="" width="818" height="460" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003067" /><br/>
To complete the challenge, Apple Watch owners will need to record a running workout of at least five kilometers (aka a 5K run) on June 4.<br/>
<blockquote>Let's run this one together. On June 4, record a running workout and go at least 5K (3.1 mi) to earn this special badge. Record it with any app that adds workouts to Health.</blockquote><br/>
Completing the challenge will provide Apple Watch users with a dedicated award in the Fitness app along with animate stickers that can be used in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/running_day_2025_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003068" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/running_day_2025_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003069" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/running_day_2025_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003070" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/running_day_2025_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003071" /><br/>
Last month, Apple provided a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-stores-to-give-away-special-pin/">limited-edition pin</a> to celebrate Global Close Your Rings day, which Apple introduced to highlight the 10th anniversary of the Apple Watch.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-watch-running-day-activity/">You Can Earn a Running Day Apple Watch Activity Award on June 4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-earn-a-running-day-apple-watch-activity-award-on-june-4.2457777/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Invites App Gains New Link Feature for Trip Planning, Potlucks and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-invites-app-link-feature/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-invites-app-gains-new-link-feature-for-trip-planning-potlucks-and-more.2457776/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:22:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-invites-app-link-feature/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Invites</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-invites/id6472498645?eventid=6745800884">updated the Invites app</a> to introduce a new option to add a link to an invitation. Event creators can use the feature to send important details to invitees.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988154" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/General-Apple-Invites-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple says that links can be used for things like planning a trip, adding a gift registry, or working out who is bringing what to a potluck. Links are open ended, so any website can be added to an invite that you create.<br/>
<br/>
Links are located in a new "Tiles" section in the Invites app. Tapping on "Add Tile" at the bottom of the app allows for link insertion, with users able to include the link, a link title, and a link description.<br/>
<br/>
Introduced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">earlier this year</a>, Invites is an event planning app designed by Apple. It supports creating custom invitations with unique background images, fonts, and relevant information like directions and weather. Today's 1.2 app update is the first feature update that Invites has received.<br/>
<br/>
Invites is an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+ service, and an &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ subscription is needed to create an event. &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ is Apple's paid &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage upgrade option, with plans that start at &#36;0.99 per month.<br/>
<br/>
While an &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ subscription is needed for creating an event, anyone can respond to an invitation through an RSVP feature. Invitations can be sent to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users and Android users alike, with the app facilitating planning and RSVPs.<br/>
<br/>
The Invites app can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for free. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-invites/id6472498645">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-invites/">Apple Invites</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-invites-app-link-feature/">Apple&#039;s Invites App Gains New Link Feature for Trip Planning, Potlucks and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-invites-app-gains-new-link-feature-for-trip-planning-potlucks-and-more.2457776/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Android Phones With Qualcomm Modems Top iPhone 16e in New 5G Test</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/qualcomm-vs-iphone-16e-study/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/android-phones-with-qualcomm-modems-top-iphone-16e-in-new-5g-test.2457774/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 10:53:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/qualcomm-vs-iphone-16e-study/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16e</category>
		<category>C1</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A <a href="https://cellularinsights.com/comparative-5g-performance-report-android-smartphones-vs-iphone-16e/">new Cellular Insights report</a> commissioned by Qualcomm has found that two unnamed Android smartphone models equipped with Qualcomm's Snapdragon X75 and Snapdragon X80 modems achieved faster 5G speeds compared to the iPhone 16e, which is equipped with Apple's first-ever, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-unveils-c1/">custom-designed C1 modem</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-iPhone-16e-C1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990833" /><br/>
Testing was conducted with T-Mobile's sub-6GHz 5G network in New York City, across a variety of real-world environments, according to Cellular Insights.<br/>
<br/>
The report found that the Android devices "consistently outperformed" the iPhone 16e in terms of 5G connectivity, especially indoors. Specifically, the Android devices achieved up to 35% faster download speeds compared to the iPhone 16e, and up to 91% faster upload speeds. The report also found that the iPhone 16e frequently became hot to the touch during testing, but it could not confirm if this directly impacted performance.<br/>
<br/>
The two Android smartphones were priced at &#36;619 and &#36;799 in the U.S., the report said, while the iPhone 16e starts at &#36;599.<br/>
<br/>
Based on its findings, Cellular Insights concluded that the Qualcomm-powered devices "hold a clear edge" over the iPhone 16e for individuals seeking "consistent, high-throughput 5G performance." Qualcomm's PR department is now touting the favorable results, which they relayed to us in an email sent earlier today.<br/>
<br/>
The full report is <a href="https://cellularinsights.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/5G-sub6-Report-Final-Cellular-Insights.pdf">available as a PDF</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's C1 modem achieved equal to faster performance than some Qualcomm modems <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/28/apple-c1-modem-5g-speed-tests/">in some earlier tests</a>, but a Qualcomm spokesperson said this study is the "only comprehensive, scientific" comparison completed on a U.S. network so far.<br/>
<br/>
Performance is not the only metric that matters for a smartphone modem, with power efficiency also being an important factor. Apple has advertised the C1 modem as being the most power-efficient iPhone modem ever, which contributes to the iPhone 16e offering the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/iphone-16e-battery-life/">longest battery life of any 6.1-inch iPhone model ever</a>. With its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apples-second-5g-modem-said-to-support-mmwave/">next-generation C2 and C3 modems</a>, Apple hopes to continue to close the gap on the performance front.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/c1/">C1</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16e">iPhone 16e (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/qualcomm-vs-iphone-16e-study/">Android Phones With Qualcomm Modems Top iPhone 16e in New 5G Test</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/android-phones-with-qualcomm-modems-top-iphone-16e-in-new-5g-test.2457774/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Rumored to Get 200MP Camera Like Samsung&#039;s Galaxy S25 Ultra</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-200-megapixel-camera-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-rumored-to-get-200mp-camera-like-samsungs-galaxy-s25-ultra.2457771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:48:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-200-megapixel-camera-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is testing a 200-megapixel camera sensor, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a>, a user with a large following on Chinese social media platform Weibo. The account has previously shared accurate information about Apple's future products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
While the <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PtJ4ZzwhL">account's post today</a> does not provide any further details, this 200-megapixel camera sensor would likely be for the main rear camera on a future high-end iPhone model. Samsung introduced a 200-megapixel rear camera <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/01/samsung-galaxy-s23-lineup/">on its Galaxy S23 Ultra in 2023</a>, and the follow-up S24 Ultra and S25 Ultra models also have one.<br/>
<br/>
With a 200-megapixel camera, an iPhone would be able to shoot photos with greater detail. The increased megapixel count would also result in higher-resolution photos, which can be cropped further and printed at larger sizes without a loss of image quality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's upcoming iPhone 17 Pro models are rumored to feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/">entirely 48-megapixel cameras</a>, so the 200-megapixel camera is unlikely to be available this year. In addition, a 200-megapixel camera has yet to be rumored for the iPhone 18 Pro models. Ultimately, the upgraded camera specification could be at least a few years away.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-200-megapixel-camera-rumor/">iPhone Rumored to Get 200MP Camera Like Samsung&#039;s Galaxy S25 Ultra</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-rumored-to-get-200mp-camera-like-samsungs-galaxy-s25-ultra.2457771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Pro Launching Later This Year With These 12 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-17-pro-rumors-list/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-launching-later-this-year-with-these-12-new-features.2457766/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:10:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-17-pro-rumors-list/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max are not expected to launch until September, there are already plenty of rumors about the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-Blue-Feature-Tighter-Crop.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999328" /><br/>
Below, we recap key changes rumored for the iPhone 17 Pro models as of May 2025:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Aluminum frame:</strong> iPhone 17 Pro models are rumored to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/18/iphone-17-pro-models-aluminum-frame-rumor/">have an aluminum frame</a>, whereas the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro models have a titanium frame, and the iPhone X through iPhone 14 Pro have a stainless steel frame. The back of the devices will supposedly have a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/20/iphone-17-pro-dummies-highlight-apples-new-design/">"part-aluminum, part-glass" design.</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Rectangular camera bump:</strong> iPhone 17 Pro models are expected to have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/iphone-17-pro-no-two-tone-rear-design/">large rectangular camera bump</a> with rounded corners. Apple apparently plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/18/iphone-17-pro-to-stick-with-triangular-camera/">stick with a triangular arrangement</a> for the rear camera lenses.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Sky Blue finish:</strong> Like the latest MacBook Air, the iPhone 17 Pro models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/iphone-17-pro-sky-blue-color/">rumored to be available in a Sky Blue color</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Larger battery:</strong> The iPhone 17 Pro Max is rumored to have a slightly thicker design that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/iphone-17-pro-max-thicker-larger-battery/">allows for a larger battery</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>A19 Pro chip:</strong> iPhone 17 Pro models are expected to use Apple's next-generation A19 Pro chip, which will reportedly be manufactured <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/a19-and-a19-pro-n3p-rumor/">with TSMC's newer third-generation 3nm process</a>. Like usual, expect modest year-over-year performance gains and power efficiency improvements compared to the current iPhones.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple-designed Wi-Fi 7 chip:</strong> All four iPhone 17 models are rumored to get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/">Wi-Fi 7 chip designed by Apple</a> rather than Broadcom.</li><br/>
<li><strong>24-megapixel front camera:</strong> All four iPhone 17 models are said to feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-rumor/">upgraded 24-megapixel front-facing camera</a>, whereas all iPhone 16 models are equipped with a 12-megapixel front-facing camera.</li><br/>
<li><strong>48-megapixel rear Telephoto camera:</strong> An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/">upgraded 48-megapixel Telephoto camera</a> is rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-pro-rumored-features/">for the iPhone 17 Pro models</a>, up from the 12-megapixel Telephoto camera on iPhone 16 Pro models.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Dual video recording:</strong> According to Jon Prosser, of the YouTube channel Front Page Tech, the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max will allow users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/iphone-17-pro-dual-video-recording-rumor/">record video with the front and rear cameras simultaneously</a> in the Camera app.</li><br/>
<li><strong>8K video recording:</strong> Apple allegedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/iphone-16-pro-4k-at-120fps-video-rumor/">tested 8K video recording on the iPhone 16 Pro models</a>, but such functionality is still not available. With the iPhone 17 Pro models expected to have entirely 48-megapixel rear cameras, perhaps 8K video recording will debut on those devices.</li><br/>
<li><strong>12GB of RAM:</strong> iPhone 17 Pro models, and even the iPhone 17 Air, are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">rumored to have 12GB of RAM</a>. This upgrade should help to improve the performance of Apple Intelligence and multitasking. All four iPhone 16 models have 8GB of RAM.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Improved cooling:</strong> All four iPhone 17 models are rumored to feature internal design changes that result in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/17/iphone-17-major-thermal-upgrade/">better heat dissipation</a>. A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/iphone-17-pro-advanced-cooling-better-performance/">vapor chamber cooling system</a> has been rumored for the Pro models.</ul>Bookmark our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro roundup</a> to stay up to date with more rumors.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-17-pro-rumors-list/">iPhone 17 Pro Launching Later This Year With These 12 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-launching-later-this-year-with-these-12-new-features.2457766/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Battled Apple Over Satellite Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/elon-musk-battled-apple-over-satellite-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/elon-musk-battled-apple-over-satellite-features.2457765/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:56:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/elon-musk-battled-apple-over-satellite-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Elon Musk</category>
		<category>Emergency SOS via Satellite</category>
		<category>iPhone Satellite Features</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[SpaceX CEO Elon Musk has been embroiled in a battle with Apple over its satellite connectivity features, according to <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apples-satellite-ambitions-threatened-elon-musk-internal-resistance"><em>The Information</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-Satellite-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2072" height="1166" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-977666" /><br/>
The report claims when SpaceX CEO Elon Musk heard that Apple was planning to announce a satellite connectivity feature for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 14 in partnership with Globalstar, he approached the company with an offer. He proposed that SpaceX would exclusively provide satellite connectivity to iPhones for 18 months, for an upfront cost of &#36;5 billion. After that, Apple would pay SpaceX &#36;1 billion per year for Starlink service.<br/>
<br/>
Musk threatened that if Apple did not agree to a deal with SpaceX within 72 hours, he would announce a similar satellite feature on his own that could work with iPhones. Apple rejected the proposal, and two weeks before the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 was announced SpaceX revealed a partnership with T-Mobile that allowed smartphone users to send and receive text messages in areas with no reception using Starlink.<br/>
<br/>
SpaceX has also filed legal challenges to Globalstar's use of the radio spectrum it has licensed, which could cripple the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s satellite service if they succeed. As part of this litigation, SpaceX challenged Globalstar's application to launch new satellites in 2023, accusing the satellite company of underutilizing the spectrum it already possessed. SpaceX accused the company of trying to block competition by hogging spectrum for itself.<br/>
<br/>
SpaceX also named Apple in the regulatory filings, which apparently irked Apple executives who wanted to keep their distance from the conflict. Moreover, Apple employees are said to believe that Musk's close relationship with the Trump administration could give him an advantage over Apple and others with the FCC.<br/>
<br/>
More recently, Apple and SpaceX have clashed over how far Apple would support SpaceX's partnership with T-Mobile. Over the past year, Musk asked Apple to support the T-Mobile satellite feature across a broad range of its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, which would help maximize the potential market for the service, but Apple was reluctant to support the service on models older than the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14, which frustrated Musk.<br/>
<br/>
The series of satellite connectivity spats added to animosity between Musk and Apple, who have also grappled with disagreements over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> fees. In recent years, Musk has plotted the idea of building his own phone to get around Apple's "gatekeeper" position in the market. Musk has reportedly discussed Tesla building the phone and satellite connectivity being provided by Starlink.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emergency-sos-via-satellite/">Emergency SOS via Satellite</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-satellite-features/">iPhone Satellite Features</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/elon-musk-battled-apple-over-satellite-features/">Elon Musk Battled Apple Over Satellite Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/elon-musk-battled-apple-over-satellite-features.2457765/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the M4 iPad Pro for Its Lowest-Ever Price of &#36;855.04 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/m4-ipad-pro-lowest-ever-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-m4-ipad-pro-for-its-lowest-ever-price-of-855-04-on-amazon.2457764/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:30:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/m4-ipad-pro-lowest-ever-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is discounting numerous models of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple's M4 iPad Pro</a> this week, mainly focusing on 11-inch models this time around. Simultaneously, Amazon has the Apple Pencil Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a> right now, and it's compatible with these iPad Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m4-iPad-Pro-Horizontal-Feature-Orange-and-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950739" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In this sale, the 256GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Pro has hit a new all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;855.04</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. There are multiple record low prices on 11-inch iPad Pros right now on Amazon, with up to &#36;300 off these tablets and no coupon codes required.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;145 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Pro for &#36;855.04</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
These iPad Pro models feature Apple's M4 chip, OLED displays, and support for the Apple Pencil Pro and the Magic Keyboard. Don't forget that you can get the Apple Pencil Pro for a match of its all-time low price of &#36;99.00 today on Amazon, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><h3>11-Inch iPad Pro - Wi-Fi</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;866.03 (&#36;133 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,077.00 (&#36;122 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,439.00 (&#36;160 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6RX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,554.00 (&#36;145 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J72NMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JBCRYW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">2TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,914.00 (&#36;185 off)</li></ul><br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/m4-ipad-pro-lowest-ever-price/">Get the M4 iPad Pro for Its Lowest-Ever Price of &#36;855.04 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-m4-ipad-pro-for-its-lowest-ever-price-of-855-04-on-amazon.2457764/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp for iPad Now Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/whatsapp-for-ipad-now-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-for-ipad-now-available.2457762/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:06:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/whatsapp-for-ipad-now-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Meta</category>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp is <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/whatsapp-messenger/id310633997">now available</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Meta today <a href="https://www.threads.com/@whatsapp/post/DKKOp82RviY">announced</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Whatsapp-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-786421" /><br/>
&zwnj;iPad&zwnj; support comes more than 15 years after the messaging service launched. In September, Meta <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/whatsapp-beta-native-ipad-support/">started beta testing</a> WhatsApp for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; via TestFlight.<br/>
<br/>
WhatsApp allows users of the encrypted messaging platform to link up to four devices to their account even when their main smartphone is not connected to the internet. Each linked device connects to WhatsApp independently, ensuring that personal messages, media, and calls are end-to-end encrypted.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to WhatsApp, Meta owns Facebook, Threads, and Instagram. There is an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app for Facebook, but the Threads app remains <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> only. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/instagram-ipad-app/">Instagram app for the iPad</a> is reportedly in the works.<br/>
<br/>
WhatsApp for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/whatsapp-messenger/id310633997">available to download from the App Store</a> now.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/whatsapp-for-ipad-now-available/">WhatsApp for iPad Now Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-for-ipad-now-available.2457762/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PopSockets Launches New Kick-Out iPhone Stand With Unique Twist</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/popsockets-kick-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popsockets-launches-new-kick-out-iphone-stand-with-unique-twist.2457760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:05:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/popsockets-kick-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>PopSockets</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[PopSockets today announced the launch of its new <a href="https://www.popsockets.com/en-us/new-and-featured/kick-out-grip-and-stand">Kick-Out grip and stand</a> for iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/PopSockets-Kick-Out.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003004" /><br/>
Unlike other PopSockets, the Kick-Out model offers the long-awaited ability to prop up an iPhone in a vertical Portrait Mode position. This added functionality is useful for watching vertical videos in apps like TikTok, Instagram, and YouTube.<br/>
<br/>
You can twist the built-in MagSafe ring, and then pop open the hinged stand to prop up the iPhone horizontally or vertically on a table.<br/>
<br/>
For those who are unfamiliar with PopSockets, they are a popular accessory that serves as both a hand grip and stand for iPhones. This latest Kick-Out model attaches magnetically to iPhone 12 models and newer with MagSafe.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., the PopSockets Kick-Out is priced at &#36;40.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/popsockets/">PopSockets</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/popsockets-kick-out/">PopSockets Launches New Kick-Out iPhone Stand With Unique Twist</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popsockets-launches-new-kick-out-iphone-stand-with-unique-twist.2457760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Planned to Offer Starlink-Like Home Internet Service</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-planned-home-internet-service/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-planned-to-offer-starlink-like-home-internet-service.2457755/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:08:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-planned-home-internet-service/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Emergency SOS via Satellite</category>
		<category>iPhone Satellite Features</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple had plans to offer a Starlink-like satellite home internet service in collaboration with Boeing, <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apples-satellite-ambitions-threatened-elon-musk-internal-resistance"><em>The Information</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/Emergency-SOS-via-Satellite-iPhone-YT.jpg" alt="" width="3564" height="1996" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-873000" /><br/>
Starting in 2015, Apple held discussions with Boeing about "Project Eagle," a plan to launch a service to provide wireless internet services to iPhones and homes. The companies would have launched thousands of satellites into orbit around the Earth to beam internet services down to the surface. Apple intended to sell antennas that users could attach to their windows to disperse internet connectivity throughout their homes.<br/>
<br/>
Apple believed the plan would help provide a more seamless experience, with mobile carriers seen as "necessary but inconvenient partners" that held back the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. Similar to the transition to Apple silicon, Apple saw Project Eagle as another way to reduce its reliance other companies. Apple spent &#36;36 million testing out a Project Eagle concept at a facility in El Segundo, California.<br/>
<br/>
The service was originally scheduled to launch in 2019, but it never saw the light of day. CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> was concerned that Project Eagle would endanger Apple's relationship with the telecoms industry. He also expressed concerns over its significant cost with an unclear near-term business case. In 2016, Apple canceled the project and senior staff involved in it left the company.<br/>
<br/>
Former hardware engineering chief Dan Riccio then formed a group looking at new wireless opportunities that would help differentiate Apple's devices. In 2018, Apple conducted talks with satellite internet providers such as OneWeb about investing in them to deploy a home internet service via satellites. OneWeb purportedly told Apple that the service would cost &#36;30 billion and &#36;40 billion to deliver, and similar concerns to those that killed Project Eagle put an end to the ambition.<br/>
<br/>
The group then refocused around the idea of offering satellite communications to iPhones in remote areas that were not already served by conventional cellular networks. Apple launched its Emergency SOS via Satellite feature in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
In 2023, Apple's satellite team proposed to use a new generation of satellites to deliver full, unrestricted internet service to iPhones in remote locations. The feature would have cost Apple significantly more than Globalstar's existing service for Apple, increasing from several dozen satellites to hundreds. Apple ultimately again declined to offer it due to concerns that it would anger mobile carriers.<br/>
<br/>
Today, some Apple employees and senior executives question the long-term viability of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s satellite connectivity features. Former Apple employees who worked on the project say the Globalstar network is already outdated, slow, and limited compared to SpaceX, and will continue to be through the next decade.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet started charging &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users for satellite connectivity features, and has extended the free access period through at least September 2025. The company's reluctance to charge customers is apparently related to fear  that it could trigger the U.S. government to regulate Apple like a telecommunications carrier, which could force the company to build surveillance back doors into iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
The existing satellite connectivity features cost Apple hundreds of millions of dollars per year. Some top executives, including software chief Craig Federighi and head of corporate development Adrian Perica, have advocated discontinuing the features. They argue that customers are more likely to sign up for satellite features through their mobile carriers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emergency-sos-via-satellite/">Emergency SOS via Satellite</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-satellite-features/">iPhone Satellite Features</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-planned-home-internet-service/">Report: Apple Planned to Offer Starlink-Like Home Internet Service</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-planned-to-offer-starlink-like-home-internet-service.2457755/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains How the App Store Keeps Users Safe in Big-Number Ways</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/app-store-fraud-analysis/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-the-app-store-keeps-users-safe-in-big-number-ways.2457754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:01:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/app-store-fraud-analysis/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/the-app-store-prevented-more-than-9-billion-usd-in-fraudulent-transactions/">shared a variety of statistics</a> that are intended to show how the App Store is a safe and trusted place for users to download apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/2024-App-Store-Awards.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981508" /><br/>
This announcement comes less than a month after a U.S. judge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-app-store-anti-steering-injunction-violation/">ordered Apple</a> to allow iPhone apps to show links or buttons that direct customers to make purchases outside of the ‌App Store‌. The timing is coincidental, though, as Apple has shared an App Store fraud analysis press release in May or early June for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/14/apple-fraud-prevention-analysis-2024/">five</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/apple-app-store-security-features/">consecutive</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/01/apple-app-store-fraud-analysis/">years</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/11/apple-highlights-app-store-antifraud-efforts/">now</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Here are some of the key statistics shared by Apple:<ul><li>Over the last five years, the App Store has prevented more than &#36;9 billion in fraudulent transactions, including over &#36;2 billion in 2024 alone.</li><br/>
<li>In 2024, Apple terminated more than 146,000 developer accounts over fraud concerns.</li><br/>
<li>In 2024, Apple rejected more than 711 million customer account creations, and it deactivated nearly 129 million customer accounts.<br/>
<li>Over the past month, Apple stopped nearly 4.6 million attempts to install or launch apps distributed illicitly outside the App Store or approved third-party marketplaces.</li><br/>
<li>Of the more than 7.7 million App Store submissions reviewed in 2024, Apple says it rejected more than 1.9 million of them for failing to meet the company's standards for security, reliability, and user experience, including for privacy violations or fraud concerns.</li><br/>
<li>In 2024, Apple removed more than 37,000 apps for fraudulent activity.</li><br/>
<li>In 2024, Apple removed more than 143 million fraudulent ratings and reviews from the App Store.</li><br/>
<li>In 2024, Apple identified nearly 4.7 million stolen credit cards and banned over 1.6 million accounts from transacting again.</li></ul>More statistics are outlined <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/the-app-store-prevented-more-than-9-billion-usd-in-fraudulent-transactions/">in Apple's announcement</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also published an updated <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/122712">support document</a> that explains how customers can stay safe while using the App Store.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/app-store-fraud-analysis/">Apple Explains How the App Store Keeps Users Safe in Big-Number Ways</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-the-app-store-keeps-users-safe-in-big-number-ways.2457754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Rumored to Redesign the iPhone Every Year Through to 2027</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-rumored-to-redesign-iphone-until-2027/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-rumored-to-redesign-the-iphone-every-year-through-to-2027.2457749/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 05:17:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-rumored-to-redesign-iphone-until-2027/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly preparing to implement significant <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> hardware redesigns each year for the next three generations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iPhone-Top-Left-Hole-Punch-Face-ID-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1000580" /><br/>
According leaks from the Chinese supply chain disclosed by Weibo user "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a>," Apple plans to carry out a series of phased industrial design changes affecting different parts of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; across three consecutive years: 2025, 2026, and 2027. The changes are said to target the rear camera system, the front-facing components, and eventually the complete removal of visible sensors, leading to an uninterrupted full-screen experience.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> is expected to launch in the fall as the first in this sequence of design shifts. Apple is widely expected to redesign the back of the device, with the most notable change being a new horizontal camera layout. The leak describes the move to a "horizontal large matrix lens decorative component." This change is set to be the first major update to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s rear camera module since the introduction of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
In 2026, attention will reportedly turn to the front of the device. Apple is expected to remove the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, the pill-shaped cutout that houses the front camera and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> components introduced on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro, and replace it with a single circular punch-hole cutout for the selfie camera. The hardware for &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; will be hidden beneath the display.<br/>
<br/>
By 2027, Apple is reportedly seeking a fully uninterrupted screen with no visible cutouts, holes, or notches of any kind. This will involve integrating both the &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; system and the selfie camera beneath the display, resulting in a true so-called "full-screen" &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.  <br/>
<br/>
The post does not mention whether these design changes will be limited to the Pro models or extend to the entire &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup. Historically, Apple has introduced new display and camera technologies on its high-end models before bringing them to the standard iPhones in subsequent years. The &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;, for example, debuted on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 Pro in 2022 before being added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and 15 Plus in 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-rumored-to-redesign-iphone-until-2027/">Apple Rumored to Redesign the iPhone Every Year Through to 2027</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-rumored-to-redesign-the-iphone-every-year-through-to-2027.2457749/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Tap to Pay on iPhone and Tap to Provision Features Coming to These 18 New Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-coming-to-18-new-countries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-and-tap-to-provision-features-coming-to-these-18-new-countries.2457747/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 04:41:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-coming-to-18-new-countries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Europe</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is bringing Tap to Pay on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to new eight countries, providing a way for sellers to use an ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ as a contactless payment terminal, with plans to introduce tap to provision in 10 more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-credit-card.jpeg" alt="" width="1306" height="735" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-836335" /><br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; first arrived in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/08/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-iphone-feature/">February 2022</a> in the U.S., and allows iPhones to accept payments via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, contactless credit and debit cards, and other digital wallets‌‌‌. All transactions are encrypted, and Apple has no information about what is purchased or the person who made the purchase.<br/>
<br/>
No additional hardware or credit card machine is required‌ to use Tap to Pay on ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌. The feature uses NFC technology to securely authenticate the contactless payments, plus the feature also supports PIN entry, which includes accessibility options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/newsroom/2025/05/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-eight-more-european-countries/">announced</a> that Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is now available in the following countries and payment platforms:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Belgium</strong>: Adyen, Axepta, Mollie, myPOS, Pay.nl, Revolut, Stripe, SumUp, Viva, and Worldline.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Croatia</strong>: Adyen, Viva, and Worldline.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Cyprus</strong>: Adyen, Revolut, SumUp, Viva, and Worldline.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Denmark</strong>: Adyen, Mollie, Nexi, Revolut, Stripe, SumUp, Surfboard Payments, and Viva; with PayPal coming soon.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Greece</strong>: myPOS, Viva, and Worldline; with NBG Pay coming soon.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Iceland</strong>: Adyen, Rapyd, and Revolut; with Teya coming soon.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Luxembourg</strong>: Adyen, Mollie, Revolut, Stripe, SumUp, Viva, and Worldline.  </li><br/>
<li><strong>Malta</strong>: Adyen, Global Payments, Revolut, SumUp, and Viva.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on ‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌ requires ‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌ XS or newer models, and works for customers as any normal ‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌ transaction would. Sellers just need to open up the app, register the sale, and present their ‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌ to the buyer, who can then use an appropriate contactless payment method.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's website <a href="https://developer.apple.com/tap-to-pay/regions/">maintains a list of countries</a> where Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is available.<br/>
<br/>
According to updates to Apple's backend, tap to provision is also coming to these 10 new countries in the near future:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Austria</li><br/>
<li>Croatia</li><br/>
<li>Czechia</li><br/>
<li>Hungary</li><br/>
<li>Italy</li><br/>
<li>Netherlands</li><br/>
<li>San Marino</li><br/>
<li>Slovenia</li><br/>
<li>Switzerland</li><br/>
<li>Vatican City</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Distinct from Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, tap to provision allows users to add a payment card to their digital wallet by simply tapping the card against their phone. This process eliminates the need for manual data entry, making it easier to add cards to digital wallets like Apple Wallet. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/europe/">Europe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-coming-to-18-new-countries/">Apple&#039;s Tap to Pay on iPhone and Tap to Provision Features Coming to These 18 New Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-and-tap-to-provision-features-coming-to-these-18-new-countries.2457747/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Raises iCloud+ Prices in Three Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/apple-raises-icloud-prices-in-three-countries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-raises-icloud-prices-in-three-countries.2457735/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 13:45:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/apple-raises-icloud-prices-in-three-countries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently raised prices for its iCloud+ plans in Brazil, Chile, and Peru, according to a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/108047">support document</a> updated last Thursday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/iCloud-General-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-982796" /><br/>
The table below outlines the price changes in each country.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison" style="text-align: center;"><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <th>Country</th><br/>
    <th>Old Prices</th><br/>
    <th>New Prices</th><br/>
  </tr><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <td>Brazil</td><br/>
    <td>50GB: R&#36; 4.90<br/>
      200GB: R&#36; 14.90<br/>
      2TB: R&#36; 49.90<br/>
      6TB: R&#36; 149.90<br/>
      12TB: R&#36; 299.90<br/>
    </td><br/>
    <td>50GB: R&#36; 5.90<br/>
      200GB: R&#36; 19.90<br/>
      2TB: R&#36; 66.90<br/>
      6TB: R&#36; 199.90<br/>
      12TB: R&#36; 399.90<br/>
    </td><br/>
  </tr><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <td>Chile</td><br/>
    <td>50GB: &#36;790<br/>
      200GB: &#36;2,490<br/>
      2TB: &#36;8,490<br/>
      6TB: &#36;29,990<br/>
      12TB: &#36;59,990<br/>
    </td><br/>
    <td>50GB: &#36;990<br/>
      200GB: &#36;3,290<br/>
      2TB: &#36;10,990<br/>
      6TB: &#36;32,990<br/>
      12TB: &#36;64,990<br/>
    </td><br/>
  </tr><br/>
  <tr><br/>
    <td>Peru</td><br/>
    <td>50GB: S/. 2.90<br/>
      200GB: S/. 9.90<br/>
      2TB: S/. 34.90<br/>
      6TB: S/. 99.90<br/>
      12TB: S/. 199.90<br/>
    </td><br/>
    <td>50GB: S/. 3.90<br/>
      200GB: S/. 12.90<br/>
      2TB: S/. 42.90<br/>
      6TB: S/. 129.90<br/>
      12TB: S/. 259.90<br/>
    </td><br/>
  </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The price increases in Brazil were first reported <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2025/05/26/apple-hikes-icloud-and-apple-one-subscription-prices-in-brazil/">by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>, and we subsequently confirmed that Chile and Peru were also affected.<br/>
<br/>
Throughout 2024, Apple raised prices for some or all iCloud+ storage plans in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/icloud-storage-price-increases/">at least 10 other countries</a>, including Japan, South Korea, Thailand, Indonesia, Turkey, Pakistan, Nigeria, Egypt, Tanzania, and the Philippines. <br/>
<br/>
So far, other countries like the U.S., Canada, and the U.K. have avoided iCloud+ price increases.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/apple-raises-icloud-prices-in-three-countries/">Apple Raises iCloud+ Prices in Three Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-raises-icloud-prices-in-three-countries.2457735/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Teases Long-Awaited iPad App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/whatsapp-teases-ipad-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-teases-long-awaited-ipad-app.2457726/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 10:23:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/whatsapp-teases-ipad-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The popular messaging app WhatsApp has teased a long-awaited iPad app, which would be offered alongside its existing iPhone and Mac apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Whatsapp-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786421" /><br/>
The official WhatsApp account on X today <a href="https://x.com/WhatsApp/status/1927047493797192070">reacted</a> with an eyes emoji to a post saying that WhatsApp should release an iPad app. This could be a hint that Meta is gearing up to release WhatsApp for iPad, which has already been available for beta testing via TestFlight for nearly two years. File this news under "finally."<br/>
<br/>
With an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/instagram-ipad-app/">Instagram app for the iPad</a> also reportedly in the works, it appears that Meta is at last embracing the iPad for more of its most popular apps.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to WhatsApp and Instagram, Meta owns Facebook and Threads. There is an iPad app for Facebook, but the Threads app remains iPhone only.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/whatsapp-teases-ipad-app/">WhatsApp Teases Long-Awaited iPad App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-teases-long-awaited-ipad-app.2457726/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone App for Keeping Track of More Than 800 Apple Watch Bands Receives Major Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/bandbreite-app-version-2-0-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-app-for-keeping-track-of-more-than-800-apple-watch-bands-receives-major-update.2457724/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 09:29:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/bandbreite-app-version-2-0-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Bands</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The ultimate app for keeping track of Apple Watch bands is now even better.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Bandbreite-2.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1920" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002915" /><br/>
<a href="https://bandbreite.watch/">Bandbreite</a> version 2.0 was recently released <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bandbreite/id1528561380">in the App Store</a> for the iPhone and iPad. According to the app's lead creator, Filip Chudzinski, the update introduces more than 30 new features and changes, including everything from a revamped logbook and richer stats to faster iCloud sync and improved search functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Launched in 2020, Bandbreite provides comprehensive information about every official Apple Watch band ever released, with more than 840 bands organized by style, color, or release date. The app also lets you keep track of bands that you already own, and there are now more  filter and sort options for your personal collection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Bandbreite-2-2.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1920" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002916" /><br/>
Bandbreite was totally free to use for more than four years, with Chudzinski relying on a combination of his passion and donations to keep the project going. Starting with version 2.0, however, the app charges a one-time &#36;7.49 fee if you want to manage a collection of more than five Apple Watch bands. Chudzinski <a href="https://bandbreite.watch/statement.html">said</a> this decision will ensure that his team can provide the best possible experience in a financially-sustainable manner.<br/>
<br/>
Existing users of the Bandbreite app who already have a collection of more than five bands can access all free and paid features in version 2.0 of the app, but they must pay the fee if they wish to add more bands to their collection.<br/>
<br/>
An updated version of the Mac app is also in the works, and the Apple Watch companion app will return soon, according to Chudzinski.<br/>
<br/>
Chudzinski also has a long-running <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/every-apple-watch-band-apple-released-ever.2005810/">MacRumors Forums thread</a> dedicated to tracking Apple Watch band releases — it is the precursor to the app.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-bands/">Apple Watch Bands</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/bandbreite-app-version-2-0-update/">iPhone App for Keeping Track of More Than 800 Apple Watch Bands Receives Major Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-app-for-keeping-track-of-more-than-800-apple-watch-bands-receives-major-update.2457724/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
