<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 04:04:29 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Models to Come With 2TB Storage Option, Claims Rumor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/iphone-16-pro-2tb-option-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-come-with-2tb-storage-option-claims-rumor.2416765/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 03:06:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/iphone-16-pro-2tb-option-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Naver</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year's forthcoming iPhone 16 Pro models will be available with a new 2TB maximum storage option, claims a new rumor coming out of Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Pro-Mock-Header-Updated.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924442" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostView.naver?blogId=yeux1122&logNo=223327662832&navType=by">news aggregator account "yeux1122"</a> on the Naver blog, the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be available with double the maximum storage capacity as the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
The move is said to be a result of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/1tb-iphone-16-pro-could-face-performance-setback/">recently rumored</a> switch to higher-density Quad-Level Cell (QLC) NAND flash for higher storage models. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's use of QLC NAND could allow Apple to fit more storage into a smaller space and it is less expensive than Triple-Level Cell (TLC) NAND, which current iPhones use. On the downside, QLC has comparatively slower read and write speeds.<br/>
<br/>
It's worth noting that in the last couple of years we have seen rumors that both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/10/01/iphone-14-to-feature-2tb-storage/">iPhone 14 Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/07/iphone-15-pro-2tb-storage-option/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> would feature 2TB options for the same reason, but they turned out to be false. <br/>
<br/>
That said, this year Apple is expected to add a new "Capture Button" to the iPhone 16 models for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">taking video</a>. According to <em>The Information</em>, the button is being introduced to further push the iPhone as a camera alternative for shooting horizontal video, so offering higher storage options could be part of that plan.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/naver/">Naver</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/iphone-16-pro-2tb-option-rumor/">iPhone 16 Pro Models to Come With 2TB Storage Option, Claims Rumor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-come-with-2tb-storage-option-claims-rumor.2416765/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store Down Ahead of Vision Pro Headset Pre-Orders</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-store-down-vision-pro-pre-orders/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-ahead-of-vision-pro-headset-pre-orders.2416760/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:11:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-store-down-vision-pro-pre-orders/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's online store is down in the U.S. ahead of Vision Pro pre-orders, which are scheduled to open at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time, ahead of the device's official launch on Friday, February 2. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-store-down-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931625" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> is the company's first foray into the world of mixed reality, or "spatial computing" as Apple likes to call it. The device has been in development for more than a decade and features an array of sophisticated technologies that allow it to display augmented reality content superimposed on the world around you, and entirely virtual content for immersive entertainment and gaming experiences.<br/>
<br/>
Starting at &#36;3,499, the wearable headset device features two micro-OLED displays that deliver over 4K resolution to each eye, and an external display called EyeSight that projects an image of your eyes so people can tell whether you're using the headset in an immersive mode or if you can see what's going on around you. For glasses wearers, there are custom prescription Zeiss Optical Inserts (&#36;149) that can be attached magnetically to the headset's lenses, and optional readers (&#36;99) will be available.<br/>
<br/>
The device includes an array of sensors and cameras for monitoring hand gestures and mapping the external environment, and there are speakers on either side of the headset. Vision Pro is powered by an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> processor and a separate R1 processor dedicated to processing information coming from these sensors. It also comes with 16GB of RAM and at least 256GB of onboard storage, with the potential for Apple to offer models with up to 1TB of storage, although this hasn't been officially confirmed. An external battery pack is included in the box.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-vision-pro-pre-order-need-to-know/">Pre-Ordering Apple Vision Pro: What You Need to Know</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple is planning to produce between 60,000 and 80,000 Vision Pro units for the February 2 launch of the device, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/11/kuo-vision-pro-sellout-likely/">according to analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. With the small size of the shipment, Kuo believes that the Vision Pro will "sell out soon after the release."<br/>
<br/>
Orders are limited to the United States for the time being, but Apple is likely to launch the Vision Pro headset <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">outside the U.S. before WWDC 2024 in June</a>, with Canada and the United Kingdom tipped as the first two other countries in which the headset will be available. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-store-down-vision-pro-pre-orders/">Apple Store Down Ahead of Vision Pro Headset Pre-Orders</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-ahead-of-vision-pro-headset-pre-orders.2416760/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>UK &#039;Body Coach&#039; Joe Wicks to Make Guest Appearance on Apple Fitness+</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/joe-wicks-guest-appearance-apple-fitness/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-body-coach-joe-wicks-to-make-guest-appearance-on-apple-fitness.2416757/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 01:32:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/joe-wicks-guest-appearance-apple-fitness/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Fitness Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/newsroom/2024/01/celebrity-trainer-joe-wicks-makes-guest-appearance-in-apple-fitness-plus/">announced</a> that British fitness coach Joe Wicks MBE, also known as "The Body Coach," is set to make a guest appearance in Apple Fitness+ to "help users kick-start their fitness routine" this new year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Fitness-Plus-UK-Joe-Wicks.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931617" /><br/>
Starting January 22, the service will host Wicks in exclusive 10-minute Strength and HIIT workouts alongside Fitness+ trainers Kim Ngo and Jamie-Ray Hartshorne. Apple says the workouts are designed to be "easy for anyone to join in, no matter where they are at on their health and wellbeing journey." The workouts are inspired by Wicks’s favorite HIIT and strength moves, and will feature songs from his new playlist on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Readers in the United Kingdom will recognize Wicks from his inclusive online home workout series that went viral during the 2020 lockdown, earning him the moniker "PE teacher to the nation." Wicks also received a high honor from the late Queen for his extensive fitness and charity work.<br/>
<blockquote>"I'm a huge fan of Apple Fitness+ and its welcoming and inclusive approach to fitness and wellbeing," said Wicks. "We had a lot fun developing these workouts together, and I'm looking forward to helping as many people as possible start, continue, or reach their fitness goals this year."</blockquote>Apple Fitness+ is available as a subscription service for £9.99 per month or £79.99 per year, and can be shared with up to five other family members. Fitness+ is also included in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> Premier plan, which, where available, also gives customers access to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>+, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+ with 2TB of storage, and can be shared with up to five other family members.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-fitness-plus/">Apple Fitness Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/joe-wicks-guest-appearance-apple-fitness/">UK &#039;Body Coach&#039; Joe Wicks to Make Guest Appearance on Apple Fitness+</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-body-coach-joe-wicks-to-make-guest-appearance-on-apple-fitness.2416757/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Capture Button Will Respond to Touch and Pressure for Zooming and Focusing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-capture-button-will-respond-to-touch-and-pressure-for-zooming-and-focusing.2416735/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 17:09:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to add a new "Capture Button" to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">we first reported</a> back in September. When the news broke about the extra button, we didn't initially know what it was for, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">name gave us some hints</a> and <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> confirmed in December that it would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/iphone-16-capture-button-video/">used for taking video</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Pro-Mock-Header-Updated.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924442" /><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-plans-iphone-camera-button-as-creators-shift-to-horizontal-videos">The Information</a></em> has now shared a few new details on the function of the Capture Button, including some of the gestures that it will support. The site says that the button is mechanical rather than capacitive, but it will respond to pressure and touch.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users will be able to zoom in and out by swiping left and right on the button, focus with a light press, and activate a recording with a more forceful press.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to put the Capture Button on the right side of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, located below the Power button and in an ideal spot for finger access when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is held in a horizontal orientation. At the current time, this is the location of the mmWave antenna in the United States, but the antenna will move to the left side of the device with the addition of the extra button.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em>The Information</em>, Apple believes the new button will be a major selling point for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, and it is being introduced to further push the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a camera alternative for shooting horizontal video.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet finalized the design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, so the function and design of the button could change in the future.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">iPhone 16 Capture Button Will Respond to Touch and Pressure for Zooming and Focusing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-capture-button-will-respond-to-touch-and-pressure-for-zooming-and-focusing.2416735/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Giving Employees 25% Discount on Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-employee-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-giving-employees-25-discount-on-vision-pro.2416733/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 16:33:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-employee-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple employees will be able to purchase the Vision Pro at a 25 percent discount, which drops the price of the device &#36;3,500 to approximately &#36;2624, not including tax.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Purple-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929681" /><br/>
Employees were told about the discount in a memo that was sent out today, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-18/apple-vision-pro-chief-sees-surgery-training-as-future-vision-pro-growth-areas">Bloomberg</a></em>. In the past, Apple has offered 50 percent discounts on new products like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and the Apple Watch, but the Vision Pro is more expensive.<br/>
<br/>
Every three years, employees are provided with a &#36;500 credit toward a Mac, and that credit will also be able to be used for the Vision Pro, plus Apple is planning to reimburse employees that purchase the headset for the cost of any prescription lenses that are required.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders for the Vision Pro begin tomorrow at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time, with a launch to follow on Friday, February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-employee-discount/">Apple Giving Employees 25% Discount on Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-giving-employees-25-discount-on-vision-pro.2416733/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Vision Pro Could Be Used for Surgeries, Technical Training and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/vision-pro-enterprise-uses/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-vision-pro-could-be-used-for-surgeries-technical-training-and-more.2416731/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 16:05:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/vision-pro-enterprise-uses/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple executives believe the Vision Pro has a number of enterprise applications, from advanced technical training to use in operating rooms, according to a video sent out to employees.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-macbook.jpg" alt="" width="3022" height="1698" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930147" /><br/>
The video, which features Apple's Mike Rockwell and Alan Dye, both of whom are involved in the development of the device, discusses the development of the Vision Pro and what it might be used for in the future. <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-18/apple-vision-pro-chief-sees-surgery-training-as-future-vision-pro-growth-areas">Bloomberg</a></em> received a transcript of the video, and shared details on the information included.<br/>
<br/>
"Oftentimes, surgeons struggle to look at displays during procedures, where information is spread out," Rockwell said. "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> could bring all of that together and hopefully improve patient outcomes."<br/>
<br/>
Rockwell said that technicians or aircraft mechanics could use the Vision Pro for "high-quality training" that hasn't been possible before, and he said that Apple is "excited" about the opportunities in learning and education. "We strived to make a product that was a tool, not a toy," said Rockwell.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, two employees under Rockwell are responsible for discovering new applications for the Vision Pro. One is exploring enterprise uses for the device, while the other is looking into potential education opportunities.<br/>
<br/>
Finding enterprise uses for the headset could be key to its success, given the high price of the device. The Vision Pro starts at &#36;3,500, which puts it out of the reach of some consumers.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/vision-pro-enterprise-uses/">Apple Says Vision Pro Could Be Used for Surgeries, Technical Training and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-vision-pro-could-be-used-for-surgeries-technical-training-and-more.2416731/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pre-Ordering Apple Vision Pro: What You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-vision-pro-pre-order-need-to-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pre-ordering-apple-vision-pro-what-you-need-to-know.2416727/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:01:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-vision-pro-pre-order-need-to-know&#038;post_date=1705629685/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">announced</a> that its Vision Pro headset will officially launch in the United States on February 2, and that pre-orders will be open starting Friday, January 19, at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time. Here's everything you need to know about pre-ordering your unit on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/vision-pro-headset-1.jpg" alt="" width="2698" height="1518" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898460" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>When Will Pre-Orders Begin?</h2><br/>
Apple Vision Pro is initially launching only in the United States, with pre-orders beginning at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time on Friday, January 19. For those in other U.S. time zones, here is the full list of pre-order times:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>8:00 a.m. Eastern Time</li><br/>
<li>7:00 a.m. Central Time</li><br/>
<li>6:00 a.m. Mountain Time</li><br/>
<li>5:00 a.m. Pacific Time</li><br/>
<li>4:00 a.m. Alaska Time</li><br/>
<li>3:00 a.m. Hawaii–Aleutian Time</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pre-Order Configuration Options</h2><br/>
Apple has yet to share full tech specs for the Vision Pro, so only limited details are available in terms of what configuration options you will be able to select during the pre-order process. <br/>
<br/>
The headset starts from &#36;3,499, and Apple has so far said the device is equipped with an M2 chip, an all-new R1 chip that processes camera and microphone input, and 256GB of base storage. Apple could offer models with up to 1TB of storage, but the existence of bigger capacities has not yet been confirmed. <em>MacRumors</em> has additionally discovered that the headset is equipped with 16GB of RAM, but this is likely to be a fixed amount of memory in all units. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>What's in the Box</h2><br/>
Apple says customers can expect the Vision Pro packaging to include the following:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>Vision Pro headset</li><br/>
    <li>Polishing cloth</li><br/>
    <li>Solo Knit Band</li><br/>
    <li>Dual Loop Band</li><br/>
    <li>Light Seal</li><br/>
    <li>Two Light Seal cushions</li><br/>
    <li>Vision Pro cover</li><br/>
    <li>External battery pack</li><br/>
    <li>USB-C charging cable</li><br/>
    <li>Power adapter</li><br/>
</ul>For customers who want to use the headset on the go without pockets or a backpack, Belkin will sell an accessory clip that allows the battery pack to be attached to clothing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Vision Pro Payment Options</h2><br/>
Apple customers will be able to purchase the Vision Pro online and at retail stores using Apple Card installments. Typically, Apple Card installments let customers spread the purchase over monthly payments with no interest. iPhone purchases can be made over 24 monthly payments, for example. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pre-Order Requirements</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><b>Face ID Scan</b>: Ensure you have an iPhone or iPad with Face ID available. This is required to scan your face for a custom fit of the Light Seal and headbands.</li><br/>
    <li><b>Apple Store App Update</b>: Update your Apple Store app to the latest version (released January 11) to support Vision Pro face scanning.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Vision Correction Options</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><b>Reading Lenses</b>: For an additional &#36;99, attachable Zeiss readers are available for those with vision correction needs. Assuming no other configuration options are selected, for a Vision Pro with reading lenses, the combined outlay is &#36;3,598.</li><br/>
    <li><b>Prescription Lenses</b>: For &#36;149, Zeiss prescription lenses that magnetically attach to the headset are offered. A valid prescription is required. Assuming no other configuration options are selected, for a Vision Pro with prescription lenses, the combined outlay is &#36;3,648.</li><br/>
    <li><b>Prescription Upload</b>: Post-checkout, you'll need to upload a valid, unexpired prescription from a U.S. eye-care professional. Note that the prescription lens options are only sold online.</li><br/>
    <li><b>Health App Integration</b>: You can <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213226">store your vision prescription in the Health app</a> for convenient retrieval.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Post Pre-Order Demos</h2><br/>
Following pre-orders, the Vision Pro will launch in the U.S. on Friday, February 2. Starting at 8 a.m. local time that day, customers are invited to sign up for a demo of the headset at their local Apple Store, with slots to be available through the weekend on a first-come, first-served basis<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Vision Pro Availability Outside the U.S.</h2><br/>
Orders are limited to the United States for the time being, but Apple is likely to launch the Vision Pro headset outside the U.S. before WWDC 2024 in June, with Canada and the United Kingdom tipped as the first two other countries in which the headset will be available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
<h2>Further Reading</h2><br/>
For more detailed insights and updates about the Apple Vision Pro after pre-orders open, stay tuned to our comprehensive Vision Pro coverage. It's also worth checking out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">dedicated Apple Vision Pro roundup</a>. The latter provides a deeper dive into the capabilities and features of the device, ensuring you're well-informed before making your purchase.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-vision-pro-pre-order-need-to-know/">Pre-Ordering Apple Vision Pro: What You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pre-ordering-apple-vision-pro-what-you-need-to-know.2416727/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube and Spotify Apps Won&#039;t Be Available on Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/youtube-spotify-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-and-spotify-apps-wont-be-available-on-vision-pro.2416725/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:42:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/youtube-spotify-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>YouTube</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube and Spotify do not plan to offer apps on the Vision Pro headset, according to a new report from <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-18/youtube-and-spotify-join-netflix-in-not-launching-apple-vision-pro-apps">Bloomberg</a></em>. YouTube said that it is not developing a YouTube Vision Pro app, nor will it allow the YouTube <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> app to run on the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Spotify is also not working on an app, and it does not have plans to allow the Spotify &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app to be available through the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. YouTube and Spotify will instead be accessible through Safari, similar to Netflix.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/">said earlier this week</a> that Netflix subscribers can watch content through the Vision Pro web browser, and that no dedicated app would be developed.<br/>
<br/>
Given Apple's contentious relationship with Spotify, it is not surprising that Spotify has no intention of creating an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> app. Many companies may also be taking a wait-and-see approach with the Vision Pro, as the device is expensive and Apple is not expected to sell many units. Far fewer people will be using the Vision Pro compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, so there could be some hesitation to invest resources in the headset.<br/>
<br/>
At the same time, while &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps can run on Vision Pro with little to no effort, YouTube and Netflix customers might be disappointed with the lackluster experience compared to entertainment apps designed specifically for Vision Pro, such as Disney+, which could cause issues for the companies. There are fewer expectations with a web-based experience, so it is likely the safest bet for streaming services not yet ready to build out full Vision Pro experiences.<br/>
<br/>
If the Vision Pro headset is a hit, and apps like Disney+ and Max get a lot of use, companies that are not yet inspired to release apps could debut them in the future.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-vision-pro-app-store-launches/">Vision Pro App Store</a> launched earlier this week, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> compatibility is listed on &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; pages, giving some insight into which apps will be available on the headset and which apps will not. <a href="https://www.macstories.net/news/a-survey-of-popular-apps-currently-compatible-with-apple-vision-pro/"><em>MacStories</em> did a survey</a> of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and found that there are as of yet no signs of several popular apps like Instagram, Facebook, WhatsApp, Snapchat, Amazon, Google, and Gmail.<br/>
<br/>
While &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps are available on Vision Pro by default, developers can opt out of having their apps appear on the device. It is not yet clear if the major apps listed above are opting out of the Vision Pro entirely, but they have turned off &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app access and have not yet announced dedicated Vision Pro apps.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders for the Vision Pro begin tomorrow morning at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time, with a launch set to follow on Friday, February 2.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube/">YouTube</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/youtube-spotify-vision-pro/">YouTube and Spotify Apps Won&#039;t Be Available on Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-and-spotify-apps-wont-be-available-on-vision-pro.2416725/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Super Fruit Ninja on Vision Pro Lets Gamers Chop Fruit With Hand Gestures</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/super-fruit-ninja-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/super-fruit-ninja-on-vision-pro-lets-gamers-chop-fruit-with-hand-gestures.2416719/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 12:50:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/super-fruit-ninja-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Fruit Ninja from Halfbrick Studios was developed for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in 2010, and since then, it's been one of the best-known mobile games. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> version is set to come to the Vision Pro, and Halfbrick today shared details on how it was customized for Apple's spatial computer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/fruit-ninja-vision-pro-1.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931587" /><br/>
Halfbrick Studios lead gameplay programmer Samantha Turner said in a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=455tez3y">profile published by Apple</a> that the game on Vision Pro is "truly bananas" and has the potential to "do something very special."<br/>
<br/>
To develop the game, the team worked to bring a traditional 2D interface to 3D space. "We were full of ideas: What if players could squeeze juice out of an orange? What if they could rip apart a watermelon and cover the table and walls with juice?" she said. Halfbrick had to work out how to launch fruit at people, and settled on a set of cannons in a virtual space.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/fruit-ninja-vision-pro.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931588" /><br/>
How to interact with fruit was also a question, and while Halfbrick experimented with variety of hand motions and weapons, they settled on hands. Fruit is chopped up with hands, which turned out to be the most satisfying interaction experience.<blockquote>"We always knew hands would be the center of the experience," she says. "We wanted players to be able to grab things and knock them away. And we can tailor the arc of the fruit to make sure it's a comfortable fruit-slicing experience -- we're actually using the vertical position of the device itself to make sure that we're not throwing fruit over your head or too low."</blockquote>Users will be able to slice and dice pineapples and watermelons by jabbing at them, send bombs away by pushing them to a far wall, and fire shuriken into fruit by brushing the palms in an outward direction.<br/>
<br/>
Super Fruit Ninja is just one game coming to the Vision Pro. The headset will support more than 250 &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; titles, some of which have been customized with spatial experiences. Other options include Game Room and What the Golf, plus other titles that third-party developers are working on.<br/>
<br/>
Gaming will be one of the key features of the Vision Pro headset, but there are also a number of productivity and entertainment apps coming to the device. Slack, Microsoft 365, Fantastical, JigSpace, Disney+, and Max are just some of the customized Vision Pro apps that will be available at launch.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders for the Vision Pro begin tomorrow, January 19, at 5:00 a.m. Pacific Time. A launch is set to follow on Friday, February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/super-fruit-ninja-vision-pro/">Super Fruit Ninja on Vision Pro Lets Gamers Chop Fruit With Hand Gestures</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/super-fruit-ninja-on-vision-pro-lets-gamers-chop-fruit-with-hand-gestures.2416719/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Masimo CEO: Apple Watch Blood Oxygen Sensor is Not Reliable, Customers Are &#039;Better Off Without It&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/masimo-ceo-apple-blood-oxygen-sensor-unreliable/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/masimo-ceo-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-is-not-reliable-customers-are-better-off-without-it.2416716/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 12:04:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/masimo-ceo-apple-blood-oxygen-sensor-unreliable/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As Apple starts selling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and Ultra 2 models without the blood oxygen sensor enabled, Masimo CEO Joe Kiani <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-18/masimo-ceo-says-users-are-better-off-without-apple-s-oxygen-tool">confirmed to <em>Bloomberg</em></a> that there has been no chat with Apple about a possible settlement.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/apple-watch-ultra-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895884" /><br/>
According to Kiani, he has not spoken to anyone from Apple "personally" and no one from Apple has reached out about an agreement. He did say there have been court-ordered mediations he is unable to discuss, and that there are likely to be additional meetings in the future, but he does not believe those meetings will serve as steps to settling the legal dispute with Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/19/masimo-ceo-on-apple-watch-ban/">Back in December</a>, Kiani said that Masimo would be open to a settlement with Apple and would help the Cupertino company "improve their product," but he said he would want an apology and "honest dialogue" as part of any settlement discussion.<br/>
<br/>
Kiani maligned the Apple Watch blood oxygen sensor, even though it is allegedly using Masimo-patented technology. "Apple is masquerading what they are offering to consumers as a reliable, medical pulse oximeter, even though it is not," said Kiani. "I really feel wholeheartedly that consumers are better off without it."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's blood oxygen sensor does not have FDA clearance, but Masimo's <a href="https://investor.masimo.com/news/news-details/2023/Masimo-W1-Medical-Watch-Receives-FDA-510k-Clearance-for-Over-the-Counter-and-Prescription-Use/default.aspx">W1 watch</a> does. Masimo's device offers continuous real-time oxygen saturation and pulse rate monitoring, and it can be used as a medical device in hospitals, clinics, and at home. Kiani says that pulse oximetry "is not useful unless it is a continuous monitor."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has accused Masimo of copying the Apple Watch with the W1, and claims that it infringes on several Apple patents. Apple has said that Masimo is using litigation to eliminate the Apple Watch from the market to make room for the W1 watch. Kiani says that Apple's narrative is "false" and that Apple is living in a "fake reality."<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. International Trade Commission ruled in October that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">Apple violated Masimo patents</a> with the Apple Watch blood oxygen sensor, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">levied an import ban</a> on the component in December. Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">forced to stop selling</a> the Apple Watch for a short period, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">sales resumed</a> while the Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit considered whether or not to stay the import ban during the appeals process.<br/>
<br/>
The court <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">decided yesterday</a> that the import ban would not be paused while Apple's appeal is considered, and as of today, Apple is not allowed to sell &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> models with a functional blood oxygen sensor in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
To avoid having to stop sales, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-app-removal/">opted to sell</a> modified &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; models that do not contain pulse oximetry functionality, and those devices are now available for purchase. These Apple Watches <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-website-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-removal/">still have a blood oxygen sensor</a> inside, but it is disabled.<br/>
<br/>
In the future, should Apple come to some sort of arrangement with Masimo or should the ITC's ruling be overturned, the Apple Watch models sold with the disabled sensor should be able to be returned to working condition with a software update. &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 models sold prior to the import ban will continue to offer blood oxygen sensing technology, as well Apple Watches sold outside of the United States.<br/>
<br/>
The import ban is only applicable in the U.S., and Apple is able to sell the Apple Watch as usual in other countries.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/masimo-ceo-apple-blood-oxygen-sensor-unreliable/">Masimo CEO: Apple Watch Blood Oxygen Sensor is Not Reliable, Customers Are &#039;Better Off Without It&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/masimo-ceo-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-is-not-reliable-customers-are-better-off-without-it.2416716/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some Apple Stores Closing Early on Sunday Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/some-apple-stores-closing-early-sunday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-stores-closing-early-on-sunday-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2416715/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 11:53:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/some-apple-stores-closing-early-sunday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At least 70 of Apple's retail stores in the U.S. will be closing earlier than usual on Sunday, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/storelist/">Apple's website</a>. Most of Apple's other retail stores across the country already have reduced hours on Sundays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-at-Steve-Jobs-Theater.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898794" /><br/>
In his newsletter earlier this month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said all Apple retail stores would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/07/gurman-vision-pro-launch-imminent/">holding three-hour meetings for all employees on January 21</a>, the same day that some stores are closing early. Some employees believe these meetings will discuss Vision Pro sales procedures and other training material for Apple's headset, according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not respond to our request for comment.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro launches in the U.S. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">on February 2</a>, with pre-orders beginning this Friday. Starting on February 2 at 8 a.m. local time, at least some of Apple's stores in the U.S. will allow customers to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/apple-store-vision-pro-demos-details/">sign up for a demo of the headset</a>. Apple said it will offer demos from February 2 through February 4 on a first‑come, first‑served basis.<br/>
<br/>
We previously reported on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/12/apple-vision-pro-preorder-tips/">how to prepare for Vision Pro pre-orders</a>, for customers who are willing to spend &#36;3,499 on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a> assisted with this story.</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/some-apple-stores-closing-early-sunday/">Some Apple Stores Closing Early on Sunday Ahead of Vision Pro Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-stores-closing-early-on-sunday-ahead-of-vision-pro-launch.2416715/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Back to School Offer Live in Australia and Some Other Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-2024-back-to-uni-australia-nz/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-back-to-school-offer-live-in-australia-and-some-other-countries.2416695/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 07:13:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-2024-back-to-uni-australia-nz/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Back to School Promotion</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's annual Back to School/Back to Uni promotion is ongoing in <a href="https://www.apple.com/au-hed/shop/back-to-school">Australia</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/nz/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">New Zealand</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/br-hed/shop/back-to-school">Brazil</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/kr-edu/shop/back-to-school">South Korea</a>. From January 4 through March 13, qualifying higher-education students in these countries can receive a free item with the purchase of an eligible Mac or iPad on Apple's online store, in the Apple Store app, at at Apple Store locations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/2022-back-to-school-apple-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2178" height="1224" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851334" /><br/>
The free item is as follows:<ul><li><strong><a href="https://www.apple.com/au/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">Australia</a>:</strong> Up to a &#36;240 Apple gift card</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://www.apple.com/nz/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">New Zealand</a>:</strong> A free Apple Pencil with an iPad, and free AirPods with a Mac</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://www.apple.com/br/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">Brazil</a>:</strong> A free Apple Pencil with an iPad, and free AirPods with a Mac</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://www.apple.com/kr/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">South Korea</a>:</strong> A free Apple Pencil with an iPad, and free AirPods with a Mac</li></ul>The free Apple Pencil and AirPods models provided vary based on the iPad or Mac model purchased, with complete details about eligibility and more outlined in the full terms and conditions for each country, linked above.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Back to School promotion typically launches in the U.S. around June or July each year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/back-to-school-promotion/">Back to School Promotion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-2024-back-to-uni-australia-nz/">Apple&#039;s Back to School Offer Live in Australia and Some Other Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-back-to-school-offer-live-in-australia-and-some-other-countries.2416695/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pre-Ordering the Apple Vision Pro? Get AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;189 to Add Lossless Audio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-airpods-pro-189/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pre-ordering-the-apple-vision-pro-get-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-189-to-add-lossless-audio.2416691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:58:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-airpods-pro-189/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Pre-orders for the Apple Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">begin tomorrow</a>, and if you're planning to use the headset's lossless audio feature you'll need to be sure you have the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C. Luckily, these earbuds are still at their lowest price of all time on Amazon at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/airpods-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931501" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The headlining feature update on this version of the AirPods Pro is the addition of the USB-C port, replacing the Lightning port. Additionally, they feature improved dust resistance and, when paired with the Apple Vision Pro, they <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/apple-vision-pro-lossless-new-airpods-pro-2-only/">support 20-bit 48kHz lossless audio</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-vision-pro-airpods-pro-189/">Pre-Ordering the Apple Vision Pro? Get AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;189 to Add Lossless Audio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pre-ordering-the-apple-vision-pro-get-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-189-to-add-lossless-audio.2416691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reintroduced the HomePod a Year Ago Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-reintroduced-the-homepod-a-year-ago-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reintroduced-the-homepod-a-year-ago-today.2416687/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:36:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-reintroduced-the-homepod-a-year-ago-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple relaunched the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> one year ago today, debuting a second-generation model almost five years after the original model's introduction.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-White-and-Midnight-Feature-Blue-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-881771" /><br/>
The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was announced at WWDC in 2017 and launched in 2018 after a heavily delayed launch. The device was met with mixed reviews; critics praised its outstanding sound quality but pointed out its high price, missing features, and limited functionality compared to rivals.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/04/apple-cuts-homepod-price-worldwide/">dropped its price</a> from &#36;349 to &#36;299 in April 2019 and, in March 2021, the company announced that it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/12/apple-discontinuing-homepod/">discontinuing</a> the first-generation &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, instead shifting its focus to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, which launched the previous year. The decision left a gap in Apple's product lineup for a full-sized smart speaker until the company introduced the second-generation model via a press release on January 18, 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The second-generation &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; looks virtually identical to the original, although it is 0.2 inches shorter and has a larger edge-to-edge LED touchscreen on top. It also boasts a range of upgrades and changes compared to its 2018 predecessor:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; (second-generation, 2023)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; (first-generation, 2018)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Refined design with acoustically transparent mesh fabric</td><br/>
 <td>Design with acoustically transparent mesh fabric</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Larger backlit touch surface that illuminates from edge to edge</td><br/>
 <td>Backlit touch surface</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>S7 chip from 2021's Apple Watch Series 7</td><br/>
 <td>A8 chip from 2013's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6 and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6 Plus</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>U1 ultra wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>–</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Five horn-loaded tweeters</td><br/>
 <td>Seven horn-loaded tweeters</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Four far-field beamforming microphones</td><br/>
 <td>Six far-field beamforming microphones</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6.6 inches tall</td><br/>
 <td>6.8 inches tall</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 5.16 pounds</td><br/>
 <td>Weighs 5.5 pounds</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Removable power cable</td><br/>
 <td>Fixed power cable</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 4 connectivity (802.11n)</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 5 connectivity (802.11ac)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Thread support</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Temperature and humidity sensor</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Sound Recognition</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in White and Midnight</td><br/>
 <td>Available in White and Space Gray</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
While Apple's potential plans for a third-generation &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; are unclear a year after the current model was introduced, there are a multitude of rumors surrounding a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/future-homepod-to-add-curved-lcd-display/">with an LCD touchscreen display</a> arriving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/20/homepod-with-screen-delayed-next-year/">as soon as 2024</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-reintroduced-the-homepod-a-year-ago-today/">Apple Reintroduced the HomePod a Year Ago Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reintroduced-the-homepod-a-year-ago-today.2416687/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Images of Ultra-Rare Apple Watch Band Designed for Sir Jony Ive Surface Online</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/rare-apple-watch-band-designed-for-jony-ive/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/images-of-ultra-rare-apple-watch-band-designed-for-sir-jony-ive-surface-online.2416684/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:12:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/rare-apple-watch-band-designed-for-jony-ive/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Jony Ive</category>
		<category>Prototypes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Images of an Apple Watch band designed to celebrate former Apple design chief Sir Jony Ive's 50th birthday have emerged online, providing a look at what could be one of the rarest official Apple Watch bands ever made. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/jony-ive-50-apple-watch-band.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-931469" /><br/>
The images come from "<a href="https://twitter.com/StellaFudge">Stella Fudge</a>" on X (formerly Twitter), who claims that the unit is one of just ten prototypes made to test the unusual product before the finalized one was given to Ive with a 42mm Ceramic <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-2/">Apple Watch Series 2</a> "Edition" model in February 2017. The Apple Watch band itself is "Cloud" white and features a personalized "J50" monogram engraved on the ceramic pin in silver lettering. Ive departed Apple in June 2019 and now runs an independent design firm called LoveFrom. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Story goes that this unique Cloud Sport Band would&#39;ve originally come with a Ceramic 42mm Series 2 Watch as a gift to Jony Ive for his 50th birthday, hence the &quot;I50&quot; engraved on the pin. Allegedly around 10 or so exist, most are a test batch with the finalized one given to Ive <a href="https://t.co/pfPPfcSRUT">pic.twitter.com/pfPPfcSRUT</a></p>&mdash; Stella - Fudge (@StellaFudge) <a href="https://twitter.com/StellaFudge/status/1747670861501378963?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
While the Sport Band has been a ubiquitous style for the Apple Watch since its introduction in 2014, only some models feature engraved pins, such as the Apple Watch Hermès and Black Unity band. These are invisible when the band is worn on the wrist but provide a subtle indication of the model's special nature to the owner.<br/>
<br/>
The white ceramic &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 2&zwnj; was the first of its kind, expanding to a new gray version with the Series 3. While there was no ceramic Apple Watch Edition for Series 4 models, Apple revived the high-end white ceramic Edition model for the Series 5 in 2019 – the last time we've seen the material used on the device. The ceramic Apple Watch Edition was markedly cheaper than its 24K gold predecessor, but it remains one of the most striking and beloved casings ever offered by Apple.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jony-ive/">Jony Ive</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prototypes/">Prototypes</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/rare-apple-watch-band-designed-for-jony-ive/">Images of Ultra-Rare Apple Watch Band Designed for Sir Jony Ive Surface Online</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/images-of-ultra-rare-apple-watch-band-designed-for-sir-jony-ive-surface-online.2416684/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Updates Website to Highlight Removal of Apple Watch Blood Oxygen Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-website-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-removal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-website-to-highlight-removal-of-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-feature.2416669/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 23:58:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-website-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-removal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/">As expected</a>, Apple has updated its U.S. website to notify customers that the Blood Oxygen feature on the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 is no longer included.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-watch-series-6-blood-oxygen-monitoring-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-759072" /><br/>
Apple has added a banner to the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-watch-series-9/">store webpages</a> related for both devices, and removed all mention of the feature in its <a href="https://www.apple.com/watch/compare/">product comparison tool</a>. The change was spotted by developer <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanMcD8/status/1747864724312670228">Dylan McDonald</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The modified Series 9 and Ultra 2 models without a functional Blood Oxygen app have part numbers ending in LW/A, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
"The ability to measure blood oxygen is no longer available on Apple Watch units sold by Apple in the United States after January 18, 2024," says Apple's website. "These are indicated with part numbers ending in LW/A."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has removed access to the Blood Oxygen feature in the U.S. to allow it to avoid a sales ban on the associated models. The ban was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered</a> by the U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents with the feature, which first appeared on the Series 6 model in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch models sold by Apple will still include the Blood Oxygen app, but when a user opens it, they will be presented with an alert saying that the app is no longer available, and directed to the Health app on the iPhone. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple&#39;s website has now been updated to reflect the lack of Blood Oxygen on Apple Watch Series 9 / Ultra 2. Banner at top of webpage, missing from health features section, and missing from the compare models list. <a href="https://t.co/sAutmMDJJg">pic.twitter.com/sAutmMDJJg</a></p>&mdash;  (@DylanMcD8) <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanMcD8/status/1747864724312670228?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 18, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The Blood Oxygen app still works on previously-sold Series 9 and Ultra 2 models. The feature also remains available on Apple Watch models sold outside the U.S., as the sales ban does not apply internationally. Apple strongly disagrees with the ITC's decision, and its appeal is ongoing.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-website-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-removal/">Apple Updates Website to Highlight Removal of Apple Watch Blood Oxygen Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-updates-website-to-highlight-removal-of-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-feature.2416669/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Special AirPods Pro and More for Year of the Dragon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-pro-year-of-dragon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-special-airpods-pro-and-more-for-year-of-the-dragon.2416659/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 18:44:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-pro-year-of-dragon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In celebration of the upcoming Lunar New Year on February 10, Apple has released limited-edition second-generation AirPods Pro with a Year of the Dragon engraving on its online store in <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/shop/product/MW4F3CH/A">China</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/shop/product/MW4F3ZP/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Hong Kong</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/tw/shop/product/MW4F3TA/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Taiwan</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/sg/shop/product/MW4F3ZA/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Singapore</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/vn/shop/product/MW4F3ZP/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">Vietnam</a>, and Macao. They are also available in <a href="https://www.apple.com/kr/shop/product/MW4F3KH/A/special-edition-airpods-pro">South Korea</a>, where it is the Year of the Blue Dragon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/AirPods-Pro-Year-of-the-Dragon.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931451" /><br/>
The special AirPods Pro have a dragon engraving on the USB-C charging case, and there is a red dragon printed on the box they come in. Otherwise, these AirPods Pro are unchanged in terms of features and pricing compared to the regular ones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has previously offered limited-edition AirPods Pro in some Asian countries for the Year of the Ox, Year of the Tiger, and Year of the Rabbit.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also shared a <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/store">Chinese New Year gift guide</a> in the countries and regions listed above, along with Malaysia. As we previously reported, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">offering limited-time savings</a> on a variety of products in China from January 18 through January 21.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Year-of-the-Dragon-Wallpaper.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931455" /><br/>
From January 18 through February 13, free <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/en/today/collection/create-new-year-magic/">Today at Apple sessions with a Lunar New Year theme</a> will be held in some countries, as spotted by Michael Steeber, who publishes the <a href="https://michaelsteeber.substack.com/">Apple retail newsletter Tabletops</a>. He also noted there are <a href="https://weibo.com/6045623381/4991142772875767">window decals</a> celebrating the Lunar New Year at select Apple Stores in Asia, along with a Year of the Dragon wallpaper available for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac <a href="https://www.apple.com/hk/store">on Apple's website in Hong Kong</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S. and many other countries, Apple is selling <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/accessories/all/new-arrivals?page=1&s=newest">Year of the Dragon accessories</a> from OtterBox and Mophie on its online store, including iPhone cases, an AirTag holder, and a battery pack, as spotted by <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/17/iphone-airtag-year-of-the-dragon/"><em>9to5Mac</em>'s Zac Hall</a>. Apple is also releasing <a href="https://twitter.com/beatsbydre/status/1747807917951373449">limited-edition Beats Solo3 Wireless headphones</a> with a red-and-gold color scheme.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently offered a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/">limited-edition AirTag</a> with a Year of the Dragon engraving in Japan, in celebration of the Japanese New Year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/airpods-pro-year-of-dragon/">Apple Releases Special AirPods Pro and More for Year of the Dragon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-special-airpods-pro-and-more-for-year-of-the-dragon.2416659/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Sell Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen Feature in U.S. Starting Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-sell-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches-without-blood-oxygen-feature-in-u-s-starting-tomorrow.2416657/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 18:12:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models will be sold without the Blood Oxygen feature in the U.S. starting on January 18, according to <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen-sensor/"><em>9to5Mac</em>'s Chance Miller</a>, allowing Apple to avoid a sales ban on these models. On its online store in the U.S., this change will occur starting at 6 a.m. Pacific Time tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-watch-series-6-blood-oxygen-monitoring-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-759072" /><br/>
The report says these Apple Watch models will still include the Blood Oxygen app, but when a user opens it, they will be presented with an alert saying that the app is no longer available, and directed to the Health app on the iPhone. Apple plans to share more details in a support document that will be published on its website.<br/>
<br/>
Apple confirmed that the Blood Oxygen app will remain functional on previously-sold Series 9 and Ultra 2 models. The feature will also remain available on Apple Watch models sold outside the U.S., as the sales ban does not apply internationally.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered an import and sales ban</a> on Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents with the feature, first introduced on the Series 6 model in 2020. Masimo has accused Apple of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/18/apple-masimo-legal-battle/">stealing trade secrets and poaching employees</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The sales ban first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">began last month</a>, but it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">quickly paused</a>, as Apple received an interim stay. Apple was denied a longer-term stay, however, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">ban is set to be reinstated</a> tomorrow starting at 2 p.m. Pacific Time. In a statement, Apple said it disabled the blood oxygen sensing feature on new U.S. models to comply with the ruling and ensure that customers have access to the Apple Watch with limited disruption.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's appeal is ongoing. The company said it strongly disagrees with the ITC's decision, and it feels the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit should reverse it. As a longer-term solution, Apple is reportedly working on changes to the Blood Oxygen app's algorithm in an attempt to avoid Masimo's patented technology. It's unclear when those changes will be ready, or if they will be enough for Apple to avoid patent infringement.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/">Apple to Sell Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches Without Blood Oxygen Feature in U.S. Starting Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-sell-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches-without-blood-oxygen-feature-in-u-s-starting-tomorrow.2416657/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Won&#039;t Offer Apple Vision Pro App at Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-wont-offer-apple-vision-pro-app-at-launch.2416642/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 14:19:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix has no plans to release an app for Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-17/watching-netflix-on-apple-vision-pro-you-ll-have-to-use-the-web"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Instead, the streaming service will be accessible through Safari and other web browsers on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Vision-Pro-Living-Room.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931385" /><br/>
"Our members will be able to enjoy Netflix on the web browser on the Vision Pro, similar to how our members can enjoy Netflix on Macs," a Netflix spokesperson told Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-07-23/apple-vision-pro-will-developers-sell-visionos-apps-for-the-3-499-device-lkfg5b1l">July 2023 edition</a> of his <em>Power On</em> newsletter, Gurman said Netflix would "still let its iPad app run on the headset unmodified," but he now says the streaming service will not offer an app of any kind on the Vision Pro at launch. Apple makes it easy for developers to port their iPadOS apps to visionOS, with over one million apps to be available on the Vision Pro's App Store at launch, but Netflix has evidently opted out.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-streaming-services-and-sports-apps/">various video and sports apps</a> that will be available on the Vision Pro at launch, including Disney+, Discovery+, Max, Amazon Prime Video, Paramount+, Peacock, ESPN, MLB, NBA, and more. There is also MLS Season Pass in the Apple TV app.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro pre-orders begin Friday in the U.S., and the headset launches February 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/">Netflix Won&#039;t Offer Apple Vision Pro App at Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-wont-offer-apple-vision-pro-app-at-launch.2416642/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Sales Ban Reinstated in U.S. Effective Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated-in-u-s-effective-tomorrow.2416628/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 11:41:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's motion to stay an Apple Watch sales ban for the duration of its appeal was denied today by the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit, according to a <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/699619677/Federal-Circuit-Denies-Apple-Motion-to-Stay">court document</a> viewed by <em>MacRumors</em>. Apple's interim stay will be lifted as of January 18 at 2 p.m. Pacific Time, the filing indicates, meaning the sales ban will be reinstated tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
The order means that Apple will once again no longer be able to sell Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing in the U.S., including the Series 9 and Ultra 2. The ban <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">first began last month</a>, but it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">quickly paused</a> after Apple received an interim stay.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. International Trade Commission last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered the import and sales ban</a> after ruling that Apple violated Masimo's pulse oximetry patents with the Apple Watch's blood oxygen sensing feature, first introduced on the Series 6 model in 2020. Masimo has accused Apple of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/18/apple-masimo-legal-battle/">stealing trade secrets and poaching employees</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely sell modified Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-app-removal/">without the Blood Oxygen app</a> in the U.S. to sidestep the sales ban, while it continues to appeal.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple's claim that its redesigned watch does not contain pulse oximetry is a positive step toward accountability," a Masimo spokesperson told <em>MacRumors</em>. "It is especially important that one of the world's largest and most powerful companies respects the intellectual property rights of smaller companies and complies with ITC orders when it is caught infringing."<br/>
<br/>
As a longer-term measure, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-15/apple-to-remove-watch-blood-oxygen-app-to-avoid-ban-masimo-says"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> recently reported that Apple is preparing a software update that would adjust the Blood Oxygen app's algorithms, in an attempt to avoid Masimo's patented technology. It's unclear if this effort will be successful, and the legal battle between Apple and Masimo is likely far from over.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> In a <a href="https://www.masimo.com/company/news/news-media/#Masimo_Announces_Reinstatement_of_Import_Ban_on_Infringing_Apple_Watches">press release</a>, Masimo CEO Joe Kiani shared the following statement in response to Apple's motion for stay being denied.<br/>
<br/>
"The Federal Circuit's decision to lift the temporary stay is a victory for the integrity of the American patent system and the safety of people relying on pulse oximetry," said Kiani. "It affirms that even the largest and most powerful companies must respect the intellectual rights of American inventors and must deal with the consequences when they are caught infringing others' patents."<br/>
<br/>
Masimo said it previously released a study showing that the Apple Watch's blood oxygen sensing feature "missed over 90% of potentially life-threatening events," while touting the effectiveness of its own Masimo W1 health watch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">Apple Watch Sales Ban Reinstated in U.S. Effective Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated-in-u-s-effective-tomorrow.2416628/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
