<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 08:04:30 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M2 Mac Mini on Sale From &#36;499 With Up to &#36;109 in Savings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apples-m2-mac-mini-on-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-mac-mini-on-sale-from-499-with-up-to-109-in-savings.2420062/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:00:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apples-m2-mac-mini-on-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's M2 Mac mini has a few notable discounts today on Amazon, with up to &#36;109 off select versions of the computer. You can get the 256GB M2 Mac mini for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGHGXR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;499.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.00, and no coupon is required to see this deal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/mac-mini-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-887524" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The 512GB M2 Mac mini is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGTPMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;689.99</strong></a> when you clip the on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00. Both of these are solid second-best prices on the Mac mini, and just about &#36;10-&#36;20 higher than the all-time low prices we've tracked in the past.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGHGXR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M2 Mac mini (256GB) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSHGTPMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;109 OFF</div>M2 Mac mini (512GB) for &#36;689.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple updated this Mac mini back in January 2023, marking the first big update to the lineup since the introduction of the M1 models in 2020. The 2023 models feature Apple's M2 and M2 Pro chips, but no major external design changes. As of writing, we aren't tracking any deals on the M2 Pro Mac mini.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apples-m2-mac-mini-on-sale/">Apple&#039;s M2 Mac Mini on Sale From &#36;499 With Up to &#36;109 in Savings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-mac-mini-on-sale-from-499-with-up-to-109-in-savings.2420062/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Mini: All the Rumors So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apples-2024-ipad-mini-all-the-rumors-so-far/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-ipad-mini-all-the-rumors-so-far.2420060/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:44:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apples-2024-ipad-mini-all-the-rumors-so-far&#038;post_date=1708537486/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's seventh-generation iPad mini is rumored to be launching this year, according to multiple sources. Keep reading to learn what the rumors say we can expect from Apple's small form factor tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iPad-Mini-6-YouTubed-2.jpg" alt="" width="2397" height="1348" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-814228" /><br/>
The current iPad mini was released in September 2021, and includes a 8.3-inch display, a USB-C port, a Touch ID power button, an A15 Bionic chip, 5G support on cellular models, a 12-megapixel rear camera, second-generation Apple Pencil support, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="display_changes">Display Changes</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">According to one rumor</a>, the seventh-generation ‌iPad mini‌'s screen assembly will be rotated to reduce the effect of "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">jelly scrolling</a>" that some users complain about with the current model when viewed in portrait orientation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/ipad-mini-9.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-818328" /><br/>
The term refers to a noticeable effect when scrolling vertically through text-based content like a webpage or document, where each line of text appears to tilt down towards the left of the screen as it passes by. The effect makes it look as though one side of the display is responding faster than the other when a finger drags to scroll the page. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says the phenomenon is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">normal behavior for LCD iPads</a>, but based on user feedback, it can appear more obvious and distracting when observed on the ‌‌‌iPad mini‌'s smaller screen‌‌. Apple reportedly plans to rotate the screen assembly to reduce the jelly scrolling effect in portrait orientation, but whether that will merely move the issue to landscape orientation is unknown.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="internal_upgrades">Internal Upgrades</h2><br/>
We are expecting the seventh-generation iPad mini to be updated with a faster chip, likely the A16 Bionic, though the A17 or even an M-series chip is a possibility. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/iphone-15-a16-bionic.jpg" alt="" width="2030" height="1142" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912526" /><br/>
If Apple goes with the A16 Bionic, it will put the ‌iPad mini‌ on par with the iPhone 14 Pro, ‌iPhone 14‌ Pro Max, iPhone 15, and ‌iPhone 15‌ Plus. The chip would deliver around 10% better performance, 50% more GPU memory bandwidth, and a new image processor (ISP) compared to the current model.<br/>
<br/>
The tablet will also likely get support for Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3, two of the latest standards that Apple has been adding to other recent product updates. Apple already added Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 support to the latest iPad Pro, iPhone 15 Pro models, and most new Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="camera_upgrades">Camera Upgrades</h2><br/>
Updated front and rear cameras are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades/">expected to be added</a> to the iPad mini this year. The current ‌iPad mini‌ shares the same cameras found across all current iPad models: A 12-megapixel rear camera with an ƒ/1.8 aperture, and a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide front-facing camera with an ƒ/2.4 aperture. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/ipad-mini-rear-camera.jpg" alt="" width="1300" height="825" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816896" /><br/>
Given that it has been over 850 days since the current iPad mini was released, upgraded cameras are almost certain to be included in the seventh-generation model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_colors">New Colors</h2><br/>
New color options are on the way for the new iPad mini, according to one rumor. The current ‌iPad mini‌ is available in Space Gray, Starlight, Pink, and Purple. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/ipad-mini-6-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="1953" height="1186" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816894" /><br/>
There's no information on what colors Apple could adopt, but it could potentially take inspiration from its ‌standard iPhone 15‌ models, which come in Black, Blue, Green, Yellow, and Pink color options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_not_to_expect_yet">What Not to Expect (Yet)</h2><br/>
<h3 id="120hz_promotion">120Hz ProMotion</h3><br/>
The new seventh-generation iPad mini will not feature a 120Hz ProMotion display, one leaker with alleged supply chain sources <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/ipad-mini-7-no-promotion-display/">has claimed</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/ipad-mini-display.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1153" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816897" /><br/>
Suggestions that Apple could conceivably adopt ProMotion for a next-generation ‌iPad mini‌ began to receive attention when the "jelly scrolling" phenomenon was identified shortly after the iPad mini 6 was released in September 2021.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="oled_display">OLED Display</h3><br/>
After bringing OLED technology to the iPad Pro this year, Apple is rumored to be planning to expand OLED displays to the iPad mini in the future, but not for a couple of years yet. An iPad mini with an OLED display could be introduced in 2026, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/">separate</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-oled-roadmap/">reports</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-screen-colorful.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937314" /><br/>
Apple has apparently not yet fully committed to bringing the more advanced display technology to its mid-range tablets, and may be planning to review how the market responds to the first iPad Pro models that feature OLED displays, which are expected to launch as early as March 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="foldable_ipad_mini">Foldable iPad Mini</h3><br/>
Apple is rumored to be working on a foldable device that's around 7 to 8 inches in size and that could ultimately <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-foldable-2026-could-replace-ipad-mini/">replace Apple's 8.3-inch iPad mini</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/FoldPad-Redux-24-Magenta-and-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934078" /><br/>
Samsung Display and LG Display have reportedly already been sending samples of 7-inch and 8-inch foldable panels to Apple since last year, but Apple is said to be reviewing a launch timeframe for the device between 2026 and 2027.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
Apple plans to update its entire iPad lineup throughout 2024, according to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/all-ipads-expected-to-be-updated-in-2024/">November report</a> by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. However, while iPad Pro and iPad Air models are expected as soon as March, the release of a seventh-generation iPad mini could be a little further away. <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/2024年新款ipad機型與量產時程預測-predictions-for-new-ipad-models-and-production-timeline-in-2024-650a5fc9bbee">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> more recently claimed that the iPad mini 7 is last on Apple's 2024 iPad production roadmap, after its Q1 mass production plans were delayed until the second half of the year. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apples-2024-ipad-mini-all-the-rumors-so-far/">Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Mini: All the Rumors So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-ipad-mini-all-the-rumors-so-far.2420060/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Apple Sports&#039; App Announced With Personalized Scoreboards and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-announced/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-announced-with-personalized-scoreboards-and-more.2420056/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:16:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-announced/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/02/introducing-apple-sports-a-new-app-for-sports-fans/">announced</a> "<a href="https://apple.co/AppleSports">Apple Sports</a>," a new free app that provides real-time statistics, scores, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Sports-App-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1961" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-937385" /><br/>
Apple Sports features a personalized experience with a user's favorite leagues, tournaments, teams shown on an easy-to-read scoreboard. Users can navigate between scores and upcoming games, explore play-by-play information, team statistics, lineup details, and live betting odds, with relevant links to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, and connected streaming services. The app is "designed for speed and simplicity," according to Apple. Apple's senior vice president of Services <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a> said:<blockquote>We created Apple Sports to give sports fans what they want — an app that delivers incredibly fast access to scores and stats. Apple Sports is available for free in the App Store, and makes it easy for users to stay up to date with their favorite teams and leagues.</blockquote>Apple Sports will keep fans up to date on MLS, NBA, NCAA basketball, NHL, Bundesliga, LaLiga, Liga MX, Ligue 1, Premier League, and Serie A. Additional leagues, including MLB, NFL, NCAAF, NWSL, and WNBA, will become available in the app over time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports is <a href="https://apple.co/AppleSports">now available for free</a> in the United States, United Kingdom, and Canada. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-announced/">&#039;Apple Sports&#039; App Announced With Personalized Scoreboards and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-announced-with-personalized-scoreboards-and-more.2420056/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces &#039;Groundbreaking&#039; New Security Protocol for iMessage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-announces-imessage-security-upgrade/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-groundbreaking-new-security-protocol-for-imessage.2420054/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 06:00:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-announces-imessage-security-upgrade/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://security.apple.com/blog/imessage-pq3/">announced</a> a new post-quantum cryptographic protocol for iMessage called PQ3. Apple says this "groundbreaking" and "state-of-the-art" protocol provides "extensive defenses against even highly sophisticated quantum attacks."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
Apple believes the PQ3 protocol's protections "surpass those in all other widely deployed messaging apps," according to its <a href="https://security.apple.com/blog/imessage-pq3/">blog post</a>:<blockquote>Today we are announcing the most significant cryptographic security upgrade in iMessage history with the introduction of PQ3, a groundbreaking post-quantum cryptographic protocol that advances the state of the art of end-to-end secure messaging. With compromise-resilient encryption and extensive defenses against even highly sophisticated quantum attacks, PQ3 is the first messaging protocol to reach what we call Level 3 security — providing protocol protections that surpass those in all other widely deployed messaging apps. To our knowledge, PQ3 has the strongest security properties of any at-scale messaging protocol in the world.</blockquote>PQ3 will be gradually rolling out for supported iMessage conversations starting with iOS 17.4, iPadOS 17.4, macOS 14.4, and watchOS 10.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/ios-17-4-new-features-and-changes/">in March</a>, and it is already in the latest beta versions of these updates, according to Apple. visionOS will not support the PQ3 protocol during the initial rollout, the company confirmed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says PQ3 will fully replace iMessage's existing cryptography protocol within all supported conversations later this year. All devices in an iMessage conversation must be updated to the above software versions or later to be eligible.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Post-Quantum Cryptography</h2><br/>
iMessage already supports end-to-end encryption, but existing cryptographic protocols that are commonly used by messaging apps rely on mathematical problems that could potentially be solved by future quantum computers.<br/>
<br/>
PQ3 is designed to protect users against "Harvest Now, Decrypt Later" attacks, in which malicious actors collect large amounts of encrypted data now and store it in hopes they will be able to decrypt it with a quantum computer in the future:<blockquote>Although such quantum computers don't yet exist, extremely well-resourced attackers can already prepare for their possible arrival by taking advantage of the steep decrease in modern data storage costs. The premise is simple: such attackers can collect large amounts of today's encrypted data and file it all away for future reference. Even though they can't decrypt any of this data today, they can retain it until they acquire a quantum computer that can decrypt it in the future, an attack scenario known as Harvest Now, Decrypt Later.</blockquote>Apple says PQ3 achieves what it calls "Level 3" security, meaning it secures "both the initial key establishment and the ongoing message exchange."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iMessage-PQ3.jpg" alt="" width="1676" height="972" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937379" /><br/>
For deeply technical details about the protocol, read the <a href="https://security.apple.com/blog/imessage-pq3/">Apple Security Research blog post</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-announces-imessage-security-upgrade/">Apple Announces &#039;Groundbreaking&#039; New Security Protocol for iMessage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-groundbreaking-new-security-protocol-for-imessage.2420054/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top 7 Best-Selling Smartphones Last Year Were All iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/iphones-top-7-best-selling-smartphones-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-7-best-selling-smartphones-last-year-were-all-iphones.2420048/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 05:32:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/iphones-top-7-best-selling-smartphones-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Counterpoint</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models dominated the top 10 best-selling smartphones in 2023, with only Samsung's mid-range devices making the list, according to Counterpoint Research's <a href="https://www.counterpointresearch.com/insights/apple-captures-top-7-spots-in-global-top-10-best-selling-smartphones/">Global Monthly Handset Model Sales Tracker</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Share-of-Global-Top-10-Best-selling-Smartphones-2023.jpg" alt="" width="3330" height="2226" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937320" /><br/>
Apple took all top seven positions – a first for the company. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models made up the top three for the series to become the best-selling smartphone of 2023, with the US and China making up half of its sales. The model contributed 19% of the total &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales for 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> came fourth largely thanks to popularity in Japan and India, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models took the fifth, sixth, and seventh slots, with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max the best-selling model in Apple's newest lineup, despite its relatively late launch in September last year. From the tracker report:<br/>
<blockquote>Apple's total sales remained flat in 2023 even as major competitors declined. This stability was partly due to a significant boost from emerging markets like India and the Middle East and Africa (MEA). In 2023, India became the fifth smartphone market to exceed 10 million iPhone unit sales in a single year, highlighting the market's growing importance for Apple. These factors contributed to the iPhone 15 series sales matching the performance of the iPhone 14 series in 2022.</blockquote>Samsung's budget A series devices filled eighth, ninth, and tenth positions, thanks to their strong value proposition, but none of the Korean company's flagship premium Galaxy phones even made the list. <br/>
<br/>
Counterpoint's research backs up previous data from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/apple-top-spot-global-smartphone-shipments/">market research firm IDC</a>, which showed Apple overtook Samsung as the top global smartphone manufacturer in 2023, shipping more phones annually than Samsung for the first time. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/counterpoint/">Counterpoint</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/iphones-top-7-best-selling-smartphones-2023/">Top 7 Best-Selling Smartphones Last Year Were All iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-7-best-selling-smartphones-last-year-were-all-iphones.2420048/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s OLED Roadmap: New iPad Mini, Foldable iPad Pro, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-oled-roadmap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-oled-roadmap-new-ipad-mini-foldable-ipad-pro-and-more.2420046/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 05:29:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-oled-roadmap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 13&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		<category>Foldable iPad</category>
		<category>Omdia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to launch at least nine new devices with OLED displays across the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and MacBook product lines, according to an updated forecast from research firm <a href="https://omdia.tech.informa.com/blogs/2024/feb/apples-new-oled-it-roadmap-can-help-boost-oled-penetration-rate-in-the-mobile-pc-market-to-14-by-2028">Omdia</a> that sets out the company's plans in detail.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/Oled-iPads-and-MackBook-Pro-Notch.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1403" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-824300" /><br/>
As widely rumored, Apple's push to transition to OLED will apparently be jump-started by the release of new 11- and 13-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models this year. The displays will feature 2,388 by 1,668 and 2,880 by 1,920 resolutions, respectively, Omdia claims. This would be a slight increase in height and a reduction in width for the larger model, while the smaller &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; would retain the same resolution.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-oled-roadmap-by-omdia-estimation.png" alt="" width="975" height="717" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-937313" /></div><br/>
In 2026, Apple will launch 8.3-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and 10.8-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models with OLED displays, as well as 14.2-inch and 16.2-inch OLED MacBook Pro models designed to replace the current mini-LED units. The company is also reportedly working on 13.6-inch and 15.3-inch OLED <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models for launch no earlier than 2027. These machines will still lack ProMotion technology with a refresh rate of 60Hz like the current models.<br/>
<br/>
In 2027 or later, Apple may introduce a 20.3-inch foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a> with ProMotion. This product is still said to be in the conceptual stage, but broadly lines up with other rumors about such a device. Overall, the report largely corroborates existing rumors about Apple's upcoming plans to transition almost all of its portable devices to OLED technology.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-ipad/">Foldable iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/omdia/">Omdia</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_13">13" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-oled-roadmap/">Apple&#039;s OLED Roadmap: New iPad Mini, Foldable iPad Pro, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-oled-roadmap-new-ipad-mini-foldable-ipad-pro-and-more.2420046/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Duo That Defrauded Apple Out of 5,000 iPhones With Repair Scheme Could Spend Up to 20 Years in Prison</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-store-repair-scheme-fraud/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/duo-that-defrauded-apple-out-of-5-000-iphones-with-repair-scheme-could-spend-up-to-20-years-in-prison.2420014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:30:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-store-repair-scheme-fraud/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Two Maryland residents that tried to defraud Apple out of 5,000 iPhones worth millions of dollars <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-dc/pr/two-maryland-residents-found-guilty-multimillion-dollar-scheme-defraud-apple-inc-out">were today found guilty</a> of mail fraud. Chinese nationals Haotian Sun and Pengfei Xue masterminded a scheme to get Apple to exchange genuine iPhones for counterfeit iPhones sent in for repair.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912515" /><br/>
Between May 2017 and September 2019, Sun and Xue received shipments of inauthentic iPhones from Hong Kong, using spoofed serial numbers and/or IMEI numbers to return them to Apple retail stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers. <br/>
<br/>
More than 5,000 total iPhones were submitted to Apple during that two year period. <br/>
<br/>
The two have been found guilty of mail fraud and conspiracy to commit mail fraud, and are facing a statutory maximum sentence of 20 years in prison. Sentencing will take place on June 21, 2024.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-store-repair-scheme-fraud/">Duo That Defrauded Apple Out of 5,000 iPhones With Repair Scheme Could Spend Up to 20 Years in Prison</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/duo-that-defrauded-apple-out-of-5-000-iphones-with-repair-scheme-could-spend-up-to-20-years-in-prison.2420014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Supreme Court Refuses to Hear VirnetX Patent Case, Saving Apple &#36;503 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-wins-virnetx-503-million/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/u-s-supreme-court-refuses-to-hear-virnetx-patent-case-saving-apple-503-million.2420013/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:45:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-wins-virnetx-503-million/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>VirnetX</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Supreme Court today said that it will not hear the VirnetX vs. Apple patent case, putting an end to a 14-year-long legal battle and ultimately saving Apple &#36;502.8 million.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/11/virnetx_apple.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="344" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-719205" /><br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/02/20/us-supreme-court-wont-review-apples-win-against-503-million-patent-verdict-.html">CNBC</a></em>, with the Supreme Court not weighing in, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/30/apple-virnetx-successful-patent-appeal/">March 2023 ruling</a> from the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit will stand, so Apple will not have to pay the damages that VirnetX won in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
VirnetX <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/30/apple-virnetx-503-million-patent-infringement/">won a successful jury trial</a> against Apple in 2020 and Apple was found to have violated VirnetX patents with its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> VPN on demand feature. The two patents cited in the case were later invalidated in a separate ruling from the United States Patent and Trademark Office.<br/>
<br/>
After Apple appealed the initial 2020 ruling, it was able to point to the invalidation of the patents and get the initial award vacated by the federal appeals court. VirnetX attempted to escalate the patent invalidation case to the Supreme Court, but has been denied.<br/>
<br/>
VirnetX is viewed as a patent holding company or "patent troll" that does not offer actual products or services. It generates revenue by suing technology companies that infringe on or license its patents.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple will not have to pay the &#36;503 million from this particular trial, Apple did have to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/01/15/virnetx-wins-440-million-from-apple/">shell out &#36;440 million</a> in 2019 for violating VirnetX's communications security patents with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and iMessage.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/virnetx/">VirnetX</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-wins-virnetx-503-million/">U.S. Supreme Court Refuses to Hear VirnetX Patent Case, Saving Apple &#36;503 Million</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/u-s-supreme-court-refuses-to-hear-virnetx-patent-case-saving-apple-503-million.2420013/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Masters of the Air&#039; Sees Most Watched Apple TV+ Launch to Date</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/masters-of-the-air-launch-record/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/masters-of-the-air-sees-most-watched-apple-tv-launch-to-date.2420010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:05:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/masters-of-the-air-launch-record/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> series Masters of the Air had more viewers in its opening weekend than any other &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; show has had in its first season, Apple told <em><a href="https://variety.com/2024/tv/news/masters-of-the-air-premiere-ratings-apple-tv-plus-1235916408/">Variety</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/masters-of-the-air.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937279" /><br/>
Apple did not provide details on the exact number of viewers, but the show beat out popular &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; offerings like The Morning Show and Severance. Masters of the Air features the 100th Bomb Group that performed dangerous aviation raids in Nazi Germany.<br/>
<br/>
After the premiere of Masters of the Air, viewership across &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; grew 65 percent worldwide compared to the prior seven-day period, plus Apple maintained double-digit growth across more than 100 territories.<br/>
<br/>
Masters of the Air was a highly anticipated show that was created as a companion series to Band of Brothers and The Pacific, both of which were popular when they debuted, so it had a built-in audience. The show is executive produced by Steven Spielberg and Tom Hanks, who also worked on the prior shows.<br/>
<br/>
Masters of the Air debuted on January 26, and episodes are being released weekly. The finale is set to air on Friday, March 15.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/masters-of-the-air-launch-record/">&#039;Masters of the Air&#039; Sees Most Watched Apple TV+ Launch to Date</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/masters-of-the-air-sees-most-watched-apple-tv-launch-to-date.2420010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Upcoming OLED iPad Pro Models Rumored to Be Much Thinner</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-models-rumored-to-be-much-thinner.2420001/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:39:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to update the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> lineups as soon as March, and the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will be significantly thinner according to dimensions shared by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/02/20/larger-ipad-air-thinner-ipad-pro/">9to5Mac</a></em>. Citing sources with knowledge of Apple's plans, the site claims that the larger version will be more than 1mm thinner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/iPad-Pro-OLED-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853666" /><br/>
The current 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; measures in at 6.4mm thick, but the new model is said to be 5mm thick. As for the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, it is currently 5.9mm thick, while the updated version is said to be 5.1mm thick. Both tablets may also be slightly bigger in size.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Current 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 247.6mm x 178.5mm x 5.9 mm</li><br/>
 	<li>Upcoming 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 249.7mm x 177.5mm x 5.1mm</li></ul><br/>
 	<br/>
<ul><li>Current 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 280.6mm x 214.9mm x 6.4mm</li><br/>
 	<li>Upcoming 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 281.5mm x 215.5mm x 5.0mm</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Such a slimmed down body suggests a notable design change, which is enabled by an even more significant update -- OLED display technology. OLED display panels are thinner than LCD panels, allowing Apple to cut down on the thickness of its tablets.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, Apple is expected to introduce two new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models, including a larger 12.9-inch version for the first time. The larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be almost the same size as the current &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, measuring in at 280.6mm by 214.9mm by 6mm.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is limiting OLED display technology to the Pro lineup, so while the 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be similar in length and width to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, it will be thicker because it will continue to feature an LCD display.<br/>
<br/>
All of the new iPads are expected to have Apple's M3 chip technology, which was first introduced last year in updated MacBook Pro models. We haven't heard specifics about an event, but we are expecting something in late March to early April.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/">Apple&#039;s Upcoming OLED iPad Pro Models Rumored to Be Much Thinner</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-models-rumored-to-be-much-thinner.2420001/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Increases iPhone 15&#039;s Advertised Battery Lifespan</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-raises-iphone-15-advertised-battery-lifespan/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-increases-iphone-15s-advertised-battery-lifespan.2419999/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:31:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-raises-iphone-15-advertised-battery-lifespan/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that it retested the batteries in all iPhone 15 models and determined that they are able to meet a higher bar.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911429" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106348">support document</a> updated today, Apple says the batteries in the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max are designed to retain 80% of their original capacity at 1,000 complete charge cycles under ideal conditions, compared to the 500 charge cycles it advertises for all older iPhone models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple told <em>MacRumors</em> that its latest testing for iPhone 15 models involved charging and discharging the battery 1,000 times under specific conditions, but it did not provide any exact details about the process. Apple added that it has continually made improvements to iPhone battery components and its power management system.<br/>
<br/>
This revelation means that it could take longer for the maximum battery capacity of iPhone 15 models to decline to 80% compared to previous iPhone models. However, Apple said it is "investigating" the battery lifespans of older iPhone models, so a comparison based on the latest testing parameters remains to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
In its support document, Apple says the battery lifespan of any iPhone model ultimately depends on how the device is regularly used and charged.<br/>
<br/>
To view an iPhone's battery capacity, open the Settings app and tap Battery → Battery Health & Charging. On iPhone 15 models updated to the latest iOS 17.4 beta, the menu is now simply called Battery Health and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-iphone-15-battery/">shows more info at a glance</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This news was <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/02/20/iphone-15-battery-lifescyle-span/">first reported by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-raises-iphone-15-advertised-battery-lifespan/">Apple Increases iPhone 15&#039;s Advertised Battery Lifespan</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-increases-iphone-15s-advertised-battery-lifespan.2419999/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Acoustics VP Leaves Role, AirPods and HomePod Audio Team Gets New Leadership</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-acoustics-vp-leaves-role/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acoustics-vp-leaves-role-airpods-and-homepod-audio-team-gets-new-leadership.2419988/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 11:52:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-acoustics-vp-leaves-role/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The team responsible for audio at Apple will soon undergo leadership changes due to the departure of longtime acoustics vice president Gary Geaves, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-20/apple-shuffles-leadership-of-team-responsible-for-audio-products">Bloomberg</a></em>. Geaves is stepping down from his role, though he will be replaced with "top deputy" Ruchir Davé.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/airpods-january.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931748" /><br/>
Apple's acoustics group has approximately 300 members that have developed audio technology for the AirPods, HomePods, and other Apple devices. The team was responsible for creating spatial audio, the 3D sound feature that has been built into AirPods, the Vision Pro, and other devices.<br/>
<br/>
AirPods product designer Tang Tan was overseeing the acoustic team under John Ternus, but he started preparing to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/another-apple-designer-to-work-on-openai-hardware/">leave Apple</a> back in December. Since then, the acoustics team has been reporting to Matt Costello, who oversees the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and Beats headphones.<br/>
<br/>
Geaves joined Apple in 2011 from Bowers &amp; Wilkins, and <em>Bloomberg</em> says he will be staying on at Apple as an advisor to Costello as he prepares to retire. Over the course of the last two years, Geaves has been working on an overhaul to the AirPods lineup, and the first updates are expected this year.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest we will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/airpods-4-new-design/">see AirPods 4</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/new-airpods-later-this-year-rumor/">new AirPods Max</a> this year, with revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-pro-3/">to follow in 2025</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-acoustics-vp-leaves-role/">Apple Acoustics VP Leaves Role, AirPods and HomePod Audio Team Gets New Leadership</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acoustics-vp-leaves-role-airpods-and-homepod-audio-team-gets-new-leadership.2419988/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Lets You See Your iPhone 15 Battery Health at a Glance</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-iphone-15-battery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-lets-you-see-your-iphone-15-battery-health-at-a-glance.2419984/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 11:26:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-iphone-15-battery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iOS 17.4, Apple is tweaking how battery health is reported to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> users, making it easier for them to understand their battery status at a glance.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ios-17-4-battery-health-optimization-iphone-15.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937223" /><br/>
In the Battery section of the Settings app, the Battery Health listing now has a readout such as "Normal" that is accessible without tapping in to the prior "Battery Health & Charging" section.<br/>
<br/>
If you tap on the battery health readout on an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, the battery cycle count, manufacture date, and first use will be listed. This information was previously hidden in the General > About section of the Settings app. <br/>
<br/>
The Charging Optimization section continues to provide the same settings. Optimized Battery Charging preserves battery health by learning usage habits and limiting the amount of time that the battery sits at a 100 percent charge. There is also an option to limit charging to 80 percent to further preserve health, and a toggle for turning off optimized charging all together.<br/>
<br/>
Note that these changes are limited to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. Battery settings have not changed on older <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-iphone-15-battery/">iOS 17.4 Lets You See Your iPhone 15 Battery Health at a Glance</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-lets-you-see-your-iphone-15-battery-health-at-a-glance.2419984/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Beta Adds CarPlay Option to Show Upcoming Maneuvers in Instrument Cluster</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-beta-carplay-instrument-cluster/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-adds-carplay-option-to-show-upcoming-maneuvers-in-instrument-cluster.2419982/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:47:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-beta-carplay-instrument-cluster/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The fourth beta of iOS 17.4 that Apple released today adds a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> feature, according to the notes that Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/ios-ipados-release-notes/ios-ipados-17_4-release-notes">provided to developers</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908367" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/volvo-s60-drivers-apple-maps.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
In supported &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; vehicles, there's now an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> option to show information about upcoming maneuvers in the instrument cluster. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; users will be able to swap the display type between the main and instrument cluster by tapping on the map configuration button located in the upper right of the main Maps screen.<br/>
<br/>
Apple this year introduced a new next-generation &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; experience that will show up in high-end vehicles starting in 2024, but this feature addition is separate from that.<br/>
<br/>
It appears this new experience will be available in vehicles that support a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/volvo-dual-screen-apple-maps-carplay/">dual-screen Apple Maps CarPlay experience</a>, with a supplementary &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; view that's located in the driver display or head-up display. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; began supporting this functionality several years ago, but manufacturers have been slow to adopt it with BMW, Volvo, and Polestar being among the first on select vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
While those vehicles have supported an &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; view in the driver display, they have not shown text prompts such as upcoming turns or lane guidance, so it appears today's addition will give users some control about what information appears where.<br/>
<br/>
With the iOS 17.4 update, the driver display will optionally display turn-by-turn directions so that &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; users can navigate without having to look away from the display directly in front of them.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 is limited to developers and public beta testers at this time, but it will see a public release in March.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-beta-carplay-instrument-cluster/">iOS 17.4 Beta Adds CarPlay Option to Show Upcoming Maneuvers in Instrument Cluster</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-adds-carplay-option-to-show-upcoming-maneuvers-in-instrument-cluster.2419982/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third Beta of visionOS 1.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-1.2419977/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:14:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1 update for developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The third beta comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/visionos-1-1-beta-2/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 brings support for iMessage Contact Key Verification and it adds Apple device management to the Vision Pro. With this functionality, IT departments at companies and educational institutions can manage Vision Pro headsets in the same way they manage iPhones, iPads, and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's beta notes, users can now reposition volumetric scenes closer than before, enabling easier direct interaction with the volumetric scene content. That means objects can be placed closer to you.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also improved Personas in &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1, making them look more natural and lifelike than before. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-1/">Apple Releases Third Beta of visionOS 1.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-1.2419977/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2419972/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:08:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth betas of upcoming iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to developers for testing purposes, with the updates coming one week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/ios-17-4-beta-3/">Apple seeded the third betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932463" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. A free or paid <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 introduces sweeping changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps operate in the European Union, paving the way for alternative app marketplaces, alternative payment systems, third-party browser engine support, and NFC access for banks and third-party payment providers. These features are limited to the EU, and won't be available in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
There are, however, changes to gaming apps, and with the launch of iOS 17.4, Apple will be allowing cloud gaming apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW. Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
Along with these updates, iOS 17.4 adds new emoji characters, transcripts for podcasts in the Podcasts app, support for using SharePlay with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, Stopwatch Live Activities, and more. Full details on everything new in iOS 17.4 can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-beta-features/">our iOS 17.4 features guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2419972/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.4 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-4-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2419971/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:07:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-3/">release of the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 introduces some of the features in the iOS 17.4 beta, such as new emoji characters. We don't know what Mac-specific features are included, and little else was found in the first three betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-4/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.4 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-4-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2419971/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of watchOS 10.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-4-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-watchos-10-4-to-developers.2419976/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:06:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-4-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/watchos-10-4-beta-3/">release of the third watchOS 10.4 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.4‌ update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.4 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.4 includes new emoji characters such as a lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
There is also a Setting to disable the Double Tap feature on Apple Watch when using Vision Pro, as the Double Tap gestures might be accidentally activated when controlling Vision Pro.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-4-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of watchOS 10.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-watchos-10-4-to-developers.2419976/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of tvOS 17.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-tvos-17-4-to-developers.2419975/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:05:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-beta-3/">release of the third tvOS 17.4 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.4 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes.<br/>
<br/>
The tvOS 17.4 update adds support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> SharePlay on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;. The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; user can pull up an &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; QR code that can be scanned by anyone, which then allows multiple people to contribute to what's playing via &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;. An &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscription is not required.<br/>
<br/>
We've also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/tvos-17-4-homeos-mention/">seen references to homeOS</a> in tvOS 17.4, but it's not yet clear what homeOS is.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 17.4 is expected to see a release in March alongside iOS 17.4.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-4-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of tvOS 17.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-tvos-17-4-to-developers.2419975/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Models Again Rumored to Feature Upgraded Microphones for iOS 18&#039;s Revamped Siri</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/iphone-16-upgraded-microphones-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-models-again-rumored-to-feature-upgraded-microphones-for-ios-18s-revamped-siri.2419966/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:38:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/iphone-16-upgraded-microphones-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone 16 models will feature upgraded microphones with a higher signal-to-noise ratio compared to previous models, allowing for the devices to hear your voice more clearly, according to Haitong analyst Jeff Pu. This upgrade should improve the accuracy of Siri, which is expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">revamped with generative AI features on iOS 18</a> later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-18-Mock-iPhone-16-Feature-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936483" /><br/>
In a research note earlier this month, Pu said some of iOS 18's generative AI features will likely be limited to iPhone 16 models, as a result of the upgraded microphones and a larger Neural Engine in the A18 and A18 Pro chips for the devices. Both of these hardware changes have been rumored by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/">other</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">sources</a>, increasing their likelihood.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/">previously said</a> the upgraded microphones on iPhone 16 models could "improve the Siri experience significantly." In addition to a higher signal-to-noise ratio, he said the new microphones will offer improved water resistance.<br/>
<br/>
On an earnings call earlier this month, Apple CEO Tim Cook confirmed that the company was working on generative AI and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">will share details "later this year."</a> In addition to Siri, iOS 18 is rumored to add new generative AI capabilities to Spotlight, Shortcuts, Messages, Apple Music, Numbers, Pages, Keynote, Health, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce iOS 18 at WWDC in June, and the update should be released to all users in September alongside the iPhone 16 series.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/iphone-16-upgraded-microphones-rumor/">iPhone 16 Models Again Rumored to Feature Upgraded Microphones for iOS 18&#039;s Revamped Siri</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-models-again-rumored-to-feature-upgraded-microphones-for-ios-18s-revamped-siri.2419966/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
