<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:02:47 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube Music Integration May Be Coming to HomePod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/youtube-music-homepod-integration/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-music-integration-may-be-coming-to-homepod.2401097/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 17:15:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/youtube-music-homepod-integration/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube Music may soon be available directly on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> integration, according to code hidden in the YouTube Music app that was discovered by software miner <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">@aaronp613</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/youtube-music-logo.png" alt="" width="1200" height="626" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910085" /><br/>
There is a section in the YouTube Music app that is labeled "Connect With &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;," which suggests that integration could be coming at some point in the future. Apple has supported a handful of third-party music services on &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; for the last couple of years, so this functionality is already available with Pandora, iHeartRadio, Deezer, and TuneIn Radio.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">YouTube Music is working on adding HomePod support! <a href="https://t.co/71KzB0UsZA">pic.twitter.com/71KzB0UsZA</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1701388774985392351?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 12, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Music services like Spotify have not adopted this option even though Apple made the SiriKit Media feature available in iOS 14, so it remains limited in scope. With the direct play function, users can set a third-party service as a default music option, and when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; is asked to play content, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will play music from the selected service.<br/>
<br/>
If YouTube Music does indeed add support for playing music directly on the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, it could make the streaming service more appealing to Apple users.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/youtube-music-homepod-integration/">YouTube Music Integration May Be Coming to HomePod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-music-integration-may-be-coming-to-homepod.2401097/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Likely to Feature Up to 8GB RAM, 1TB Storage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-ram-and-storage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-likely-to-feature-up-to-8gb-ram-1tb-storage.2401077/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 11:44:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-ram-and-storage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past few months, we've heard multiple claims about the storage and RAM of the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, with seemingly contradictory information.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/iPhone-15-Pro-Colors-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907572" /><br/>
<i>MacRumors</i> has now confirmed that Apple tested the following storage configurations for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>128 GB</li><br/>
 	<li>256 GB</li><br/>
 	<li>512 GB</li><br/>
 	<li>1 TB</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
For the storage options, Apple is using NAND from a few different vendors:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>SK Hynix</li><br/>
 	<li>Western Digital</li><br/>
 	<li>Kioxia</li><br/>
 	<li>Samsung</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Though there were rumors of a 2TB storage configuration from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/07/iphone-15-pro-2tb-storage-option/">Naver user Yeux1122</a>, <em>MacRumors</em> has seen no evidence that it was considered. A <a href="https://weibo.com/5601796159/4931807738593495">Weibo leak</a> also suggested that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; would start out with 256GB of storage, but that appears to be incorrect as well. Storage options will align with the storage tiers of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a>, according to our findings. <br/>
<br/>
As for RAM, <i>MacRumors</i> has learned that Apple plans to use LPDDR5 DRAM for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, the same RAM type found in last year's flagship devices. Two RAM configurations were tested -- 6GB and 8GB, with the RAM supplied by the following companies:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Samsung</li><br/>
 	<li>Micron</li><br/>
 	<li>SK Hynix</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
It is currently unclear which of these two RAM configurations Apple chose for the final mass production units. One possible explanation is that the RAM will vary depending on the storage capacity of the phone, with higher storage capacity models receiving 8GB of RAM rather than 6GB. According to a recent report from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/iphone-15-pro-128gb-storage-8gb-ram-trendforce/">TrendForce</a>, Apple will offer 8GB on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, so it's possible that the 6GB configuration has been scrapped.<br/>
<br/>
Apart from RAM, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; will use an upgraded A17 SoC built using TSMC's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> manufacturing process. The A17 is expected to feature an additional GPU core, allowing for better graphics performance. Additionally, the performance cores will feature an increased clock speed of 3.70 GHz, up from the from the 3.46 GHz of the A16.<br/>
<br/>
Other improvements expected for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; include an all-new titanium frame, USB-C, and a periscope zoom lens on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-ram-and-storage/">iPhone 15 Pro Likely to Feature Up to 8GB RAM, 1TB Storage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-likely-to-feature-up-to-8gb-ram-1tb-storage.2401077/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Reliefband Flex Attaches to Your Apple Watch to Quell Motion Sickness</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/reliefband-flex-for-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-reliefband-flex-attaches-to-your-apple-watch-to-quell-motion-sickness.2401073/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 11:25:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/reliefband-flex-for-apple-watch&#038;post_date=1694467537/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The &#36;180 <a href="https://www.reliefband.com/collections/reliefband/products/reliefband-flex">Reliefband Flex</a> is an anti-nausea accessory that is designed to attach to an Apple Watch, allowing for a single wrist-worn device that is able to cut down on or eliminate motion sickness, migraine nausea, pregnancy nausea, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-flex.jpg" alt="" width="1693" height="952" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910043" /><br/>
You might be wondering what an anti-nausea device has to do with Apple, but many VR headsets cause motion sickness in people who are prone to feeling ill from motion, and Apple's own VR headset is set to launch in the not too distant future. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> won't be coming until 2024, so it's not yet clear if it will cause the same motion sickness in vulnerable people that other headsets cause, but if it does, the Reliefband might be a solution for some.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-components.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910049" /><br/>
I am prone to motion sickness, so I thought I'd give the Reliefband a try. I get ill from car rides, 3D rides (and sometimes movies), VR headsets, boats, and first-person shooter video games - basically anything where my brain gets signals that I'm moving while my body is stationary. I've always had this problem, so I'm familiar with various treatments.<br/>
<br/>
The Reliefband uses electrical pulses targeted at the underside of the wrist. It targets the median nerve in the wrist, and the pulses stimulate the nerve to interrupt nausea signals traveling to the brain. There are several similar products on the market, and there <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/001650859290305I">have been studies</a> that suggest this kind of acustimulation is effective for nausea, but there have also been studies that <a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/15018290/">suggest it is not</a>, so keep that in mind here.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910050" /><br/>
The Reliefband Flex that I tested looks like a medical device. It's not at all sleek, and in fact, it's bulky on my small wrist. It's made from a plastic material with a button and pulse level indicators on the front and two metal plates on the back. It has watch straps and can be worn alone with a nylon band, but it is also designed to attach to an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-on-wrist.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910051" /><br/>
Reliefband provides a special band that attaches to both the Apple Watch and the Reliefband hardware, so the Apple Watch goes on the top of the wrist and the Reliefband goes at the underside of the wrist. With this setup, you don't have to wear a device on both wrists if you need the benefits of the Reliefband.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-side-close-up-bulk.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910054" /><br/>
I have small wrists so there's not a lot of space between the Apple Watch and the Reliefband, and it's not the most comfortable setup, but it can be better than having two separate devices. The band that Reliefband provides is reasonably comfortable, and it reminds me of Apple's woven bands, but again, there's a lot of bulk on a small wrist with the dual-band setup. The band is made of a soft velcro-like material with velcro fasteners to size it. The Flex version uses replaceable batteries, so it does not need to be charged. Batteries need to be swapped at around the year mark, though that varies based on usage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="3490" height="1963" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910052" /><br/>
To get the Reliefband to work properly, it needs to be precisely positioned. It has to go a half inch or so above the crease of the wrist, and it needs to be in the middle of the wrist. When it's turned on and in the proper spot, the pulses are felt in the palm and the middle finger. To use the Reliefband, conductivity gel is required, and a small tube comes with the device. The gel needs to be applied before use and also refreshed if it wears off because it makes the pulsing less uncomfortable and more effective.<br/>
<br/>
There are five levels of power with the Reliefband Flex, and the idea is to set it on the lowest level that you need to address nausea. To me, it feels a little bit like getting a small shock. I did not find levels 1-3 to be too painful, but levels four and five really get my attention. With the lower levels, the pulsing can kind of fade into the background, and I think on someone with a larger wrist, the higher levels would too.<br/>
<br/>
So does it work? For me, yes and no. I experimented with the Reliefband several times, in the car, when I had nausea from a migraine, playing a first-person video game, and using an Oculus, which always makes me ill. If I put the Reliefband on before I anticipated getting motion sick, it kept it at bay. Putting it on when I was already feeling nauseous did not work as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reliefband-side-view.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910053" /><br/>
I think part of the reason for that was because I didn't like setting the power above a level three, and I needed a higher power to distract from the nausea. I did meet with the Reliefband team, and they said that it's common for people to need some customization and help with optimal settings. They advised me to use extra conductivity gel to make more of a barrier between the band and my skin, which did help, and they also helped me figure out that I could kick it up to a 4 or 5 for a short period of time and then drop it back down. Their customer service team is accustomed to helping people troubleshoot.<br/>
<br/>
If you look up the Reliefband, you'll see a lot of comments about how it works, plus a lot of comments about how it's snake oil or a placebo. In my experience it wasn't perfect, but it did help with my motion sickness on several occasions, and it's something I plan to try again if Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset causes me to become motion sick when I use it.<br/>
<br/>
When I'm in a situation where I know I am going to have intensive motion sickness over multiple days, I get a prescription patch with scopolamine. Day to day, I have used the acupressure bands with the plastic nubs that dig into the wrist, taken high-dose ginger pills (my preferred anti-nausea option), used benadryl, taken dramamine, and more, so I am used to trying all kinds of unusual things. I don't care for dramamine and benadryl so it is nice to have a more functional alternative when the ginger pills are unavailable or aren't working.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
I don't know that the Reliefband Flex is going to work for everyone, but if you have the kind of intense motion sickness that I do, you're probably willing to experiment.<br/>
<br/>
The &#36;180 price on the Reliefband seems high for the all-plastic build and the clunky design, and it's definitely expensive enough that it will put off some buyers. There is a 14-day return policy, so there is an option to test it out just for the cost of shipping, and it can also be bought on Amazon for a simpler return process.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Reliefband Flex can be <a href="https://www.reliefband.com/collections/reliefband/products/reliefband-flex">purchased from the Reliefband website</a> for &#36;180.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/reliefband-flex-for-apple-watch/">Review: Reliefband Flex Attaches to Your Apple Watch to Quell Motion Sickness</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-reliefband-flex-attaches-to-your-apple-watch-to-quell-motion-sickness.2401073/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Samsung&#039;s Smart Monitor M8 Drops to &#36;549.99 (Up to &#36;120 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-samsung-monitor-m8-549/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-drops-to-549-99-up-to-120-off.2401070/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 10:47:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-samsung-monitor-m8-549/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has record low prices on the new Smart Monitor M8 today as part of its <a href="https://howl.me/cky3K0zuwFG">"Discover Samsung" fall sale</a>. Both the 27-inch and 32-inch versions of the Smart Monitor M8 are available at record low prices during this event. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/samsung-m8-2023-update.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897017" /><br/>
<br/>
The 27-inch model has hit <a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4WFFxpJ"><strong>&#36;549.99</strong></a> (&#36;100 off) and the 32-inch model has hit <a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4hg4R0B"><strong>&#36;579.99</strong></a> (&#36;120 off), and both have multiple colors available on sale. The Discover Samsung sale is set to end later in the week, so be sure to <a href="https://howl.me/cky3K0zuwFG">check out Samsung's website</a> for even more discounts on other monitors, storage accessories, and smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4WFFxpJ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>27-Inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckxO4hg4R0B"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>32-Inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;579.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Regarding the 32-inch model, the last time we tracked a sale on that monitor was the first week of August, and it was only at &#36;100 off. This makes Samsung's new deal the best discounted price we've seen to date. Samsung launched this refreshed version of the Smart Monitor M8 back in June, including updates like HDR10+ support and a portrait orientation option.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-samsung-monitor-m8-549/">Deals: Samsung&#039;s Smart Monitor M8 Drops to &#36;549.99 (Up to &#36;120 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-samsungs-smart-monitor-m8-drops-to-549-99-up-to-120-off.2401070/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Nanoleaf 4D Adds Easy Content-Synced Backlighting to Your TV or Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-4d-camera-and-light-strip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-nanoleaf-4d-adds-easy-content-synced-backlighting-to-your-tv-or-display.2401068/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 10:38:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-4d-camera-and-light-strip&#038;post_date=1694464694/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://nanoleaf.me/">Nanoleaf</a> in June launched the <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/nanoleaf-4d/">Nanoleaf 4D Screen Mirror and Lightstrip Kit</a>, which is an LED gradient light strip designed to go behind a television set. It uses a camera to detect what's on the screen, matching the colors of the light strip to the content on the TV.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901709" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/nanoleaf-4d-kit.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
The light strip comes in two sizes, one that fits TVs and monitors up to 65 inches and one that fits TVs up to 85 inches. Either one can be cut to the ideal size for the TV or computer monitor that it's being used with. I tested with an 85-inch TV, so I didn't need to do any trimming, and in terms of size, the light strip was able to wrap almost the entire way around the TV.<br/>
<br/>
There are 10 color zones per meter, so the light strip can display several different colors at once, and like other LED light strips on the market, it supports more than 16 million colors. Nanoleaf designed the light strips specifically for TV sets and monitors, and these are meant to be used for backlighting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-components.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910023" /><br/>
A camera attaches to the top of the TV with a mounting stand or it can be positioned at the bottom of the screen, and the colors detected by the camera are relayed to the light strip so that it can match what's displayed. Both the light strip and the camera attach to a controller unit that itself plugs into a power outlet.<br/>
<br/>
Because of the way my TV is mounted, I have a small power strip at the back of it where I plugged in the light. I used adhesive to attach the controller, so all of the cords are hidden behind the TV. The design of the light does facilitate a setup where all of the cords can be hidden, but you will need some strong adhesive. The controller unit has options to turn on the lighting effect, so you might want to place it in a reachable location unless you're able to always use the app for control purposes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-lightstrip-attached.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910024" /><br/>
So far, the adhesive on the light strip has kept it up on my TV, but there are a couple corners where it's coming loose. Nanoleaf included some corner mounting hardware to route the 4D Lightstrip around corners, but the exterior design of my Sony TV didn't work with the hardware. I had to use the light strip alone, and I didn't have a good way to do the corners so they're always going to be angled in an odd way.<br/>
<br/>
The main feature of the Nanoleaf 4D is the setup's ability to mirror the colors on the display to the LEDs on the light strip so the backlighting matches the TV content. There are HDMI boxes like the Hue Sync that do this, but with Nanoleaf's method, you don't need to have everything plugged into a central box and there are no limitations like no support for HDMI 2.1.<br/>
<br/>
Backlighting that matches the content on a TV set or display adds to the immersiveness of what's being viewed, and it's a fun addition to a home theater or gaming setup. Not having to route accessories like my consoles and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> through a secondary box is a major plus of the method that Nanoleaf is using to get this effect.<br/>
<br/>
It's a little odd to have a camera at the top of the TV, but it blends into the background quickly enough and I don't notice it now. Nanoleaf included a privacy cover for the camera for when it's not in use, but the camera does not capture content and is only used to relay color to the light strip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-camera.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910025" /><br/>
Nanoleaf has four "Mirror Modes" that affect the intensity of the light and the frequency of the color changes. There's 1D, 2D, 3D, and 4D. 1D is a plain white lighting effect, 2D is a single color that matches one of the colors on the screen, 3D is multiple colors, and 4D is similar to 3D, but the colors shift more often. I prefer 2D or 3D mode over 4D, which can be a little too distracting. My partner, who does not care for behind-the-TV lighting, did not have a problem with 1D or 2D mode. I definitely appreciate Nanoleaf providing options, because it ensures the Lightstrip can suit a wide range of tastes.<br/>
<br/>
There are two modes to control the saturation of the color. Cinematic is more subtle, while vivid is more saturated. For movie content, I prefer Cinematic, while games work well with Vivid, but there's also an option to choose your own settings for saturation, dynamic range, and white balance. A rhythm mode can be enabled to time the colors to the sound coming from the TV, but the colors change so frequently that I wouldn't recommend this mode if you're actually watching the TV. It's nice for if you have music on in the background and want matching ambient lighting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-subtle.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910026" /><br/>
To match the colors of the light with the appropriate part of the TV content, there is a calibration process done through the Nanoleaf app. You mark each corner of the Nanoleaf Lightstrip once it's been applied to the TV, and then you use the camera view to adjust what the camera can see. You need to make sure it only has a view of the TV and not anything in the surrounding area, because this will determine the colors you get.<br/>
<br/>
The size of my TV (or maybe the position) seemed to be an issue for the camera and I wasn't able to get it to align accurately with each corner. I had to cut off a bit of the bottom corner, but I'm not sure how much of an impact this has on the colors that are displayed.<br/>
<br/>
Color vibrancy will depend on the saturation of your TV, the lighting in the room, and what's behind the TV. If you have your TV a foot or two in front of a blank wall with a high-quality TV, you'll see bright, vivid colors depending on the content that you're playing. My TV is mounted above a brick fireplace with shelving on either side so I don't have the most ideal setup for a light strip, but even in this scenario, it throws off a lot of light and casts color over much of the area behind the TV.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910027" /><br/>
A lot of TV shows and movies have subtler colors than you might imagine, so colors are not always super saturated and bright even in 4D mode. For black shades, the Nanoleaf seems to default to red, which does not always match, and I also seem to get a lot of green when there doesn't seem to be much green on the screen. Sometimes the camera is also choosing a dominant color like white instead of an accent color like blue or green, which would look better with the scene, so there may be some work to do on whatever algorithm Nanoleaf is using.<br/>
<br/>
I thought there might be some lag between what the camera picks up and the colors that are relayed on screen, but the 4D setup seems to be quick at shifting colors. The colors match and blend with the background for the most part rather than becoming distracting, and that's especially true of the more subdued modes.<br/>
<br/>
I think the camera method works well overall and I've enjoyed the Lightstrip's color effects as a person who likes TV backlighting, but where something like the Hue Sync might have an edge is the color interpretation. The Sync Box is pulling color from video signal instead of using a camera and I feel that it gives me a more vibrant overall look, but it's hard to compare because they are two different lighting systems.<br/>
<br/>
Like the Philips Hue setup, you can pair other Nanoleaf lights to the Nanoleaf 4D kit. If you have Nanoleaf Light Panels, bulbs, or light strips around your TV area or in your gaming setup, all of those will also automatically sync with the colors being picked up by the 4D Camera. There is a calibration process where you can choose where each light is in the room for the best color syncing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-colors-light.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910028" /><br/>
Being able to sync Light Panels and bulbs to the Nanoleaf 4D is great for gaming, but I think it might get a little overwhelming when watching TV if the panels are on the same wall. I don't have Light Panels in my living room where I tested the 4D, but I did bring some out to test the syncing, and it definitely adds another layer of depth to the system. Nanoleaf has so many different lighting options at this point, including the Lines, Light Panels, bulbs, and light strips, that you can create an incredible entertainment area. Later this year, the Skylight ceiling panels are coming for even more flexibility.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/nanoleaf-4d-red.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910029" /><br/>
The Nanoleaf 4D setup is controlled through the Nanoleaf app, where you can set the Mirror Mode, choose a color shifting scene that has nothing to do with the content on the TV, or set a solid backlighting color. As with all of Nanoleaf's products, you can create your own lighting scenes too.<br/>
<br/>
You can control the Nanoleaf 4D with the Home app, but it can only be turned on or off or set to a static color, so this is an accessory where you need to have the Nanoleaf app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Nanoleaf 4D Bottom Line</h2><br/>
At &#36;100, the Nanoleaf 4D Screen Mirror and Lightstrip Kit is a solid deal for what you're getting. It's an all-in-one hassle free Lightstrip that goes on the TV and a matching camera for color syncing, so you can have a whole entertainment setup for &#36;100 and 10 minutes of time.<br/>
<br/>
Comparatively, the 4D kit is a lot more affordable than something like the Hue Sync Box, which is priced at &#36;250, making it a much easier lighting ecosystem to get into. I wouldn't recommend this if you have a whole setup of Hue lights in your Living Room because it's designed to work solely with Nanoleaf lights, but if you're starting from scratch or already have Nanoleaf panels, it's a must buy.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Nanoleaf's Ultra Black Hexagons</h2><br/>
Alongside the Nanoleaf 4D, Nanoleaf also introduced Shapes Ultra Black Hexagons, which join the Ultra Black Triangles that we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/14/nanoleaf-ultra-black-shapes-triangles/">reviewed last year</a>. The Ultra Black Hexagons are identical to the standard Hexagons, but are made from a black plastic material that better matches darker-colored decor schemes when not activated.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901711" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/nanoleaf-black-hexagons.jpg" alt="" width="1472" height="828" /><br/>
The Hexagons are probably my favorite panel shape, and the black color looks better than the white color. With the darker plastic, the edges that connect the hexagons better blend into the background, and it's an overall sleeker look. The Black Hexagons look better on the wall when the lights are off, and when turned on, the color brightness is the same. If you've ever wanted Nanoleaf panels but were put off by the stark white plastic look when the lights aren't on, the black panels are an excellent alternative.<br/>
<br/>
As with all of Nanoleaf's Light Panels, the Hexagons can be set to any color, paired with the triangles, and synced with content on a TV or display. There are thousands of patterns and colors available through Nanoleaf's app, or you can create your own. The major downside to Nanoleaf's Ultra Black Hexagons is the price - these are &#36;220 for a set of nine, like Nanoleaf's other products.<br/>
<br/>
Given the amount of light these put off, you can use them in place of a standard lamp, and the color options are second to none for those who like accent lighting. I don't think people who are intrigued by the light panels will be disappointed, even at the price point. Nanoleaf has bundles and sales that can make them slightly more affordable, so it may be worth waiting for a discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/nanoleaf-4d/">Nanoleaf 4D and Lightstrip Kit</a> for up to a 65-inch television set is priced at &#36;100, while the Nanoleaf Lightstrip Kit for an up to an 85-inch TV is priced at &#36;120. There's also a camera-only kit for &#36;80, which can be used with an existing light strip.<br/>
<br/>
The Nanoleaf Shapes Ultra Black Hexagons <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/nanoleaf-shapes/?category=ultra-black-hexagons&amp;pack=smarter-kit&amp;size=9">can be purchased from the Nanoleaf website</a> for &#36;220 for a set of nine panels.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/nanoleaf-4d-camera-and-light-strip/">Review: Nanoleaf 4D Adds Easy Content-Synced Backlighting to Your TV or Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-nanoleaf-4d-adds-easy-content-synced-backlighting-to-your-tv-or-display.2401068/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 15.7.9, iPadOS 15.7.9, macOS 12.6.9 and macOS 11.7.10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-security-updates-older-operating-systems/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-15-7-9-ipados-15-7-9-macos-12-6-9-and-macos-11-7-10.2401067/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 10:23:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-security-updates-older-operating-systems/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new iOS, iPadOS, and macOS updates that are aimed at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac users who are still running older versions of operating systems and are not able to upgrade to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-13/">macOS Ventura</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iOS-15-General-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-803772" /><br/>
The macOS Monterey‌‌ 12.6.9 and macOS Big Sur 11.7.10 updates can be downloaded on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Preferences.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 15.7.9 and iPadOS 15.7.9 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones over-the-air by going to Settings &gt; General &gt; Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
It is likely that these software updates include the same security fixes that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/ios-16-6-1-macos-13-5-2-active-vulnerabilities/">Apple provided last week</a> in the iOS 16.6.1, iPadOS 16.16.1, watchOS 9.6.2, and &zwnj;macOS Ventura&zwnj; 13.5.2 releases.<br/>
<br/>
The software addressed security vulnerabilities that could allow hackers to gain access to an operating system through a PassKit (Wallet) image. The vulnerabilities are part of the BLASTPASS exploit chain that has been used to deliver the NSO Group's Pegasus spyware to devices owned by government officials, journalists, and more.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-security-updates-older-operating-systems/">Apple Releases iOS 15.7.9, iPadOS 15.7.9, macOS 12.6.9 and macOS 11.7.10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-15-7-9-ipados-15-7-9-macos-12-6-9-and-macos-11-7-10.2401067/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro and Grade 5 Titanium: A Detailed Overview</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-grade-5-titanium/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-and-grade-5-titanium-a-detailed-overview.2401059/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 09:00:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-grade-5-titanium/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> is widely rumored to feature an all-new titanium frame. Over the past several months, a variety of credible sources such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/iphone-15-pro-10-percent-lighter-report/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/02/iphone-15-pro-features-specs-rumors/">Apple analyst Jeff Pu</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/21/iphone-15-titanium-curved-rear-edges/">leaker ShrimpApplePro</a>, have all claimed that Apple would be switching to titanium for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, finally replacing stainless steel.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/iPhone-15-Pro-Blue-Front-Perspective-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-905593" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> has confirmation that Apple intends to use Grade 5 Titanium as the exact material for the chassis of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and the larger &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. <br/>
<br/>
Grade 5 Titanium, also known as Ti-6Al-4V, is a titanium alloy consisting of titanium along with small amounts of aluminum and vanadium. Most commonly known for its excellent corrosion resistance, Grade 5 Titanium is used in a wide variety of industries, including aerospace, racing, and prosthetics manufacturing. The light weight, strength, and hardness of the material could explain why Apple decided to use Grade 5 Titanium for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has a history of using titanium for its products – from the PowerBook G4 Titanium in 2001 to the Apple Watch Series 5, down to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra</a>. Apple's decision to use titanium for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models may have been influenced by the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra&zwnj;, as the new Pro iPhones are also set to adopt the multi-purpose Action Button from the high-end Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
The use of titanium on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; also brings with it a change to the chassis finish. Previously, all Pro iPhones used heavily polished stainless steel with a mirror finish as the chassis material. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; will have a brushed finish that is considerably less reflective than the finish of previous Pro iPhones. The image below is perhaps the most accurate representation of the new brushed finish, closely resembling the finish found on prototype devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/iPhone-15-Pro-Colors-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907572" /><br/>
The new brushed finish is expected to reduce scratch visibility. Early in the development of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, Apple experimented with a mirror finish for the device for the titanium frame, in appearance very similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a>. The versions of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; with mirror finish, however, were found to be prone to scratches and dents – both of which were immediately noticeable on the frame. Because of this, the mirror finish for the device was seemingly quickly abandoned in favor of the new brushed look.<br/>
<br/>
While titanium in combination with the brushed finish will allow for better fingerprint resistance and fewer visible scratches - durability issues may still be a potential concern. Although titanium has a higher hardness compared to stainless steel, it's also lighter, making it more prone to dents. To be more specific, the devices may be especially affected by corner dents, which can result in the color coating flaking off, revealing bare metal underneath. This phenomenon has been seen on prototype devices, although it is unclear if improvements have been made since.<br/>
<br/>
The introduction of titanium also influenced the selection of color options planned for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and 15 Pro Max. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/07/iphone-15-pro-blue/">Back in early July, we revealed</a> Apple was testing four different color options for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Blue</li><br/>
<li>Space Black / Space Gray</li><br/>
<li>Titanium Gray</li><br/>
<li>Silver</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
With the removal of the gold color option, we can expect a switch to more gray tones for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. Apple is expected to replace gold with a color option known internally as "Titanium Gray." Titanium Gray, as the name implies, is a color option similar to the color of natural titanium - darker than Silver, but lighter than the Space Black option.<br/>
<br/>
More recently, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/29/apple-september-12-event-announcement/">Apple issued invitations to its September 12 event</a> with the tagline "Wonderlust." The accompanying image and animation feature a multi-colored Apple logo made up of metallic particles, which many consider a subtle nod to the upcoming titanium frame on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. Furthermore, the colors used for the Apple logo match the color options for the 15 Pro, with varying shades of silver, gray, black and dark blue.<br/>
<br/>
The titanium chassis is also expected to lead to lighter devices. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/iphone-15-weights-and-dimensions/">According to information obtained by <em>MacRumors</em></a>, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and 15 Pro Max are expected to be lighter than their respective predecessors by 18 grams, which is a reduction in weight by around 10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
To sum up, these are the key benefits and changes titanium is set to bring to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Brushed finish</li><br/>
<li>Scratches will be less visible</li><br/>
<li>Improved fingerprint resistance</li><br/>
<li>Device weight reduced by 18 grams</li><br/>
<li>New color option – Titanium Gray</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For more details on what to expect, check out our rumor roundup pages for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-grade-5-titanium/">iPhone 15 Pro and Grade 5 Titanium: A Detailed Overview</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-and-grade-5-titanium-a-detailed-overview.2401059/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling Refurbished 15-Inch MacBook Air in U.S. and Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-refurbished-15-inch-macbook-air-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-15-inch-macbook-air-in-u-s-and-canada.2401057/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:49:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-refurbished-15-inch-macbook-air-us/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today started selling certified refurbished 15-inch MacBook Air models online <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/refurbished/mac/2023-macbook-air">in the U.S.</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/shop/refurbished/mac/2023-macbook-air">Canada</a>, following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/refurbished-15-inch-macbook-air-europe/">select European countries</a> last week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898576" /><br/>
As usual for refurbished Macs, prices are discounted by approximately 15% compared to brand new models. A variety of configurations are available to order.<br/>
<br/>
Apple inspects, cleans, tests, and repackages all refurbished Macs to ensure they are fully functional and in good condition, and Apple's refurbished products are covered by a one-year limited warranty and eligible for AppleCare+ coverage.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released the 15-inch MacBook Air <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/wwdc-2023-recap/">at WWDC in June</a>, with pricing starting at &#36;1,299 in the U.S. The laptop has the same overall design and M2 chip as the 13-inch MacBook Air, but it features a larger display and two additional speakers. The laptop is available in four color options: Midnight, Starlight, Space Gray, and Silver.<br/>
<br/>
Keep in mind that the 15-inch MacBook Air is frequently on sale at resellers, so be sure to keep track of our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-pro-air-deals/">MacBook Air deals guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-refurbished-15-inch-macbook-air-us/">Apple Now Selling Refurbished 15-Inch MacBook Air in U.S. and Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-15-inch-macbook-air-in-u-s-and-canada.2401057/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Event: Recapping Last-Minute Rumors for iPhone 15 and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-event-iphone-15-last-minute-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-recapping-last-minute-rumors-for-iphone-15-and-more.2401045/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:08:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-event-iphone-15-last-minute-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>September 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're just one day away from Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-apple-fall-event-2023/">annual September event</a>, and as usual, there have been several last-minute rumors about the iPhone 15 and other devices. The event begins on Tuesday at 10 a.m. Pacific Time, with a live stream to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/05/apple-wonderlust-event-live-stream/">available on YouTube</a>, Apple's website, and in the Apple Events app on the Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/What-to-Expect-at-Apples-Wonderlust-Event-Feature-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909518" /><br/>
Below, we recap some recent rumors related to the iPhone 15 series, Apple Watch Series 9, AirPods, accessories, and more.<ul><li>iPhone 15 Pro models will reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/last-minute-iphone-15-report-reveals-new-details/">weigh around 10% less</a> than iPhone 14 Pro models thanks to a lightweight titanium frame. Based on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/iphone-15-weights-and-dimensions/">leaked figures</a>, the iPhone 15 Pro could be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/iphone-15-pro-10-percent-lighter-report/">lightest Pro model since the iPhone XS or iPhone 11 Pro</a>.</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/17/apple-may-not-offer-leather-cases-for-iphone-15/">Leather</a> (and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/apple-planning-to-discontinue-silicone-accessories/">potentially silicone</a>) accessories like iPhone cases and Apple Watch bands are expected to be replaced with more eco-friendly alternatives</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/no-iphone-15-ultra-says-gurman/">"Pro Max" branding will reportedly live on</a> for at least another year, as "iPhone 15 Ultra" appears to be ruled out</li><br/>
<li>An estimated &#36;100 price increase <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/iphone-15-pro-will-still-start-at-999-trendforce/">might be limited to the iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> in the U.S.</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro models are predicted to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/iphone-15-pro-128gb-storage-8gb-ram-trendforce/">start at 128GB of storage, with 8GB of RAM</a></li><br/>
<li>USB-C ports are expected for all four iPhone 15 models, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/usb-c-airpods-pro-no-other-hardware-changes/">AirPods Pro charging case</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/counterfeiters-preparing-for-usb-c-magsafe-battery/">potentially the MagSafe Battery Pack</a></li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/iphone-mini-might-be-discontinued-this-week/">likely to be discontinued</a></li><br/>
<li>All of the iPhone 15, Apple Watch Series 9, and second-generation Apple Watch Ultra models will reportedly be equipped with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/series-9-and-ultra-2-to-feature-sensors-and-more/">next-generation "U2" chip</a> for enhanced Ultra Wideband connectivity</li></ul>Watch our video recap of last-minute rumors ahead of Apple's event:<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PTG2AE6hS9A?si=_RukWxqRCh6MgxSI" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
Stay tuned for our in-depth coverage of Apple's announcements this week.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/september-2023-apple-event/">September 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-event-iphone-15-last-minute-rumors/">Apple Event: Recapping Last-Minute Rumors for iPhone 15 and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-recapping-last-minute-rumors-for-iphone-15-and-more.2401045/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Watch Apple&#039;s &#039;Wonderlust&#039; iPhone 15 Event on Tuesday, September 12</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wonderlust-iphone-15-event-sep-12/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-watch-apples-wonderlust-iphone-15-event-on-tuesday-september-12.2401035/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:26:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wonderlust-iphone-15-event-sep-12&#038;post_date=1694453186/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>September 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is hosting an online streaming event for the public and press on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/29/apple-september-12-event-announcement/">September 12, 2023 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time</a>. The company is expected to announce its new iPhone 15 lineup alongside an Apple Watch Series 9, an Apple Watch Ultra 2, and potentially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/28/iphone-15-apple-event-four-other-announcements/">other products during the event</a>, dubbed "Wonderlust." Here's how you can watch it and when, wherever you are in the world.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PTG2AE6hS9A" title="Last Minute Leaks: What to Expect at Apple&#39;s Fall iPhone Event!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
There are multiple ways to watch the September 12 event, with details listed below. We've also included a useful guide on when the event will take place in your particular time zone.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Events Website</h2><br/>
With the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">Apple Events website</a>, you can watch the event live on a Mac, iPhone, ‌iPad‌, PC, or any other device with a web browser. The Apple Events website works in Safari, Chrome, Firefox, and other main browsers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-events-webpage-sept-2023.jpg" alt="" width="1215" height="919" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908292" /><br/>
Just navigate to <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">www.apple.com/apple-events/</a> using a web browser at the appropriate time to watch. You can visit the site now to add an event reminder to your calendar.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>YouTube</h2><br/>
Apple also plans to stream the event <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZiP1l7jlIIA">live on YouTube</a>, which is perhaps the easiest and most efficient way to watch because the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZiP1l7jlIIA">YouTube live stream</a> can be viewed on every platform where YouTube is available, which is pretty much all platforms, from smartphones and tablets to consoles and smart TVs.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZiP1l7jlIIA?si=bH8ArKCsA-jtmR0J" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?">posted a placeholder for the September 12 event</a> on YouTube, and you can visit it now to set an event reminder.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple TV App</h2><br/>
Apple used to have a dedicated Apple Events app on the Apple TV, but ahead of WWDC 2020, it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/06/18/events-app-apple-tv-app-wwdc/">folded into the Apple TV app</a>. On event day, there will be a prominent ‌Apple TV‌ app section dedicated to the live stream, which can be watched on any device where the ‌Apple TV‌ app is available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/appleevents1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1112" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-746566" /><br/>
This includes the ‌Apple TV‌, iPhones, iPads, and Macs, as well as select smart TVs, streaming devices, and gaming consoles. If you have an ‌Apple TV‌, the ‌Apple TV‌ app is one of the best ways to watch the event live. Apple hasn't updated the ‌Apple TV‌ app with the new event as of yet, but it should be added soon.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/28/iphone-15-apple-event-four-other-announcements/">Apple's 'Wonderlust' Event: New Products to Expect Beyond the iPhone 15</a></li></ul><br/>
<h2>When to Watch the Apple Event</h2><br/>
Apple's event will take place at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time, like most Apple events. Event times in other time zones are listed below.<br/>
<ul><li>Honolulu, Hawaii — 7:00 a.m. HAST</li><br/>
<li>Anchorage, Alaska — 9:00 a.m. AKDT</li><br/>
<li><strong>Cupertino, California — 10:00 a.m. PDT</strong></li><br/>
<li>Phoenix, Arizona — 10:00 a.m. MST</li><br/>
<li>Vancouver, Canada — 10:00 a.m. PDT</li><br/>
<li>Denver, Colorado — 11:00 a.m. MDT</li><br/>
<li>Dallas, Texas — 12:00 noon CDT</li><br/>
<li>New York, New York — 1:00 p.m. EDT</li><br/>
<li>Toronto, Canada — 1:00 p.m. EDT</li><br/>
<li>Halifax, Canada — 2:00 p.m. ADT</li><br/>
<li>Rio de Janeiro, Brazil — 2:00 p.m. BRT</li><br/>
<li>London, United Kingdom — 6:00 p.m. BST</li><br/>
<li>Berlin, Germany — 7:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
<li>Paris, France — 7:00 p.m. CEST</li><br/>
<li>Cape Town, South Africa — 7:00 p.m. SAST</li><br/>
<li>Helsinki, Finland — 8:00 p.m. EEST</li><br/>
<li>Istanbul, Turkey — 8:00 p.m. TRT</li><br/>
<li>Dubai, United Arab Emirates — 9:00 p.m. GST</li><br/>
<li>Delhi, India — 10:30 p.m. IST</li><br/>
<li>Jakarta, Indonesia — 12:00 a.m. WIB next day</li><br/>
<li>Shanghai, China — 1:00 a.m. CST next day</li><br/>
<li>Singapore — 1:00 a.m. SGT next day</li><br/>
<li>Perth, Australia — 1:00 a.m. AWST next day</li><br/>
<li>Hong Kong — 1:00 a.m. HKT next day</li><br/>
<li>Seoul, South Korea — 2:00 a.m. KST next day</li><br/>
<li>Tokyo, Japan — 2:00 a.m. JST next day</li><br/>
<li>Adelaide, Australia — 2:30 a.m. ACST next day</li><br/>
<li>Sydney, Australia — 3:00 a.m. AEST next day</li><br/>
<li>Auckland, New Zealand — 5:00 a.m. NZST next day</ul><br/>
<h2>MacRumors Coverage</h2><br/>
If you're not able to watch or just want to follow along with us as we watch the event unfold, visit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/">MacRumors.com</a> for our liveblog or follow us on Twitter at <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive">MacRumorsLive</a> for our live tweet coverage.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/what-not-to-expect-apple-september-iphone-15-event/">What <em>Not</em> to Expect at Apple's 'Wonderlust' September 12 Event</a><br/>
</li></ul><br/>
Both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/">MacRumors site</a> and our <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive">Twitter account</a> are excellent ways to discuss the new announcements with other Apple enthusiasts as Apple unveils its new products. Later in the day and throughout the week, we'll also have much more in-depth coverage of all of Apple's announcements, so make sure to stay tuned.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/september-2023-apple-event/">September 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/watch-apple-wonderlust-iphone-15-event-sep-12/">How to Watch Apple&#039;s &#039;Wonderlust&#039; iPhone 15 Event on Tuesday, September 12</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-watch-apples-wonderlust-iphone-15-event-on-tuesday-september-12.2401035/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: AirPods 3 With MagSafe Charging Case Available for &#36;159 (&#36;20 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-airpods-3-with-magsafe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-airpods-3-with-magsafe-charging-case-available-for-159-20-off.2401030/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:11:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-airpods-3-with-magsafe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Verizon today is discounting the AirPods 3 with MagSafe Charging Case, available for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku4820001"><strong>&#36;159.00</strong></a>, from &#36;179.00. It's been a few months since we tracked a deal on the MagSafe version of the AirPods 3, and this is a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-3-Discount-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895373" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Verizon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, the AirPods 3 with Lightning Charging Case is down to <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation-lightning-charging-case%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5600049"><strong>&#36;149.99</strong></a> on Verizon, from &#36;169.00. This is another second-best price on the AirPods 3.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation-lightning-charging-case%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5600049"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirPods 3 (Lightning) for &#36;149.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-3rd-generation%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku4820001"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirPods 3 (MagSafe) for &#36;159.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should remember that you don't need to be a Verizon customer to take advantage of these deals. Verizon offers free two-day shipping and you can also opt for free express pick-up if there is a Verizon store near you with stock on the AirPods 3.<br/>
<br/>
Verizon also has the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-charging-case%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku3390160"><strong>&#36;99.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is one of the most consistent deals on AirPods that we've seen this year, and although we've seen it go lower, that's typically only been around major holidays or discount events.<br/>
<br/>
We track sales for every model of the AirPods in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-deals/">Best AirPods Deals</a> guide, so be sure to bookmark that page while you shop around for the wireless headphones. Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/deals-airpods-3-with-magsafe/">Deals: AirPods 3 With MagSafe Charging Case Available for &#36;159 (&#36;20 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-airpods-3-with-magsafe-charging-case-available-for-159-20-off.2401030/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Extends Deal With Qualcomm as Custom 5G Modem Delayed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-custom-5g-modem-delayed.2401021/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:52:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has extended its agreement to obtain modems from Qualcomm for three more years, in what appears to be a sign that work on the company's own custom 5G modem is taking longer than previously expected, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-11/apple-aapl-renews-qualcomm-qcom-deal-in-sign-its-own-modem-chip-isn-t-ready"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/5G-Modem-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-886940" /><br/>
Apple is Qualcomm's biggest client, accounting for almost a quarter of the supplier's revenue. In a statement, Qualcomm said that the deal with Apple covers "smartphone launches in 2024, 2025 and 2026." The agreement was originally set to expire this year and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup was once rumored to be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/09/apple-in-house-modem-chips-2024/">last to rely on Qualcomm</a> modems.<br/>
<br/>
The extension of the deal indicates that Apple's work on its own custom 5G modem is taking considerably longer than expected. Apple has reportedly been working on its own modem since 2018 and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/25/apple-intel-acquisition/">acquired the majority of Intel's smartphone modem business</a> in 2019. The time frame for launching the modem has slipped from 2023 to 2024 or 2025, but <em>Bloomberg</em> now believes it has an even "longer runway" before it will be ready.<br/>
<br/>
While the new agreement extends to 2026, Apple could still begin rolling out its own modem in new devices before then. Earlier this month, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that the modem will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/apple-modem-in-2025-kuo/">launch in 2025</a>. Apple's apparent plan to gradually transition to its custom modem technology is indicated by the fact that Qualcomm expects to still have a 20 percent share of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> shipments when the 2026 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; launches, suggesting that Apple will continue using Qualcomm modems in a minority of iPhones at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple purportedly wants its custom 5G modem to mirror its work on Apple silicon, touting considerable battery life and performance benefits. Thus far, the company's work on the component has apparently been mired by battery life issues and bureaucratic challenges, such as certifying the modem with connectivity authorities.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/">Apple Extends Deal With Qualcomm as Custom 5G Modem Delayed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-custom-5g-modem-delayed.2401021/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17: How to Separate Your Browsing Habits With Safari Profiles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/separate-browsing-habits-safari-profiles-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-how-to-separate-your-browsing-habits-with-safari-profiles.2401018/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:12:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/separate-browsing-habits-safari-profiles-ios&#038;post_date=1694441566/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 17, Safari has gained a new feature called Profiles, which is designed to help separate your browsing sessions into things like Work, School, or Personal. Here's how to use it in the <a href="http://How to Install the iOS 17 Public Beta">beta</a> and when iOS 17 is released to the general public later this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/iOS-17-General-Safari-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904916" /><br/>
In ‌iOS 17‌, Apple expands on Tab Groups with a Profile feature that is designed to let you separate your browsing for different use cases. You can create a "Work" profile and a "Personal" profile, for example, so all of your work-related browsing is kept separate from your personal browsing.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-ios-17-public-beta/">How to Install the iOS 17 Public Beta</a></li></ul><br/>
Each profile gets its own icon and silos your history, Tab Groups, Favorites, Private Browsing tabs, and cookies. You can even assign specific extensions to different profiles to optimize your browsing experience based on the task at hand.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Create a Safari Profile</h2><br/>
To set up profiles on iPhones running iOS 17, simply follow these steps:<br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app on you iPhone or iPad.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down to <strong>Safari</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Under the "Profiles" section, tap <strong>New Profile</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Select an icon, name, and background color for the profile.<br/>
<li>Choose your settings for <strong>Favorites</strong> and <strong>New Tabs</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Done</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/how-to-use-safari-profiles-ios1.jpg" alt="safari" width="4320" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909889" /><br/>
<br/>
When you create a new profile, your device will automatically generate a "Personal" profile to differentiate other browsing sessions conducted outside of the profile you created. <br/>
<br/>
Both profiles and additional ones you create can be edited in the same section of the Settings app. When editing an existing profile, you can also opt to enable any Safari extensions you have installed on your device, as well as delete the profile if desired.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Switch Between Profiles in Safari</h2><br/>
<ol><li>In Safari, tap the <strong>Tabs icon</strong> with two overlapping squares.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>middle icon</strong> to bring up the active profile's menu.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the <strong>Profile</strong> option to change which profile is active.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/how-to-use-safari-profiles-ios3.jpg" alt="safari" width="4320" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909888" /><br/>
<br/>
The Safari Profiles feature is available in iOS 17, iPadOS 17 and macOS Sonoma, as well as being part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-safari-17-macos-ventura-monterey/">Safari 17 for macOS Monterey and macOS Ventura</a>. Any profiles you create will be synced across devices logged into the same Apple ID.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-safari-17-macos-ventura-monterey/">How to Download Safari 17 Beta for macOS Ventura and Monterey</a></li></ul><br/>
The new Safari also brings additional privacy functionality, improvements to search, updated Siri integration, and more. A rundown on all of the new features in the ‌iOS 17‌ update can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">comprehensive iOS 17 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/separate-browsing-habits-safari-profiles-ios/">iOS 17: How to Separate Your Browsing Habits With Safari Profiles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-how-to-separate-your-browsing-habits-with-safari-profiles.2401018/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Mini Might Be Discontinued Following Apple Event This Week After Three-Year Run</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/iphone-mini-might-be-discontinued-this-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-mini-might-be-discontinued-following-apple-event-this-week-after-three-year-run.2400995/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 19:17:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/iphone-mini-might-be-discontinued-this-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 13</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Fans of smaller phones rejoiced when Apple introduced the iPhone 12 mini in 2020, followed by the iPhone 13 mini a year later. However, after nearly three years of availability, the end of the road might be near for the 5.4-inch device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/iPhone-mini-wonder-feature-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="1444" height="812" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-794050" /><br/>
As noted <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1700953564577923085">by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, iPhone 13 mini stock is running low, with Apple's online store in the U.S. quoting a 2-3 week shipping estimate for some models, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-iphone/iphone-13/5.4-inch-display-256gb-green-unlocked">even 6-8 weeks</a> for a few others. The shortage suggests that the iPhone 13 mini might be discontinued after Apple announces new iPhones at its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-apple-fall-event-2023/">"Wonderlust" event on Tuesday</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not release an iPhone 14 mini last year, but it kept the iPhone 13 mini available as a lower-cost option, with pricing starting at &#36;599 in the U.S. If you are interested in buying the iPhone 13 mini, now might be your last chance, as it is looking likely that Apple will discontinue the device on Tuesday after unveiling the iPhone 15 series. Apple's new lineup will likely consist of the 6.1-inch iPhone 15, 6.7-inch iPhone 15 Plus, 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro, 6.7-inch iPhone 15 Pro Max, 4.7-inch iPhone SE, and the 6.1-inch iPhone 13.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I just want to say that I hate you all for not buying the iPhone mini resulting in its cancellation and I’ll never forgive you for it.</p>&mdash; Snazzy Labs (@SnazzyLabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/SnazzyLabs/status/1699471555695370384?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 6, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
While there initially appeared to be pent-up demand for a smaller iPhone, actual data suggested that the iPhone mini had low sales relative to other iPhone models. In April 2022, research firm CIRP estimated that the ‌iPhone 13‌ mini accounted for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/21/iphone-13-mini-unpopular-march-quarter/">just 3% of ‌overall iPhone 13‌ sales</a> in the U.S. in the first quarter of that year.<br/>
<br/>
Going forward, customers who want a small iPhone from Apple will have to settle for the entry-level iPhone SE, but even that device is rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/27/kuo-iphone-se-4-oled-display/">updated with a larger 6.1-inch display</a> in the next year or two. At least for the time being, it appears that Apple has realized that smaller phones just aren't that popular after all.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/iphone-mini-might-be-discontinued-this-week/">iPhone Mini Might Be Discontinued Following Apple Event This Week After Three-Year Run</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-mini-might-be-discontinued-following-apple-event-this-week-after-three-year-run.2400995/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple May Be Planning to Discontinue All of Its Silicone Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/apple-planning-to-discontinue-silicone-accessories/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-may-be-planning-to-discontinue-all-of-its-silicone-accessories.2400974/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 11:48:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/apple-planning-to-discontinue-silicone-accessories/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone Cases</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Bands</category>
		<category>Silicone Case</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple may be planning to discontinue its silicone rubber and fluoroelastomer accessories, replacing them with ones made of more eco-friendly next-generation materials, <em>MacRumors</em> has been told.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/iPhone-14-and-14-Plus-New-Silcone-Case-Colors-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2056" height="1156" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-887977" /><br/>
The move is expected to include accessories such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Silicone Case with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a>, Sport Band, Solo Loop, and AirTag Loop. The rumor comes from Apple device collector and leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>," who has previously shared information about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/21/iphone-15-could-come-with-color-matched-cables/">braided USB-C cable</a>, various prototypes such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/apple-planned-magsafe-charger-color-options/">MagSafe chargers</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/apple-prototyped-airpods-in-five-color-options/">AirPods</a> in different color options, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is widely expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/17/apple-may-not-offer-leather-cases-for-iphone-15/">discontinue</a> its leather &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; cases following the introduction of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup, replacing them accessories made with a premium material marketed as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/finewoven-cases-may-match-new-watch-band/">FineWoven</a>." The discontinuation of silicone accessories is not expected to be imminent, instead taking place via a more gradual transition whereby existing models are not refreshed with new color options. For example, Sport Band may not be refreshed with new color options following the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, being available until supplies of the current units run out. Apple is expected to release new accessory designs, such as a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/09/new-apple-watch-magnetic-band/">"FineWoven" Apple Watch band</a> with a magnetic buckle, to replace its outgoing products.<br/>
<br/>
The discontinuation of all leather and silicone Apple accessories is believed to be part of a wider move to transition to more environmentally friendly materials. While Apple's silicone rubber accessories have a lower carbon footprint than their leather counterparts, they are not made with any recycled materials. Materials like fluoroelastomer are also difficult to recycle due to their heat-resistant properties and strong, crosslinked structure.<br/>
<br/>
"FineWoven" is expected to be the first next-generation material used by Apple, replacing leather in the immediate term, but it could also displace some silicone accessories at some point. There will likely also be other new, more eco-friendly materials introduced on other accessories in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-cases/">iPhone Cases</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-bands/">Apple Watch Bands</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/silicone-case/">Silicone Case</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/apple-planning-to-discontinue-silicone-accessories/">Apple May Be Planning to Discontinue All of Its Silicone Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-may-be-planning-to-discontinue-all-of-its-silicone-accessories.2400974/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Counterfeiters Preparing for Launch of USB-C MagSafe Battery Pack</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/counterfeiters-preparing-for-usb-c-magsafe-battery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/counterfeiters-preparing-for-launch-of-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack.2400972/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 11:39:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/counterfeiters-preparing-for-usb-c-magsafe-battery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		<category>MagSafe Battery Pack</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Images of fake <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Battery Packs with a USB-C charging port instead of Lightning are being shared on social media sites, potentially hinting at preparations to mirror Apple's release of such an accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/magsafe-battery-pack-with-usb-c-port.jpg" alt="" width="3200" height="1800" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-909783" /><br/>
The current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a> is a widely counterfeited accessory, but most one-to-one replicas available to date feature a Lightning port. The latest series of images, shared across X (formerly Twitter) and Weibo, depict the same one-to-one replicas but with a USB-C charging port.<br/>
<br/>
The entire <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup is expected to move away from Lightning and feature a USB-C charging port for the first time, and Apple is expected to bring USB-C to other devices and accessories <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/usb-c-airpods-and-airpods-max-2024/">over the next year</a>. It is not clear if Apple plans to release a new version of the &zwnj;MagSafe Battery Pack&zwnj; with a USB-C port, but it is expected to do so with other accessories such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>'s &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Charging Case alongside the release of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">All new Apple accessories will have to follow USB C standards, this means that even older models will be updated. Here is a Usb C model of the MagSafe Battery <a href="https://t.co/QrMVJOld5u">pic.twitter.com/QrMVJOld5u</a></p>&mdash; Majin Bu (@MajinBuOfficial) <a href="https://twitter.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1700859263034298647?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 10, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><br/>
<br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/the-macrumors-show-mark-gurman-iphone-15-event-expectations/">most recent episode</a> of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> podcast, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-planned/">seeking to move to USB-C</a> across its lineup of accessories by next year, likely including the &zwnj;MagSafe Battery Pack&zwnj;. The transition will apparently be relatively fast, mirroring the transition to the Lightning connector following its introduction in 2012.<br/>
<br/>
"They're going to need to do a new &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Duo with USB-C," Gurman said, and Apple "certainly can update the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; battery pack" to add USB-C. It is not entirely clear if these refreshed accessories will be introduced at its "Wonderlust" event on Tuesday, September 12, but the proliferation of images of fakes could hint that Apple is preparing to launch some of them next week.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">mangetic wireless power bank charges <a href="https://t.co/BvWaxKOEzn">pic.twitter.com/BvWaxKOEzn</a></p>&mdash; fix Apple &#x1f34f; (@lipilipsi) <a href="https://twitter.com/lipilipsi/status/1700491406589284687?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 9, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><br/>
<br/>
In addition, Gurman explained that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-planned/">all-new MagSafe Battery Pack</a> is in development, but it is not yet ready to be introduced. The next-generation battery pack apparently involves a new concept that allows users to "daisy-chain" multiple battery packs together by stacking them and wirelessly charge multiple devices at the same time. For example, it will be possible to charge two iPhones at the same time, with one placed on either side of the battery pack.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/counterfeiters-preparing-for-usb-c-magsafe-battery/">Counterfeiters Preparing for Launch of USB-C MagSafe Battery Pack</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/counterfeiters-preparing-for-launch-of-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack.2400972/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Air 6 Rumored to Launch in October as Only iPad Refresh of 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october-as-only-ipad-refresh-of-2023.2400947/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 01:57:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> should launch in October as the only <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> refresh of 2023, according to a plausible rumor shared on Chinese social media site Weibo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/ipad-air-5-colors.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-839734" /><br/>
"Only the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; series should be updated this year," the post reads, with a subsequent clarification that the product refresh will take place in October, with "no mini and Pro this year." The information comes from an account with a proven track record for disclosing accurate information about Apple's plans.<br/>
<br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/the-macrumors-show-mark-gurman-iphone-15-event-expectations/">latest episode</a> of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> podcast, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that there is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/gurman-october-apple-event-unlikely/">new iPad Air</a> with improved specifications in the works and the device is apparently "coming soonish," likely in October. The rumor was posted to Weibo prior to Gurman's most recent remarks.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman believes that there will be a further Apple product launch in October, but expressed skepticism that an entire event will take place to introduce new devices. He said that it could be similar to the introduction of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max MacBook Pro models earlier this year, which were announced via press release and a short video. Gurman claimed that October could see something "along those lines." "I'm not sure they have enough to drag people down to Cupertino to watch the video like they do for this [<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>] launch," he added.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last updated the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/08/apple-unveils-new-ipad-air/">in March 2022</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip, an upgraded 12-megapixel front camera with Center Stage support, a faster USB-C port, 5G support on cellular models, and new color options. Pricing starts at &#36;599 in the U.S. for 64GB of storage. It is unclear what <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/19/ipad-air-6-key-upgrades-to-expect/">new features</a> the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will offer, but possibilities include the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, a Thunderbolt port like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> hover, and new color options.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/">iPad Air 6 Rumored to Launch in October as Only iPad Refresh of 2023</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october-as-only-ipad-refresh-of-2023.2400947/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro: Complete Weights and Dimensions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/iphone-15-weights-and-dimensions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-complete-weights-and-dimensions.2400901/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:28:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/iphone-15-weights-and-dimensions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iPhone 15 Pro is expected to feature a new midframe made from <a href="https://twitter.com/URedditor/status/1683130501626773504">Grade 5 titanium</a>, resulting in a substantially lighter device overall. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-08/apple-event-2023-iphone-15-pro-max-airpods-watch-series-9-products-to-expect">Mark Gurman recently said</a> that the iPhone 15 Pro could be up to 10 percent lighter than the iPhone 14 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Blue-Front-Perspective-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910061" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> has obtained the exact dimensions of the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max, and the information appears to corroborate Gurman's claims.<br/>
<br/>
<b>iPhone 15 dimensions and weight</b>:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>Thickness</b>: 7.8mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Length</b>: 147.6mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Width</b>: 71.6mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Weight</b>: 171 grams</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<b>iPhone 14 dimensions and weight:</b><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>Thickness</b>: 7.8mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Length: </b>146.7mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Width: </b>71.5mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Weight:</b> 172 grams</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The base model iPhone 15 could be considered the least different of the lineup, with its dimensions and total weight being similar to that of the iPhone 14. The iPhone 15 will maintain the exact same thickness as last year's model, with negligible changes to the length and width of the device. According to our sources, the iPhone 15 is said to continue to use the exact same chassis material as the iPhone 14 -- 6013 T6 aluminum. With no significant differences in materials and no noteworthy structural changes, it's easy to see why the weight of the standard iPhone 15 is close to that of the iPhone 14.<br/>
<br/>
While the exact dimensions of the iPhone 15 Plus are not apparent at the time of writing, it is safe to assume the size difference between the iPhone 15 Plus and iPhone 14 Plus is minimal at best. As no major design changes, structural changes, or changes in materials are expected, the iPhone 15 Plus will also likely have a weight similar to that of its predecessor.<br/>
<br/>
<b>iPhone 15 Pro dimensions and weight:</b><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>Thickness</b>: 8.25mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Length</b>: 146.6mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Width</b>: 70.6mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Weight</b>: 188 grams</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<b>iPhone 14 Pro dimensions and weight:</b><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>Thickness</b>: 7.85mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Length: </b>147.5mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Width: </b>71.5mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Weight:</b> 206 grams</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro is set to bring improvements in at least one key area -- weight. Compared to its predecessor, the iPhone 15 Pro will be 18 grams lighter due to the change in materials. Our sources were able to verify that Apple is using Grade 5 Titanium for the iPhone 15 Pro, which represents a notable departure from the stainless steel used on every Pro iPhone thus far. Grade 5 Titanium, also known as Ti-6Al-4V, is a titanium alloy used in a variety of industries and is widely known for its excellent corrosion resistance.<br/>
<br/>
As far as the dimensions are concerned, the iPhone 15 Pro is expected to maintain a form factor similar to its predecessor, with slight differences in the length and width of the device. One noteworthy difference, though, is the thickness of the device. The iPhone 15 Pro features an increased thickness -- 8.25mm compared to 7.85 on the iPhone 14 Pro. The thickness change could be regarded as an interesting choice, considering the company has previously used reduced thickness as a selling point for certain devices. The reduced bezel size of the iPhone 15 Pro display will likely overshadow the increase in thickness, however.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro is expected to have thinner bezels due to the use of advanced display technology known as LIPO, an acronym for "low-injection pressure over-molding". <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-07-30/apple-iphone-15-pro-features-usb-c-port-new-design-thinner-bezels-lkpemg29">First mentioned by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, and since independently confirmed by <em>MacRumors</em>, the use of LIPO technology for iPhone 15 Pro displays is expected to reduce the bezel size from the current 2.2mm to approximately 1.55mm.<br/>
<br/>
<b>iPhone 15 Pro Max dimensions and weight:</b><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>Thickness</b>: 8.25mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Length: </b>159.9mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Width: </b>76.7mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Weight:</b> 221 grams</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<b>iPhone 14 Pro Max dimensions and weight</b>:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><b>Thickness</b>: 7.85mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Length: </b>160.7mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Width: </b>77.6mm</li><br/>
 	<li><b>Weight:</b> 240 grams</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro Max is expected to feature the same changes as the smaller iPhone 15 Pro, weighing 19 grams less than the iPhone 14 Pro Max. Because of this, it's safe to assume that the difference in weight is a result of the change in materials, rather than any sort of significant structural changes or design differences compared to the iPhone 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
It's worth noting that the information presented here is <b>pre-production information</b>, and may not reflect the hardware of mass production units, but it represents our best insight into the dimensions of the iPhone 15 range. According to our sources, the dimensions of the iPhone 15 lineup have remained unchanged throughout development, although slight differences in weight may be possible due to the different hardware configurations Apple tested.<br/>
<br/>
For additional information on what to expect with the iPhone 15 series, check out our dedicated rumor roundup pages for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/iphone-15-weights-and-dimensions/">iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro: Complete Weights and Dimensions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-complete-weights-and-dimensions.2400901/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Event Expectations for iPhone 15, Apple Watch, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/top-stories-iphone-15-event-preview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-expectations-for-iphone-15-apple-watch-and-more.2400889/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/top-stories-iphone-15-event-preview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The calendar has turned to September, and new iPhone season is upon us! Apple will be announcing the iPhone 15 series at an event scheduled for Tuesday, September 12, at 10 a.m. Pacific Time, with a live stream to be available on YouTube and on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/top-stories-9sep2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909646" /><br/>
Read on below for all the details on what we're expecting (and not expecting) next week, and tune in on Tuesday as <em>MacRumors</em> will be on hand to see what Apple has in store.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What to Expect From Apple's September 12 Event: iPhone 15, Apple Watch Ultra 2, USB-C AirPods and More</h2><br/>
Ahead of Tuesday's event we've recapped everything we expect to see on Tuesday, which includes the iPhone 15 lineup, new Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/What-to-Expect-at-Apples-Wonderlust-Event-Feature-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909518" /><br/>
The iPhone 15 lineup will be the headliner of the show, with all four models expected to be equipped with a USB-C port and the Dynamic Island, while many additional features have been rumored for the Pro models, including a titanium frame, customizable Action button, A17 Bionic chip, Wi-Fi 6E support, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything You Need to Know About the iPhone 15 Camera Specifications</h2><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/05/iphone-15-series-camera-specs/">shared detailed camera specifications for the entire iPhone 15 lineup</a>, ahead of the devices being unveiled next week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Blue-Three-Quarters-Perspective-Camera-Closeup-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909014" /><br/>
Key camera-related features expected include a stacked camera sensor for the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus, and a periscope telephoto lens for the iPhone 15 Pro Max that enables up to 6x optical zoom. These camera features will supposedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/iphone-15-camera-upgrades-trendforce/">be the "star of the show" at Apple's event</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 to Feature New Heart Rate Monitor, More Accurate Sensors, U2 Chip, and More</h2><br/>
While we're not expecting significant design changes for the upcoming Apple Watch models, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman says there will be a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/series-9-and-ultra-2-to-feature-sensors-and-more/">fair number of under-the-hood changes</a> led by a new S9 chip that will deliver the first real upgrade in that regard since the Apple Watch Series 6.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/Apple-Watch-Series-9-Pink-Aluminum-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905452" /><br/>
In addition, there should be some upgrades to the various sensors and other components with a "focus on speed, efficiency, and accuracy." A new "U2" Ultra Wideband chip will enhance location tracking capabilities with an eye toward improvements to the Find My ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Stores to Update Overnight After 'Wonderlust' Event in Preparation for iPhone 15 Launch</h2><br/>
Apple retail stores <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/05/apple-retail-stores-overnight-event-update/">will be making updates on the night after the Apple event</a> next week, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-store-washington.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891495" /><br/>
It's likely that the stores will be rolling out marketing materials for new products announced at the Apple event, including the iPhone 15 series. Other products expected to be unveiled include the Apple Watch Series 9, a new Apple Watch Ultra, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/29/usb-c-airpods-at-iphone-15-event-report/">a USB-C AirPods case</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Pro Models Again Rumored to See &#36;100 Price Increase</h2><br/>
The upcoming iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max models may some price increases compared to the current models, although rumors are unclear on how exactly things will play out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/iPhone-15-Pro-Blue-Front-Perspective-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905593" /><br/>
Wedbush analyst Dan Ives and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/major-price-hike-rumored-for-iphone-15-pro-models/">others</a> believe <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/iphone-15-pro-models-rumored-to-see-price-increase/">each will cost &#36;100 more</a> than the current Pro models in the U.S., meaning the iPhone 15 Pro would start at &#36;1,099 and the iPhone 15 Pro Max would start at &#36;1,199.<br/>
<br/>
Research firm TrendForce believes, however, that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/iphone-15-pro-will-still-start-at-999-trendforce/">price increase will be limited to the Pro Max model</a>, with the smaller iPhone 15 Pro still starting at &#36;999.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What Not to Expect at Apple's 'Wonderlust' Event</h2><br/>
To help set expectations ahead of Apple's "Wonderlust" event, we've compiled a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/what-not-to-expect-apple-september-iphone-15-event/">list of products that Apple is unlikely to announce</a> during the keynote.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/What-Not-To-Expect-at-Apples-Wonderlust-Event-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2098" height="1180" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908618" /><br/>
For example, the first Macs with the M3 chip are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/apple-m3-macs-october-event/">not expected to be announced until October</a>. Other rumored products, such as a second-generation HomePod mini and iPad Pro models with OLED displays, are not expected to be released until 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/sep-7-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/top-stories-iphone-15-event-preview/">Top Stories: Apple Event Expectations for iPhone 15, Apple Watch, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-expectations-for-iphone-15-apple-watch-and-more.2400889/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Multiple USB-C Apple Accessories Reportedly Planned, All-New &#039;Stackable&#039; MagSafe Battery Pack in Development</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-planned/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-reportedly-planned-all-new-stackable-magsafe-battery-pack-in-development.2400885/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 04:10:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-planned/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>MagSafe Accessories</category>
		<category>MagSafe Battery Pack</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to refresh many of its accessories to add a USB-C port following the transition away from Lightning on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> told <em>MacRumors</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/magsafe-battery-pack-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="2490" height="1401" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-807787" /><br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/the-macrumors-show-mark-gurman-iphone-15-event-expectations/">most recent episode</a> of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> podcast, Gurman said that Apple is seeking to move to USB-C across its lineup of accessories by next year, including all of its AirPods models and Mac accessories. The transition will apparently be relatively fast, mirroring the transition to the Lightning connector following its introduction in 2012.<br/>
<br/>
"They're going to need to do a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Duo with USB-C," Gurman said, and Apple "certainly can update the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; battery pack" to add USB-C. It is not entirely clear if these refreshed accessories will be introduced at Apple's "Wonderlust" event on Tuesday, September 12.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also mused that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/08/apple-discontinues-apple-watch-dock/">now-discontinued</a> Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock could be reintroduced with a USB-C port. Although Apple needs to refresh a large selection of its cables and accessories relatively quickly, he is "not expecting any curveballs or any brand new types of accessories" to be announced at the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Apple event.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, Gurman explained that a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a> is in development, but it is likely not yet ready to be introduced. The next-generation battery pack involves a new concept that allows users to "daisy-chain" multiple battery packs together by stacking them and wirelessly charge multiple devices at the same time. For example, it will be possible to charge two iPhones at the same time, with one placed on either side of the battery pack. It will also, of course, feature a USB-C port.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said that he does not think the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> with a USB-C port on the charging case, due to be announced next week, will be marketed as "third-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;." The third-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; will be a more significant update launching next year or early 2025, Gurman claimed. Listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/the-macrumors-show-mark-gurman-iphone-15-event-expectations/">The MacRumors Show</a> podcast for Gurman's full thoughts and expectations.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-accessories/">MagSafe Accessories</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-planned/">Multiple USB-C Apple Accessories Reportedly Planned, All-New &#039;Stackable&#039; MagSafe Battery Pack in Development</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/multiple-usb-c-apple-accessories-reportedly-planned-all-new-stackable-magsafe-battery-pack-in-development.2400885/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
