<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:00:56 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone and Apple Watch Likely to Support NFC Multi-Purpose Tap in the Future</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-and-apple-watch-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap-in-the-future.2430457/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:43:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>NFC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhones and Apple Watches could support multiple actions via NFC simultaneously in the future, the NFC Forum today suggested.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/apple-card-via-apple-pay.jpeg" alt="" width="1524" height="909" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-843215" /><br/>
The NFC Forum, the leading standards body for Near Field Communication (NFC) technology, <a href="https://nfc-forum.org/news/2024-07-nfc-forum-defines-next-generation-of-contactless-user-experience-with-multi-purpose-tap/">today published</a> its first overview of NFC Multi-Purpose Tap. The technology, which supports multiple actions with one tap, is designed to bring more convenience to various NFC use cases such as point-to-point receipt delivery, loyalty programs, identification, and total-journey transit ticketing.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is a prominent member of the NFC Forum and likely contributed to the development of the technology. The company first introduced NFC in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 6 and original Apple Watch, initially focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, allowing users to make contactless payments. <br/>
<br/>
NFC Multi-Purpose Tap would allow &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to perform multiple transactions with a single tap. For instance, consumers could make payments, log loyalty points, and receive receipts instantaneously. The potential applications are considerable, from retail payments to public transportation, where users could tap their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to pay for a journey, apply discounts, and get travel receipts all at once.<br/>
<br/>
Since Apple is a member of the NFC Forum, it seems highly likely that NFC Multi-Purpose Tap will come to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch at some point in the future. The company often adds support for new NFC functionalities, such as reading NFC tags and facilitating more interactions with a broader range of NFC devices. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nfc/">NFC</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap/">iPhone and Apple Watch Likely to Support NFC Multi-Purpose Tap in the Future</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-and-apple-watch-likely-to-support-nfc-multi-purpose-tap-in-the-future.2430457/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reclassifies iPhone X, HomePod, and Original AirPods as &#039;Vintage&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reclassifies-iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-as-vintage.2430454/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:52:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>iPhone X</category>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today reclassified the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> X, first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, and first-generation AirPods as "vintage" products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/homepod-feature-blue2.jpg" alt="" width="2144" height="1206" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-788875" /><br/>
The products appeared on Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage and obsolete products list</a> earlier today. Products are considered vintage when Apple stopped distributing them for sale more than five and less than seven years ago. Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers continue to offer repairs for vintage products for up to two more years, subject to parts availability.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X, announced on September 12, 2017 and released on November 3, 2017, represented a significant leap forward in Apple's smartphone design and feature-set. Marking the 10th anniversary of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it introduced several significant changes such as the removal of the home button, allowing for an edge-to-edge 5.8-inch Super Retina OLED display. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, a facial recognition system, replaced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> for authentication, utilizing a TrueDepth camera system in a "notch" that also enabled Animojis. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X was powered by the A11 Bionic chip, featuring the company's first dedicated Neural Engine for enhanced machine learning capabilities, and it supported wireless charging for the first time. Its stainless steel frame and glass back design marked a return to a more premium aesthetic.<br/>
<br/>
The original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was announced on June 5, 2017, at the Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) and released on February 9, 2018. Initially priced at &#36;349, the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was designed to deliver high-quality audio and integrate closely with Apple's ecosystem, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>. It featured a custom-engineered high-excursion woofer and an array of seven beamforming tweeters. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; was powered by the Apple A8 chip, enabling real-time acoustic modeling, audio beamforming, and multi-channel echo cancellation. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> came built-in, allowing users to control music playback, manage smart home devices, and access information and services via voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced the original AirPods on September 7, 2016 and officially released them on December 13, 2016, with a retail price of &#36;159. The wireless earbuds were groundbreaking due to their seamless integration with Apple's ecosystem, facilitated by the custom-designed W1 chip. The chip enabled effortless pairing with Apple devices, long battery life, and efficient wireless connectivity. The AirPods also featured optical sensors and motion accelerometers, allowing them to detect when they were in the user's ears, automatically pausing playback when removed. Their unusual, compact design, combined with the convenience of a portable charging case, set a new standard for wireless earphones, making them highly popular and influential in the audio accessory market.<br/>
<br/>
Sometime after becoming "vintage," an Apple product will be reclassified as "obsolete." Apple says it considers a product obsolete once seven years have passed since the company last distributed it for sale. When this happens, Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers no longer offer repairs or other hardware service for it. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-now-vintage/">Apple Reclassifies iPhone X, HomePod, and Original AirPods as &#039;Vintage&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reclassifies-iphone-x-homepod-and-original-airpods-as-vintage.2430454/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fortnite and Epic Games Store Submitted to Apple for iOS Launch in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-and-epic-games-store-submitted-to-apple-for-ios-launch-in-eu.2430446/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 05:37:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Epic Games says it has <a href="https://x.com/epicnewsroom/status/1806819627181219995">submitted</a> the Epic Games Store to Apple for notarization under Apple's alternative app marketplace policy in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite-apple-logo-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-756080" /><br/>
The ‌Epic Games‌ Store will include popular game Fortnite, which means ‌iPhone‌ users in the EU will be able to install and play the title without having to use a cloud gaming service. Epic said it was "targeting the next couple months for the store and Fortnite on iOS in the EU." An ‌iPad‌ version of Fortnite is expected to follow this year.<br/>
<br/>
Fortnite has been banned from the iOS App Store for the last several years due to the legal dispute between Apple and ‌Epic Games‌. An avenue for its return was only made possible after Apple made it possible for iPhone‌ users in the EU to download apps from alternative app marketplaces rather than the App Store, as well as directly from developer websites.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is charging a 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee per year for apps installed outside of the ‌App Store‌ (and in the ‌App Store‌ for developers who opt in to the new terms and also still choose to use Apple's system), but there are no ‌App Store‌ commissions or in-app fees. While Apple is waiving fees for the first one million installs, the 0.50 per user fee will cost app developers like ‌Epic Games‌ a notable amount of money, especially given that Epic will often be charged twice – once for its app marketplace and once again for every Fortnite install. <br/>
<br/>
Epic CEO Tim Sweeney has been critical of Apple's App Store changes to bring its policies in line with the Digital Markets Act (DMA). Sweeney has <a href="https://x.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1750589570880516402">described</a> the changes as a "devious new instance of malicious compliance," and called Apple's charges "junk fees." The European Commission last week formally announced its preliminary view that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/eu-accuses-apple-violating-dma-rules/">Apple's App Store policies are in breach of the DMA</a>. The Commission also said it would open a new non-compliance procedure against Apple over concerns that its contractual requirements for third-party app developers and app marketplaces, including its Core Technology Fee, "fall short of ensuring effective compliance with Apple's obligations under the DMA."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/fortnite-epic-game-store-submitted-apple/">Fortnite and Epic Games Store Submitted to Apple for iOS Launch in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-and-epic-games-store-submitted-to-apple-for-ios-launch-in-eu.2430446/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google to Unveil Pixel 9 Phones Next Month Ahead of iPhone 16 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-august/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-next-month-ahead-of-iphone-16-launch.2430443/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 04:41:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-august/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google will refresh its product lineup this year in the middle of August rather than its usual October timing, which means its latest flagship Pixel smartphones will debut ahead of Apple's annual iPhone upgrade cycle for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/google-pixel-announcements.jpg" alt="" width="2060" height="1159" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915310" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Google Pixel 8 series</em></div><br/>
Google last week began sending out media invitations to an August 13 hardware event that will "showcase the base of Google AI, Android software and the Pixel portfolio of devices." Google typically holds its annual Made by Google event in early October to unveil its latest Pixel phones, smartwatches, and Nest-branded devices. <br/>
<br/>
Rumors indicate Google will launch three devices in its forthcoming Pixel 9 lineup, with a new larger 6.2-inch Pixel 9 Pro XL device joining the regular Pixel 9 and Pixel 9 Pro. Leaks suggest the Pixel 9 Pro will have a triple rear camera setup. Google is also expected to launch Android 15 touting Gemini AI enhancements and other services. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Get ready for magic at <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MadeByGoogle?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#MadeByGoogle</a> <br><br>Learn more and sign up for updates: <a href="https://t.co/ZnBcg6S6vK">https://t.co/ZnBcg6S6vK</a> <a href="https://t.co/C6Of1L9g4a">pic.twitter.com/C6Of1L9g4a</a></p>&mdash; Made by Google (@madebygoogle) <a href="https://twitter.com/madebygoogle/status/1805713788416434332?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 25, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Alongside new phones, Google is expected to release a Pixel Fold 2 tablet, a Pixel Watch 3 series, and new Pixel earbuds, all of which will compete with Apple devices. The decision to bring forward the hardware upgrades was likely made with one eye on Apple's hardware launches in September, when the iPhone 16 and Apple Watch Series 9 are expected to be revealed alongside iOS 18 with Apple Intelligence.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-august/">Google to Unveil Pixel 9 Phones Next Month Ahead of iPhone 16 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-to-unveil-pixel-9-phones-next-month-ahead-of-iphone-16-launch.2430443/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some Apple Intelligence Features Likely to Require Paid Subscription</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-intelligence-features-likely-paid-sub/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-intelligence-features-likely-to-require-paid-subscription.2430439/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 03:51:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-intelligence-features-likely-paid-sub/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple eventually plans to turn some of its artificial intelligence features into paid services, similar to iCloud+ subscriptions, according to <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
Writing in his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman said that while Apple Intelligence will be free to start, Apple's long-term plan is to launch something like "Apple Intelligence+," with extra features that users pay monthly fees to access.<br/>
<br/>
Making its own AI features another services revenue stream should allow Apple to compensate for the slowing pace of hardware upgrades and make the company less reliant on hardware tweaks to drive its business, argues Gurman. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is also expected to receive a cut of revenue whenever a user signs up to features offered by its AI partners, such as ChatGPT provided by OpenAI. Gurman says he expects Apple to agree a deal with Google and Anthropic to offer their AI services through its devices, with the former expected to be announced when Apple Intelligence launches in the fall as part of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> previously reported that Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-meta-ai-privacy-concerns/">turned down</a> an AI partnership with Facebook parent company Meta due to privacy concerns. Meanwhile, Apple is said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-ai-partner-china/">seeking partnerships for the Chinese market</a>, where ChatGPT and other similar AI services are not available. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-intelligence-features-likely-paid-sub/">Some Apple Intelligence Features Likely to Require Paid Subscription</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-intelligence-features-likely-to-require-paid-subscription.2430439/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Models to Adopt &#039;M14&#039; Advanced Samsung OLED Panels for Improved Brightness and Lifespan</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-16-pro-max-advanced-oled-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-adopt-m14-advanced-samsung-oled-panels-for-improved-brightness-and-lifespan.2430434/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 02:52:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-16-pro-max-advanced-oled-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be the first Apple smartphones to adopt Samsung's high performance "M14" OLED display panel, claims a new report coming out of South Korea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Update-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953750" /><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.etnews.com/20240628000294">ETNews</a></em>, Samsung's "M" series of OLED panels are made for flagship smartphones, while "14" refers to the number of high-performance materials used to produce them. "M14" is the first series of its kind, and the panel is said to have been developed to deliver superior brightness and longevity.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung has reportedly placed orders for the M14 materials and is preparing to mass produce the displays in the second half of the year for Apple's iPhone 16 Pro models. Google's Pixel 9 smartphone is the only other device that is expected to adopt the high-performance displays in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
A previous report out of China <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/iphone-16-pro-brighter-display/">claimed</a> that this year's ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ models will feature up to 1,200 nits of typical SDR brightness – a 20% increase over the current models – so Samsung's new panel could be the reason for the expected improvement. That said, peak HDR brightness is expected to remain at 1,600 nits, the same as the current iPhone 15 Pro Display.<br/>
<br/>
Another rumor last year suggested that all iPhone 16 models will adopt new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">micro-lens OLED display technology</a> for improved brightness and reduced power consumption, although it's not clear if this is related to M14 panels specifically.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">larger display sizes</a> than the iPhone 15 Pro models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/iphone-16-display-sizes/">according to multiple sources</a>. The iPhone 16 Pro will have a display that's 6.27 inches in size (rounded to 6.3), while the iPhone 16 Pro Max is expected to have a display that's 6.85 inches in size (rounded to 6.9). <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/iphone-16-pro-max-biggest-rumored-features/">5 Biggest Changes Rumored for iPhone 16 Pro Max</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple is expected to launch the iPhone 16 series in the fall, or around mid-September going on previous years.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/iphone-16-pro-max-advanced-oled-display/">iPhone 16 Pro Models to Adopt &#039;M14&#039; Advanced Samsung OLED Panels for Improved Brightness and Lifespan</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-to-adopt-m14-advanced-samsung-oled-panels-for-improved-brightness-and-lifespan.2430434/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Likely Planning to Use Bigger, Lower Resolution Displays for Cheaper Vision Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-use-bigger-lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-vision-headset.2430415/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:41:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is exploring new suppliers for OLED-on-Silicon panels, likely signaling the development of a more affordable headset destined to sit alongside the Vision Pro, <a href="http://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=28806"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-lenses.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898584" /><br/>
The Korean website has apparently detected a shift in Apple's supply chain management for OLED-on-Silicon (OLEDoS) panels, a key component in the Vision Pro headset. Currently, Sony provides these high-resolution microdisplays, but its limited production capacity of up to 900,000 panels per year and lack of expansion plans have prompted Apple to seek alternatives for the future. Apple has apparently issued a request for information (RFI) to Samsung Display and LG Display to evaluate their capabilities in producing larger OLEDoS panels, ranging from 2.0 to 2.1 inches in size with a display density of around 1,700 pixels per inch (PPI).<br/>
<br/>
These displays would be larger than those currently used in the Vision Pro and feature a lower resolution. The Vision Pro uses Sony's OLEDoS panels featuring a 1.42-inch screen with a pixel density of nearly 3,400 PPI, employing a white OLED display with color filter (wOLED+CF) technology. This sophisticated display technology is one of the main reasons for the headset's high price point.<br/>
<br/>
At Displayweek 2024, both Samsung and LG showcased advancements in OLED microdisplay technology that could appeal to Apple. Samsung presented a 1.03-inch RGB (direct-emission) OLED microdisplay, developed in collaboration with eMagin, which promises higher brightness levels compared to the wOLED+CF method. Meanwhile, LG revealed a 10,000 nits 1.3-inch 4K OLED microdisplay, utilizing a micro lens array (MLA) to boost brightness by around 40 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's interest in larger OLEDoS panels with lower resolution than those used in the Vision Pro suggests these could be intended for a new, lower-cost mixed reality headset. Apple has been rumored to be working on such a device for over a year, and the latest indications suggest that it may be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/cheaper-apple-vision-pro-tethered-iphone-mac/">designed to tether to an iPhone or Mac</a> to eliminate the need for a costly processor. The lower-cost Apple Vision headset could launch as soon as the end of next year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-headset/">Apple Likely Planning to Use Bigger, Lower Resolution Displays for Cheaper Vision Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-use-bigger-lower-resolution-displays-for-cheaper-vision-headset.2430415/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Starts Work on iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/apple-starts-work-on-ios-19-and-macos-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-starts-work-on-ios-19-macos-16-watchos-12-and-visionos-3.2430409/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:01:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/apple-starts-work-on-ios-19-and-macos-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has already begun work on the iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 3 software updates for next year, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/aapl-logo-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="890" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-776656" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined">most recent</a> "Power On" newsletter, Gurman said that Apple has formally begun development of its major operating systems for 2025 with the codenames "Luck" for iOS 19, "Cheer" for macOS 16, "Nepali" for watchOS 12, and "Discovery" for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 3.<br/>
<br/>
While <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, macOS 15 Sequoia, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> have not yet been released to the public, the initiation of work on the next major software updates for Apple's major devices is in line with its normal schedule. This is partly due to the fact that hardware products destined for launch next year require software for testing purposes, but it is currently too early to know what sort of features the new operating systems will offer.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also said that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/">Vision Pro headset should gain Apple Intelligence</a> as soon as next year, so this could make sense for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 3. Meanwhile, the public beta versions of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, macOS 15 Sequoia, &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, and &zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; should arrive next month ahead of official release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/apple-starts-work-on-ios-19-and-macos-16/">Apple Reportedly Starts Work on iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-starts-work-on-ios-19-macos-16-watchos-12-and-visionos-3.2430409/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPhone Battery Should Be Up to 10% Denser for Longer Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-iphone-battery-denser-for-longer-life/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-battery-should-be-up-to-10-denser-for-longer-life.2430407/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:48:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-iphone-battery-denser-for-longer-life/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> battery with a metal casing should allow for higher energy density to deliver longer battery life, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> claims. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-battery-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1333" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-923492" /><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/"><em>Alleged iPhone 16 Pro battery</a> with new metal casing.</em></div><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1807432542934732953">post on X</a> (formerly Twitter), Kuo said that Apple's adoption of a stainless steel casing for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery will allow for five to 10 percent higher cell density while remaining within safety limits, as well as meeting the requirements of new EU regulations. Alleged images of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">iPhone 16 Pro battery with a metal casing</a> leaked in late 2023 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/"><em>The Information</em></a> has since detailed Apple's work to simplify &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery replacement starting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<br/>
New EU law requires smartphone manufacturers to ensure batteries can be replaced by owners using easily accessible tools by 2025. Apple plans to achieve this with the use of electrically induced adhesive debonding technology, allowing users to apply a low voltage of electricity to quickly dislodge the battery instead of finicky adhesive strips. This new battery replacement method is anticipated to debut in at least one &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model later this year and could extend to all versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> next year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-iphone-battery-denser-for-longer-life/">New iPhone Battery Should Be Up to 10% Denser for Longer Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-battery-should-be-up-to-10-denser-for-longer-life.2430407/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple Intelligence Coming to Vision Pro, but Not HomePod</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro-but-not-homepod.2430404/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 11:17:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has no plans to bring Apple Intelligence to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, but it should arrive on the Vision Pro headset in the future, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined">latest edition</a> of his "Power On" newsletter, Gurman said that Apple is preparing to bring Apple Intelligence to its Vision Pro headset, but not this year. The device has sufficient memory to run on-device Apple Intelligence features such as notification summaries, writing tools, and an updated version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. Apple's user interface design team apparently needs to ensure that Apple Intelligence looks appropriate in a mixed-reality environment. The company also needs to guarantee that it has sufficient cloud-computing capacity to support more devices.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman does not expect the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; to offer Apple Intelligence, instead focusing on "an entirely new robotic device with a display that includes Apple Intelligence at its core." Apple Intelligence requires a minimum of eight gigabytes of memory, but the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> only feature a single gigabyte of memory. The current &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; is said to be "too low-volume a product to waste the engineering time" bringing Apple Intelligence to the device.<br/>
<br/>
Going forward, Gurman believes that Apple Intelligence will become increasingly critical to Apple devices and form a pillar of its business. Apple Intelligence should get updated more frequently than services like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>, at least as often as the company's hardware and software offerings. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro/">Gurman: Apple Intelligence Coming to Vision Pro, but Not HomePod</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-intelligence-coming-to-vision-pro-but-not-homepod.2430404/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: New AirPods to Feature Cameras for Enhanced Spatial Experiences</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-airpods-to-feature-ir-cameras/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-new-airpods-to-feature-cameras-for-enhanced-spatial-experiences.2430394/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 09:08:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-airpods-to-feature-ir-cameras/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will launch new AirPods featuring infrared cameras to improve spatial experiences with the Vision Pro headset, according to Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/airpods-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-931501" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/配備ir相機的新款airpods可望提升人機交互體驗與強化apple空間音訊-空間運算生態-new-ir-camera-equipped-airpods-to-enhance-2daa96913d7f">post on Medium</a>, Kuo explained that Apple plans to mass-produce new AirPods with integrated IR camera modules by 2026. These IR cameras will apparently be similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> receiver. <br/>
<br/>
The purpose of IR cameras on AirPods is related to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> and future headsets from the company, enhancing the spatial computing and audio experience. The IR cameras can detect environmental image changes, facilitating a broader range of gestures to improve user interaction. For example, if a user watches a video using &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; and the new AirPods, and turns their head to look in a specific direction, the sound source in that direction can be "emphasized to enhance the spatial audio/computing experience."<br/>
<br/>
Foxconn is said to be the supplier of the new IR component, with the Taiwanese electronics manufacturer preparing to provide enough parts for about 10 million AirPods initially. It is not clear which AirPods model is likely to get the feature first, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> may be most likely since they already offer lossless audio exclusively with the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-airpods-to-feature-ir-cameras/">Kuo: New AirPods to Feature Cameras for Enhanced Spatial Experiences</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-new-airpods-to-feature-cameras-for-enhanced-spatial-experiences.2430394/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 18 Beta 2, Apple Vision Pro International Launch, New Beats Speaker, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/29/top-stories-ios-18-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18-beta-2-apple-vision-pro-international-launch-new-beats-speaker-and-more.2430336/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/29/top-stories-ios-18-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is moving right along on iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and other new operating systems that were unveiled at WWDC earlier this month, releasing the second developer betas of the updates this week with a number of new changes and additions. Public betas will follow sometime next month ahead of a full public release in the fall.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/top-stories-29jun2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957255" /><br/>
Other news and rumors this week included international availability of the Vision Pro headset, upcoming expansion of support for third-party display and battery replacement parts for iPhones, the debut of a revamped Beats Pill speaker, and more, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything New in iOS 18 Beta 2</h2><br/>
Apple this week seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-2-to-developers/">second betas of iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, watchOS 11, and more to developers for testing. A handful of changes have been discovered on the iPhone in the second iOS 18 beta, as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-2/">outlined in our list of everything new</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
The first public beta of iOS 18 will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/ios-18-macos-sequoia-public-betas/">released at some point in July</a>, according to Apple. However, anyone with a free Apple developer account is able to install the developer beta, as a &#36;99/year Apple Developer Program membership is no longer required for this purpose. As always, make sure to back up your device before installing beta software.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Launches in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore</h2><br/>
Availability of Apple Vision Pro has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/">expanded beyond the United States for the first time</a>, with the headset now availabile in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/">Pre-orders have also gone live</a> in Australia, Canada, France, Germany, and the United Kingdom ahead of a July 12 launch in those countries.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-availability-Wangfujing-Beijing-first-purchase.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957191" /><br/>
During WWDC earlier this month, Apple announced visionOS 2, the first major update to the Vision Pro's operating system. visionOS 2 includes several new features and changes, including a redesigned Photos app with SharePlay support, the ability to turn existing 2D photos into spatial photos, a larger ultra-wide version of Mac Virtual Display that is equivalent to two 4K monitors side by side, plus support for a physical mouse.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Says iPhones Will Better Support Third-Party Displays and Batteries Later This Year</h2><br/>
Apple this week published a lengthy whitepaper that highlights the company's approach to device repairability and longevity. In the document, Apple revealed that iPhones will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/iphone-third-party-display-battery-support/">better support third-party displays and batteries later in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912514" /><br/>
More specifically, Apple said third-party iPhone displays will support True Tone, while battery health metrics will be visible when a third-party battery is installed. However, Apple said it cannot guarantee that the features will work properly.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beats Pill Speaker Makes a Comeback With Improved Sound, Water Resistance, and Lower Price</h2><br/>
Over two and a half years after Apple discontinued the Beats Pill, the company has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">brought the portable Bluetooth speaker back to life</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-pill-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956811" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">The new Beats Pill</a> features improved sound, water resistance, a lower &#36;149.99 price, an optional lanyard, Find My support, and other enhancements compared to the previous version. The speaker comes in three colors, and is available to order now on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 to Bring These 5 New Features to AirPods Pro</h2><br/>
The upcoming iOS 18 update for the iPhone <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-new-features-airpods-pro/">includes five notable new features for the AirPods Pro</a>, with more details outlined <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/ios-18-new-features-airpods-pro/">in our list</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-and-AirPods-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956922" /><br/>
One particular feature that Apple showed off during its WWDC 2024 keynote was hands-free Siri interactions. With the second-generation AirPods Pro and iOS 18, you can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/head-gestures-airpods-pro-later-this-year/">gently nod your head "yes" or gently shake your head "no"</a> to accept or decline an incoming call, without having to speak.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 60+ Upgrades to Expect</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max have yet to be announced, there are already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">many new features and changes rumored</a> for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-13-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956610" /><br/>
If you still have a three-year-old iPhone 13 Pro model, and will be considering upgrading to an iPhone 16 Pro model when they are released later this year, read our in-depth <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro/">iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro guide</a>. In it, we outline <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro/">over 60 changes to expect</a> if you upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jun-27-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/29/top-stories-ios-18-beta-2/">Top Stories: iOS 18 Beta 2, Apple Vision Pro International Launch, New Beats Speaker, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18-beta-2-apple-vision-pro-international-launch-new-beats-speaker-and-more.2430336/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple Vision Pro Available Around the World</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/the-macrumors-show-vision-pro-international-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-available-around-the-world.2430285/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:07:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/the-macrumors-show-vision-pro-international-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/apodcast/apple-vision-pro-goes-international/id1602394741?i=1000660560162">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the international rollout of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> and the new Beats Pill Bluetooth speaker.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nHIHVFV6D_c?si=b_0lsCadRx90X6WU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple's Vision Pro headset is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/">now available</a> to pre-order in Australia, Canada, France, Germany, and the United Kingdom, with availability beginning Friday, July 12. The device also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/">launched today</a> in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore. It has been available in the United States since February. We discuss key considerations when buying the Vision Pro, such as storage configurations and accessories, as well as the significance of the device's long-awaited rollout around the world. We also look to the future with Apple's rumored low-cost Vision headset, which may <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/cheaper-apple-vision-pro-tethered-iphone-mac/">rely on a tethered iPhone</a> for processing power to reduce costs. <br/>
<br/>
In addition, we discuss Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">new Beats Pill Bluetooth speaker</a>, featuring a completely redesigned speaker system consisting of a single tweeter and a single racetrack woofer, a removable lanyard, USB-C and Bluetooth connectivity, 24 hours of battery life, and IP67 water and sweat resistance. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple Intelligence, the apparent suspension of work on the second-generation Vision Pro headset, and Apple's rumored plans to move to thinner device designs.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/the-macrumors-show-vision-pro-international-launch/">The MacRumors Show: Apple Vision Pro Available Around the World</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apple-vision-pro-available-around-the-world.2430285/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Alogic&#039;s Echelon Series Delivers Budget-Friendly Keyboard and Mouse Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-echelon-series-delivers-budget-friendly-keyboard-and-mouse-accessories.2430283/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:01:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse&#038;post_date=1719604919/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Alogic</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Accessory company <a href="https://alogic.co/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic</a> recently launched a few new input devices with Mac support as part of its Echelon series, and I've been spending some time testing out the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-keyboard-for-macos/?ref=y2uwzwu">USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Keyboard for macOS</a> and the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-mouse-white/?ref=y2uwzwu">USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Mouse</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957182" /><br/>
The Echelon series is a budget-friendly line of accessories, seeking to offer a mid-range feature set at value pricing, and the mouse and keyboard do just that. The keyboard is priced at &#36;59.99 and the mouse at &#36;24.99, with Alogic frequently running promotional discounts of around 20% to bring prices down even further.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Keyboard for macOS</h2><br/>
<a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-keyboard-for-macos/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic's keyboard</a> offers a full-size 109-key layout with function row and number pad. The membrane-style keyboard with chiclet keys has some similarities to Apple's Magic Keyboard for Mac, though you obviously don't have an option for an integrated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> key with Alogic's offering. I've found the keys to be well spaced to allow for smooth typing, and have not experienced any problems with missing keystrokes, double letters, or other issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-keyboard-front.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957186" /><br/>
The Echelon keyboard offers a traditional extended keyboard layout, optimized for Mac with key arrangement and labels such as Command. The function keys in the top row include most of the usual Mac-specific functions such as display brightness controls, Spotlight, Mission Control, Launchpad, media playback controls, mute, volume controls, and even one to jump straight to your home folder when you're in Finder. There's also a dedicated system sleep key in that top row. In the bottom row, there's another dedicated key that will open up your Downloads folder when Finder is active. <br/>
<br/>
At the far right of the keyboard is the number pad, which includes the usual layout of number and arithmetic keys, plus a top row that serves double duty for switching among paired devices and as dedicated keys for select all, cut, copy, and paste.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-keyboard-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957224" /><br/>
Unlike Apple's Magic Keyboard which inexplicably still uses Lightning to charge, Alogic's Echelon keyboard charges over USB-C, and a white braided USB-C to USB-C cable is included in the box. Alogic says the battery lasts "weeks" between charges, but the battery level on my unit has barely dropped at all after several days of heavy usage, so I'm expecting charge intervals to be on the order of a couple of months, similar to what I see with the Magic Keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that Alogic's keyboard goes to sleep within a few minutes of going idle, even if the computer it's connected to remains active, and you'll need to hit a key on it and wait a beat for the keyboard to wake up before you can begin typing. That took a little getting used to for me given my long-term experience with the Magic Keyboard that pretty much always seems to be ready to go.<br/>
<br/>
The Alogic keyboard easily connects to Apple devices over Bluetooth using the standard pairing steps, with support for both Bluetooth 3.0 and Bluetooth 5.0 included. One distinct advantage compared to Apple's Magic Keyboard is that the Echelon supports connections to up to three devices, so you can pair it to your Mac, your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and even another device and easily switch between those devices with a key combo.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, I've found Alogic's Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Keyboard for macOS to be a solid budget keyboard, with a slim profile, a solid typing experience, and a nice set of key functions. The matte white plastic is a clean look that complements the Apple aesthetic, though I'll have to see how well it holds up to picking up dirt and stains over time. I do miss having &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; right on my external keyboard, but if that's not a deal-breaker for you, this keyboard might be worth a look. It's <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-keyboard-for-macos/?ref=y2uwzwu">normally priced at &#36;59.99</a>, but an Independence Day sale going on now knocks the price down to &#36;48.00 with promo code ID20.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Mouse </h2><br/>
<a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-mouse-white/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic's new mouse</a> is a well-matched complement to the Echelon keyboard, coming in the same matte white plastic. It's an ambidextrous mouse, so it's a simple matter of switching between left and right hands in macOS settings, though it's not as ergonomic as a handed mouse.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957183" /><br/>
The Echelon mouse includes the standard left and right mouse buttons and a scroll wheel in between them. The scroll wheel can also be pressed to act as a middle mouse button, but that's it as far as input options on this mouse. There are no additional side or thumb buttons, so if those are something that's become part of your workflow, this mouse isn't for you, at least as an everyday mouse.<br/>
<br/>
The left and right mouse buttons have relatively quiet clicks, which I tend to like, but the middle scroll wheel button is quite loud. Fortunately, that one isn't needed nearly as often so it's not a significant issue. The scroll wheel has well-defined clicks as you scroll to help you feel the movement, but there's no inertial free-spinning capability for quickly scrolling long pages or documents as I have come to appreciate on the Logitech MX Master 3 mouse that has been my daily driver for many years.<br/>
<br/>
At just &#36;24.99 for a wireless mouse, this is definitely a budget pick, and it does show in the overall experience, especially when you're used to a more powerful option. Alogic's Echelon mouse is extremely lightweight, and I find it glides best with some sort of desk pad or mat under it for a better feel, though it is certainly usable on a bare desk surface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/alogic-echelon-mouse-bottom.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957184" /><br/>
Alogic's Echelon mouse supports both Bluetooth 3.0 and Bluetooth 5.0, and it easily connects to a Mac or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; using the system settings, but the mouse also supports 2.4GHz connections that can deliver improved performance such as lower latency. That 2.4GHz support comes via a small USB-A dongle that conveniently fits into the underside of the mouse when not in use so you don't lose it. Of course, most modern Macs don't include any USB-A ports, but I typically use my MacBook Pro in a desk setup with a Thunderbolt dock that does include some USB-A ports, and the mouse connects fine via the dongle that way. Regardless, most users will likely opt for a Bluetooth connection given the simplicity.<br/>
<br/>
As with the Echelon keyboard, the mouse goes to sleep after just a few minutes of inactivity, which can be a bit disconcerting when returning to my Mac after a short break. I use a total of three displays in my desk setup, so when I sit down at my desk I usually give my mouse a quick shake to locate my pointer. With this Echelon mouse, the pointer doesn't move if the mouse has gone to sleep, so I have to first click once to wake it up before I shake it, which runs the risk of an inadvertent click if it the mouse hadn't been idle long enough to go to sleep. It's possible I'd get used to this over time, but so far I still find it a bit annoying.<br/>
<br/>
As with most sensible wireless mice (sorry, Apple), the Echelon mouse charges via a USB-C port on the front, meaning it can still be used while it's charging. A white braided USB-C to USB-C cable is included in the box for charging purposes. Alogic says a charge should last two to three weeks with typical office usage, although I haven't been using it long enough to fully test those numbers. But given the small drop in charge I've seen in a few days of use, it seems reasonable, and perhaps even conservative, to me. Alogic indicates it takes about an hour to fully recharge the mouse.<br/>
<br/>
The Echelon mouse can be paired with up to three devices simultaneously, two via Bluetooth and one via the 2.4GHz USB dongle. A small connection button on the bottom of the mouse is used for pairing and cycling through the connected devices. There's also an on/off switch on the bottom to conserve battery life and prevent unintended inputs.<br/>
<br/>
Coming from a more powerful Logitech mouse, I can safely say that Alogic's Echelon mouse isn't going to become a full-time part of my setup. But at its budget price, it's potentially a solid option for tossing in a computer bag to use while on the go. While it doesn't include more advanced features, it does offer the basic mouse buttons and a scroll wheel and can pair to multiple devices, and that's all many users may be looking for. The <a href="https://alogic.co/products/echelon-usb-c-rechargeable-wireless-mouse-white/?ref=y2uwzwu">Echelon USB-C Rechargeable Wireless Mouse is normally priced at &#36;24.99</a>, but the Independence Day sale with promo code ID20 brings the price down to just &#36;20.00.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: Alogic provided MacRumors with the Echelon keyboard and mouse for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Alogic. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/alogic/">Alogic</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-echelon-keyboard-mouse/">Review: Alogic&#039;s Echelon Series Delivers Budget-Friendly Keyboard and Mouse Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-echelon-series-delivers-budget-friendly-keyboard-and-mouse-accessories.2430283/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-grid-studio-june/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2430280/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 09:32:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-grid-studio-june/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with GRID Studio to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 256GB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>. GRID Studio is well known for transforming old, discarded Apple devices into displayable artwork.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/grid-studio-iphone-2g.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957241" /><br/>
GRID Studio deconstructs Apple devices and artfully arranges the components underneath a glass frame. Each part is labeled and accompanied by relevant historical details. GRID Studio's most iconic piece <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">is the GRID 1</a>, priced at &#36;400.<br/>
<br/>
The GRID 1 features the original Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from 2007, highlighting the parts that made up an important part of Apple's history. The iconic original ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ casing is positioned next to the power button, headphone socket, speaker, logic board, ear piece, and other components, and this is before the days where Apple started making its own chips so there are some unique components to see.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Grid-1st-gen.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934263" /><br/>
iPod fans will be interested in the <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-ipod-photo">&#36;120 GRID iPod Photo</a>, which originally came out in 2004, and was the first iPod featuring a color display. It has the same classic click wheel design, but with a 220x176 LCD display. This model is a fun part of Apple's past because it was the first iPod that really supported storing and showing off photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/grid-studio-ipod-photo.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957243" /><br/>
Most of GRID Studio's pieces are designed to be hung on the wall, but there are also a selection of products that can be displayed on a shelf or tabletop. The &#36;99 <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-3gs-wooden-tabletop-frames">GRID 3GS Wooden Tabletop Frame</a> has an attractive wood backing and acrylic cover that can be hung on the wall or displayed upright on a table with a support rod.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/grid-studio-iphone-3GS.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957244" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 3GS followed the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 3G, and that "S" was meant to represent speed. It had a processor that was twice as fast, and was Apple's first foray into really focusing on blazing fast performance. The GRID 3GS features the classic pre-iPhone 4 design, and it looks great in the wooden frame.<br/>
<br/>
GRID Studio is <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/pages/summersale">hosting a summer sale</a> that will last until July 17, and various GRID pieces are available at up to 50 percent off.<br/>
<br/>
We have one 256GB &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; to give away to a <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/aAdHs/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (June 28) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on July 5. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after July 5 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-grid-studio-june/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2430280/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Planning to Debut New Battery Replacement Method With iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-planning-to-debut-new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16.2430273/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:38:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on technology to simplify <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> battery replacement that could debut later this year, <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-explores-novel-method-for-making-iphone-batteries-more-replaceable"><em>The Information</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-battery-kosutami.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1333" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-923492" /><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/"><em>Alleged iPhone 16 Pro battery</a> with new metal casing.</em></div><br/>
The move comes in response to a new EU law requiring smartphone manufacturers to ensure batteries can be replaced by owners using easily accessible tools by 2025. According to sources involved in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s manufacturing process, Apple is exploring the use of electrically induced adhesive debonding technology to achieve this.<br/>
<br/>
The current method of replacing an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery is challenging and involves removing adhesive strips with tweezers. If these strips break during the process, additional steps involving heat or solvents are necessary to dislodge the adhesive. After removing the old battery, a tray and specialized machine are required to install a new one securely. <br/>
<br/>
In contrast, the new technology Apple is testing involves encasing the battery in metal rather than black foil. Alleged images of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">iPhone 16 Pro battery with a metal casing</a> leaked earlier this year. By applying a low voltage of electricity, the new battery can be quickly dislodged from the chassis. Despite this advancement, consumers will still need to open the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; themselves, which remains complicated due to the use of adhesives and screws to keep the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s display in place and retain water resistance. <br/>
<br/>
This new battery replacement method is anticipated to debut in at least one <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> model later this year and could be extended to all versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> next year. Apple is expected to continue recommending that users seek professional assistance for battery replacements, given the complexities and potential risks associated with the procedure.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may be exempt from the EU's legislation requiring consumer-friendly battery replacement if its devices meet certain criteria, such as retaining 83% of their capacity after 500 full charges and 80% after 1,000 full charges. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> meets the criteria for 1,000 charges, but earlier models do not meet the 500-charge requirement.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple has a history of offering devices that are challenging to repair due to their tightly sealed designs which enhance water resistance and durability, the company has taken steps to address these concerns by introducing self-repair options and making diagnostic tools available in recent years.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16/">Report: Apple Planning to Debut New Battery Replacement Method With iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-planning-to-debut-new-battery-replacement-method-with-iphone-16.2430273/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Best Buy Has Big MacBook Discounts During Its Prime Day-Like Sale, Plus AirTag Deals and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-28-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-best-buy-has-big-macbook-discounts-during-its-prime-day-like-sale-plus-airtag-deals-and-more.2430272/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:30:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-28-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy's Prime Day-like sale is the headline of this week's best Apple deals, featuring up to &#36;400 off the 16-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro and other MacBook discounts. Additionally, this week you'll find great sales on AirTag, Apple Pencil Pro, and Anker accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0007.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847997" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best Buy Member Deals Days</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macbook-pro-16-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957121" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Members can save sitewide at Best Buy this weekend</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/best-buy-member-deals-days/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmydmDOWOd2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE SALE</div>Best Buy Member Deals Days</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's "Member Deals Days" sale kicked off this week, and it will run all weekend. Only My Best Buy Plus and Total members can save during this event, which includes notable discounts on Apple products, PCs, smart home products, video games, TVs, and more. In terms of Apple products, the best deals available during this event are on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air and 16-inch M3 Pro MacBook Pro, with up to &#36;400 in savings on these computers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bluetooth Trackers</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airtag-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957120" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on AirTag and Eufy SmartTrack Card</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%2Fref%3Dfs_a_md_0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;78.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1719408239814"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Bluetooth tracker discounts were in abundance this week, and you can still get some of the best discounts today on Amazon. The AirTag 1 Pack is on sale for &#36;24.99, down from &#36;29.00, the AirTag 4 Pack is available for &#36;78.99, down from &#36;99.00, and the Eufy SmartTrack Card is discounted to &#36;19.99, down from &#36;29.99.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957118" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;10 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/airtag-amazon-eufy-apple-pencil-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Last week we saw the Apple Pencil Pro drop to a new record low price of &#36;119.00 on Amazon, and this &#36;10 discount is still available this week. Although only a &#36;10 discount, this is still the best deal we've seen to date on the newest Apple Pencil. For more savings, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.99</a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/anker-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957119" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1719241439861">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/amazons-new-sale-anker/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1719241439861"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;15 OFF</div>MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station for &#36;84.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving to Anker's charging accessories, you can get multiple MagSafe-compatible devices at a discount this week on Amazon, like a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1718896305471">portable battery</a> and a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1718896354198">wireless charging station</a>. The highlight of the sale is Anker's 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for &#36;109.99, down from &#36;149.99. Many of these will require you to clip an on-page coupon before you head to the checkout screen in order to see the sales.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1717512554052">MagGo Power Bank 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1717512037932">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;38.24 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;164.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;184.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;84.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1717513024737">MagGo 3-in-1 Folding Charging Station</a> - &#36;93.49, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;129.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/jackery-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957117" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Jackery accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L_1719241793961">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/amazons-new-sale-anker/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L_1719241793961"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Similar to the Anker discounts, Amazon this week introduced a new selection of markdowns on Jackery batteries and other accessories. Jackery is known for its reliable portable battery stations, and the best deal this time around can be found on the Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;229.99.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KVRWSQU2IO0L_1719241793961">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;199.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3UJLIACLEUQIR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3UJLIACLEUQIR_1719242084580">Solar Generator 300 Plus</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_title">Expansion Battery Pack 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;549.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR_1719241929028">Expansion Battery Pack 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,259.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KGYEKIXRZ05H%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2KGYEKIXRZ05H_1719242023321">Explorer 2000 Pro</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CMD7MC6V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1BZ0OGIME7Z68%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1BZ0OGIME7Z68_1719242095491">Explorer 3000 Pro</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.17834S7BIREPR_1719241929027">Solar Generator 2000 Plus + Explorer 2000 Plus + Battery</a> - &#36;3,599.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-6-28-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Best Buy Has Big MacBook Discounts During Its Prime Day-Like Sale, Plus AirTag Deals and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-best-buy-has-big-macbook-discounts-during-its-prime-day-like-sale-plus-airtag-deals-and-more.2430272/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store Down in UK, Canada, and Other Countries Ahead of Vision Pro Pre-Orders [Update: It&#039;s Back Up]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-in-uk-canada-and-other-countries-ahead-of-vision-pro-pre-orders-update-its-back-up.2430261/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:56:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's online store went down this morning in Germany, France, Australia, the UK, and Canada, as the company prepared to begin taking <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> pre-orders in the five regions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-store-down-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="826" height="519" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957199" /><br/>
Pre-orders begin at 5.00 a.m. Pacific Time, or the following local times. The starting prices given below in local currency are for the 256GB model minus prescription lenses and other accessories.<br/>
<ul><li>Australia – 10:00 pm AEST – &#36;5,999 </li><br/>
<li>Canada – 5.00 a.m. PT – &#36;4,999</li><br/>
<li>France – 2.00 p.m. – €3,999</li><br/>
<li>Germany – 2.00 p.m. – €3,999</li><br/>
<li>United Kingdom – 1.00 p.m. – £3,499</li></ul>&zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; will launch in the five countries on Friday, July 12, and interested customers can currently book a 30-minute demo of the device in their local <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> from launch day up until Thursday, July 18. <br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro is unquestionably Apple's most technically advanced product and a remarkable engineering achievement that impresses at first glance. However, potential buyers should visit an &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; to try it out and thoroughly research its capabilities before making a purchase. Be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">dedicated Vision Pro roundup</a> to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to produce fewer than 400,000 Vision Pro headsets in 2024 due to the complexity of manufacturing, according to analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. However, Apple is said to be already working on a new version of the ‌&zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;‌ for 2025 that will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">priced more affordably</a>. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-store-down-uk-canada-vision-pro/">Apple Store Down in UK, Canada, and Other Countries Ahead of Vision Pro Pre-Orders [Update: It&#039;s Back Up]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-down-in-uk-canada-and-other-countries-ahead-of-vision-pro-pre-orders-update-its-back-up.2430261/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Launches in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-launches-in-china-hong-kong-japan-and-singapore.2430257/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:09:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro spatial computing headset today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/apple-vision-pro-arrives-in-china-mainland-hong-kong-japan-and-singapore/">arrived at Apple Store locations</a> across China mainland, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore. The launches mark the first time the Vision Pro has been officially available outside of the United States, where the device has been on sale since February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-availability-Wangfujing-Beijing-first-purchase.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957191" /><br/>
Consumer interest in the &#36;3,499 headset has reportedly waned at home, where sales are said to have slowed in the five months since its launch. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> is set to launch in the United Kingdom and Canada on July 12. <br/>
<br/>
The headset will also launch on the same day in Australia, France, and Germany, as part of a staggered release in additional markets, which may be just what the company needs to reinvigorate enthusiasm for the device.  <br/>
<br/>
Reviews for the device have been mixed overall. For the most part, users have been impressed with the hardware and the technology introduced by the Vision Pro, but there are questions about the actual function of the device, the intuitiveness of the gesture-based control, the weight and comfort, and VR in general.<br/>
<br/>
During WWDC earlier this month, Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, the first major update to the Vision Pro's operating system. &zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; includes several new features and changes, including a redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app with SharePlay support, the ability to turn existing 2D photos into spatial photos, a larger ultra-wide version of Mac Virtual Display that is equivalent to two 4K monitors side by side, plus support for a physical mouse.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/28/apple-vision-pro-launches-china-japan-singapore/">Apple Vision Pro Launches in China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Singapore</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-launches-in-china-hong-kong-japan-and-singapore.2430257/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung to Begin Rolling Out Hotel Room TVs With AirPlay Support for iPhone and iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/samsung-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-to-begin-rolling-out-hotel-room-tvs-with-airplay-support-for-iphone-and-ipad.2430238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:38:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/samsung-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>AirPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung today <a href="https://news.samsung.com/global/samsung-enhances-hotel-stays-with-apple-airplay-on-hospitality-tvs">announced</a> that it will be rolling out AirPlay support for its series of hotel room TVs, allowing iPhone and iPad users to wirelessly stream videos, music, photos, and more from their device to the TV in their room.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airplay-hotels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898340" /><br/>
The feature allows you to scan a unique QR code on the hotel room TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing you to wirelessly stream content from your iPhone or iPad. After the pairing process, your device will also automatically be connected to the hotel's Wi-Fi network. The device must be updated to iOS 17.3 or iPadOS 17.3 or later.<br/>
<br/>
AirPlay on hotel room TVs works with apps and services like Apple Music, Apple TV+, Apple Arcade for games, Apple Fitness+ for workouts, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung said no personal info is ever stored or saved for this AirPlay feature, and the paired device is automatically removed when you check out of the hotel.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung did not reveal which hotel chains will be offering its AirPlay-enabled TVs. The feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/ios-17-airplay-hotel-feature-now-available/">launched earlier this year</a> on LG hotel room TVs at select IHG Hotels & Resorts properties in the U.S., Canada, and Mexico, with more locations to follow.<br/>
<br/>
Google has long offered a similar Chromecast streaming feature on many hotel room TVs that works with both iPhones and Android devices.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/27/samsung-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">Samsung to Begin Rolling Out Hotel Room TVs With AirPlay Support for iPhone and iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-to-begin-rolling-out-hotel-room-tvs-with-airplay-support-for-iphone-and-ipad.2430238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
